<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Context and System Fusion in Post-ASR Emotion Recognition with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-and-system-fusion-in-post-asr-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have started to play a vital role in modelling speech and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-and-system-fusion-in-post-asr-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Film Subtitles: Is YouTube the Best Approximation of Spoken Vocabulary?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-film-subtitles-is-youtube-the-best</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Word frequency is a key variable in psycholinguistics, useful for modeling human familiarity with words even in the era of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-film-subtitles-is-youtube-the-best</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking into Concept Explanation Methods for Diabetic Retinopathy Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-into-concept-explanation-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diabetic retinopathy is a common complication of diabetes, and monitoring the progression of retinal abnormalities using fundus imaging is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-into-concept-explanation-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating and Mitigating Object Hallucinations in Pretrained Vision-Language (CLIP) Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-and-mitigating-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) have achieved impressive performance, yet research has pointed out a serious issue with object hallucinations within these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-and-mitigating-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Interval Bound Propagation great again</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-interval-bound-propagation-great-again</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two crucial problems in NNC are of profound interest to the scientific community: how to calculate the robustness of a given pre-trained network and how to construct robust networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-interval-bound-propagation-great-again</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Robot Motion Planning with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-robot-motion-planning-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have recently been successfully applied to a wide range of robotics applications for learning complex multi-modal behaviors from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-robot-motion-planning-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning UQ Box: A Comprehensive Framework for Uncertainty Quantification in Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightning-uq-box-a-comprehensive-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty quantification (UQ) is an essential tool for applying deep neural networks (DNNs) to real world tasks, as it attaches a degree of confidence to DNN outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightning-uq-box-a-comprehensive-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning LLMs with Individual Preferences via Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-llms-with-individual-preferences-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we train LLMs that can ''interact to align'', essentially cultivating the meta-skill of LLMs to implicitly infer the unspoken personalized preferences of the current user through multi-turn conversations, and then dynamically align their following behaviors and responses to these inferred preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-llms-with-individual-preferences-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Benefit of Activation Sparsity in Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefit-of-activation-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SSD adaptively switches between the Mixtures-of-Experts (MoE) based sparse training and the conventional dense training during the pre-training process, leveraging the efficiency of sparse training and avoiding the static activation correlation of sparse training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefit-of-activation-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Temporal Modeling in Video Diffusion: The Vectorized Timestep Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redefining-temporal-modeling-in-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have revolutionized image generation, and their extension to video generation has shown promise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redefining-temporal-modeling-in-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive BPE Tokenization for Enhanced Vocabulary Adaptation in Finetuning Pretrained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-bpe-tokenization-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current approaches trivially append the target domain-specific vocabulary at the end of the PLM vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-bpe-tokenization-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounded-VideoLLM: Sharpening Fine-grained Temporal Grounding in Video Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-videollm-sharpening-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Large Language Models (Video-LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in coarse-grained video understanding, however, they struggle with fine-grained temporal grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounded-videollm-sharpening-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does SpatioTemporal information benefit Two video summarization benchmarks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-spatiotemporal-information-benefit-two</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models achieved state-of-the-art correlation scores on important benchmark datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-spatiotemporal-information-benefit-two</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXAQ: Exponent Aware Quantization For LLMs Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaq-exponent-aware-quantization-for-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of accelerating both $e^x$ and $\sum(e^x)$ results in a 36. 9% acceleration in the softmax operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaq-exponent-aware-quantization-for-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Bayes Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayes-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting has emerged as a promising approach for modeling 3D scenes using mixtures of Gaussians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayes-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Diffusion Model Activations Have Been Evaluated as Discriminative Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-diffusion-model-activations-have-been</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, the early study of this field performs a large-scale quantitative comparison of the discriminative ability of the activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-diffusion-model-activations-have-been</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cayley Graph Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cayley-graph-propagation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One well regarded family of bottleneck-free graphs within the mathematical community are expander graphs, with prior work$\unicode{x2014}$Expander Graph Propagation (EGP)$\unicode{x2014}$proposing the use of a well-known expander graph family$\unicode{x2014}$the Cayley graphs of the $\mathrm{SL}(2,\mathbb{Z}_n)$ special linear group$\unicode{x2014}$as a computational template for GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cayley-graph-propagation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-diffusion-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we design a Spatial-wise Dynamic Token (SDT) strategy to avoid redundant computation at unnecessary spatial locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-diffusion-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlearnable 3D Point Clouds: Class-wise Transformation Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearnable-3d-point-clouds-class-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional unlearnable strategies have been proposed to prevent unauthorized users from training on the 2D image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearnable-3d-point-clouds-class-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Adversarial Perturbations for Deep Reinforcement Learning via Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-adversarial-perturbations-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies reveal that well-performing reinforcement learning (RL) agents in training often lack resilience against adversarial perturbations during deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-adversarial-perturbations-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBDS: A Multi-Body Dynamics Simulation Dataset for Graph Networks Simulators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbds-a-multi-body-dynamics-simulation-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The datasets employed for training and evaluating physical simulation techniques are typically generated by researchers themselves, often resulting in limited data volume and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbds-a-multi-body-dynamics-simulation-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARB-LLM: Alternating Refined Binarizations for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arb-llm-alternating-refined-binarizations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current binarization methods struggle to narrow the distribution gap between binarized and full-precision weights, while also overlooking the column deviation in LLM weight distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arb-llm-alternating-refined-binarizations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCert: Federated Accuracy Certification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcert-federated-accuracy-certification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, this study proposed a method named FedCert to take the first step toward evaluating the robustness of FL systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcert-federated-accuracy-certification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECHOPulse: ECG controlled echocardio-grams video generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echopulse-ecg-controlled-echocardio-grams</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Echocardiography (ECHO) is essential for cardiac assessments, but its video quality and interpretation heavily relies on manual expertise, leading to inconsistent results from clinical and portable devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echopulse-ecg-controlled-echocardio-grams</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manikin-Recorded Cardiopulmonary Sounds Dataset Using Digital Stethoscope</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manikin-recorded-cardiopulmonary-sounds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this dataset, we used a digital stethoscope to capture both heart and lung sounds, including individual and mixed recordings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manikin-recorded-cardiopulmonary-sounds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tadashi: Enabling AI-Based Automated Code Generation With Guaranteed Correctness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tadashi-enabling-ai-based-automated-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Frameworks and DSLs auto-generating code have traditionally relied on human experts developing them to have in place rigorous methods to assure the legality of the applied code transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tadashi-enabling-ai-based-automated-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphCroc: Cross-Correlation Autoencoder for Graph Structural Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphcroc-cross-correlation-autoencoder-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph-structured data is integral to many applications, prompting the development of various graph representation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphcroc-cross-correlation-autoencoder-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entanglement-induced provable and robust quantum learning advantages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entanglement-induced-provable-and-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate, through both numerical simulations and trapped-ion experiments on IonQ Aria, the desired quantum-classical learning separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entanglement-induced-provable-and-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CommonIT: Commonality-Aware Instruction Tuning for Large Language Models via Data Partitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commonit-commonality-aware-instruction-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With instruction tuning, Large Language Models (LLMs) can enhance their ability to adhere to commands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commonit-commonality-aware-instruction-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enriching Ontologies with Disjointness Axioms using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enriching-ontologies-with-disjointness-axioms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ontologies often lack explicit disjointness declarations between classes, despite their usefulness for sophisticated reasoning and consistency checking in Knowledge Graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enriching-ontologies-with-disjointness-axioms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Artificial Intelligence for Navigating Synthesizable Chemical Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-artificial-intelligence-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate SynFormer's effectiveness in two key applications: (1) local chemical space exploration, where the model generates synthesizable analogs of a reference molecule, and (2) global chemical space exploration, where the model aims to identify optimal molecules according to a black-box property prediction oracle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-artificial-intelligence-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Segmentation Based Quality Control of Histopathology Whole Slide Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-based-quality-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed a software pipeline for quality control (QC) of histopathology whole slide images (WSIs) that segments various regions, such as blurs of different levels, tissue regions, tissue folds, and pen marks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-based-quality-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedStein: Enhancing Multi-Domain Federated Learning Through James-Stein Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedstein-enhancing-multi-domain-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) facilitates data privacy by enabling collaborative in-situ training across decentralized clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedstein-enhancing-multi-domain-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Action Sequence Learning for Robotic Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-action-sequence-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the Chunking Causal Transformer (CCT), which extends the next-single-token prediction of causal transformers to support multi-token prediction in a single pass.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-action-sequence-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba in Vision: A Comprehensive Survey of Techniques and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-in-vision-a-comprehensive-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mamba is emerging as a novel approach to overcome the challenges faced by Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) and Vision Transformers (ViTs) in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-in-vision-a-comprehensive-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table Question Answering for Low-resourced Indic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/table-question-answering-for-low-resourced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TableQA models trained on our large-scale datasets outperform state-of-the-art LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/table-question-answering-for-low-resourced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPenBench: Benchmarking Generative Agents for Penetration Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopenbench-benchmarking-generative-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assess the agent performance with generic and specific milestones that allow us to compare results in a standardised manner and understand the limits of the agent under test.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopenbench-benchmarking-generative-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-World Benchmarks Make Membership Inference Attacks Fail on Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-benchmarks-make-membership</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, we are the first to discover the performance overestimation of MIAs on diffusion models and present a unified benchmark for more realistic evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-world-benchmarks-make-membership</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action Selection Learning for Multi-label Multi-view Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-selection-learning-for-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work has focused on multi-view action recognition in a narrow area with strong labels available, where the onset and offset of each action are labeled at the frame-level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-selection-learning-for-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Uncertainty In Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-uncertainty-in-natural-language-processing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The last decade in deep learning has brought on increasingly capable systems that are deployed on a wide variety of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-uncertainty-in-natural-language-processing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature Diversity-Driven Deformation and Domain Alignment for Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-diversity-driven-deformation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach first introduces a \textit{\textbf{Curv}ature Diversity-driven Deformation \textbf{Rec}onstruction (CurvRec)} task, which effectively mitigates the gap between the source and target domains by enabling the model to extract salient features from semantically rich regions of a given point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-diversity-driven-deformation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiddenGuard: Fine-Grained Safe Generation with Specialized Representation Router</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiddenguard-fine-grained-safe-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ideally, LLMs should provide informative responses while avoiding the disclosure of harmful or sensitive information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiddenguard-fine-grained-safe-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BadCM: Invisible Backdoor Attack Against Cross-Modal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badcm-invisible-backdoor-attack-against-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel bilateral backdoor to fill in the missing pieces of the puzzle in the cross-modal backdoor and propose a generalized invisible backdoor framework against cross-modal learning (BadCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badcm-invisible-backdoor-attack-against-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynCo: Synthetic Hard Negatives in Contrastive Learning for Better Unsupervised Visual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synco-synthetic-hard-negatives-in-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce SynCo (Synthetic Negatives in Contrastive learning), a novel contrastive learning approach that improves model performance by generating synthetic hard negatives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synco-synthetic-hard-negatives-in-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents' Room: Narrative Generation through Multi-step Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-room-narrative-generation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Writing compelling fiction is a multifaceted process combining elements such as crafting a plot, developing interesting characters, and using evocative language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-room-narrative-generation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Implicit Bias Detection and Mitigation in Multi-Agent LLM Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-implicit-bias-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, our study investigates the presence of implicit gender biases in multi-agent LLM interactions and proposes two strategies to mitigate these biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-implicit-bias-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCA: Highly Efficient Semantic-Consistent Unrestricted Adversarial Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sca-highly-efficient-semantic-consistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unrestricted adversarial attacks typically manipulate the semantic content of an image (e. g., color or texture) to create adversarial examples that are both effective and photorealistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sca-highly-efficient-semantic-consistent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMetrics: Calibrating Metrics For Generation Tasks Using Human Preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metametrics-calibrating-metrics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This makes MetaMetrics a powerful tool for improving the evaluation of generation tasks, ensuring that metrics are more representative of human judgment across diverse contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metametrics-calibrating-metrics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Grasp Legal Theories? Enhance Legal Reasoning with Insights from Multi-Agent Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) could struggle to fully understand legal theories and perform complex legal reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Preference Modeling with Preference Representations for Aligning Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-preference-modeling-with-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce preference representation learning, an approach that embeds responses into a latent space to capture intricate preference structures efficiently, achieving linear query complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-preference-modeling-with-preference</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
