<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 09:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Intensity-free Integral-based Learning of Marked Temporal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intensity-free-integral-based-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the marked temporal point processes (MTPP), a core problem is to parameterize the conditional joint PDF (probability distribution function) $p^*(m, t)$ for inter-event time $t$ and mark $m$, conditioned on the history.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intensity-free-integral-based-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT Reconstruction from Few Planar X-rays with Application towards Low-resource Radiotherapy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-reconstruction-from-few-planar-x-rays-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a method to generate CT volumes from few (<5) planar X-ray observations using a prior data distribution, and perform the first evaluation of such a reconstruction algorithm for a clinical application: radiotherapy planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-reconstruction-from-few-planar-x-rays-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Referring Video Object Segmentation from Weak Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-referring-video-object-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To relieve the burden of data annotation while maintaining sufficient supervision for segmentation, we propose a new annotation scheme, in which we label the frame where the object first appears with a mask and use bounding boxes for the subsequent frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-referring-video-object-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting to Change: Robust Counterfactual Explanations in Dynamic Data Landscapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-change-robust-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The GAEs minimise the reconstruction error between the original graph and its learned representation during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-change-robust-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Defensive Underpainting Patch: Making Your Text Invisible to Optical Character Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-defensive-underpainting-patch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel and effective defense mechanism termed the Universal Defensive Underpainting Patch (UDUP) that modifies the underpainting of text images instead of the characters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-defensive-underpainting-patch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Vet: Evaluating Large Multimodal Models for Integrated Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-vet-evaluating-large-multimodal-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Problems include: (1) How to systematically structure and evaluate the complicated multimodal tasks; (2) How to design evaluation metrics that work well across question and answer types; and (3) How to give model insights beyond a simple performance ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-vet-evaluating-large-multimodal-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutions Die Hard: Open-Vocabulary Segmentation with Single Frozen Convolutional CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutions-die-hard-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed FC-CLIP, benefits from the following observations: the frozen CLIP backbone maintains the ability of open-vocabulary classification and can also serve as a strong mask generator, and the convolutional CLIP generalizes well to a larger input resolution than the one used during contrastive image-text pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutions-die-hard-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-UNet: Triplet UNet for Change Detection in High-Resolution Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-unet-triplet-unet-for-change-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Siamese structure focuses on extracting object features at different times but lacks attention to change information, which leads to false alarms and missed detections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-unet-triplet-unet-for-change-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinhala-English Parallel Word Dictionary Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinhala-english-parallel-word-dictionary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in the cases where one of the considered language pairs is a low-resource language, the existing top-down parallel data such as corpora are lacking in both tally and quality due to the dearth of human annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinhala-english-parallel-word-dictionary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Labelling of Affective Video Datasets via Few-Shot &amp; Multi-Task Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-labelling-of-affective-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whilst deep learning techniques have achieved excellent emotion prediction, they still require large amounts of labelled training data, which are (a) onerous and tedious to compile, and (b) prone to errors and biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-labelling-of-affective-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion-robust free-running cardiovascular MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-robust-free-running-cardiovascular-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For validation, CORe is first compared to traditional compressed sensing (CS), robust regression (RR), and another outlier rejection method using two simulation studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-robust-free-running-cardiovascular-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Painterly Image Harmonization using Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/painterly-image-harmonization-using-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Painterly image harmonization aims to insert photographic objects into paintings and obtain artistically coherent composite images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/painterly-image-harmonization-using-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Personalized Prompt-Model Retrieval for Generative Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-personalized-prompt-model-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With recent advances in Generative AI such as GPT and Diffusion models, a new form of recommendation task is yet to be explored where items are to be created by generative models with personalized prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-personalized-prompt-model-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-interactive Feature Learning and a Full-time Multi-modality Benchmark for Image Fusion and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-interactive-feature-learning-and-a-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modality image fusion and segmentation play a vital role in autonomous driving and robotic operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-interactive-feature-learning-and-a-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Paraphrase Sentences to Different Complexity Levels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-paraphrase-sentences-to-different</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare these datasets, one labeled by a weak classifier and the other by a rule-based approach, with a single supervised dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-paraphrase-sentences-to-different</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emo-DNA: Emotion Decoupling and Alignment Learning for Cross-Corpus Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emo-dna-emotion-decoupling-and-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On one hand, our contrastive emotion decoupling achieves decoupling learning via a contrastive decoupling loss to strengthen the separability of emotion-relevant features from corpus-specific ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emo-dna-emotion-decoupling-and-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Tori: Self-supervised Learning for Analyzing Korean Folk Song</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-tori-self-supervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a computational analysis of the field recording dataset of approximately 700 hours of Korean folk songs, which were recorded around 1980-90s.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-tori-self-supervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A stochastic optimization approach to train non-linear neural networks with regularization of higher-order total variation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-approach-to-train</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While highly expressive parametric models including deep neural networks have an advantage to model complicated concepts, training such highly non-linear models is known to yield a high risk of notorious overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-approach-to-train</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Semantic Model Fusion for Ancient Agricultural Terrace Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-semantic-model-fusion-for-ancient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discovering ancient agricultural terraces in desert regions is important for the monitoring of long-term climate changes on the Earth's surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-semantic-model-fusion-for-ancient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining Relation Classification Models with Semantic Extents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-relation-classification-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce semantic extents, a concept to analyze decision patterns for the relation classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-relation-classification-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A State-Space Perspective on Modelling and Inference for Online Skill Rating</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-state-space-perspective-on-modelling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper offers a comprehensive review of the main methodologies used for skill rating in competitive sports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-state-space-perspective-on-modelling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likelihood-ratio-based confidence intervals for neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-ratio-based-confidence-intervals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a first implementation of a novel likelihood-ratio-based approach for constructing confidence intervals for neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-ratio-based-confidence-intervals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balanced Classification: A Unified Framework for Long-Tailed Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-classification-a-unified-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we contend that the learning bias originates from two factors: 1) the unequal competition arising from the imbalanced distribution of foreground categories, and 2) the lack of sample diversity in tail categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-classification-a-unified-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generalist Foundation Model for Radiology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalist-foundation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contribution can be concluded as follows: (i), we construct a large-scale Medical Multi-modal Dataset, MedMD, consisting of 16M 2D and 3D medical scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalist-foundation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoML4ETC: Automated Neural Architecture Search for Real-World Encrypted Traffic Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automl4etc-automated-neural-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in production use, it has been shown that a DL classifier's performance inevitably decays over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automl4etc-automated-neural-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Estimation Under Distribution Shift: Wasserstein Perturbations and Minimax Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-estimation-under-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under a squared loss for mean estimation and prediction error in linear regression, we find the exact minimax risk, a least favorable perturbation, and show that the sample mean and least squares estimators are respectively optimal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-estimation-under-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Collapse Terminus: A Unified Solution for Class Incremental Learning and Its Variants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-terminus-a-unified-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Beyond the normal case, long-tail class incremental learning and few-shot class incremental learning are also proposed to consider the data imbalance and data scarcity, respectively, which are common in real-world implementations and further exacerbate the well-known problem of catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-terminus-a-unified-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Multi-view Representations Beyond Inductive Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-multi-view-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel multi-view representation disentangling method that aims to go beyond inductive biases, ensuring both interpretability and generalizability of the resulting representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-multi-view-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Cross-restoration Framework for Electrocardiogram Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-cross-restoration-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, this paper introduces a novel multi-scale cross-restoration framework for ECG anomaly detection and localization that considers both local and global ECG characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-cross-restoration-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balanced Destruction-Reconstruction Dynamics for Memory-replay Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-destruction-reconstruction-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By dynamically manipulating the gradient during training based on these factors, BDR can effectively alleviate knowledge destruction and improve knowledge reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balanced-destruction-reconstruction-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoissonNet: Resolution-Agnostic 3D Shape Reconstruction using Fourier Neural Operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poissonnet-resolution-agnostic-3d-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we demonstrate that the Poisson surface reconstruction problem is well-posed in the limit case by showing a universal approximation theorem for the solution operator of the Poisson equation with distributional data utilizing the Fourier Neuronal Operator, which provides a theoretical foundation for our numerical results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poissonnet-resolution-agnostic-3d-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NuInsSeg: A Fully Annotated Dataset for Nuclei Instance Segmentation in H&amp;E-Stained Histological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuinsseg-a-fully-annotated-dataset-for-nuclei</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we release one of the biggest fully manually annotated datasets of nuclei in Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E)-stained histological images, called NuInsSeg.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nuinsseg-a-fully-annotated-dataset-for-nuclei</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterization of differences in immune responses during bolus and continuous infusion endotoxin challenges using mathematical modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterization-of-differences-in-immune</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cytokine measurements reveal that the bolus injection leads to significantly higher peaks for IL-8, while IL-10 reaches significantly higher peaks during continuous administration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterization-of-differences-in-immune</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path Shadowing Monte-Carlo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-shadowing-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a Path Shadowing Monte-Carlo method, which provides prediction of future paths, given any generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-shadowing-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point2Mask: Point-supervised Panoptic Segmentation via Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point2mask-point-supervised-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly-supervised image segmentation has recently attracted increasing research attentions, aiming to avoid the expensive pixel-wise labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point2mask-point-supervised-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMDC: Dynamic-mask-based dual camera design for snapshot Hyperspectral Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmdc-dynamic-mask-based-dual-camera-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, the system learns the spatial feature distribution of the scene based on the RGB images, then instructs the SLM to encode each scene, and finally sends both RGB and CASSI images to the network for reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmdc-dynamic-mask-based-dual-camera-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Visibility in Nighttime Haze Images Using Guided APSF and Gradient Adaptive Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visibility-in-nighttime-haze-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we enhance the visibility from a single nighttime haze image by suppressing glow and enhancing low-light regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visibility-in-nighttime-haze-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Representation Learning for Time Series: A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-representation-learning-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there is a lack of systematic analysis of unsupervised representation learning approaches for time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-representation-learning-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Training of Denoising Diffusion Model Using Dual Discriminators for High-Fidelity Multi-Speaker TTS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-of-denoising-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation results show that the proposed model outperforms recent state-of-the-art models such as FastSpeech2 and DiffGAN-TTS in various metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-of-denoising-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Recklessness to Collaborative Filtering based Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-recklessness-to-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems that include some reliability measure of their predictions tend to be more conservative in forecasting, due to their constraint to preserve reliability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-recklessness-to-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal thinking for decision making on Electronic Health Records: why and how</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-thinking-for-decision-making-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We illustrate the various choices in studying the effect of albumin on sepsis mortality in the Medical Information Mart for Intensive Care database (MIMIC-IV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-thinking-for-decision-making-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URET: Universal Robustness Evaluation Toolkit (for Evasion)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uret-universal-robustness-evaluation-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new framework to enable the generation of adversarial inputs irrespective of the input type and task domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uret-universal-robustness-evaluation-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisAlign: Dataset for Measuring the Degree of Alignment between AI and Humans in Visual Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visalign-dataset-for-measuring-the-degree-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the models' visual perception alignment with humans, further referred to as AI-human visual alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visalign-dataset-for-measuring-the-degree-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniG-Encoder: A Universal Feature Encoder for Graph and Hypergraph Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unig-encoder-a-universal-feature-encoder-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a universal feature encoder for both graph and hypergraph representation learning is designed, called UniG-Encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unig-encoder-a-universal-feature-encoder-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Noise Boosts DNN Generalization under Label Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-noise-boosts-dnn-generalization-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce and theoretically demonstrate a simple feature noise method, which directly adds noise to the features of training data, can enhance the generalization of DNNs under label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-noise-boosts-dnn-generalization-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Multiplex Graph Learning with Complementary and Consistent Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multiplex-graph-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised multiplex graph learning (UMGL) has been shown to achieve significant effectiveness for different downstream tasks by exploring both complementary information and consistent information among multiple graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multiplex-graph-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models for Counterfactual Generation and Anomaly Detection in Brain Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-counterfactual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation masks of pathological areas are useful in many medical applications, such as brain tumour and stroke management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-counterfactual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RegionBLIP: A Unified Multi-modal Pre-training Framework for Holistic and Regional Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regionblip-a-unified-multi-modal-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose to extract features corresponding to regional objects as soft prompts for LLM, which provides a straightforward and scalable approach and eliminates the need for LLM fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regionblip-a-unified-multi-modal-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP: A Model-agnostic Pretraining Framework for Click-through Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-a-model-agnostic-pretraining-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large capacity of neural models helps digest such massive amounts of data under the supervised learning paradigm, yet they fail to utilize the substantial data to its full potential, since the 1-bit click signal is not sufficient to guide the model to learn capable representations of features and instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-a-model-agnostic-pretraining-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClassEval: A Manually-Crafted Benchmark for Evaluating LLMs on Class-level Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classeval-a-manually-crafted-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third, we find that generating the entire class all at once (i. e. holistic generation strategy) is the best generation strategy only for GPT-4 and GPT-3. 5, while method-by-method generation (i. e. incremental and compositional) is better strategies for the other models with limited ability of understanding long instructions and utilizing the middle information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classeval-a-manually-crafted-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
