<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 21:06:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Engineering: A Top-Down Approach to AI Transparency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-engineering-a-top-down</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we identify and characterize the emerging area of representation engineering (RepE), an approach to enhancing the transparency of AI systems that draws on insights from cognitive neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-engineering-a-top-down</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-NeRF: Parent-Child Neural Radiance Fields under Partial Sensor Data Loss in Autonomous Driving Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-nerf-parent-child-neural-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing large-scale 3D scenes is essential for autonomous vehicles, especially when partial sensor data is lost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-nerf-parent-child-neural-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Dialogue Management: Quality Datasets vs Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-dialogue-management-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this generator, we demonstrated that errors in the datasets contribute proportionally to the performance of the models]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-dialogue-management-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosis and Prognosis of Faults in High-Speed Aeronautical Bearings with a Collaborative Selection Incremental Deep Transfer Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosis-and-prognosis-of-faults-in-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis and prognosis of aeronautical-bearing health conditions are essential to proactively ensuring efficient power transmission, safety, and reduced downtime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosis-and-prognosis-of-faults-in-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling Vision-Language Models for Universal Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-vision-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a degradation-aware vision-language model (DA-CLIP) to better transfer pretrained vision-language models to low-level vision tasks as a universal framework for image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-vision-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing and Mitigating Object Hallucination in Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-and-mitigating-object-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision-language models (LVLMs) have shown remarkable abilities in understanding visual information with human languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-and-mitigating-object-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNRK: Graph Neural Runge-Kutta method for solving partial differential equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnrk-graph-neural-runge-kutta-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks have proven to be efficient surrogate models for tackling partial differential equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnrk-graph-neural-runge-kutta-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pink: Unveiling the Power of Referential Comprehension for Multi-modal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pink-unveiling-the-power-of-referential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model represents the referring object in the image using the coordinates of its bounding box and converts the coordinates into texts in a specific format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pink-unveiling-the-power-of-referential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>causalimages: An R Package for Causal Inference with Earth Observation, Bio-medical, and Social Science Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalimages-an-r-package-for-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The causalimages R package enables causal inference with image and image sequence data, providing new tools for integrating novel data sources like satellite and bio-medical imagery into the study of cause and effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalimages-an-r-package-for-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memorization with neural nets: going beyond the worst case</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorization-with-neural-nets-going-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practice, deep neural networks are often able to easily interpolate their training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorization-with-neural-nets-going-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructCV: Instruction-Tuned Text-to-Image Diffusion Models as Vision Generalists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructcv-instruction-tuned-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then use a large language model to paraphrase prompt templates that convey the specific tasks to be conducted on each image, and through this process, we create a multi-modal and multi-task training dataset comprising input and output images along with annotated instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructcv-instruction-tuned-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Cephalometric Landmark Detection from the view of Human Pose Estimation with Lightweight Super-Resolution Head</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-cephalometric-landmark-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate localization of cephalometric landmarks holds great importance in the fields of orthodontics and orthognathics due to its potential for automating key point labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-cephalometric-landmark-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComSD: Balancing Behavioral Quality and Diversity in Unsupervised Skill Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comsd-balancing-behavioral-quality-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ideal unsupervised skill discovery methods are able to produce diverse and qualified skills in the absence of extrinsic reward, while the discovered skill set can efficiently adapt to downstream tasks in various ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comsd-balancing-behavioral-quality-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Free Data Selection with General-Purpose Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-free-data-selection-with-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current approaches, represented by active learning methods, typically follow a cumbersome pipeline that iterates the time-consuming model training and batch data selection repeatedly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-free-data-selection-with-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Sensitive Information Be Deleted From LLMs? Objectives for Defending Against Extraction Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sensitive-information-be-deleted-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimentally, we show that even state-of-the-art model editing methods such as ROME struggle to truly delete factual information from models like GPT-J, as our whitebox and blackbox attacks can recover "deleted" information from an edited model 38% of the time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-sensitive-information-be-deleted-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networked Inequality: Preferential Attachment Bias in Graph Neural Network Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/networked-inequality-preferential-attachment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further bridge GCN's preferential attachment bias with unfairness in link prediction and propose a new within-group fairness metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/networked-inequality-preferential-attachment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nnSAM: Plug-and-play Segment Anything Model Improves nnUNet Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsam-plug-and-play-segment-anything-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent developments of foundation models in computer vision, especially the Segment Anything Model (SAM), allow scalable and domain-agnostic image segmentation to serve as a general-purpose segmentation tool.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsam-plug-and-play-segment-anything-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Shift Equivalence of Convolutional Neural Networks in Industrial Defect Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-shift-equivalence-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In industrial defect segmentation tasks, while pixel accuracy and Intersection over Union (IoU) are commonly employed metrics to assess segmentation performance, the output consistency (also referred to equivalence) of the model is often overlooked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-shift-equivalence-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Membership Inference Attacks Against Large-Scale Multi-Modal Models: A Pilot Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-membership-inference-attacks-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our enhanced attacks outperform the baseline across multiple models and datasets, with the weakly supervised attack demonstrating an average-case performance improvement of $17\%$ and being at least $7$X more effective at low false-positive rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-membership-inference-attacks-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Receive Help: Intervention-Aware Concept Embedding Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-receive-help-intervention-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose Intervention-aware Concept Embedding models (IntCEMs), a novel CBM-based architecture and training paradigm that improves a model's receptiveness to test-time interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-receive-help-intervention-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Foundation Models are Susceptible to Targeted Misinformation Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-foundation-models-are-susceptible-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate our findings in a set of 1, 038 incorrect biomedical facts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-foundation-models-are-susceptible-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Streaming Language Models with Attention Sinks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-streaming-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first demonstrate that the emergence of attention sink is due to the strong attention scores towards initial tokens as a ``sink'' even if they are not semantically important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-streaming-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstruction of Patient-Specific Confounders in AI-based Radiologic Image Interpretation using Generative Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruction-of-patient-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current techniques for evaluating deep learning models cannot visualize confounding factors at a diagnostic level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruction-of-patient-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redistributing the Precision and Content in 3D-LUT-based Inverse Tone-mapping for HDR/WCG Display</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistributing-the-precision-and-content-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latter requires more efficiency, thus the pre-calculated LUT (look-up table) has become a popular solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistributing-the-precision-and-content-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspicion-Agent: Playing Imperfect Information Games with Theory of Mind Aware GPT4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suspicion-agent-playing-imperfect-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike perfect information games, where all elements are known to every player, imperfect information games emulate the real-world complexities of decision-making under uncertain or incomplete information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suspicion-agent-playing-imperfect-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Path Learning for Multi-relational Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-path-learning-for-multi-relational-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing multi-relational graph neural networks use one of two strategies for identifying informative relations: either they reduce this problem to low-level weight learning, or they rely on handcrafted chains of relational dependencies, called meta-paths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-path-learning-for-multi-relational-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToRA: A Tool-Integrated Reasoning Agent for Mathematical Problem Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tora-a-tool-integrated-reasoning-agent-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have made significant progress in various language tasks, yet they still struggle with complex mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tora-a-tool-integrated-reasoning-agent-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SegRCDB: Semantic Segmentation via Formula-Driven Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segrcdb-semantic-segmentation-via-formula-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SegRCDB has a high potential to contribute to semantic segmentation pre-training and investigation by enabling the creation of large datasets without manual annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segrcdb-semantic-segmentation-via-formula-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Wish to Have an Argument: Argumentative Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-wish-to-have-an-argument-argumentative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We frame our experiments in terms of the argument mining (AM) and argument pair extraction (APE) tasks, and evaluate their ability to perform reasoning at increasing levels of abstraction in the input and output representations (e. g., arbitrary label sets, semantic graphs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-wish-to-have-an-argument-argumentative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Incremental Transfer Learning: Combining Peer-to-Peer Federated Learning and Domain Incremental Learning for Multicenter Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-incremental-transfer-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incremental transfer learning, which combines peer-to-peer federated learning and domain incremental learning, can overcome the data privacy issue and meanwhile preserve model performance by using continual learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-incremental-transfer-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task View Synthesis with Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-view-synthesis-with-neural-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the MTVS problem, we propose MuvieNeRF, a framework that incorporates both multi-task and cross-view knowledge to simultaneously synthesize multiple scene properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-view-synthesis-with-neural-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Instruction-based Image Editing via Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-instruction-based-image-editing-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results demonstrate that expressive instructions are crucial to instruction-based image editing, and our MGIE can lead to a notable improvement in automatic metrics and human evaluation while maintaining competitive inference efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-instruction-based-image-editing-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Epipolar Constraint Meets Non-local Operators in Multi-View Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-epipolar-constraint-meets-non-local-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This constraint reduces the 2D search space into the epipolar line in stereo matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-epipolar-constraint-meets-non-local-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOR-Based Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolor-based-multi-task-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-task learning (MTL) aims to learn multiple tasks using a single model and jointly improve all of them assuming generalization and shared semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolor-based-multi-task-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARLA: Adjusted common average referencing for cortico-cortical evoked potential data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carla-adjusted-common-average-referencing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In CARLA, the channels are ordered by increasing mean cross-trial covariance, and iteratively added to the common average until anticorrelation between any single channel and all re-referenced channels reaches a minimum, as a measure of shared noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carla-adjusted-common-average-referencing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Flow in Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-flow-in-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a comprehensive toolbox for understanding and enhancing self-supervised learning (SSL) methods through the lens of matrix information theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-flow-in-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utility-based Adaptive Teaching Strategies using Bayesian Theory of Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utility-based-adaptive-teaching-strategies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, human teachers seem to build mental models of the learner's internal state, a capacity known as Theory of Mind (ToM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utility-based-adaptive-teaching-strategies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Cognition Enhancement via Interaction-Aware Automated Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-cognition-enhancement-via-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating an effective representation space is crucial for mitigating the curse of dimensionality, enhancing model generalization, addressing data sparsity, and leveraging classical models more effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-cognition-enhancement-via-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Activation via Multivariate Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-activation-via-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Activation functions are essential to introduce nonlinearity into neural networks, with the Rectified Linear Unit (ReLU) often favored for its simplicity and effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-activation-via-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimation and Inference in Distributional Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-and-inference-in-distributional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This implies the distributional policy evaluation problem can be solved with sample efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimation-and-inference-in-distributional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Bridge Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-bridge-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, for many applications such as image editing, the model input comes from a distribution that is not random noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-bridge-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Too Big, so Fail? -- Enabling Neural Construction Methods to Solve Large-Scale Routing Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/too-big-so-fail-enabling-neural-construction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years new deep learning approaches to solve combinatorial optimization problems, in particular NP-hard Vehicle Routing Problems (VRP), have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/too-big-so-fail-enabling-neural-construction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCALE: Synergized Collaboration of Asymmetric Language Translation Engines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-synergized-collaboration-of-asymmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SCALE, a collaborative framework that connects compact Specialized Translation Models (STMs) and general-purpose Large Language Models (LLMs) as one unified translation engine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-synergized-collaboration-of-asymmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Gym: Partially Observable Challenges to Memory-Based Agents in Endless Episodes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-gym-partially-observable-challenges-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It features partially observable 2D environments with discrete controls, namely Mortar Mayhem, Mystery Path, and Searing Spotlights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-gym-partially-observable-challenges-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRANDE: Gradient-Based Decision Tree Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grande-gradient-based-decision-tree-ensembles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success of deep learning for text and image data, tree-based ensemble models are still state-of-the-art for machine learning with heterogeneous tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grande-gradient-based-decision-tree-ensembles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Empirical Measurements to Augmented Data Rates: A Machine Learning Approach for MCS Adaptation in Sidelink Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-empirical-measurements-to-augmented-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a machine learning approach to predict suitable MCS levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-empirical-measurements-to-augmented-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Water quality prediction using machine learning and neural network approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/water-quality-prediction-using-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Water resources serve as the cornerstone of human livelihoods and economic progress, with intrinsic links to both public health and environmental well-being.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/water-quality-prediction-using-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Depth Branches Network for Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-depth-branches-network-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based SR methods, while incorporating global structural details, frequently come with an abundance of parameters, leading to high computational overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-depth-branches-network-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Representation Learning for Prediction of Temporal Event Sets in the Continuous Time Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-representation-learning-for-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first work that solves the problem of predicting event set intensities in the continuous time domain by using TPPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-representation-learning-for-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G4SATBench: Benchmarking and Advancing SAT Solving with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g4satbench-benchmarking-and-advancing-sat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have recently emerged as a promising approach for solving the Boolean Satisfiability Problem (SAT), offering potential alternatives to traditional backtracking or local search SAT solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g4satbench-benchmarking-and-advancing-sat</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
