<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 09:14:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Convolutional Vision Transformer for Semantic Segmentation of Side-Scan Sonar Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convolutional-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome the lack of CNN-like inductive biases, thereby making ViTs more conducive to applications in low data regimes, we propose a novel feature extraction module to replace the Multi-layer Perceptron (MLP) block within transformer layers and a novel module to extract multiscale patch embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-convolutional-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVERED, CollabOratiVE Robot Environment Dataset for 3D Semantic segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covered-collaborative-robot-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the importance of semantic understanding for such applications, 3D semantic segmentation of collaborative robot workspaces lacks sufficient research and dedicated datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covered-collaborative-robot-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Efficient Neural Offline Reinforcement Learning via Perturbed Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-neural-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel offline reinforcement learning (RL) algorithm, namely Value Iteration with Perturbed Rewards (VIPeR) which amalgamates the randomized value function idea with the pessimism principle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-neural-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against Backdoor Attacks by Layer-wise Feature Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-backdoor-attacks-by-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find out that the feature difference between benign and poisoned samples tends to be maximum at a critical layer, which is not always the one typically used in existing defenses, namely the layer before fully-connected layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-backdoor-attacks-by-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Laplace Control for Continuous-time Delayed Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-laplace-control-for-continuous-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many real-world offline reinforcement learning (RL) problems involve continuous-time environments with delays.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-laplace-control-for-continuous-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Temporal Reasoning for Evidence-Based Fact-Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-reasoning-for-evidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that the presence of temporal information and the manner in which timelines are constructed greatly influence how fact-checking models determine the relevance and supporting or refuting character of evidence documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-temporal-reasoning-for-evidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HULAT at SemEval-2023 Task 9: Data augmentation for pre-trained transformers applied to Multilingual Tweet Intimacy Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hulat-at-semeval-2023-task-9-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the development phase, our best results were obtained by using XLM-T. Data augmentation techniques provide a very slight improvement in the results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hulat-at-semeval-2023-task-9-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Massively Multilingual ASR With Auxiliary CTC Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-massively-multilingual-asr-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce our work on improving performance on FLEURS, a 102-language open ASR benchmark, by conditioning the entire model on language identity (LID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-massively-multilingual-asr-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvivalGAN: Generating Time-to-Event Data for Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survivalgan-generating-time-to-event-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SurvivalGAN outperforms multiple baselines at generating survival data, and in particular addresses the failure modes as measured by the new metrics, in addition to improving downstream performance of survival models trained on the synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survivalgan-generating-time-to-event-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Targeted Accuracy Diagnostic for Variational Approximations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-targeted-accuracy-diagnostic-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational Inference (VI) is an attractive alternative to Markov Chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) due to its computational efficiency in the case of large datasets and/or complex models with high-dimensional parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-targeted-accuracy-diagnostic-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks against Synthetic Data through Overfitting Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-against-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we argue for a realistic MIA setting that assumes the attacker has some knowledge of the underlying data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-against-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProofNet: Autoformalizing and Formally Proving Undergraduate-Level Mathematics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proofnet-autoformalizing-and-formally-proving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ProofNet, a benchmark for autoformalization and formal proving of undergraduate-level mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proofnet-autoformalizing-and-formally-proving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Data Efficiency of Multi-Objective Quality-Diversity through Gradient Assistance and Crowding Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-data-efficiency-of-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that MOME-PGX is between 4. 3 and 42 times more data-efficient than MOME and doubles the performance of MOME, NSGA-II and SPEA2 in challenging environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-data-efficiency-of-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Stable Test-Time Adaptation in Dynamic Wild World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-test-time-adaptation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the unstable reasons and find that the batch norm layer is a crucial factor hindering TTA stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-stable-test-time-adaptation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Membership Inference Attack under Local Differential Privacy in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-membership-inference-attack-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) was originally regarded as a framework for collaborative learning among clients with data privacy protection through a coordinating server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-membership-inference-attack-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA: Open and Efficient Foundation Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-open-and-efficient-foundation-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLaMA, a collection of foundation language models ranging from 7B to 65B parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-open-and-efficient-foundation-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STA: Self-controlled Text Augmentation for Improving Text Classifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sta-self-controlled-text-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in Machine Learning, many tasks still involve working in low-data regimes which can make solving natural language problems difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sta-self-controlled-text-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Phenotype: Discovering Phenotypes of Predictive Temporal Patterns in Disease Progression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-phenotype-discovering-phenotypes-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering time-series data in healthcare is crucial for clinical phenotyping to understand patients' disease progression patterns and to design treatment guidelines tailored to homogeneous patient subgroups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-phenotype-discovering-phenotypes-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GANterfactual-RL: Understanding Reinforcement Learning Agents' Strategies through Visual Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ganterfactual-rl-understanding-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, research focusing on counterfactual explanations, specifically for RL agents with visual input, is scarce and does not go beyond identifying defective agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ganterfactual-rl-understanding-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Driven Representation Learning for Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we demonstrate that existing representations yield inconsistent results across these tasks: masked autoencoding approaches pick up on low-level spatial features at the cost of high-level semantics, while contrastive learning approaches capture the opposite.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotion Prediction Oriented method with Multiple Supervisions for Emotion-Cause Pair Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-prediction-oriented-method-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotion-cause pair extraction (ECPE) task aims to extract all the pairs of emotions and their causes from an unannotated emotion text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-prediction-oriented-method-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnbiasedNets: A Dataset Diversification Framework for Robustness Bias Alleviation in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiasednets-a-dataset-diversification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, UnbiasedNets provides a notable improvement over existing works, while even reducing the robustness bias significantly in some cases, as observed by comparing the NNs trained on the diversified and original datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiasednets-a-dataset-diversification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slate-Aware Ranking for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-aware-ranking-for-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, the ranking stage is still essential for most applications to provide high-quality candidate set for the re-ranking stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slate-aware-ranking-for-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrospective Uncertainties for Deep Models using Vine Copulas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrospective-uncertainties-for-deep-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the major progress of deep models as learning machines, uncertainty estimation remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrospective-uncertainties-for-deep-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Sentence Similarity Estimation for Unsupervised Extractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sentence-similarity-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised extractive summarization aims to extract salient sentences from a document as the summary without labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-sentence-similarity-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Unbalanced Sobolev Transport for Measures on a Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-unbalanced-sobolev-transport-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the proposed unbalanced Sobolev transport (UST) admits a closed-form formula for fast computation, and it is also negative definite.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-unbalanced-sobolev-transport-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieved Sequence Augmentation for Protein Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieved-sequence-augmentation-for-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RSA links query protein sequences to a set of sequences with similar structures or properties in the database and combines these sequences for downstream prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieved-sequence-augmentation-for-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Depth Look at Word Filling Societal Bias Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-depth-look-at-word-filling-societal-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many measures of societal bias in language models have been proposed in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-depth-look-at-word-filling-societal-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Limitations of Physics-informed Deep Learning: Illustrations Using First Order Hyperbolic Conservation Law-based Traffic Flow Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-limitations-of-physics-informed-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detailed in the case study, we present the contradistinction in PIDL results between learning the traffic flow model (LWR PDE) and its variation with diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-limitations-of-physics-informed-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving differential equations using physics informed deep learning: a hand-on tutorial with benchmark tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-differential-equations-using-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We revisit the original approach of using deep learning and neural networks to solve differential equations by incorporating the knowledge of the equation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-differential-equations-using-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object-Centric Video Prediction via Decoupling of Object Dynamics and Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-centric-video-prediction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework for the task of object-centric video prediction, i. e., extracting the compositional structure of a video sequence, as well as modeling objects dynamics and interactions from visual observations in order to predict the future object states, from which we can then generate subsequent video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-centric-video-prediction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Paradigm Analysis of Thai Capital Market Linkages: Bivariate/Vine Copulas, Granger Causality, Network Centrality, and Graph Neural Network/Graph Embedding Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-paradigm-analysis-of-thai-capital</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analytically thorough understanding of causal, probabilistic, and informational linkages amongst modern, highly-interconnected capital markets is fundamental to the promotion of capital-market innovation, efficiency, and resilience; whereupon innovative, efficient, and resilient capital markets are fundamental to the sustainable economic development of any nation and the robust financial stability of her economy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-paradigm-analysis-of-thai-capital</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPINDLE: Spinning Raw Text into Lambda Terms with Graph Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spindle-spinning-raw-text-into-lambda-terms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes SPINDLE - an open source Python module implementing an efficient and accurate parser for written Dutch that transforms raw text input to programs for meaning composition, expressed as {\lambda} terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spindle-spinning-raw-text-into-lambda-terms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditing for Spatial Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-for-spatial-fairness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similar to established notions of algorithmic fairness, we define spatial fairness as the statistical independence of outcomes from location.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-for-spatial-fairness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Impact of Competing Events on Heterogeneous Treatment Effect Estimation from Time-to-Event Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-impact-of-competing-events</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of inferring heterogeneous treatment effects (HTEs) from time-to-event data in the presence of competing events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-impact-of-competing-events</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In What Languages are Generative Language Models the Most Formal? Analyzing Formality Distribution across Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-what-languages-are-generative-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual generative language models (LMs) are increasingly fluent in a large variety of languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-what-languages-are-generative-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set Features for Fine-grained Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set-features-for-fine-grained-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained anomaly detection has recently been dominated by segmentation based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set-features-for-fine-grained-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Adaptive Conformal Prediction Using Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adaptive-conformal-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the use of self-supervision beyond model pretraining and representation learning has been largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adaptive-conformal-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Span-Based Continual Named Entity Recognition Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-span-based-continual-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named Entity Recognition (NER) models capable of Continual Learning (CL) are realistically valuable in areas where entity types continuously increase (e. g., personal assistants).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-span-based-continual-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTM: A Frame-level Timeline Modeling Method for Temporal Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ftm-a-frame-level-timeline-modeling-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing neighborhood aggregation strategies fail to capture either the short-term features or the long-term features of temporal graph attributes, leading to unsatisfactory model performance and even poor robustness and domain generality of the representation learning method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ftm-a-frame-level-timeline-modeling-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Intervention: Improving Convergence of Quantization Aware Training for Ultra-Low Precision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-intervention-improving-convergence-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Transformer models such as BERT have shown great success in a wide range of applications, but at the cost of substantial increases in model complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-intervention-improving-convergence-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change is Hard: A Closer Look at Subpopulation Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-is-hard-a-closer-look-at-subpopulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning models often perform poorly on subgroups that are underrepresented in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-is-hard-a-closer-look-at-subpopulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCWDST: a Minimum-Cost Weighted Directed Spanning Tree Algorithm for Real-Time Fake News Mitigation in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcwdst-a-minimum-cost-weighted-directed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread availability of internet access and handheld devices confers to social media a power similar to the one newspapers used to have.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcwdst-a-minimum-cost-weighted-directed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Structure Scores for Probabilistic Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-structure-scores-for-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic circuits (PCs) are a prominent representation of probability distributions with tractable inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-structure-scores-for-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted Search Control in AlphaZero for Effective Policy Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-search-control-in-alphazero-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AlphaZero trains upon self-play matches beginning from the initial state of a game and only samples actions over the first few moves, limiting its exploration of states deeper in the game tree.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-search-control-in-alphazero-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiTs: Fine-grained Two-stage Training for Knowledge-aware Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fits-fine-grained-two-stage-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the promising result of recent KAQA systems which tend to integrate linguistic knowledge from pre-trained language models (PLM) and factual knowledge from knowledge graphs (KG) to answer complex questions, a bottleneck exists in effectively fusing the representations from PLMs and KGs because of (i) the semantic and distributional gaps between them, and (ii) the difficulties in joint reasoning over the provided knowledge from both modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fits-fine-grained-two-stage-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Guided Ensemble Self-Training for Semi-Supervised Global Field Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-ensemble-self-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recovering a globally accurate complex physics field from limited sensor is critical to the measurement and control in the aerospace engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-ensemble-self-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MesoGraph: Automatic Profiling of Malignant Mesothelioma Subtypes from Histological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesograph-automatic-profiling-of-malignant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tissue is represented by a cell graph with both cell-level morphological and regional features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesograph-automatic-profiling-of-malignant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Adapter Network for Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side-adapter-network-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A side network is attached to a frozen CLIP model with two branches: one for predicting mask proposals, and the other for predicting attention bias which is applied in the CLIP model to recognize the class of masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side-adapter-network-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying &amp; Modeling Feature Interactions: An Information Decomposition Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-modeling-feature-interactions-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent explosion of interest in multimodal applications has resulted in a wide selection of datasets and methods for representing and integrating information from different signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-modeling-feature-interactions-an</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
