<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 21:06:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SHARP Challenge 2023: Solving CAD History and pArameters Recovery from Point clouds and 3D scans. Overview, Datasets, Metrics, and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-challenge-2023-solving-cad-history-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we define the proposed SHARP 2023 tracks, describe the provided datasets, and propose a set of baseline methods along with suitable evaluation metrics to assess the performance of the track solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharp-challenge-2023-solving-cad-history-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGS: An Dataset and Taxonomy for Domestic Scene Sound Event Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ags-an-dataset-and-taxonomy-for-domestic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, there is no public common data set for the research field of sound event recognition for the data set of the indoor environmental sound scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ags-an-dataset-and-taxonomy-for-domestic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Likelihood-based inference and forecasting for trawl processes: a stochastic optimization approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-based-inference-and-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop the first likelihood-based methodology for the inference of real-valued trawl processes and introduce novel deterministic and probabilistic forecasting methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/likelihood-based-inference-and-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nemo: First Glimpse of a New Rule Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-first-glimpse-of-a-new-rule-engine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This system demonstration presents Nemo, a new logic programming engine with a focus on reliability and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-first-glimpse-of-a-new-rule-engine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-to-OverpassQL: A Natural Language Interface for Complex Geodata Querying of OpenStreetMap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-overpassql-a-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Text-to-OverpassQL, a task designed to facilitate a natural language interface for querying geodata from OpenStreetMap (OSM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-overpassql-a-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMVP: Motion-Matrix-based Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmvp-motion-matrix-based-video-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A central challenge of video prediction lies where the system has to reason the objects' future motions from image frames while simultaneously maintaining the consistency of their appearances across frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmvp-motion-matrix-based-video-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peering Through Preferences: Unraveling Feedback Acquisition for Aligning Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peering-through-preferences-unraveling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we find that LLMs that leverage rankings data for alignment (say model X) are preferred over those that leverage ratings data (say model Y), with a rank-based evaluation protocol (is X/Y's response better than reference response?)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peering-through-preferences-unraveling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CircleFormer: Circular Nuclei Detection in Whole Slide Images with Circle Queries and Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circleformer-circular-nuclei-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the recent anchor free CNN-based circular object detection method (CircleNet) for ball-shape glomeruli detection in renal pathology, in this paper, we present CircleFormer, a Transformer-based circular medical object detection with dynamic anchor circles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circleformer-circular-nuclei-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Earlier Detection of Oral Diseases On Smartphones Using Oral and Dental RGB Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-earlier-detection-of-oral-diseases-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Oral diseases such as periodontal (gum) diseases and dental caries (cavities) affect billions of people across the world today.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-earlier-detection-of-oral-diseases-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latency-aware Unified Dynamic Networks for Efficient Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latency-aware-unified-dynamic-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic computation has emerged as a promising avenue to enhance the inference efficiency of deep networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latency-aware-unified-dynamic-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretability-guided Data Augmentation for Robust Segmentation in Multi-centre Colonoscopy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-guided-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-centre colonoscopy images from various medical centres exhibit distinct complicating factors and overlays that impact the image content, contingent on the specific acquisition centre.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-guided-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-Med2D</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-med2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce SAM-Med2D, the most comprehensive studies on applying SAM to medical 2D images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-med2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GREC: Generalized Referring Expression Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grec-generalized-referring-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset encompasses a range of expressions: those referring to multiple targets, expressions with no specific target, and the single-target expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grec-generalized-referring-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Response: Emergent analogical reasoning in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-emergent-analogical-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In their recent Nature Human Behaviour paper, "Emergent analogical reasoning in large language models," (Webb, Holyoak, and Lu, 2023) the authors argue that "large language models such as GPT-3 have acquired an emergent ability to find zero-shot solutions to a broad range of analogy problems."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-emergent-analogical-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Wikimedia: A 77 Language Multilingual Speech Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-wikimedia-a-77-language-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Speech Wikimedia Dataset is a publicly available compilation of audio with transcriptions extracted from Wikimedia Commons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-wikimedia-a-77-language-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deontic Paradoxes in ASP with Weak Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deontic-paradoxes-in-asp-with-weak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of powerful AI technology for a range of applications that are sensitive to legal, social, and ethical norms demands decision-making support in presence of norms and regulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deontic-paradoxes-in-asp-with-weak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Reward Shaping using Human Feedback for Correcting Reward Misspecification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-reward-shaping-using-human-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach allows the user to provide trajectory-level feedback on agent's behavior during training, which can be integrated as a reward shaping signal in the following training iteration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-reward-shaping-using-human-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanations for Answer Set Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanations-for-answer-set-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from xASP, the new system, xASP2, supports different clingo constructs like the choice rules, the constraints, and the aggregates such as #sum, #min.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanations-for-answer-set-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Few-shot Image Generation by Structural Discrimination and Textural Modulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-image-generation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the frequency awareness of the model is reinforced by encouraging the model to distinguish frequency signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-image-generation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-light image enhancement based on sharpening-smoothing image filter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-image-enhancement-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, inverse HSV transform is applied to the enhanced V component and H, S components to obtain the enhanced image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-image-enhancement-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SharpSAT-TD in Model Counting Competitions 2021-2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpsat-td-in-model-counting-competitions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe SharpSAT-TD, our submission to the unweighted and weighted tracks of the Model Counting Competition in 2021-2023, which has won in total $6$ first places in different tracks of the competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpsat-td-in-model-counting-competitions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaSM: Large Language and Speech Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llasm-large-language-and-speech-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Large Language and Speech Model (LLaSM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llasm-large-language-and-speech-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Underwater Visual Tracking With a Large Scale Dataset and Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-underwater-visual-tracking-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method has resulted in a significant performance improvement, of up to 5. 0% AUC, of state-of-the-art (SOTA) visual trackers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-underwater-visual-tracking-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards One-Shot Learning for Text Classification using Inductive Logic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-one-shot-learning-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the ever-increasing potential of AI to perform personalised tasks, it is becoming essential to develop new machine learning techniques which are data-efficient and do not require hundreds or thousands of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-one-shot-learning-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Multilabel Topic Classification in the Kyrgyz Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multilabel-topic-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kyrgyz is a very underrepresented language in terms of modern natural language processing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multilabel-topic-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Deep Learning for Full-disk Solar Flare Prediction with Empirical Insights from Guided Grad-CAM Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-deep-learning-for-full-disk-solar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study progresses solar flare prediction research by presenting a full-disk deep-learning model to forecast $\geq$M-class solar flares and evaluating its efficacy on both central (within $\pm$70$^\circ$) and near-limb (beyond $\pm$70$^\circ$) events, showcasing qualitative assessment of post hoc explanations for the model's predictions, and providing empirical findings from human-centered quantitative assessments of these explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-deep-learning-for-full-disk-solar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Multi-Modalities Fusion in Sequential Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-modalities-fusion-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a graph-based approach (named MMSR) to fuse modality features in an adaptive order, enabling each modality to prioritize either its inherent sequential nature or its interplay with other modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-multi-modalities-fusion-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Model Transferability through the Lens of Potential Energy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-model-transferability-through-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results on 10 downstream tasks and 12 self-supervised models demonstrate that our approach can seamlessly integrate into existing ranking techniques and enhance their performances, revealing its effectiveness for the model selection task and its potential for understanding the mechanism in transfer learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-model-transferability-through-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADFA: Attention-augmented Differentiable top-k Feature Adaptation for Unsupervised Medical Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adfa-attention-augmented-differentiable-top-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then apply differentiable top-k feature adaptation to train the patch descriptor, mapping the extracted feature representations to a new vector space, enabling effective detection of anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adfa-attention-augmented-differentiable-top-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect, Augment, Compose, and Adapt: Four Steps for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-augment-compose-and-adapt-four-steps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) plays a crucial role in object detection when adapting a source-trained detector to a target domain without annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-augment-compose-and-adapt-four-steps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OEBench: Investigating Open Environment Challenges in Real-World Relational Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oebench-investigating-open-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, while several real-world streaming datasets are available, it is uncertain whether these open environment challenges are prevalent and how existing incremental learning algorithms perform on real datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oebench-investigating-open-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unORANIC: Unsupervised Orthogonalization of Anatomy and Image-Characteristic Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unoranic-unsupervised-orthogonalization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce unORANIC, an unsupervised approach that uses an adapted loss function to drive the orthogonalization of anatomy and image-characteristic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unoranic-unsupervised-orthogonalization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measurement Tampering Detection Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measurement-tampering-detection-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When training powerful AI systems to perform complex tasks, it may be challenging to provide training signals which are robust to optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measurement-tampering-detection-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSFlow: Multi-Scale Flow-based Framework for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msflow-multi-scale-flow-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised anomaly detection (UAD) attracts a lot of research interest and drives widespread applications, where only anomaly-free samples are available for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msflow-multi-scale-flow-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyGPT: Detecting Industrial Anomalies using Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygpt-detecting-industrial-anomalies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) such as MiniGPT-4 and LLaVA have demonstrated the capability of understanding images and achieved remarkable performance in various visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygpt-detecting-industrial-anomalies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Grid Transformer for Document Layout Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-grid-transformer-for-document-layout</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document pre-trained models and grid-based models have proven to be very effective on various tasks in Document AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-grid-transformer-for-document-layout</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-temporal MLP-graph network for 3D human pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-mlp-graph-network-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph convolutional networks and their variants have shown significant promise in 3D human pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-mlp-graph-network-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPTrans: Transferring Visual Knowledge with Pre-trained Models for Multimodal Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliptrans-transferring-visual-knowledge-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneously, there has been an influx of multilingual pre-trained models for NMT and multimodal pre-trained models for vision-language tasks, primarily in English, which have shown exceptional generalisation ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliptrans-transferring-visual-knowledge-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glocal Explanations of Expected Goal Models in Soccer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glocal-explanations-of-expected-goal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the glocal explanations (between local and global levels) of the expected goal models to enable performance analysis at the team and player levels by proposing the use of aggregated versions of the SHAP values and partial dependence profiles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glocal-explanations-of-expected-goal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Robustness of Object Detection Models in Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-object-detection-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The robustness of object detection models is a major concern when applied to real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-object-detection-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic solar flare forecasting using historical magnetogram data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-solar-flare-forecasting-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider over 4 solar cycles of daily historical magnetogram data from multiple instruments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-solar-flare-forecasting-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards quantitative precision for ECG analysis: Leveraging state space models, self-supervision and patient metadata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-quantitative-precision-for-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These components consistently enhance performance beyond the existing state-of-the-art, which is predominantly based on convolutional models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-quantitative-precision-for-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Explanation Methods for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-explanation-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many applications classification alone is not enough, we often need to classify but also understand what the model learns (e. g., why was a prediction given, based on what information in the data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-explanation-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Would I Go Next? Large Language Models as Human Mobility Predictors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-would-i-go-next-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We posit that our research marks a significant paradigm shift in human mobility modelling, transitioning from building complex domain-specific models to harnessing general-purpose LLMs that yield accurate predictions through language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-would-i-go-next-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid Membership Latent Distance Model for Unsigned and Signed Integer Weighted Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-membership-latent-distance-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph representation learning (GRL) has become a prominent tool for furthering the understanding of complex networks providing tools for network embedding, link prediction, and node classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-membership-latent-distance-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Mobile Face Anti-Spoofing: A Robust Framework for Diverse Attack Types under Screen Flash</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mobile-face-anti-spoofing-a-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an attack type robust face anti-spoofing framework under light flash, called ATR-FAS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mobile-face-anti-spoofing-a-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Modulated Transformation in GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-modulated-transformation-in-gans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of style-based generators largely benefits from style modulation, which helps take care of the cross-instance variation within data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-modulated-transformation-in-gans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Robot Learning through Learned Human-Attention Feature Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-robot-learning-through-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to model and emulate the human attention with an approximate prediction model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-robot-learning-through-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble of Counterfactual Explainers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-of-counterfactual-explainers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In eXplainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI), several counterfactual explainers have been proposed, each focusing on some desirable properties of counterfactual instances: minimality, actionability, stability, diversity, plausibility, discriminative power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-of-counterfactual-explainers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Integration of Information Using Top-Down Modulated WTA Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-integration-of-information-using-top</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that WTA circuits are capable of integrating the probabilistic information represented by other WTA networks, and that top down processes can improve a WTA network's inference and learning performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-integration-of-information-using-top</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
