<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 09:15:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Imaging Projection Cloud Scattering Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-imaging-projection-cloud-scattering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper is the first to demonstrate CT of a real cloud using empirical data directly in a DNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-imaging-projection-cloud-scattering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi Camera Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Pipeline for Object Detection in Cultural Sites through Adversarial Learning and Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection algorithms allow to enable many interesting applications which can be implemented in different devices, such as smartphones and wearable devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell-Free Latent Go-Explore</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-free-latent-go-explore</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Latent Go-Explore (LGE), a simple and general approach based on the Go-Explore paradigm for exploration in reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-free-latent-go-explore</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audiogram Digitization Tool for Audiological Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogram-digitization-tool-for-audiological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A number of private and public insurers compensate workers whose hearing loss can be directly attributed to excessive exposure to noise in the workplace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogram-digitization-tool-for-audiological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2BiVQA: Double Bi-LSTM based Video Quality Assessment of UGC Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2bivqa-double-bi-lstm-based-video-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the growing popularity of mobile devices as well as video sharing platforms (e. g., YouTube, Facebook, TikTok, and Twitch), User-Generated Content (UGC) videos have become increasingly common and now account for a large portion of multimedia traffic on the internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2bivqa-double-bi-lstm-based-video-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIM-Trans: Structure Information Modeling Transformer for Fine-grained Visual Categorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-trans-structure-information-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above limitations, we propose the Structure Information Modeling Transformer (SIM-Trans) to incorporate object structure information into transformer for enhancing discriminative representation learning to contain both the appearance information and structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-trans-structure-information-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMA Cell: A Modular and Effective Approach for Neural Autoregressive Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arma-cell-a-modular-and-effective-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce the ARMA cell, a simpler, modular, and effective approach for time series modeling in neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arma-cell-a-modular-and-effective-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fair Experimental Comparison of Neural Network Architectures for Latent Representations of Multi-Omics for Drug Response Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fair-experimental-comparison-of-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One important parameter is the depth of integration: the point at which the latent representations are computed or merged, which can be either early, intermediate, or late.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fair-experimental-comparison-of-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style-Agnostic Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-agnostic-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method of learning style-agnostic representation using both style transfer and adversarial learning in the reinforcement learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-agnostic-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NestedFormer: Nested Modality-Aware Transformer for Brain Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nestedformer-nested-modality-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal MR imaging is routinely used in clinical practice to diagnose and investigate brain tumors by providing rich complementary information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nestedformer-nested-modality-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Space NeRF: Learning Animatable Avatars and Scene Lighting in Separate Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-nerf-learning-animatable-avatars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods alleviate the inconsistency of lighting by learning a per-frame embedding, but this operation does not generalize to unseen poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-nerf-learning-animatable-avatars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTorch Image Quality: Metrics for Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-image-quality-metrics-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image Quality Assessment (IQA) metrics are widely used to quantitatively estimate the extent of image degradation following some forming, restoring, transforming, or enhancing algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-image-quality-metrics-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Online Clustering of Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-online-clustering-of-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contextual multi-armed bandit (MAB) is an important sequential decision-making problem in recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-online-clustering-of-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ant Colony Optimization for Mining Gradual Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-mining-gradual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gradual pattern extraction is a field in (KDD) Knowledge Discovery in Databases that maps correlations between attributes of a data set as gradual dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-mining-gradual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANIT: Language-Driven Image-to-Image Translation for Unlabeled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanit-language-driven-image-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing techniques for image-to-image translation commonly have suffered from two critical problems: heavy reliance on per-sample domain annotation and/or inability of handling multiple attributes per image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanit-language-driven-image-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving RGB-D Point Cloud Registration by Learning Multi-scale Local Linear Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-rgb-d-point-cloud-registration-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to previous methods that seek correspondences by hand-crafted or learnt geometric features, recent point cloud registration methods have tried to apply RGB-D data to achieve more accurate correspondence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-rgb-d-point-cloud-registration-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-based Cross-modal Auxiliary Network for Multimodal Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-based-cross-modal-auxiliary-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal sentiment analysis has a wide range of applications due to its information complementarity in multimodal interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-based-cross-modal-auxiliary-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>k-MS: A novel clustering algorithm based on morphological reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-ms-a-novel-clustering-algorithm-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a clusterization algorithm called k-Morphological Sets (k-MS), based on morphological reconstruction and heuristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-ms-a-novel-clustering-algorithm-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLDNN: Deterministic Lateral Displacement Design Automation by Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dldnn-deterministic-lateral-displacement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, this tool is generalizable to other field-based problems and since the neural network is an integral part of this method, it enables transfer learning for similar physics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dldnn-deterministic-lateral-displacement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compound Figure Separation of Biomedical Images: Mining Large Datasets for Self-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-figure-separation-of-biomedical-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to extract and separate compound figures into usable individual images for downstream learning, we propose a simple compound figure separation (SimCFS) framework without using the traditionally required detection bounding box annotations, with a new loss function and a hard case simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-figure-separation-of-biomedical-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prior-Aware Synthetic Data to the Rescue: Animal Pose Estimation with Very Limited Real Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-aware-synthetic-data-to-the-rescue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we present a very data efficient strategy targeted for pose estimation in quadrupeds that requires only a small amount of real images from the target animal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-aware-synthetic-data-to-the-rescue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAKD: Feature Augmented Knowledge Distillation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakd-feature-augmented-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the recent progress on semantic directions on feature-space, we propose to include augmentations in feature space for efficient distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakd-feature-augmented-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUAHN-VIO: Content-and-Uncertainty-Aware Homography Network for Visual-Inertial Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuahn-vio-content-and-uncertainty-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning-based visual ego-motion estimation is promising yet not ready for navigating agile mobile robots in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuahn-vio-content-and-uncertainty-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapTR: Structured Modeling and Learning for Online Vectorized HD Map Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptr-structured-modeling-and-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adopt a hierarchical query embedding scheme to flexibly encode structured map information and perform hierarchical bipartite matching for map element learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptr-structured-modeling-and-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiGNN: Hierarchical Informative Graph Neural Networks for Molecular Property Prediction Equipped with Feature-Wise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hignn-hierarchical-informative-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Elucidating and accurately predicting the druggability and bioactivities of molecules plays a pivotal role in drug design and discovery and remains an open challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hignn-hierarchical-informative-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCAM: Temporal Class Activation Maps for Object Localization in Weakly-Labeled Unconstrained Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcam-temporal-class-activation-maps-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed TCAM method achieves a new state-of-art in WSVOL accuracy, and visual results suggest that it can be adapted for subsequent tasks like visual object tracking and detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcam-temporal-class-activation-maps-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Multi-User Delay-Constrained Scheduling with Deep Recurrent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-user-delay-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-user delay constrained scheduling is important in many real-world applications including wireless communication, live streaming, and cloud computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-user-delay-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Autoencoders for Anomaly Detection in Textured Images using CW-SSIM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-autoencoders-for-anomaly-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting anomalous regions in images is a frequently encountered problem in industrial monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-autoencoders-for-anomaly-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The case for fully Bayesian optimisation in small-sample trials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-case-for-fully-bayesian-optimisation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While sample efficiency is the main motive for use of Bayesian optimisation when black-box functions are expensive to evaluate, the standard approach based on type II maximum likelihood (ML-II) may fail and result in disappointing performance in small-sample trials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-case-for-fully-bayesian-optimisation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAIR: Fast and Lightweight Multi-Scale Color Attention Network for Instagram Filter Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cair-fast-and-lightweight-multi-scale-color</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an accurate, fast, lightweight network with multi-scale and color attention for Instagram filter removal (CAIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cair-fast-and-lightweight-multi-scale-color</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representations for Hyper-Relational Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-hyper-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It motivates us to design a framework that utilizes multiple aggregators to learn representations for hyper-relational facts: one from the perspective of the base triple and the other one from the perspective of the qualifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-hyper-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDB: Fraud Dataset Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdb-fraud-dataset-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope that FDB helps in the development of customized fraud detection techniques catered to different fraud modus operandi (MOs) as well as in the improvement of AutoML systems that can work well for all datasets in the benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdb-fraud-dataset-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Multi-granular Concept Extraction Based on Machine Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-granular-concept-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to supply existing KGs with more fine-grained and new concepts, we propose a novel concept extraction framework, namely MRC-CE, to extract large-scale multi-granular concepts from the descriptive texts of entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-granular-concept-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Boosting the Open-Domain Chatbot with Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-boosting-the-open-domain-chatbot-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many open-domain dialogue models pre-trained with social media comments can generate coherent replies but have difficulties producing engaging responses when interacting with real users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-boosting-the-open-domain-chatbot-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiLink: an encyclopedia-based semantic network for design innovation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikilink-an-encyclopedia-based-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing semantic networks for design innovation is built on data source restricted to technological and scientific information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikilink-an-encyclopedia-based-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Contextual Diversity for Dense Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-contextual-diversity-for-dense-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detection of out-of-distribution (OoD) samples in the context of image classification has recently become an area of interest and active study, along with the topic of uncertainty estimation, to which it is closely related.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-contextual-diversity-for-dense-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EchoGNN: Explainable Ejection Fraction Estimation with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echognn-explainable-ejection-fraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce EchoGNN, a model based on graph neural networks (GNNs) to estimate EF from echo videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echognn-explainable-ejection-fraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Night-time Scene Parsing with Learnable Frequency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-night-time-scene-parsing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we propose to exploit the image frequency distributions for night-time scene parsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-night-time-scene-parsing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Induced Transferability Representation for Source-Free Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-induced-transferability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, based on the UTR, we propose a novel Calibrated Adaption Framework (CAF) for SFUDA, including i)the source knowledge calibration module that guides the target model to learn the transferable source knowledge and discard the non-transferable one, and ii)the target semantics calibration module that calibrates the unreliable semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-induced-transferability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MODNet: Multi-offset Point Cloud Denoising Network Customized for Multi-scale Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modnet-multi-offset-point-cloud-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, a multi-scale perception module is designed to embed multi-scale geometric information for each scale feature and regress multi-scale weights to guide a multi-offset denoising displacement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modnet-multi-offset-point-cloud-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANT: Exploiting Adaptive Numerical Data Type for Low-bit Deep Neural Network Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-exploiting-adaptive-numerical-data-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a fixed-length adaptive numerical data type called ANT to achieve low-bit quantization with tiny hardware overheads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-exploiting-adaptive-numerical-data-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Pyramid Representation Learning for Multi-Label Visual Analysis and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pyramid-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we present a cross-scale patch-level correlation learning in SS-PRL, which allows the model to aggregate and associate information learned across patch scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pyramid-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do language models make human-like predictions about the coreferents of Italian anaphoric zero pronouns?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-language-models-make-human-like</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some languages allow arguments to be omitted in certain contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-language-models-make-human-like</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable 3D Generative Adversarial Face Model via Disentangling Shape and Appearance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-generative-adversarial-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D face modeling has been an active area of research in computer vision and computer graphics, fueling applications ranging from facial expression transfer in virtual avatars to synthetic data generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-generative-adversarial-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Search Once: On Lightweight Differentiable Architecture Search for Resource-Constrained Embedded Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-search-once-on-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from the search efficiency, differentiable neural architecture search (NAS) has evolved as the most dominant alternative to automatically design competitive deep neural networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-search-once-on-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Diffusion Model Predicts 3D Shapes from 2D Microscopy Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-diffusion-model-predicts-3d-shapes-from-2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models are a class of generative models, showing superior performance as compared to other generative models in creating realistic images when trained on natural image datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-diffusion-model-predicts-3d-shapes-from-2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeloForm: Generating Melody with Musical Form based on Expert Systems and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meloform-generating-melody-with-musical-form</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, 1) we design an expert system to generate a melody by developing musical elements from motifs to phrases then to sections with repetitions and variations according to pre-given musical form; 2) considering the generated melody is lack of musical richness, we design a Transformer based refinement model to improve the melody without changing its musical form.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meloform-generating-melody-with-musical-form</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric and Online Change Detection in Multivariate Datastreams using QuantTree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-and-online-change-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Like many change-detection algorithms, QT-EWMA builds a model of the data distribution, in our case a QuantTree histogram, from a stationary training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-and-online-change-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINKS: A dataset of a hundred million planar linkage mechanisms for data-driven kinematic design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/links-a-dataset-of-a-hundred-million-planar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LINKS is made up of various components including 100 million mechanisms, the simulation data for each mechanism, normalized paths generated by each mechanism, a curated set of paths, the code used to generate the data and simulate mechanisms, and a live web demo for interactive design of linkage mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/links-a-dataset-of-a-hundred-million-planar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annotated Dataset Creation through General Purpose Language Models for non-English Medical NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotated-dataset-creation-through-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obtaining text datasets with semantic annotations is an effortful process, yet crucial for supervised training in natural language processsing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotated-dataset-creation-through-general</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
