<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 09:11:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning with Layer Pruning on Medical Report Summarization and Medical Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing size of language models raises great research interests in parameter-efficient fine-tuning (e. g. Adapter, LoRA and prompt tuning) that freezes the pre-trained model, and injects small-scale trainable parameters for multiple downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-with-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretability at Scale: Identifying Causal Mechanisms in Alpaca</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-at-scale-identifying-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With DAS, we discover that Alpaca does this by implementing a causal model with two interpretable boolean variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-at-scale-identifying-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Consistency in Text-based Financial Forecasting Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using FinTrust, we show that the consistency of state-of-the-art NLP models for financial forecasting is poor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mode Approximation Makes Good Vision-Language Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advance of large-scale model technologies, parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL) has swept across various fields of Artificial Intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Bridging the Modality Gap for Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-bridging-the-modality-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the differences between speech and text, there is always a gap between ST and MT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-bridging-the-modality-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Semantic Variation Prediction using the Distribution of Sibling Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, some of the previously associated meanings of a target word can become obsolete over time (e. g. meaning of gay as happy), while novel usages of existing words are observed (e. g. meaning of cell as a mobile phone).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coreference-aware Double-channel Attention Network for Multi-party Dialogue Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreference-aware-double-channel-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The corresponding solutions contribute to the answer-oriented reasoning on a series of well-organized and thread-aware conversational contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coreference-aware-double-channel-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Guided Tree-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-guided-tree-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To verify the effectiveness of the proposed technique, we implemented a ToT-based solver for the Sudoku Puzzle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-guided-tree-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CQE: A Comprehensive Quantity Extractor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to other information extraction approaches, interestingly only a few works exist that describe methods for a proper extraction and representation of quantities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Preserving Talking Face Generation with Landmark and Appearance Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-preserving-talking-face-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior landmark characteristics of the speaker's face are employed to make the generated landmarks coincide with the facial outline of the speaker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-preserving-talking-face-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeeQA: Natural Questions in Meeting Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meeqa-natural-questions-in-meeting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MeeQA, a dataset for natural-language question answering over meeting transcripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meeqa-natural-questions-in-meeting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerated Algorithms for Nonlinear Matrix Decomposition with the ReLU function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-algorithms-for-nonlinear-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the following nonlinear matrix decomposition (NMD) problem: given a sparse nonnegative matrix $X$, find a low-rank matrix $\Theta$ such that $X \approx f(\Theta)$, where $f$ is an element-wise nonlinear function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerated-algorithms-for-nonlinear-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Similarity-weighted Construction of Contextualized Commonsense Knowledge Graphs for Knowledge-intense Argumentation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-weighted-construction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Arguments often do not make explicit how a conclusion follows from its premises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-weighted-construction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Matter of Annotation: An Empirical Study on In Situ and Self-Recall Activity Annotations from Wearable Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-matter-of-annotation-an-empirical-study-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we discuss the advantages and disadvantages of the methods compared in our study, the biases they may could introduce and the consequences of their usage on human activity recognition studies and as well as possible solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-matter-of-annotation-an-empirical-study-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIKI: Neural Inverse Kinematics with Invertible Neural Networks for 3D Human Pose and Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niki-neural-inverse-kinematics-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present NIKI (Neural Inverse Kinematics with Invertible Neural Network), which models bi-directional errors to improve the robustness to occlusions and obtain pixel-aligned accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niki-neural-inverse-kinematics-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-Map: Offboard HD-Map Generation with Multi-view Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-map-offboard-hd-map-generation-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance multi-view consistency, we augment the uncertainty network with the global 3D structure optimized by a voxelized neural radiance field (Voxel-NeRF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-map-offboard-hd-map-generation-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A graph convolutional autoencoder approach to model order reduction for parametrized PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-convolutional-autoencoder-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we develop a non-intrusive and data-driven nonlinear reduction approach, exploiting GNNs to encode the reduced manifold and enable fast evaluations of parametrized PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-convolutional-autoencoder-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reproducible Extraction of Training Images from Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-extraction-of-training-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release code to verify our extraction attack, perform the attack, as well as all extracted prompts at \url{https://github. com/ryanwebster90/onestep-extraction}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-extraction-of-training-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLCIFAR: CIFAR-Derived Benchmark Datasets with Human Annotated Complementary Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clcifar-cifar-derived-benchmark-datasets-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two datasets, CLCIFAR10 and CLCIFAR20, based on CIFAR10 and CIFAR100, respectively, are collected.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clcifar-cifar-derived-benchmark-datasets-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLIP: Language-Image Pre-training for Person Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plip-language-image-pre-training-for-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that our model not only significantly improves existing methods on all these tasks, but also shows great ability in the few-shot and domain generalization settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plip-language-image-pre-training-for-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Attributed Change Detection on Dynamic Graphs with Density of States</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-attributed-change-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current solutions do not scale well to large real-world graphs, lack robustness to large amounts of node additions/deletions, and overlook changes in node attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-attributed-change-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL4F: Generating Natural Language Feedback with Reinforcement Learning for Repairing Model Outputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4f-generating-natural-language-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their unprecedented success, even the largest language models make mistakes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4f-generating-natural-language-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Uncertainty into Neural Network-based Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-uncertainty-into-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the benefits of modeling uncertainty in clean speech estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-uncertainty-into-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Boltzmann Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-boltzmann-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional generative models are capable of using contextual information as input to create new imaginative outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-boltzmann-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeatFSDA: Towards Few-shot Domain Adaptation for Video-based Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featfsda-towards-few-shot-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address few-shot domain adaptation for video-based activity recognition (FSDA-AR), which leverages a very small amount of labeled target videos to achieve effective adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featfsda-towards-few-shot-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KEPR: Knowledge Enhancement and Plausibility Ranking for Generative Commonsense Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kepr-knowledge-enhancement-and-plausibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within the experimental models, the T5-based GenCQA with KEPR obtains the best performance, which is up to 60. 91% at the primary canonical metric Inc@3.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kepr-knowledge-enhancement-and-plausibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Multimodal Knowledge Graph Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-multimodal-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the current continual setting for knowledge graph construction only consider entity and relation extraction from text data while neglecting other multi-modal sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-multimodal-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back Translation for Speech-to-text Translation Without Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-translation-for-speech-to-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the remarkable success of back translation in MT, we develop a back translation algorithm for ST (BT4ST) to synthesize pseudo ST data from monolingual target data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-translation-for-speech-to-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRRM: Semantic Region Relation Model for Indoor Scene Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srrm-semantic-region-relation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable success of convolutional neural networks in various computer vision tasks, recognizing indoor scenes still presents a significant challenge due to their complex composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srrm-semantic-region-relation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Tool for Visualizing Variability of Pareto Fronts over Multiple Runs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/python-tool-for-visualizing-variability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization is crucial to achieving high performance in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/python-tool-for-visualizing-variability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sustain.AI: a Recommender System to analyze Sustainability Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sustain-ai-a-recommender-system-to-analyze</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present sustain. AI, an intelligent, context-aware recommender system that assists auditors and financial investors as well as the general public to efficiently analyze companies' sustainability reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sustain-ai-a-recommender-system-to-analyze</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global and Local Mixture Consistency Cumulative Learning for Long-tailed Visual Recognitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-mixture-consistency-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, our goal is to design a simple learning paradigm for long-tail visual recognition, which not only improves the robustness of the feature extractor but also alleviates the bias of the classifier towards head classes while reducing the training skills and overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-mixture-consistency-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Zero-Shot Rankers for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-zero-shot-rankers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along this line of research, this work aims to investigate the capacity of LLMs that act as the ranking model for recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-zero-shot-rankers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C-Eval: A Multi-Level Multi-Discipline Chinese Evaluation Suite for Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-eval-a-multi-level-multi-discipline-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present C-Eval, the first comprehensive Chinese evaluation suite designed to assess advanced knowledge and reasoning abilities of foundation models in a Chinese context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-eval-a-multi-level-multi-discipline-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLG Evaluation Metrics Beyond Correlation Analysis: An Empirical Metric Preference Checklist</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlg-evaluation-metrics-beyond-correlation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we analyze NLG automatic metrics based on whether human evaluation aspect is used as context or objective to compute the metrics: (i) Task-agnostic and (ii) Human-aligned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlg-evaluation-metrics-beyond-correlation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperDialseg: A Large-scale Dataset for Supervised Dialogue Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superdialseg-a-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a feasible definition of dialogue segmentation points with the help of document-grounded dialogues and release a large-scale supervised dataset called SuperDialseg, containing 9K dialogues based on two prevalent document-grounded dialogue corpora, and also inherit their useful dialogue-related annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superdialseg-a-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cognitive Stimulation Dialogue System with Multi-source Knowledge Fusion for Elders with Cognitive Impairment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cognitive-stimulation-dialogue-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a multi-source knowledge fusion method for CS dialogue (CSD), to generate open-ended responses guided by the CS principle and emotional support strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cognitive-stimulation-dialogue-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating genetic optimization of nonlinear model predictive control by learning optimal search space size</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-genetic-optimization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nonlinear model predictive control (NMPC) solves a multivariate optimization problem to estimate the system's optimal control inputs in each control cycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-genetic-optimization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey on Segment Anything Model for Vision and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the first to comprehensively review the progress of segmenting anything task for vision and beyond based on the foundation model of SAM, this work focuses on its applications to various tasks and data types by discussing its historical development, recent progress, and profound impact on broad applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParaLS: Lexical Substitution via Pretrained Paraphraser</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parals-lexical-substitution-via-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lexical substitution (LS) aims at finding appropriate substitutes for a target word in a sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parals-lexical-substitution-via-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two is Better Than One: Digital Siblings to Improve Autonomous Driving Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-is-better-than-one-digital-siblings-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study shows that the ensemble failure predictor by the digital siblings is superior to each individual simulator at predicting the failures of the digital twin.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-is-better-than-one-digital-siblings-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding and Improving Knowledge Distillation for Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-and-improving-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first unravel this mystery from an empirical perspective and show that the knowledge comes from the top-1 predictions of teachers, which also helps us build a potential connection between word- and sequence-level KD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-and-improving-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SongDriver2: Real-time Emotion-based Music Arrangement with Soft Transition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/songdriver2-real-time-emotion-based-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing studies mainly focus on achieving emotion real-time fit, while the issue of soft transition remains understudied, affecting the overall emotional coherence of the music.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/songdriver2-real-time-emotion-based-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theta sequences as eligibility traces: a biological solution to credit assignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theta-sequences-as-eligibility-traces-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Credit assignment problems, for example policy evaluation in RL, often require bootstrapping prediction errors through preceding states \textit{or} maintaining temporally extended memory traces; solutions which are unfavourable or implausible for biological networks of neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theta-sequences-as-eligibility-traces-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile-Env: A Universal Platform for Training and Evaluation of Mobile Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobile-env-a-universal-platform-for-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help the research of InfoUI interaction, a novel platform Mobile-Env is presented in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobile-env-a-universal-platform-for-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Prompt-based Black-Box Tuning Colorful: Boosting Model Generalization from Three Orthogonal Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-prompt-based-black-box-tuning-colorful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown increasing power on various natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-prompt-based-black-box-tuning-colorful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On enhancing the robustness of Vision Transformers: Defensive Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-enhancing-the-robustness-of-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Privacy and confidentiality of medical data are of utmost importance in healthcare settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-enhancing-the-robustness-of-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Non-linguistic Skills without Sacrificing Linguistic Proficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-linguistic-skills-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of Math-NLP has witnessed significant growth in recent years, motivated by the desire to expand LLM performance to the learning of non-linguistic notions (numerals, and subsequently, arithmetic reasoning).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-linguistic-skills-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatSci-NLP: Evaluating Scientific Language Models on Materials Science Language Tasks Using Text-to-Schema Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matsci-nlp-evaluating-scientific-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments in this low-resource training setting show that language models pretrained on scientific text outperform BERT trained on general text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matsci-nlp-evaluating-scientific-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULIP-2: Towards Scalable Multimodal Pre-training For 3D Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ulip-2-towards-scalable-multimodal-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the methods used by existing multimodal pre-training frameworks to gather multimodal data for 3D applications lack scalability and comprehensiveness, potentially constraining the full potential of multimodal learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ulip-2-towards-scalable-multimodal-pre</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
