<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 09:16:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Achilles, Neural Network to Predict the Gold Vs US Dollar Integration with Trading Bot for Automatic Trading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achilles-neural-network-to-predict-the-gold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Achilles, with a classical architecture of LSTM(Long Short Term Memory) neural network this model is able to predict the Gold vs USD commodity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achilles-neural-network-to-predict-the-gold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Unauthorized Speech Synthesis for Voice Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-unauthorized-speech-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With just a few speech samples, it is possible to perfectly replicate a speaker's voice in recent years, while malicious voice exploitation (e. g., telecom fraud for illegal financial gain) has brought huge hazards in our daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-unauthorized-speech-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoformalize Mathematical Statements by Symbolic Equivalence and Semantic Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoformalize-mathematical-statements-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoformalization, the task of automatically translating natural language descriptions into a formal language, poses a significant challenge across various domains, especially in mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoformalize-mathematical-statements-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory Flow Matching with Applications to Clinical Time Series Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-flow-matching-with-applications-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose Trajectory Flow Matching (TFM), which trains a Neural SDE in a simulation-free manner, bypassing backpropagation through the dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-flow-matching-with-applications-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Back the AI-Hacker: Prompt Injection as a Defense Against LLM-driven Cyberattacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hacking-back-the-ai-hacker-prompt-injection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are increasingly being harnessed to automate cyberattacks, making sophisticated exploits more accessible and scalable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hacking-back-the-ai-hacker-prompt-injection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuZip: Memory-Efficient Training and Inference with Dynamic Compression of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuzip-memory-efficient-training-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the model sizes are constrained by the available on-device memory during training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuzip-memory-efficient-training-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Multiple Deep Learning Algorithms for Efficient Localization of Bone Joints in the Upper Limbs of Human Body</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-multiple-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides a detailed comparative study between diverse Deep Learning (DL) models - YOLOv3, YOLOv7, EfficientDet and CenterNet in multiple bone joint detections in the upper limbs of the human body.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-multiple-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geo-FuB: A Method for Constructing an Operator-Function Knowledge Base for Geospatial Code Generation Tasks Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-fub-a-method-for-constructing-an-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, a retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) approach, utilizing an external knowledge base of geospatial functions and operators, is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-fub-a-method-for-constructing-an-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARP: Tokenizing Videos with a Learned Autoregressive Generative Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larp-tokenizing-videos-with-a-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the prior model during training, LARP learns a latent space that is not only optimized for video reconstruction but is also structured in a way that is more conducive to autoregressive generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larp-tokenizing-videos-with-a-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KD-LoRA: A Hybrid Approach to Efficient Fine-Tuning with LoRA and Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kd-lora-a-hybrid-approach-to-efficient-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance across various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kd-lora-a-hybrid-approach-to-efficient-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewTerm: Benchmarking Real-Time New Terms for Large Language Models with Annual Updates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newterm-benchmarking-real-time-new-terms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their remarkable abilities in various tasks, large language models (LLMs) still struggle with real-time information (e. g., new facts and terms) due to the knowledge cutoff in their development process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newterm-benchmarking-real-time-new-terms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Yet Effective Corpus Construction Framework for Indonesian Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-yet-effective-corpus-construction-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to efficiently construct high-quality evaluation corpora for GEC in low-resource languages has become a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-yet-effective-corpus-construction-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Search Assistant: Empower Vision-Language Models as Multimodal Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-search-assistant-empower-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose Vision Search Assistant, a novel framework that facilitates collaboration between VLMs and web agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-search-assistant-empower-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skinned Motion Retargeting with Dense Geometric Interaction Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinned-motion-retargeting-with-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we develop a novel spatio-temporal representation called the dense mesh interaction (DMI) field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinned-motion-retargeting-with-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPOTS-10: Animal Pattern Benchmark Dataset for Machine Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spots-10-animal-pattern-benchmark-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognising animals based on distinctive body patterns, such as stripes, spots, or other markings, in night images is a complex task in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spots-10-animal-pattern-benchmark-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmenting Watermarked Texts From Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmenting-watermarked-texts-from-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our objective is to develop a statistical method to detect if a published text is LLM-generated from the perspective of a detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmenting-watermarked-texts-from-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLAST: Block-Level Adaptive Structured Matrices for Efficient Deep Neural Network Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blast-block-level-adaptive-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale foundation models have demonstrated exceptional performance in language and vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blast-block-level-adaptive-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODRL: A Benchmark for Off-Dynamics Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odrl-a-benchmark-for-off-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider off-dynamics reinforcement learning (RL) where one needs to transfer policies across different domains with dynamics mismatch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odrl-a-benchmark-for-off-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FusedInf: Efficient Swapping of DNN Models for On-Demand Serverless Inference Services on the Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusedinf-efficient-swapping-of-dnn-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Edge AI computing boxes are a new class of computing devices that are aimed to revolutionize the AI industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusedinf-efficient-swapping-of-dnn-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecFlow: An Industrial Full Flow Recommendation Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recflow-an-industrial-full-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Industrial recommendation systems (RS) rely on the multi-stage pipeline to balance effectiveness and efficiency when delivering items from a vast corpus to users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recflow-an-industrial-full-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoRAG: Automated Framework for optimization of Retrieval Augmented Generation Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autorag-automated-framework-for-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using LLMs (Large Language Models) in conjunction with external documents has made RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) an essential technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autorag-automated-framework-for-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uOttawa at LegalLens-2024: Transformer-based Classification Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uottawa-at-legallens-2024-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results were 86. 3% in the L-NER subtask and 88. 25% in the L-NLI subtask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uottawa-at-legallens-2024-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenUP: Generative User Profilers as In-Context Learners for Next POI Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genup-generative-user-profilers-as-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional POI recommendation systems often lack transparency, interpretability, and scrutability due to their reliance on dense vector-based user embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genup-generative-user-profilers-as-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Detection of Person Class Using Dense Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-detection-of-person-class-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the performance of person detection we have conducted a different approach which gives the state-of-the-art conclusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-detection-of-person-class-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODES: Benchmarking Coupled ODE Surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codes-benchmarking-coupled-ode-surrogates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CODES, a benchmark for comprehensive evaluation of surrogate architectures for coupled ODE systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codes-benchmarking-coupled-ode-surrogates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Enhanced Mutation Mastery: Augmenting Zero-Shot Prediction of Protein Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-enhanced-mutation-mastery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enzyme engineering enables the modification of wild-type proteins to meet industrial and research demands by enhancing catalytic activity, stability, binding affinities, and other properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-enhanced-mutation-mastery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\texttt{skwdro}$: a library for Wasserstein distributionally robust machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texttt-skwdro-a-library-for-wasserstein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present skwdro, a Python library for training robust machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texttt-skwdro-a-library-for-wasserstein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Out-of-Distribution Detection via Normalized Outlier Distribution Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-out-of-distribution-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel approach, namely normalized outlier distribution adaptation (AdaptOD), to tackle this distribution shift problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-out-of-distribution-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping MMLU: A Massive Multi-Task Online Shopping Benchmark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-mmlu-a-massive-multi-task-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shopping MMLU consists of 57 tasks covering 4 major shopping skills: concept understanding, knowledge reasoning, user behavior alignment, and multi-linguality, and can thus comprehensively evaluate the abilities of LLMs as general shop assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-mmlu-a-massive-multi-task-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Handle Complex Constraints for Vehicle Routing Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-handle-complex-constraints-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vehicle Routing Problems (VRPs) can model many real-world scenarios and often involve complex constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-handle-complex-constraints-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Visual Prompt Tuning by Gaussian Neighborhood Minimization for Long-Tailed Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-prompt-tuning-by-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel method called Random SAM prompt tuning (RSAM-PT) to improve the model generalization, requiring only one-step gradient computation at each step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-prompt-tuning-by-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Spectral Attention for Long-Range Dependency in Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-spectral-attention-for-long-range</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we introduce a fast and effective Spectral Attention mechanism, which preserves temporal correlations among samples and facilitates the handling of long-range information while maintaining the base model structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-spectral-attention-for-long-range</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACTS: A Factored State-Space Framework For World Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facts-a-factored-state-space-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[World modelling is essential for understanding and predicting the dynamics of complex systems by learning both spatial and temporal dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facts-a-factored-state-space-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeriesGAN: Time Series Generation via Adversarial and Autoregressive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seriesgan-time-series-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current Generative Adversarial Network (GAN)-based approaches for time series generation face challenges such as suboptimal convergence, information loss in embedding spaces, and instability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seriesgan-time-series-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness and Generalization in Quantum Reinforcement Learning via Lipschitz Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-and-generalization-in-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that training with RegQPG improves the robustness and generalization of the resulting policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-and-generalization-in-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Hamilton: Can A.I. Understand Hamiltonian Mechanics?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-hamilton-can-a-i-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework based on neural network that reformulates classical mechanics as an operator learning problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-hamilton-can-a-i-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CardiacNet: Learning to Reconstruct Abnormalities for Cardiac Disease Assessment from Echocardiogram Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardiacnet-learning-to-reconstruct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel reconstruction-based approach named CardiacNet to learn a better representation of local cardiac structures and motion abnormalities through echocardiogram videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardiacnet-learning-to-reconstruct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-symbolic Learning Yielding Logical Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-learning-yielding-logical-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neuro-symbolic systems combine the abilities of neural perception and logical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-learning-yielding-logical-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MrT5: Dynamic Token Merging for Efficient Byte-level Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrt5-dynamic-token-merging-for-efficient-byte</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models that rely on subword tokenization have significant drawbacks, such as sensitivity to character-level noise like spelling errors and inconsistent compression rates across different languages and scripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrt5-dynamic-token-merging-for-efficient-byte</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Component Analysis: Discovering Patterns in Short Texts Beyond Topics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-component-analysis-discovering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic modeling is a key method in text analysis, but existing approaches are limited by assuming one topic per document or fail to scale efficiently for large, noisy datasets of short texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-component-analysis-discovering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Uncertainty Metrics for Long-form Language Model Outputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-uncertainty-metrics-for-long-form</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have significantly improved text generation capabilities, but these systems are still known to hallucinate, and granular uncertainty estimation for long-form LLM generations remains challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-uncertainty-metrics-for-long-form</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Action Recognition by Leveraging the Hierarchical Structure of Actions and Textual Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-action-recognition-by-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present a novel approach to improve action recognition by exploiting the hierarchical organization of actions and by incorporating contextualized textual information, including location and prior actions to reflect the sequential context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-action-recognition-by-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Simulations of The Solar Corona Evolution With Denoising Diffusion : Proof of Concept</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-simulations-of-the-solar-corona</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The solar magnetized corona is responsible for various manifestations with a space weather impact, such as flares, coronal mass ejections (CMEs) and, naturally, the solar wind.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-simulations-of-the-solar-corona</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation and Application of an Intelligibility Protocol for Interaction with an LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-and-application-of-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we address this shortcoming for the case in which one of the agents acts as a ''generator'' using a large language model (LLM) and the other is an agent that acts as a ''tester'' using either a human-expert, or a proxy for a human-expert (for example, a database compiled using human-expertise).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-and-application-of-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuseFL: One-Shot Federated Learning through the Lens of Causality with Progressive Model Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusefl-one-shot-federated-learning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we provide a causal view to find that this performance drop of OFL methods comes from the isolation problem, which means that local isolatedly trained models in OFL may easily fit to spurious correlations due to the data heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusefl-one-shot-federated-learning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth Attention for Robust RGB Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-attention-for-robust-rgb-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RGB video object tracking is a fundamental task in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-attention-for-robust-rgb-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Response not Preference: A Stackelberg Approach for LLM Detoxification using Non-parallel Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-response-not-preference-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We model the fine-tuning process as a Stackelberg game between an LLM (leader) and a toxicity screener (follower), which is a binary style classifier (toxic or non-toxic).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-response-not-preference-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrajAgent: An Agent Framework for Unified Trajectory Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajagent-an-agent-framework-for-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In TrajAgent, we first develop UniEnv, an execution environment with a unified data and model interface, to support the execution and training of various models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajagent-an-agent-framework-for-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Referring Human Pose and Mask Estimation in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-human-pose-and-mask-estimation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Referring Human Pose and Mask Estimation (R-HPM) in the wild, where either a text or positional prompt specifies the person of interest in an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/referring-human-pose-and-mask-estimation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOMIX: A Simple yet Effective Hard Negative Generation via Mixing for Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomix-a-simple-yet-effective-hard-negative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ANOMIX is (a) A first mixing approach: firstly attempting graph mixing to generate hard negatives for GAD task and node- and subgraph-level contrasts to distinguish underlying anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomix-a-simple-yet-effective-hard-negative</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
