<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 21:06:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical State Abstraction Based on Structural Information Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-state-abstraction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State abstraction optimizes decision-making by ignoring irrelevant environmental information in reinforcement learning with rich observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-state-abstraction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven Knowledge Fusion for Deep Multi-instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-knowledge-fusion-for-deep-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DKMIL adopts a completely different idea from existing deep MIL methods by analyzing the decision-making of key samples in the data set (referred to as the data-driven) and using the knowledge fusion module designed to extract valuable information from these samples to assist the model's training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-knowledge-fusion-for-deep-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation-driven Contrastive Self-training for Zero-shot Text Classification with Instruction-tuned GPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generation-driven-contrastive-self-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, GPT-based zero-shot classification models tend to make independent predictions over test instances, which can be sub-optimal as the instance correlations and the decision boundaries in the target space are ignored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generation-driven-contrastive-self-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-in-medical-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive experiments on 21 3D segmentation tasks and 9 2D segmentation tasks demonstrate that MedSAM outperforms the default SAM model with an average Dice Similarity Coefficient (DSC) of 22. 5% and 17. 6% on 3D and 2D segmentation tasks, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-in-medical-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grad-PU: Arbitrary-Scale Point Cloud Upsampling via Gradient Descent with Learned Distance Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grad-pu-arbitrary-scale-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing point cloud upsampling methods have roughly three steps: feature extraction, feature expansion and 3D coordinate prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grad-pu-arbitrary-scale-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Track Anything: Segment Anything Meets Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-anything-segment-anything-meets-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, in this report, we propose Track Anything Model (TAM), which achieves high-performance interactive tracking and segmentation in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-anything-segment-anything-meets-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthpop++: A Hybrid Framework for Generating A Country-scale Synthetic Population</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthpop-a-hybrid-framework-for-generating-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results show that synthetic population can realistically simulate the population for various administrative units of India, producing real-scale, detailed data at the desired level of zoom -- from cities, to districts, to states, eventually combining to form a country-scale synthetic population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthpop-a-hybrid-framework-for-generating-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive-saturated RNN: Remember more with less instability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-saturated-rnn-remember-more-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Orthogonal parameterization is a compelling solution to the vanishing gradient problem (VGP) in recurrent neural networks (RNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-saturated-rnn-remember-more-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixPro: Data Augmentation with MaskMix and Progressive Attention Labeling for Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixpro-data-augmentation-with-maskmix-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TransMix uses unreliable attention maps to compute mixed attention labels that can affect the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixpro-data-augmentation-with-maskmix-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enriching Source Code with Contextual Data for Code Completion Models: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enriching-source-code-with-contextual-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For comments, we find that the models perform better in the presence of multi-line comments (again with small effect sizes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enriching-source-code-with-contextual-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KInITVeraAI at SemEval-2023 Task 3: Simple yet Powerful Multilingual Fine-Tuning for Persuasion Techniques Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinitveraai-at-semeval-2023-task-3-simple-yet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the best-performing solution to the SemEval 2023 Task 3 on the subtask 3 dedicated to persuasion techniques detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinitveraai-at-semeval-2023-task-3-simple-yet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renate: A Library for Real-World Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renate-a-library-for-real-world-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss requirements for the use of continual learning algorithms in practice, from which we derive design principles for Renate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renate-a-library-for-real-world-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directed Acyclic Transformer Pre-training for High-quality Non-autoregressive Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-transformer-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-AutoRegressive (NAR) text generation models have drawn much attention because of their significantly faster decoding speed and good generation quality in machine translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-transformer-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WizardLM: Empowering Large Language Models to Follow Complex Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardlm-empowering-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing the human evaluation results of the high complexity part, we demonstrate that outputs from our WizardLM model are preferred to outputs from OpenAI ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardlm-empowering-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARAGRAPH2GRAPH: A GNN-based framework for layout paragraph analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paragraph2graph-a-gnn-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document layout analysis has a wide range of requirements across various domains, languages, and business scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paragraph2graph-a-gnn-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stubborn: An Environment for Evaluating Stubbornness between Agents with Aligned Incentives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stubborn-an-environment-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our preliminary results, the agents learn to use their partner's stubbornness as a signal for improving the choices that they make in the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stubborn-an-environment-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Sparse Fusion for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-sparse-fusion-for-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study how to effectively leverage image modality in the emerging fully sparse architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-sparse-fusion-for-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Correspondence Matching for Generalizable Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-correspondence-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to our approach lies in the explicitly modeled correspondence matching information, so as to provide the geometry prior to the prediction of NeRF color and density for volume rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-correspondence-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking ChatGPT-4 on ACR Radiation Oncology In-Training Exam (TXIT): Potentials and Challenges for AI-Assisted Medical Education and Decision Making in Radiation Oncology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chatgpt-4-on-acr-radiation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While ChatGPT-4 is not yet suitable for clinical decision making in radiation oncology, it has the potential to assist in medical education for the general public and cancer patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-chatgpt-4-on-acr-radiation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Context Constraints of LLMs: Enhancing Context Efficiency of LLMs with Self-Information-Based Content Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-context-constraints-of-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have received significant attention by achieving remarkable performance across various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-context-constraints-of-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Tree-based Index for Efficient and Effective Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-tree-based-index-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, while ANN can improve the efficiency of DR models, it usually comes with a significant price on retrieval performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-tree-based-index-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-capacity and Flexible Video Steganography via Invertible Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-capacity-and-flexible-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For large-capacity, we present a reversible pipeline to perform multiple videos hiding and recovering through a single invertible neural network (INN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-capacity-and-flexible-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark for Cycling Close Pass Near Miss Event Detection from Video Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-cycling-close-pass-near-miss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instance-level detection aims to detect which vehicle in the scene gives rise to a close pass near miss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-cycling-close-pass-near-miss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glocal Energy-based Learning for Few-Shot Open-Set Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glocal-energy-based-learning-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot open-set recognition (FSOR) is a challenging task of great practical value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glocal-energy-based-learning-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Function-Consistent Feature Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/function-consistent-feature-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea of FCFD is to make teacher and student features not only numerically similar, but more importantly produce similar outputs when fed to the later part of the same network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/function-consistent-feature-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once Detected, Never Lost: Surpassing Human Performance in Offline LiDAR based 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/once-detected-never-lost-surpassing-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from this, we propose a high-performance offline detector in a track-centric perspective instead of the conventional object-centric perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/once-detected-never-lost-surpassing-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SocialDial: A Benchmark for Socially-Aware Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialdial-a-benchmark-for-socially-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, SocialDial is the first socially-aware dialogue dataset that covers multiple social factors and has fine-grained labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialdial-a-benchmark-for-socially-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modality-Aware Negative Sampling for Multi-modal Knowledge Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-aware-negative-sampling-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Negative sampling (NS) is widely used in knowledge graph embedding (KGE), which aims to generate negative triples to make a positive-negative contrast during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-aware-negative-sampling-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neuro-Symbolic Approach for Enhanced Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neuro-symbolic-approach-for-enhanced-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning on the context of human beings is crucial for many real-world applications especially for those deploying autonomous systems (e. g. robots).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neuro-symbolic-approach-for-enhanced-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Socially Abnormal Highway Driving Behaviors via Recurrent Graph Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-socially-abnormal-highway-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the problem of detecting a variety of socially abnormal driving behaviors, i. e., behaviors that do not conform to the behavior of other nearby drivers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-socially-abnormal-highway-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Recurrent Learning Network for Sustainable Compressed Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-recurrent-learning-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the initial reconstruction sub-network has a hierarchical structure to progressively recover the image, reducing the number of parameters, the residual reconstruction sub-network facilitates recurrent residual feature extraction via recurrent learning to perform both feature fusion and deep reconstructions across different scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-recurrent-learning-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device management and network connectivity as missing elements in TinyML landscape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-management-and-network-connectivity-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, the challenge discussed in the paper is the issue of network connectivity for such solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-management-and-network-connectivity-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Control Hydrodynamic Force on Fluidic Pinball via Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-control-hydrodynamic-force-on-fluidic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The finding from this work can control hydrodynamic force on the operation of fluidic pinball system and potentially pave the way for exploring efficient active flow control strategies in other complex fluid dynamic problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-control-hydrodynamic-force-on-fluidic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Chain-of-Thoughts Prompting with Iterative Bootstrapping in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chain-of-thoughts-prompting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By utilizing iterative bootstrapping, our approach enables LLMs to autonomously rectify errors, resulting in more precise and comprehensive reasoning chains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chain-of-thoughts-prompting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating ChatGPT's Information Extraction Capabilities: An Assessment of Performance, Explainability, Calibration, and Faithfulness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-chatgpt-s-information-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The capability of Large Language Models (LLMs) like ChatGPT to comprehend user intent and provide reasonable responses has made them extremely popular lately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-chatgpt-s-information-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transductive Few-shot Learning with Prototype-based Label Propagation by Iterative Graph Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transductive-few-shot-learning-with-prototype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel prototype-based label propagation to solve these issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transductive-few-shot-learning-with-prototype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogicRec: Recommendation with Users' Logical Requirements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logicrec-recommendation-with-users-logical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we formulate the problem of recommendation with users' logical requirements (LogicRec) and construct benchmark datasets for LogicRec.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logicrec-recommendation-with-users-logical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated-UNet: A Fast and Accurate Medical Image Segmentation Approach using a Dilated Transformer and U-Net Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-unet-a-fast-and-accurate-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation is crucial for the development of computer-aided diagnostic and therapeutic systems, but still faces numerous difficulties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-unet-a-fast-and-accurate-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Spoilers in Movie Reviews with External Movie Knowledge and User Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-spoilers-in-movie-reviews-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose MVSD, a novel Multi-View Spoiler Detection framework that takes into account the external knowledge about movies and user activities on movie review platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-spoilers-in-movie-reviews-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasing the Scope as You Learn: Adaptive Bayesian Optimization in Nested Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-the-scope-as-you-learn-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances have extended the scope of Bayesian optimization (BO) to expensive-to-evaluate black-box functions with dozens of dimensions, aspiring to unlock impactful applications, for example, in the life sciences, neural architecture search, and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-the-scope-as-you-learn-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Distillation from 3D to Bird's-Eye-View for LiDAR Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-from-3d-to-bird-s-eye</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is difficult for existing models to achieve both high inference speed and accuracy simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-from-3d-to-bird-s-eye</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lookahead Diffusion Probabilistic Models for Refining Mean Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lookahead-diffusion-probabilistic-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose lookahead diffusion probabilistic models (LA-DPMs) to exploit the correlation in the outputs of the deep neural networks (DNNs) over subsequent timesteps in diffusion probabilistic models (DPMs) to refine the mean estimation of the conditional Gaussian distributions in the backward process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lookahead-diffusion-probabilistic-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Adversarial Faces Using Only Real Face Self-Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-adversarial-faces-using-only-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial attacks aim to disturb the functionality of a target system by adding specific noise to the input samples, bringing potential threats to security and robustness when applied to facial recognition systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-adversarial-faces-using-only-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAILER: Structure-aware Pre-trained Language Model for Legal Case Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sailer-structure-aware-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, in contrast to the general retrieval, the relevance in the legal domain is sensitive to key legal elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sailer-structure-aware-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Recommendation with Probabilistic Logical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-recommendation-with-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better capture the uncertainty and evolution of user tastes, SR-PLR embeds users and items with a probabilistic method and conducts probabilistic logical reasoning on users' interaction patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-recommendation-with-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Theory-of-Mind Performance in Large Language Models via Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-theory-of-mind-performance-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GPT-4 performed best in zero-shot settings, reaching nearly 80% ToM accuracy, but still fell short of the 87% human accuracy on the test set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-theory-of-mind-performance-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Classification for Detecting Parkinson's Disease from Wrist Motions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-classification-for-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We used a random search to find the highest-scoring InceptionTime architecture and compared it to ROCKET with a ridge classifier and a multi-layer perceptron (MLP) on wrist motions of PD patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-classification-for-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eWaSR -- an embedded-compute-ready maritime obstacle detection network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ewasr-an-embedded-compute-ready-maritime</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tests on a real embedded device OAK-D show that, while WaSR cannot run due to memory restrictions, eWaSR runs comfortably at 5. 5 FPS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ewasr-an-embedded-compute-ready-maritime</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual Fairness in Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-fairness-in-bayesian-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study Individual Fairness (IF) for Bayesian neural networks (BNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-fairness-in-bayesian-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Sharp : Study of Single Image Super Resolution using Residual Dense Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-sharp-single-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study examines the Residual Dense Networks architecture proposed by Yhang et al. [17] and analyzes the importance of its components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-sharp-single-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
