<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 21:06:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>On Privacy and Personalization in Cross-Silo Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-privacy-and-personalization-in-cross-silo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the application of differential privacy (DP) has been well-studied in cross-device federated learning (FL), there is a lack of work considering DP for cross-silo FL, a setting characterized by a limited number of clients each containing many data subjects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-privacy-and-personalization-in-cross-silo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let Invariant Rationale Discovery Inspire Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-invariant-rationale-discovery-inspire</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, without supervision signals, RGCL uses a rationale generator to reveal salient features about graph instance-discrimination as the rationale, and then creates rationale-aware views for contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-invariant-rationale-discovery-inspire</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Sampling Randomized Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this hurdle, we propose a Double Sampling Randomized Smoothing (DSRS) framework, which exploits the sampled probability from an additional smoothing distribution to tighten the robustness certification of the previous smoothed classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A machine-generated catalogue of Charon's craters and implications for the Kuiper belt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-machine-generated-catalogue-of-charon-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is motivated by the recent results of Singer et al. (2019) who, using manual cataloging, found a change in the size distribution slope of craters smaller than 12 km in diameter, translating into a paucity of small Kuiper Belt objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-machine-generated-catalogue-of-charon-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Prosody Annotation with Pre-Trained Text-Speech Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-prosody-annotation-with-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prosodic boundary plays an important role in text-to-speech synthesis (TTS) in terms of naturalness and readability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-prosody-annotation-with-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting the Adversarial Transferability of Surrogate Model with Dark Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-adversarial-transferability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method of training a surrogate model with abundant dark knowledge to boost the adversarial transferability of the adversarial examples generated by the surrogate model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-adversarial-transferability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Physics between Digital Twins with Low-Fidelity Models and Physics-Informed Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-physics-between-digital-twins-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on recent advances related to physics-informed priors, Hamiltonian Monte Carlo methods and using these for inverse problems we set up an inference methodology that allows our approach to be computational feasible also for physical models based on partial differential equations and individual data that are not aligned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-physics-between-digital-twins-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-Form Diffeomorphic Transformations for Time Series Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-diffeomorphic-transformations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gradient-based optimization frameworks containing diffeomorphic transformations require to calculate derivatives to the differential equation's solution with respect to the model parameters, i. e. sensitivity analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-diffeomorphic-transformations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis and Extensions of Adversarial Training for Video Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-and-extensions-of-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our first contribution is to show that generating optimal attacks for video requires carefully tuning the attack parameters, especially the step size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-and-extensions-of-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Imputation and Cross-Attention Network Based on Incomplete Longitudinal and Multi-Modal Data for Alzheimer's Disease Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-imputation-and-cross-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, a multi-view imputation method combined with adversarial learning, which can handle a wide range of missing data situations and reduce imputation errors, was presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-imputation-and-cross-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Functional Output Regression with Infimal Convolution: Exploring the Huber and $ε$-insensitive Losses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functional-output-regression-with-infimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficiency of the approach is demonstrated and contrasted with the classical squared loss setting on both synthetic and real-world benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functional-output-regression-with-infimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous-Time Modeling of Counterfactual Outcomes Using Neural Controlled Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-time-modeling-of-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assess solutions to this problem, we propose a controllable simulation environment based on a model of tumor growth for a range of scenarios with irregular sampling reflective of a variety of clinical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-time-modeling-of-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level 2 Autonomous Driving on a Single Device: Diving into the Devils of Openpilot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-2-autonomous-driving-on-a-single-device</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equipped with a wide span of sensors, predominant autonomous driving solutions are becoming more modular-oriented for safe system design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-2-autonomous-driving-on-a-single-device</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pythae: Unifying Generative Autoencoders in Python -- A Benchmarking Use Case</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pythae-unifying-generative-autoencoders-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, deep generative models have attracted increasing interest due to their capacity to model complex distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pythae-unifying-generative-autoencoders-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at Smoothness in Domain Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-smoothness-in-domain-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the analysis, we introduce the Smooth Domain Adversarial Training (SDAT) procedure, which effectively enhances the performance of existing domain adversarial methods for both classification and object detection tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-smoothness-in-domain-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All the World's a (Hyper)Graph: A Data Drama</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-the-world-s-a-hyper-graph-a-data-drama</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Hyperbard, a dataset of diverse relational data representations derived from Shakespeare's plays.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-the-world-s-a-hyper-graph-a-data-drama</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeQuENet: Perceptual Quality Enhancement of Compressed Video with Adaptation- and Attention-based Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pequenet-perceptual-quality-enhancement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we propose a generative adversarial network (GAN) framework to enhance the perceptual quality of compressed videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pequenet-perceptual-quality-enhancement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HaGRID -- HAnd Gesture Recognition Image Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hagrid-hand-gesture-recognition-image-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce an enormous dataset HaGRID (HAnd Gesture Recognition Image Dataset) for hand gesture recognition (HGR) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hagrid-hand-gesture-recognition-image-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting Self-Supervised Vision Transformers by Probing Attention-Conditioned Masking Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-self-supervised-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the design of recent SSL approaches based on learning from partial image inputs generated via masking or cropping -- either by learning to predict the missing pixels, or learning representational invariances to such augmentations -- we propose PACMAC, a simple two-stage adaptation algorithm for self-supervised ViTs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-self-supervised-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Contrastive Attributed Graph Clustering Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-contrastive-attributed-graph-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attributed graph clustering is one of the most important tasks in graph analysis field, the goal of which is to group nodes with similar representations into the same cluster without manual guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-contrastive-attributed-graph-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Privacy Protection on Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-privacy-protection-on-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that generated adversarial examples can erase most content information in original examples or replace it with target speech content through speech enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-privacy-protection-on-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory-guided Control Prediction for End-to-end Autonomous Driving: A Simple yet Strong Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-guided-control-prediction-for-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The two branches are connected so that the control branch receives corresponding guidance from the trajectory branch at each time step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-guided-control-prediction-for-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGIC: Microlensing Analysis Guided by Intelligent Computation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-microlensing-analysis-guided-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key feature of MAGIC is the introduction of neural controlled differential equation, which provides the capability to handle light curves with irregular sampling and large data gaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-microlensing-analysis-guided-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARLANE: A Lane Detection Benchmark for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation from Simulation to multiple Real-World Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carlane-a-lane-detection-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation demonstrates great potential to mitigate domain shifts by transferring models from labeled source domains to unlabeled target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carlane-a-lane-detection-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Segmentation of LiDAR Sequences: Dataset and Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-segmentation-of-lidar-sequences</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Helix4D operates on acquisition slices that correspond to a fraction of a full rotation of the sensor, significantly reducing the total latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-segmentation-of-lidar-sequences</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAVs Beneath the Surface: Cooperative Autonomy for Subterranean Search and Rescue in DARPA SubT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uavs-beneath-the-surface-cooperative-autonomy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to the winning solution that was developed specifically for the Virtual Track, the proposed solution also proved to be a robust system for deployment onboard physical UAVs flying in the extremely harsh and confined environment of the real-world competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uavs-beneath-the-surface-cooperative-autonomy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable First-Order Bayesian Optimization via Structured Automatic Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-first-order-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the performance of BO, prior work suggested incorporating gradient information into a Gaussian process surrogate of the objective, giving rise to kernel matrices of size $nd \times nd$ for $n$ observations in $d$ dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-first-order-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Surprising Behaviour of node2vec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-surprising-behaviour-of-node2vec</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph embedding techniques are a staple of modern graph learning research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-surprising-behaviour-of-node2vec</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Capsule Endoscopy Classification using Focal Modulation Guided Convolutional Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-capsule-endoscopy-classification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare our FocalConvNet with other SOTA on Kvasir-Capsule, a large-scale VCE dataset with 44, 228 frames with 13 classes of different anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-capsule-endoscopy-classification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFormableTag: End-to-end Generation and Recognition of Deformable Fiducial Markers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepformabletag-end-to-end-generation-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, a differentiable image simulator creates a training dataset of photorealistic scene images with the deformed markers, being rendered during optimization in a differentiable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepformabletag-end-to-end-generation-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'John ate 5 apples' != 'John ate some apples': Self-Supervised Paraphrase Quality Detection for Algebraic Word Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/john-ate-5-apples-john-ate-some-apples-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a need for paraphrase scoring methods in the context of AWP to enable the training of good paraphrasers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/john-ate-5-apples-john-ate-some-apples-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dialogue-state-tracking-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a novel dialogue state tracking task to track the information of visual objects that are mentioned in video-grounded dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dialogue-state-tracking-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to talk so your robot will learn: Instructions, descriptions, and pragmatics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-talk-so-your-robot-will-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that social learning from a wider range of language -- in particular, expanding the field's present focus on instructions to include learning from descriptions -- is a promising approach for value alignment and reinforcement learning more broadly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-talk-so-your-robot-will-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Improved Normed-Deformable Convolution for Crowd Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-improved-normed-deformable-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the heads are not uniformly covered by the sampling points in the deformable convolution, resulting in loss of head information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-improved-normed-deformable-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Range Graph Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-graph-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) that are based on the message passing (MP) paradigm exchange information between 1-hop neighbors to build node representations at each layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-graph-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Space Partitioning for Nearest Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-space-partitioning-for-nearest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an end-to-end learning framework that couples the partitioning (one key step of ANNS) and learning-to-search steps using a custom loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-space-partitioning-for-nearest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forming Effective Human-AI Teams: Building Machine Learning Models that Complement the Capabilities of Multiple Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forming-effective-human-ai-teams-building</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an approach that trains a classification model to complement the capabilities of multiple human experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forming-effective-human-ai-teams-building</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-level Representation Learning for Self-supervised Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-representation-learning-for-self-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its simplicity, we demonstrate that it can significantly improve the performance of existing SSL methods for various visual tasks, including object detection and semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-level-representation-learning-for-self-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Supervised vs. Unsupervised: Representative Benchmarking and Analysis of Image Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-supervised-vs-unsupervised-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we compare methods using performance-based benchmarks such as linear evaluation, nearest neighbor classification, and clustering for several different datasets, demonstrating the lack of a clear front-runner within the current state-of-the-art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-supervised-vs-unsupervised-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nucleus Segmentation and Analysis in Breast Cancer with the MIScnn Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nucleus-segmentation-and-analysis-in-breast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The NuCLS dataset contains over 220. 000 annotations of cell nuclei in breast cancers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nucleus-segmentation-and-analysis-in-breast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catastrophic overfitting is a bug but also a feature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catastrophic-overfitting-is-a-bug-but-also-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite clear computational advantages in building robust neural networks, adversarial training (AT) using single-step methods is unstable as it suffers from catastrophic overfitting (CO): Networks gain non-trivial robustness during the first stages of adversarial training, but suddenly reach a breaking point where they quickly lose all robustness in just a few iterations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catastrophic-overfitting-is-a-bug-but-also-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Understanding How Machines Can Learn Causal Overhypotheses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-how-machines-can-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work in machine learning and cognitive science has suggested that understanding causal information is essential to the development of intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-understanding-how-machines-can-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning with Guarantees via Weight Interval Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-guarantees-via-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new training paradigm that enforces interval constraints on neural network parameter space to control forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-guarantees-via-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatially-Adaptive Multilayer Selection for GAN Inversion and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-adaptive-multilayer-selection-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new method to invert and edit such complex images in the latent space of GANs, such as StyleGAN2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatially-adaptive-multilayer-selection-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrier Certified Safety Learning Control: When Sum-of-Square Programming Meets Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/barrier-certified-safety-learning-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety guarantee is essential in many engineering implementations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/barrier-certified-safety-learning-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Private Online Convex Optimization: Optimal Algorithms in $\ell_p$-Geometry and High Dimensional Contextual Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-private-online-convex-optimization-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address such a challenge as the online convex optimization with privacy protection, we propose a private variant of online Frank-Wolfe algorithm with recursive gradients for variance reduction to update and reveal the parameters upon each data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-private-online-convex-optimization-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search-Based Testing Approach for Deep Reinforcement Learning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-based-testing-approach-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such attacks often lead to unrealistic states of the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-based-testing-approach-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Bitrate Neural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-bitrate-neural-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural approximations of scalar and vector fields, such as signed distance functions and radiance fields, have emerged as accurate, high-quality representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-bitrate-neural-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NatGen: Generative pre-training by "Naturalizing" source code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natgen-generative-pre-training-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Generative Language models (e. g. PLBART, CodeT5, SPT-Code) for source code yielded strong results on several tasks in the past few years, including code generation and translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natgen-generative-pre-training-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Data Mixing Prior for Improving Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-data-mixing-prior-for-improving-self-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More notably, our SDMP is the first method that successfully leverages data mixing to improve (rather than hurt) the performance of Vision Transformers in the self-supervised setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-data-mixing-prior-for-improving-self-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
