<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 21:07:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>RAPIDFlow: Recurrent Adaptable Pyramids with Iterative Decoding for Efficient Optical Flow Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapidflow-recurrent-adaptable-pyramids-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting motion information from videos with optical flow estimation is vital in multiple practical robot applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapidflow-recurrent-adaptable-pyramids-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TFPred: Learning Discriminative Representations from Unlabeled Data for Few-Label Rotating Machinery Fault Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfpred-learning-discriminative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in intelligent rotating machinery fault diagnosis have been enabled by the availability of massive labeled training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tfpred-learning-discriminative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightplane: Highly-Scalable Components for Neural 3D Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightplane-highly-scalable-components-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contemporary 3D research, particularly in reconstruction and generation, heavily relies on 2D images for inputs or supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightplane-highly-scalable-components-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiased Collaborative Filtering with Kernel-Based Causal Balancing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-collaborative-filtering-with-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by these gaps, we propose to approximate the balancing functions in reproducing kernel Hilbert space and demonstrate that, based on the universal property and representer theorem of kernel functions, the causal balancing constraints can be better satisfied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-collaborative-filtering-with-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Heterogeneity-Aware Hypergraph Representation for Histopathology Whole Slide Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-heterogeneity-aware-hypergraph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Survival prediction is a complex ordinal regression task that aims to predict the survival coefficient ranking among a cohort of patients, typically achieved by analyzing patients' whole slide images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-heterogeneity-aware-hypergraph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Machine Translation with Source Coreference Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-machine-translation-with-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant improvements in enhancing the quality of translation, context-aware machine translation (MT) models underperform in many cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-machine-translation-with-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Continuous and Categorical Flow Matching for 3D De Novo Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-continuous-and-categorical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the use of flow matching, a recently proposed generative modeling framework that generalizes diffusion models, for the task of de novo molecule generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-continuous-and-categorical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Spatial Propagation Network for Sparsity-Adaptive Depth Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-spatial-propagation-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main function of depth completion is to compensate for an insufficient and unpredictable number of sparse depth measurements of hardware sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-spatial-propagation-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Robust Conformal Prediction with Improved Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-robust-conformal-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we first propose a novel framework called RSCP+ to provide provable robustness guarantee in evaluation, which fixes the issues in the original RSCP method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-robust-conformal-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Multi-Query Slot Attention for Unsupervised Object Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-multi-query-slot-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we extend the slot attention to a multi-query approach, allowing the model to learn multiple sets of slots, producing more stable masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-multi-query-slot-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Llama-3's Context Ten-Fold Overnight</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-llama-3-s-context-ten-fold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend the context length of Llama-3-8B-Instruct from 8K to 80K via QLoRA fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-llama-3-s-context-ten-fold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAN: Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-kolmogorov-arnold-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the Kolmogorov-Arnold representation theorem, we propose Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks (KANs) as promising alternatives to Multi-Layer Perceptrons (MLPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-kolmogorov-arnold-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Approaches for Integrating out Subjectivity in Cognate Synonym Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-approaches-for-integrating-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as we show here, binary character matrices, which are used as input for computational methods, do allow for representing the entire dataset including all synonyms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-approaches-for-integrating-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroDreamer: Zero-shot 3D Generation in $\sim$20 Seconds by Score-based Iterative Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microdreamer-zero-shot-3d-generation-in-sim</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce score-based iterative reconstruction (SIR), an efficient and general algorithm for 3D generation with a multi-view score-based diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microdreamer-zero-shot-3d-generation-in-sim</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Mamba: CLIP Pretrained Mamba Models with OOD and Hessian Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-mamba-clip-pretrained-mamba-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State space models and Mamba-based models have been increasingly applied across various domains, achieving state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-mamba-clip-pretrained-mamba-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATOMMIC: An Advanced Toolbox for Multitask Medical Imaging Consistency to facilitate Artificial Intelligence applications from acquisition to analysis in Magnetic Resonance Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atommic-an-advanced-toolbox-for-multitask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We benchmark 25 DL models on eight publicly available datasets to present distinct applications of ATOMMIC on accelerated MRI reconstruction, image segmentation, quantitative parameter map estimation, and joint accelerated MRI reconstruction and image segmentation utilizing MTL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atommic-an-advanced-toolbox-for-multitask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCA for Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pca-for-point-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By treating point process realizations as random measures, we adopt a functional analysis perspective and propose a form of functional Principal Component Analysis (fPCA) for point processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pca-for-point-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemiPL: A Semi-supervised Method for Event Sound Source Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semipl-a-semi-supervised-method-for-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Event Sound Source Localization has been widely applied in various fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semipl-a-semi-supervised-method-for-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countering Reward Over-optimization in LLM with Demonstration-Guided Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/countering-reward-over-optimization-in-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Reinforcement Learning (RL) has been proven essential for tuning large language models (LLMs), it can lead to reward over-optimization (ROO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/countering-reward-over-optimization-in-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Graph ODEs for Irregularly-Sampled Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-odes-for-irregularly-sampled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern graph representation learning works mostly under the assumption of dealing with regularly sampled temporal graph snapshots, which is far from realistic, e. g., social networks and physical systems are characterized by continuous dynamics and sporadic observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-odes-for-irregularly-sampled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG and RAU: A Survey on Retrieval-Augmented Language Model in Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-and-rau-a-survey-on-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have catalyzed significant advancements in Natural Language Processing (NLP), yet they encounter challenges such as hallucination and the need for domain-specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-and-rau-a-survey-on-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Dynamic Data Valuation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-dynamic-data-valuation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data constitute the foundational component of the data economy and its marketplaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-dynamic-data-valuation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Correlation Learning for Generalizable Cross-Modal Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-correlation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rising prevalence of deepfakes, there is a growing interest in developing generalizable detection methods for various types of deepfakes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-correlation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G2LTraj: A Global-to-Local Generation Approach for Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2ltraj-a-global-to-local-generation-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, to ensure the optimal granularity of key steps, we design a selectable granularity strategy that caters to each predicted trajectory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2ltraj-a-global-to-local-generation-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pessimistic Value Iteration for Multi-Task Data Sharing in Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pessimistic-value-iteration-for-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further provide theoretical analysis, which shows that the optimality gap of our method is only related to the expected data coverage of the shared dataset, thus resolving the distribution shift issue in data sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pessimistic-value-iteration-for-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyXFusion: Multi-modal Anomaly Synthesis with Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyxfusion-multi-modal-anomaly-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The AnomalyXFusion framework comprises two distinct yet synergistic modules: the Multi-modal In-Fusion (MIF) module and the Dynamic Dif-Fusion (DDF) module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyxfusion-multi-modal-anomaly-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Controlled Differential Equations with Quantum Hidden Evolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-controlled-differential-equations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a class of neural controlled differential equation inspired by quantum mechanics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-controlled-differential-equations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be Aware of the Neighborhood Effect: Modeling Selection Bias under Interference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-aware-of-the-neighborhood-effect-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On this basis, we propose a novel ideal loss that can be used to deal with selection bias in the presence of neighborhood effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-aware-of-the-neighborhood-effect-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGCBS: An Optimal and Efficient Algorithm for Solving Multi-Goal Multi-Agent Path Finding Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgcbs-an-optimal-and-efficient-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this paper demonstrates that the methods based on DVS cannot always obtain the optimal solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgcbs-an-optimal-and-efficient-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Efficient and Flexible Interpretability of Data-driven Anomaly Detection in Industrial Processes with AcME-AD</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-and-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Machine Learning has become crucial for Industry 4. 0, its opaque nature hinders trust and impedes the transformation of valuable insights into actionable decision, a challenge exacerbated in the evolving Industry 5. 0 with its human-centric focus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-and-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Benchmark Leakage in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-benchmark-leakage-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing 31 LLMs under the context of mathematical reasoning, we reveal substantial instances of training even test set misuse, resulting in potentially unfair comparisons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-benchmark-leakage-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexiFilm: Long Video Generation with Flexible Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexifilm-long-video-generation-with-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating long and consistent videos has emerged as a significant yet challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexifilm-long-video-generation-with-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Line Combination Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-line-combination-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel algorithm, called semantic line combination detector (SLCD), to find an optimal combination of semantic lines is proposed in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-line-combination-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More RLHF, More Trust? On The Impact of Human Preference Alignment On Language Model Trustworthiness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-rlhf-more-trust-on-the-impact-of-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The surge in Large Language Models (LLMs) development has led to improved performance on cognitive tasks as well as an urgent need to align these models with human values in order to safely exploit their power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-rlhf-more-trust-on-the-impact-of-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Density to Geometry: YOLOv8 Instance Segmentation for Reverse Engineering of Optimized Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-density-to-geometry-yolov8-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Density-based topology optimization methods require post-processing to convert the optimal density distribution into a parametric representation for design exploration and integration with CAD tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-density-to-geometry-yolov8-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Diffusion Models for Time Series and Spatio-Temporal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-diffusion-models-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditioned models, on the other hand, utilize extra information to enhance performance and are similarly divided for both predictive and generative tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-diffusion-models-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination of Multimodal Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-of-multimodal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By drawing the granular classification and landscapes of hallucination causes, evaluation benchmarks, and mitigation methods, this survey aims to deepen the understanding of hallucinations in MLLMs and inspire further advancements in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-of-multimodal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-hoc and manifold explanations analysis of facial expression data based on deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-hoc-and-manifold-explanations-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study not only advances the application of AI technology in the field of psychology but also provides a new psychological theoretical understanding the information processing of the AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-hoc-and-manifold-explanations-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Drives Performance in Multilingual Language Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-drives-performance-in-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the factors influencing the performance of multilingual large language models (MLLMs) across diverse languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-drives-performance-in-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Data Augmentation as an Imbalanced Learning Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-data-augmentation-as-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use these techniques to create synthetic time series observations and improve the accuracy of forecasting models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-data-augmentation-as-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised learning for classifying paranasal anomalies in the maxillary sinus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-classifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we fine-tune the encoder part of the 3D CNN on a labelled dataset of normal and anomalous MS images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-classifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Evaluation of Adversarial Attacks against Speech Emotion Recognition Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In summary, this work contributes to the understanding of the robustness of CNN-LSTM models, particularly in SER scenarios, and the impact of AEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longitudinal Mammogram Risk Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longitudinal-mammogram-risk-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend a state-of-the-art ML model to ingest an arbitrary number of longitudinal mammograms and predict future breast cancer risk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longitudinal-mammogram-risk-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3oE: Multi-Domain Multi-Task Mixture-of Experts Recommendation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3oe-multi-domain-multi-task-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[M3oE integrates multi-domain information, maps knowledge across domains and tasks, and optimizes multiple objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3oe-multi-domain-multi-task-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiency-Effectiveness Tradeoff of Probabilistic Structured Queries for Cross-Language Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-effectiveness-tradeoff-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic Structured Queries (PSQ) is a cross-language information retrieval (CLIR) method that uses translation probabilities statistically derived from aligned corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-effectiveness-tradeoff-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source-Free Domain Adaptation of Weakly-Supervised Object Localization Models for Histology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-domain-adaptation-of-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A WSOL model initially trained on some labeled source image data can be adapted using unlabeled target data in cases of significant domain shifts caused by variations in staining, scanners, and cancer type.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-free-domain-adaptation-of-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-SR: Scientific Equation Discovery via Programming with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-sr-scientific-equation-discovery-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematical equations have been unreasonably effective in describing complex natural phenomena across various scientific disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-sr-scientific-equation-discovery-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Present and Past in Unsupervised Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-present-and-past-in-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate a unifying framework for unsupervised continual learning (UCL), which disentangles learning objectives that are specific to the present and the past data, encompassing stability, plasticity, and cross-task consolidation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-present-and-past-in-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Vision Mamba: Models, Applications and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-vision-mamba-models-applications</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help keep pace with the rapid advancements in computer vision, this paper aims to provide a comprehensive review of visual Mamba approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-vision-mamba-models-applications</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConPro: Learning Severity Representation for Medical Images using Contrastive Learning and Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conpro-learning-severity-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the severity of conditions shown in images in medical diagnosis is crucial, serving as a key guide for clinical assessment, treatment, as well as evaluating longitudinal progression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conpro-learning-severity-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
