<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 21:07:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Heterogeneous Graph Learning with Weighted Mixed-Curvature Product Manifold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-heterogeneous-graph-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A promising candidate for the faithful embedding of data with varying structure is product manifolds of component spaces of different geometries (spherical, hyperbolic, or euclidean).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-heterogeneous-graph-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InPars Toolkit: A Unified and Reproducible Synthetic Data Generation Pipeline for Neural Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inpars-toolkit-a-unified-and-reproducible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our toolkit not only reproduces the InPars method and partially reproduces Promptagator, but also provides a plug-and-play functionality allowing the use of different LLMs, exploring filtering methods and finetuning various reranker models on the generated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inpars-toolkit-a-unified-and-reproducible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIM: Teaching Large Language Models to Translate with Comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tim-teaching-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-sourced large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable efficacy in various tasks with instruction tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tim-teaching-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleviating Matthew Effect of Offline Reinforcement Learning in Interactive Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-matthew-effect-of-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through theoretical analyses, we find that the conservatism of existing methods fails in pursuing users' long-term satisfaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-matthew-effect-of-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injecting Logical Constraints into Neural Networks via Straight-Through Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecting-logical-constraints-into-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Injecting discrete logical constraints into neural network learning is one of the main challenges in neuro-symbolic AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecting-logical-constraints-into-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-cost semi-automatic arrhythmia detector using ECG signal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-cost-semi-automatic-arrhythmia-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cardiac arrhythmias are common heart rhythm disorders with significant global impact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-cost-semi-automatic-arrhythmia-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINFA: a Python library for variational inference with normalizing flow and annealing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linfa-a-python-library-for-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational inference is an increasingly popular method in statistics and machine learning for approximating probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linfa-a-python-library-for-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT-based Subchondral Bone Microstructural Analysis in Knee Osteoarthritis via MR-Guided Distillation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-based-subchondral-bone-microstructural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, its clinical application is limited by the cost and time of MR. Purpose: We aim to develop a novel distillation-learning-based method named SRRD for subchondral bone microstructural analysis using easily-acquired CT images, which leverages paired MR images to enhance the CT-based analysis model during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-based-subchondral-bone-microstructural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HistRED: A Historical Document-Level Relation Extraction Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histred-a-historical-document-level-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the usefulness of our dataset, we propose a bilingual RE model that leverages both Korean and Hanja contexts to predict relations between entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histred-a-historical-document-level-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearable to detect electromyographic changes in the trapezius muscle due to improper posture while sitting for long periods of time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearable-to-detect-electromyographic-changes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The trapezius muscle, located in the back, plays an important role in maintaining upright posture and is involved in movements such as lateral flexion and rotation of the head, as well as shoulder elevation and depression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearable-to-detect-electromyographic-changes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAGC-A68: a space access graph dataset for the classification of spaces and space elements in apartment buildings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sagc-a68-a-space-access-graph-dataset-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of building models for usable area, building safety, and energy use requires accurate classification data of spaces and space elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sagc-a68-a-space-access-graph-dataset-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearable to detect electromyographic changes in the trapezius muscle due to improper posture while sitting for long periods of time.</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearable-to-detect-electromyographic-changes-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The trapezius muscle, located in the back, plays an important role in maintaining upright posture and is involved in movements such as lateral flexion and rotation of the head, as well as shoulder elevation and depression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearable-to-detect-electromyographic-changes-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMEX: A Tool for Generating Customized Source Code Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comex-a-tool-for-generating-customized-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this barrier, we propose our tool COMEX - a framework that allows researchers and developers to create and combine multiple code-views which can be used by machine learning (ML) models for various SE tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comex-a-tool-for-generating-customized-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiVOLO: Multi-input Transformer for Age and Gender Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mivolo-multi-input-transformer-for-age-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Age and gender recognition in the wild is a highly challenging task: apart from the variability of conditions, pose complexities, and varying image quality, there are cases where the face is partially or completely occluded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mivolo-multi-input-transformer-for-age-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-SAM: Segment and Recognize Anything at Any Granularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-sam-segment-and-recognize-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Semantic-SAM, a universal image segmentation model to enable segment and recognize anything at any desired granularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-sam-segment-and-recognize-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advancements in End-to-End Autonomous Driving using Deep Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advancements-in-end-to-end-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-End driving is a promising paradigm as it circumvents the drawbacks associated with modular systems, such as their overwhelming complexity and propensity for error propagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advancements-in-end-to-end-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeDrag: Point Tracking is Not You Need for Interactive Point-based Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freedrag-point-tracking-is-not-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To serve the intricate and varied demands of image editing, precise and flexible manipulation of image content is indispensable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freedrag-point-tracking-is-not-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Synthetic Data for Data-Free Student Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customizing-synthetic-data-for-data-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works generally synthesize data from the pre-trained teacher model to replace the original training data for student learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customizing-synthetic-data-for-data-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoactSeg: Learning from Heterogeneous Data for New Multiple Sclerosis Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coactseg-learning-from-heterogeneous-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, a simple and effective relation regularization is proposed to ensure the longitudinal relations among the three outputs to improve the model learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coactseg-learning-from-heterogeneous-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Group Fairness in Federated Learning Using Augmented Lagrangian Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-group-fairness-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) has garnered considerable attention due to its privacy-preserving feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-group-fairness-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Vessels Annotation-based Coronary Artery Segmentation with Self-training and Prototype Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-vessels-annotation-based-coronary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose partial vessels annotation (PVA) based on the challenges of coronary artery segmentation and clinical diagnostic characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-vessels-annotation-based-coronary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stroke Extraction of Chinese Character Based on Deep Structure Deformable Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stroke-extraction-of-chinese-character-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a deep learning-based character stroke extraction method that takes semantic features and prior information of strokes into consideration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stroke-extraction-of-chinese-character-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early diagnosis of carpal tunnel syndrome using electromyogram signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-diagnosis-of-carpal-tunnel-syndrome</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The present investigation proposes to use electromyographic signals for the diagnosis of carpal tunnel with the aim of helping to reduce the number of false positives and negatives that are obtained with the criteria currently used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-diagnosis-of-carpal-tunnel-syndrome</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of EEG signals of blinking patterns in order to control a wheelchair for people with ALS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-eeg-signals-of-blinking-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) is a progressive neurodegenerative disease with no cure, emphasizing the need for innovative approaches to improve patients' quality of life.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-eeg-signals-of-blinking-patterns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-Driven Engineering Method to Support the Formalization of Machine Learning using SysML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-driven-engineering-method-to-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results: By consolidating the knowledge of domain and machine learning experts, a powerful tool to describe machine learning tasks by formalizing knowledge using the systems modeling language SysML is introduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-driven-engineering-method-to-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoCo: Dialectic Multi-Robot Collaboration with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roco-dialectic-multi-robot-collaboration-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to multi-robot collaboration that harnesses the power of pre-trained large language models (LLMs) for both high-level communication and low-level path planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roco-dialectic-multi-robot-collaboration-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-IQA: Can Segment Anything Boost Image Quality Assessment?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-iqa-can-segment-anything-boost-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments confirm the powerful feature extraction capabilities of Segment Anything and highlight the value of combining spatial-domain and frequency-domain features in IQA tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-iqa-can-segment-anything-boost-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Badgers: generating data quality deficits with Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badgers-generating-data-quality-deficits-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating context specific data quality deficits is necessary to experimentally assess data quality of data-driven (artificial intelligence (AI) or machine learning (ML)) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badgers-generating-data-quality-deficits-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Novel Cognitive Diagnosis Models via Evolutionary Multi-Objective Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-novel-cognitive-diagnosis-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose multi-objective genetic programming (MOGP) to explore the NAS task's search space by maximizing model performance and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-novel-cognitive-diagnosis-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethicist: Targeted Training Data Extraction Through Loss Smoothed Soft Prompting and Calibrated Confidence Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ethicist-targeted-training-data-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method named Ethicist for targeted training data extraction through loss smoothed soft prompting and calibrated confidence estimation, investigating how to recover the suffix in the training data when given a prefix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ethicist-targeted-training-data-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preventing Errors in Person Detection: A Part-Based Self-Monitoring Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preventing-errors-in-person-detection-a-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to detect learned objects regardless of their appearance is crucial for autonomous systems in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preventing-errors-in-person-detection-a-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MD-HIT: Machine learning for materials property prediction with dataset redundancy control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/md-hit-machine-learning-for-materials</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This issue is well known in the field of bioinformatics for protein function prediction, in which a redundancy reduction procedure (CD-Hit) is always applied to reduce the sample redundancy by ensuring no pair of samples has a sequence similarity greater than a given threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/md-hit-machine-learning-for-materials</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLTF: Reinforcement Learning from Unit Test Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rltf-reinforcement-learning-from-unit-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we proposed RLTF, i. e., Reinforcement Learning from Unit Test Feedback, a novel online RL framework with unit test feedback of multi-granularity for refining code LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rltf-reinforcement-learning-from-unit-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>False Sense of Security: Leveraging XAI to Analyze the Reasoning and True Performance of Context-less DGA Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/false-sense-of-security-leveraging-xai-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of revealing botnet activity through Domain Generation Algorithm (DGA) detection seems to be solved, considering that available deep learning classifiers achieve accuracies of over 99. 9%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/false-sense-of-security-leveraging-xai-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-Driven Engineering for Artificial Intelligence -- A Systematic Literature Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-driven-engineering-for-artificial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective: This study aims to investigate the existing body of knowledge in the field of Model-Driven Engineering MDE in support of AI (MDE4AI) to sharpen future research further and define the current state of the art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-driven-engineering-for-artificial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generate Equitable Text in Dialogue from Biased Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-equitable-text-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Absence of equitable and inclusive principles can hinder the formation of common ground, which in turn negatively impacts the overall performance of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-equitable-text-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECL: Class-Enhancement Contrastive Learning for Long-tailed Skin Lesion Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecl-class-enhancement-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose class-Enhancement Contrastive Learning (ECL), which enriches the information of minority classes and treats different classes equally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecl-class-enhancement-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Autoencoder-based Lossy Compression for Large-scale High-resolution Scientific Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-autoencoder-based-lossy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model achieves a compression ratio of 140 on several benchmark data sets without compromising the reconstruction quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-autoencoder-based-lossy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A generative flow for conditional sampling via optimal transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generative-flow-for-conditional-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sampling conditional distributions is a fundamental task for Bayesian inference and density estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generative-flow-for-conditional-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DebateKG: Automatic Policy Debate Case Creation with Semantic Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debatekg-automatic-policy-debate-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage the txtai semantic search and knowledge graph toolchain to produce and contribute 9 semantic knowledge graphs built on this dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debatekg-automatic-policy-debate-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT in the Age of Generative AI and Large Language Models: A Concise Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-in-the-age-of-generative-ai-and-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also lay out essential foundational literature on LLMs and GAI in general and their connection with ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-in-the-age-of-generative-ai-and-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultrasonic Image's Annotation Removal: A Self-supervised Noise2Noise Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrasonic-image-s-annotation-removal-a-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately annotated ultrasonic images are vital components of a high-quality medical report.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultrasonic-image-s-annotation-removal-a-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards cross-language prosody transfer for dialog</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-language-prosody-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech-to-speech translation systems today do not adequately support use for dialog purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-language-prosody-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitosis Detection from Partial Annotation by Dataset Generation via Frame-Order Flipping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitosis-detection-from-partial-annotation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we generate an image pair not containing mitosis events by frame-order flipping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitosis-detection-from-partial-annotation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histopathology Whole Slide Image Analysis with Heterogeneous Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathology-whole-slide-image-analysis-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel heterogeneous graph-based framework to leverage the inter-relationships among different types of nuclei for WSI analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathology-whole-slide-image-analysis-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design of Wearable EKG with a predictive algorithm based on ML for Telemonitoring CHD in Peru</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-of-wearable-ekg-with-a-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Normal sinus signals and left and right bundle branch block were obtained from a database as test diseases for the training process of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-of-wearable-ekg-with-a-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPNet: Bézier Primitive Segmentation on 3D Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bpnet-bezier-primitive-segmentation-on-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes BPNet, a novel end-to-end deep learning framework to learn B\'ezier primitive segmentation on 3D point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bpnet-bezier-primitive-segmentation-on-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ariadne's Thread:Using Text Prompts to Improve Segmentation of Infected Areas from Chest X-ray images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ariadne-s-thread-using-text-prompts-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of the infected areas of the lung is essential for quantifying the severity of lung disease like pulmonary infections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ariadne-s-thread-using-text-prompts-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Supervised Multilabel Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-supervised-multilabel-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they fail to design an end-to-end training framework, leading to high computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-supervised-multilabel-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing a Direct Feedback Loop between Humans and Convolutional Neural Networks through Local Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-a-direct-feedback-loop-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the gap, we designed DeepFuse, the first interactive design that realizes the direct feedback loop between a user and CNNs in diagnosing and revising CNN's vulnerability using local explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-a-direct-feedback-loop-between</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
