<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 09:11:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Context Shift Reduction for Offline Meta-Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-shift-reduction-for-offline-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach called Context Shift Reduction for OMRL (CSRO) to address the context shift problem with only offline datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-shift-reduction-for-offline-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking and Improving Multi-task Learning for End-to-end Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-and-improving-multi-task-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant improvements in end-to-end speech translation (ST) have been achieved through the application of multi-task learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-and-improving-multi-task-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilingual Corpus Mining and Multistage Fine-Tuning for Improving Machine Translation of Lecture Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilingual-corpus-mining-and-multistage-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To create the parallel corpora, we propose a dynamic programming based sentence alignment algorithm which leverages the cosine similarity of machine-translated sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilingual-corpus-mining-and-multistage-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formulating Discrete Probability Flow Through Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formulating-discrete-probability-flow-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to establish the fundamental theory for the probability flow of discrete diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formulating-discrete-probability-flow-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aspects of human memory and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aspects-of-human-memory-and-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are huge artificial neural networks which primarily serve to generate text, but also provide a very sophisticated probabilistic model of language use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aspects-of-human-memory-and-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proceedings of the 5th International Workshop on Reading Music Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proceedings-of-the-5th-international-workshop-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The International Workshop on Reading Music Systems (WoRMS) is a workshop that tries to connect researchers who develop systems for reading music, such as in the field of Optical Music Recognition, with other researchers and practitioners that could benefit from such systems, like librarians or musicologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proceedings-of-the-5th-international-workshop-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPAVE: A Generation and Classification-based Model for Joint Product Attribute Prediction and Value Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jpave-a-generation-and-classification-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the copy mechanism in value generator and the value attention module in value classifier help our model address the data discrepancy issue by only focusing on the relevant part of input text and ignoring other information which causes the discrepancy issue such as sentence structure in the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jpave-a-generation-and-classification-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender Inflected or Bias Inflicted: On Using Grammatical Gender Cues for Bias Evaluation in Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-inflected-or-bias-inflicted-on-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the work on evaluating gender bias in NMT has focused primarily on English as the source language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-inflected-or-bias-inflicted-on-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cup Curriculum: Curriculum Learning on Model Capacity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cup-curriculum-curriculum-learning-on-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Curriculum learning (CL) aims to increase the performance of a learner on a given task by applying a specialized learning strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cup-curriculum-curriculum-learning-on-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversations in Galician: a Large Language Model for an Underrepresented Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conversations-in-galician-a-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, as a demonstration of the dataset utility, we fine-tuned LLaMA-7B to comprehend and respond in Galician, a language not originally supported by the model, by following the Alpaca format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conversations-in-galician-a-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini but Mighty: Finetuning ViTs with Mini Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-but-mighty-finetuning-vits-with-mini</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers (ViTs) have become one of the dominant architectures in computer vision, and pre-trained ViT models are commonly adapted to new tasks via fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-but-mighty-finetuning-vits-with-mini</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss Balancing for Fair Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-balancing-for-fair-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imposing EL on the learning process leads to a non-convex optimization problem even if the loss function is convex, and the existing fair learning algorithms cannot properly be adopted to find the fair predictor under the EL constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-balancing-for-fair-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBCFormer: Lightweight Network Capable of Full-size ImageNet Classification at 1 FPS on Single Board Computers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbcformer-lightweight-network-capable-of-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first time, it achieves an ImageNet-1K top-1 accuracy of around 80% at a speed of 1. 0 frame/sec on the SBC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sbcformer-lightweight-network-capable-of-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Interpretable Transformer for Fine-Grained Image Classification and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-interpretable-transformer-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike mainstream classifiers that wait until the last fully-connected layer to incorporate class information to make predictions, we investigate a proactive approach, asking each class to search for itself in an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-interpretable-transformer-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeRO: Self-Supervised Reinforcement Learning for Recovery from Out-of-Distribution Situations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sero-self-supervised-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we show that our method can retrain the agent to recover from OOD situations even when in-distribution states are difficult to visit through exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sero-self-supervised-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Low-Resource Sequence Labeling by Sample-Aware Dynamic Sparse Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-low-resource-sequence-labeling-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, this requires formatting them into specialized augmented format unknown to the base pretrained language model (PLMs) necessitating finetuning to the target format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-low-resource-sequence-labeling-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Mathematical Autoformalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-mathematical-autoformalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we create $\texttt{MMA}$, a large, flexible, multilingual, and multi-domain dataset of informal-formal pairs, by using a language model to translate in the reverse direction, that is, from formal mathematical statements into corresponding informal ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-mathematical-autoformalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLORA: Fine-grained Low-Rank Architecture Search for Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flora-fine-grained-low-rank-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With our method, a more fine-grained rank configuration can be generated automatically and yield up to 33% extra FLOPs reduction compared to a simple uniform configuration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flora-fine-grained-low-rank-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RobustMat: Neural Diffusion for Street Landmark Patch Matching under Challenging Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustmat-neural-diffusion-for-street</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For autonomous vehicles (AVs), visual perception techniques based on sensors like cameras play crucial roles in information acquisition and processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustmat-neural-diffusion-for-street</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do LLMs exhibit human-like response biases? A case study in survey design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-exhibit-human-like-response-biases-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we use survey design as a case study, where human response biases caused by permutations in wordings of ``prompts'' have been extensively studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-exhibit-human-like-response-biases-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black-Box Prompt Optimization: Aligning Large Language Models without Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-prompt-optimization-aligning-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these models are often not well aligned with human intents, which calls for additional treatments on them, that is, the alignment problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-prompt-optimization-aligning-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Korean NLP Tasks with Linguistically Informed Subword Tokenization and Sub-character Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-korean-nlp-tasks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a morpheme-aware subword tokenization method that utilizes sub-character decomposition to address the challenges of applying Byte Pair Encoding (BPE) to Korean, a language characterized by its rich morphology and unique writing system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-korean-nlp-tasks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Information Integration and Propagation for Occluded Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-information-integration-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, as multiple images with the same identity are not accessible in the testing stage, we devise an Information Propagation (IP) mechanism to distill knowledge from the comprehensive representation to that of a single occluded image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-information-integration-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JaSPICE: Automatic Evaluation Metric Using Predicate-Argument Structures for Image Captioning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaspice-automatic-evaluation-metric-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image captioning studies heavily rely on automatic evaluation metrics such as BLEU and METEOR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaspice-automatic-evaluation-metric-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Instance Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-instance-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this deficiency, we propose Video Instance Matting~(VIM), that is, estimating alpha mattes of each instance at each frame of a video sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-instance-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLaMM: Pixel Grounding Large Multimodal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glamm-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Grounding LMM (GLaMM), the first model that can generate natural language responses seamlessly intertwined with corresponding object segmentation masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glamm-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical considerations for variable screening in the Super Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-considerations-for-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the performance of a Super Learner using the lasso for dimension reduction has not been fully explored in cases where the lasso is known to perform poorly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-considerations-for-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-Labeling for Domain-Agnostic Bangla Automatic Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-for-domain-agnostic-bangla</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate the efficacy of the model trained on psuedo-label data for the designed test-set along with publicly-available Bangla datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-for-domain-agnostic-bangla</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A universal framework for accurate and efficient geometric deep learning of molecular systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-framework-for-accurate-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular sciences address a wide range of problems involving molecules of different types and sizes and their complexes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-framework-for-accurate-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric modeling of the composite effect of multiple nutrients on blood glucose dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-modeling-of-the-composite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By differentiating treatment components, incorporating their dosages, and sharing statistical information across patients via a hierarchical multi-output Gaussian process, our method improves prediction accuracy over existing approaches, and allows us to interpret the different effects of carbohydrates and fat on the overall glucose response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-modeling-of-the-composite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APGL4SR: A Generic Framework with Adaptive and Personalized Global Collaborative Information in Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apgl4sr-a-generic-framework-with-adaptive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a graph-driven framework, named Adaptive and Personalized Graph Learning for Sequential Recommendation (APGL4SR), that incorporates adaptive and personalized global collaborative information into sequential recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apgl4sr-a-generic-framework-with-adaptive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persistent homology for high-dimensional data based on spectral methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistent-homology-for-high-dimensional-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a remedy, we find that spectral distances on the $k$-nearest-neighbor graph of the data, such as diffusion distance and effective resistance, allow persistent homology to detect the correct topology even in the presence of high-dimensional noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistent-homology-for-high-dimensional-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play Stability for Intracortical Brain-Computer Interfaces: A One-Year Demonstration of Seamless Brain-to-Text Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-stability-for-intracortical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results provide the first evidence for long-term stabilization of a plug-and-play, high-performance communication iBCI, addressing a major barrier for the clinical translation of iBCIs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-stability-for-intracortical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVIR-3D: Open-Vocabulary 3D Instance Retrieval Without Training on 3D Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovir-3d-open-vocabulary-3d-instance-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents OVIR-3D, a straightforward yet effective method for open-vocabulary 3D object instance retrieval without using any 3D data for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovir-3d-open-vocabulary-3d-instance-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hopfield-Enhanced Deep Neural Networks for Artifact-Resilient Brain State Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hopfield-enhanced-deep-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a two-stage computational framework combining Hopfield Networks for artifact data preprocessing with Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) for classification of brain states in rat neural recordings under different levels of anesthesia.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hopfield-enhanced-deep-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BanLemma: A Word Formation Dependent Rule and Dictionary Based Bangla Lemmatizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banlemma-a-word-formation-dependent-rule-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lemmatization holds significance in both natural language processing (NLP) and linguistics, as it effectively decreases data density and aids in comprehending contextual meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banlemma-a-word-formation-dependent-rule-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cal-DETR: Calibrated Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cal-detr-calibrated-detection-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third, we develop a logit mixing approach that acts as a regularizer with detection-specific losses and is also complementary to the uncertainty-guided logit modulation technique to further improve the calibration performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cal-detr-calibrated-detection-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Image Semantic Communication Model for Artificial Intelligent Internet of Things</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-semantic-communication-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, at the transmitter side, a high-precision image semantic segmentation algorithm is proposed to extract the semantic information of the image to achieve significant compression of the image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-semantic-communication-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Stage Generative Model with CycleGAN and Joint Diffusion for MRI-based Brain Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-generative-model-with-cyclegan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current supervised learning methods require extensively annotated images and the state-of-the-art generative models used in unsupervised methods often have limitations in covering the whole data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-generative-model-with-cyclegan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1D-Convolutional transformer for Parkinson disease diagnosis from gait</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1d-convolutional-transformer-for-parkinson</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results show that our approach is effective for detecting the different stages of Parkinson's disease from gait data, with a final accuracy of 88%, outperforming other state-of-the-art AI methods on the Physionet gait dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1d-convolutional-transformer-for-parkinson</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Foundation Model for Music Informatics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-model-for-music-informatics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates foundation models tailored for music informatics, a domain currently challenged by the scarcity of labeled data and generalization issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-model-for-music-informatics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Self-Supervised Cross-View Training For Sentence Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-self-supervised-cross-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework called Self-supervised Cross-View Training (SCT) to narrow the performance gap between large and small PLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-self-supervised-cross-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A survey and classification of face alignment methods based on face models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-and-classification-of-face-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face alignment is the process of fitting the landmarks in a face model to the respective ground truth positions in an input image containing a face.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-and-classification-of-face-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QualEval: Qualitative Evaluation for Model Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qualeval-qualitative-evaluation-for-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the shortcomings of quantitative metrics by proposing QualEval, which augments quantitative scalar metrics with automated qualitative evaluation as a vehicle for model improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qualeval-qualitative-evaluation-for-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating treatment effects from single-arm trials via latent-variable modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-treatment-effects-from-single-arm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to previous methods, our results show improved performance both for direct treatment effect estimation as well as for effect estimation via patient matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-treatment-effects-from-single-arm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LitSumm: Large language models for literature summarisation of non-coding RNAs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litsumm-large-language-models-for-literature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Availability: Code used to produce these summaries can be found here: https://github. com/RNAcentral/litscan-summarization and the dataset of contexts and summaries can be found here: https://huggingface. co/datasets/RNAcentral/litsumm-v1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litsumm-large-language-models-for-literature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning for Clinical Structured Data: A Benchmark Comparison of Engineering and Statistical Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-clinical-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal was to bridge the gap by presenting the first comprehensive comparison of FL frameworks from both engineering and statistical domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-clinical-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convergence Analysis of Sequential Federated Learning on Heterogeneous Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-analysis-of-sequential-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are two categories of methods in Federated Learning (FL) for joint training across multiple clients: i) parallel FL (PFL), where clients train models in a parallel manner; and ii) sequential FL (SFL), where clients train models in a sequential manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-analysis-of-sequential-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling Downstream Gender Bias from Large Language Models: A Study on AI Educational Writing Assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-downstream-gender-bias-from-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate that there is no significant difference in gender bias between the resulting peer reviews of groups with and without LLM suggestions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-downstream-gender-bias-from-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validity problems in clinical machine learning by indirect data labeling using consensus definitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/validity-problems-in-clinical-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a validity problem of machine learning in the vital application area of disease diagnosis in medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/validity-problems-in-clinical-machine</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
