<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2023 21:06:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Low-code LLM: Visual Programming over LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-code-llm-visual-programming-over-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed Low-code LLM framework consists of a Planning LLM that designs a structured planning workflow for complex tasks, which can be correspondingly edited and confirmed by users through low-code visual programming operations, and an Executing LLM that generates responses following the user-confirmed workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-code-llm-visual-programming-over-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Generation of Audio from Video via Foley Analogies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-generation-of-audio-from-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a model for generating a soundtrack for a silent input video, given a user-supplied example that specifies what the video should "sound like".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-generation-of-audio-from-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VALOR: Vision-Audio-Language Omni-Perception Pretraining Model and Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valor-vision-audio-language-omni-perception</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from widely-studied vision-language pretraining models, VALOR jointly models relationships of vision, audio and language in an end-to-end manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valor-vision-audio-language-omni-perception</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering the Background-Induced bias in RGB based 6-DoF Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-background-induced-bias-in-rgb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze how the presence of the markers affects the pose estimation accuracy, and how this bias may be mitigated through data augmentation and other methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-background-induced-bias-in-rgb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Multitask Learning to Improve Open Domain Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-multitask-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive models used to generate responses in open-domain dialogue systems often struggle to take long-term context into account and to maintain consistency over a dialogue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-multitask-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to Hero: Examining the Power of Symbolic Tasks in Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-to-hero-examining-the-power-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results on various benchmarks validate that the integration of SQL execution leads to significant improvements in zero-shot scenarios, particularly in table reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-to-hero-examining-the-power-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tool Learning with Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tool-learning-with-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the lack of a systematic tool learning evaluation in prior works, we experiment with 17 representative tools and show the potential of current foundation models in skillfully utilizing tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tool-learning-with-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELT: Mutual Enhancement of Long-Tailed User and Item for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melt-mutual-enhancement-of-long-tailed-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The long-tailed problem is a long-standing challenge in Sequential Recommender Systems (SRS) in which the problem exists in terms of both users and items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melt-mutual-enhancement-of-long-tailed-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMANet: Margin-aware Distillation and Modality-aware Regularization for Incomplete Multimodal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmanet-margin-aware-distillation-and-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It consists of three components: the deployment network used for inference, the teacher network transferring comprehensive multimodal information to the deployment network, and the regularization network guiding the deployment network to balance weak modality combinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmanet-margin-aware-distillation-and-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normalizing Flow-based Neural Process for Few-Shot Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flow-based-neural-process-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a normalizing flow-based neural process for few-shot knowledge graph completion (NP-FKGC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flow-based-neural-process-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Open Instruction Generalist: A Preliminary Release</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinese-open-instruction-generalist-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction tuning is widely recognized as a key technique for building generalist language models, which comes to the attention of researchers and the public with the release of InstructGPT \cite{ouyang2022training} and ChatGPT [ https://chat. openai. com/ ].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinese-open-instruction-generalist-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Efficiency Considerations for Popular AI Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-efficiency-considerations-for-popular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in artificial intelligence need to become more resource-aware and sustainable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-efficiency-considerations-for-popular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructUIE: Multi-task Instruction Tuning for Unified Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructuie-multi-task-instruction-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have unlocked strong multi-task capabilities from reading instructive prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructuie-multi-task-instruction-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadarFormer: Lightweight and Accurate Real-Time Radar Object Detection Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radarformer-lightweight-and-accurate-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This improvement was associated with the increasing use of LiDAR sensors and point cloud data to facilitate the task of object detection and recognition in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radarformer-lightweight-and-accurate-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongForm: Optimizing Instruction Tuning for Long Text Generation with Corpus Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longform-optimizing-instruction-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models outperform 10x larger language models without instruction tuning on various tasks such as story/recipe generation and long-form question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longform-optimizing-instruction-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisCo-CLIP: A Distributed Contrastive Loss for Memory Efficient CLIP Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-clip-a-distributed-contrastive-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, we can reduce the GPU memory consumption of contrastive loss computation from $\bigO(B^2)$ to $\bigO(\frac{B^2}{N})$, where $B$ and $N$ are the batch size and the number of GPUs used for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-clip-a-distributed-contrastive-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prak: An automatic phonetic alignment tool for Czech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prak-an-automatic-phonetic-alignment-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Labeling speech down to the identity and time boundaries of phones is a labor-intensive part of phonetic research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prak-an-automatic-phonetic-alignment-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political corpus creation through automatic speech recognition on EU debates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/political-corpus-creation-through-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release the resulting corpus and our analysis pipeline for future research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/political-corpus-creation-through-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone Can Be Picasso? A Computational Framework into the Myth of Human versus AI Painting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everyone-can-be-picasso-a-computational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advances of AI technology, particularly in AI-Generated Content (AIGC), have enabled everyone to easily generate beautiful paintings with simple text description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everyone-can-be-picasso-a-computational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study between Full-Parameter and LoRA-based Fine-Tuning on Chinese Instruction Data for Instruction Following Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-between-full-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we undertook experimental comparisons between full-parameter fine-tuning and LoRA-based tuning methods, utilizing LLaMA as the base model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-between-full-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Mixtures for Time-Aware Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-mixtures-for-time-aware-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers emerged as powerful methods for sequential recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-mixtures-for-time-aware-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction-Oriented Bayesian Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-oriented-bayesian-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information-theoretic approaches to active learning have traditionally focused on maximising the information gathered about the model parameters, most commonly by optimising the BALD score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-oriented-bayesian-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Residual Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-residual-metric-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In collaborative filtering, distance metric learning has been applied to matrix factorization techniques with promising results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-residual-metric-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETRs Beat YOLOs on Real-time Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrs-beat-yolos-on-real-time-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first analyze the influence of NMS in modern real-time object detectors on inference speed, and establish an end-to-end speed benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrs-beat-yolos-on-real-time-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive and Explainable Region-guided Radiology Report Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-and-explainable-region-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous methods generate reports without the possibility of human intervention and with limited explainability, our method opens up novel clinical use cases through additional interactive capabilities and introduces a high degree of transparency and explainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-and-explainable-region-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refusion: Enabling Large-Size Realistic Image Restoration with Latent-Space Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refusion-enabling-large-size-realistic-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work aims to improve the applicability of diffusion models in realistic image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refusion-enabling-large-size-realistic-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delving into Shape-aware Zero-shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-shape-aware-zero-shot-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the impressive progress of large-scale vision-language pretraining, recent recognition models can classify arbitrary objects in a zero-shot and open-set manner, with a surprisingly high accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-shape-aware-zero-shot-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchMD: A Benchmark for Modality-Agnostic Learning on Medical Images and Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmd-a-benchmark-for-modality-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we evaluate performance on out-of-distribution data collected at different hospitals than the training data, representing naturally-occurring distribution shifts that frequently degrade the performance of medical AI models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmd-a-benchmark-for-modality-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STRAP: Structured Object Affordance Segmentation with Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strap-structured-object-affordance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By label affinity, we refer to affordance segmentation as a multi-label prediction problem: A plate can be both holdable and containable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strap-structured-object-affordance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSim-Nets: Deep Similarity Networks for Stereo Image Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepsim-nets-deep-similarity-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our features are learnt on large image tiles to be expressive and capture the scene's wider context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepsim-nets-deep-similarity-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-shot and Partially-Supervised Cell Image Segmentation Using Small Visual Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-and-partially-supervised-cell-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation of microscopic cell images using deep learning is an important technique, however, it requires a large number of images and ground truth labels for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-and-partially-supervised-cell-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to "Segment Anything" in Thermal Infrared Images through Knowledge Distillation with a Large Scale Dataset SATIR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-segment-anything-in-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discovered that this ability of SAM can be leveraged to pretrain models for specific fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-segment-anything-in-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Learning Made Easy with DecentralizePy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-learning-made-easy-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decentralized learning (DL) has gained prominence for its potential benefits in terms of scalability, privacy, and fault tolerance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-learning-made-easy-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoDA: Modeling Deformable 3D Objects from Casual Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moda-modeling-deformable-3d-objects-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, we propose neural dual quaternion blend skinning (NeuDBS) to achieve 3D point deformation, which can perform rigid transformation without skin-collapsing artifacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moda-modeling-deformable-3d-objects-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCANet: Self-Paced Semi-Curricular Attention Network for Non-Homogeneous Image Dehazing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanet-self-paced-semi-curricular-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The presence of non-homogeneous haze can cause scene blurring, color distortion, low contrast, and other degradations that obscure texture details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scanet-self-paced-semi-curricular-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond first-order methods for non-convex non-concave min-max optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-first-order-methods-for-non-convex-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a study of structured non-convex non-concave min-max problems which goes beyond standard first-order approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-first-order-methods-for-non-convex-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Effective Text Encoding for Chinese LLaMA and Alpaca</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-effective-text-encoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs), such as ChatGPT and GPT-4, have revolutionized natural language processing research and demonstrated potential in Artificial General Intelligence (AGI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-effective-text-encoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeC: a method to generate interpretable energy management systems using a metaheuristic algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treec-a-method-to-generate-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method learns the decision strategy of the EMS based on historical data contrary to RBC and MPC approaches that are typically considered as non adaptive solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treec-a-method-to-generate-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-World Weakly-Supervised Object Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-weakly-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle such data, we propose a novel paradigm of contrastive representation co-learning using both labeled and unlabeled data to generate a complete G-CAM (Generalized Class Activation Map) for object localization, without the requirement of bounding box annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-weakly-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursive Joint Attention for Audio-Visual Fusion in Regression based Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-joint-attention-for-audio-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In video-based emotion recognition (ER), it is important to effectively leverage the complementary relationship among audio (A) and visual (V) modalities, while retaining the intra-modal characteristics of individual modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-joint-attention-for-audio-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Weakly Supervised Temporal Action Localization by Bridging Train-Test Gap in Pseudo Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-weakly-supervised-temporal-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, the generated pseudo-labels can be fluctuating and inaccurate at the early stage of training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-weakly-supervised-temporal-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Performer: Text-Driven Human Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2performer-text-driven-human-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Text2Performer to generate vivid human videos with articulated motions from texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2performer-text-driven-human-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MasaCtrl: Tuning-Free Mutual Self-Attention Control for Consistent Image Synthesis and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masactrl-tuning-free-mutual-self-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success in large-scale text-to-image generation and text-conditioned image editing, existing methods still struggle to produce consistent generation and editing results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masactrl-tuning-free-mutual-self-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCPNet: An Efficient and Semantic-Enhanced Transformer Network for Point Cloud Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcpnet-an-efficient-and-semantic-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this letter, we propose a novel efficient Transformer-based network to predict the future LiDAR point clouds exploiting the past point cloud sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcpnet-an-efficient-and-semantic-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Evaluation of GNN Expressiveness with BREC Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-evaluation-of-gnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research on the theoretical expressiveness of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) has developed rapidly, and many methods have been proposed to enhance the expressiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-evaluation-of-gnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaitRef: Gait Recognition with Refined Sequential Skeletons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitref-gait-recognition-with-refined</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two common modalities used for representing the walking sequence of a person are silhouettes and joint skeletons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitref-gait-recognition-with-refined</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularized Complete Cycle Consistent GAN for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-complete-cycle-consistent-gan-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents an adversarial method for anomaly detection in real-world applications, leveraging the power of generative adversarial neural networks (GANs) through cycle consistency in reconstruction error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-complete-cycle-consistent-gan-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLRegTest: A Benchmark for the Machine Learning of Regular Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlregtest-a-benchmark-for-the-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating machine learning (ML) systems on their ability to learn known classifiers allows fine-grained examination of the patterns they can learn, which builds confidence when they are applied to the learning of unknown classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlregtest-a-benchmark-for-the-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M2GNN: Metapath and Multi-interest Aggregated Graph Neural Network for Tag-based Cross-domain Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m2gnn-metapath-and-multi-interest-aggregated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) From the CDR perspective, not all inter-domain interests are helpful to infer intra-domain interests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m2gnn-metapath-and-multi-interest-aggregated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Instruction Following Language Models for Chinese: Investigating the Impact of Training Data and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-instruction-following-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, significant public efforts have been directed towards developing low-cost models with capabilities akin to ChatGPT, thereby fostering the growth of open-source conversational models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-instruction-following-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
