<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 21:07:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Multiple Object Detection and Pose Estimation using 3D Model Infusion with Monocular Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-multiple-object-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the labeling method, we provide the KITTI-6DoF dataset with $\sim7. 5$K annotated frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-multiple-object-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Denoising Process for Perceptron Bias in Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-denoising-process-for-perceptron</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under this assumption, we design new detection methods and indicator scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-denoising-process-for-perceptron</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural network based generation of 1-dimensional stochastic fields with turbulent velocity statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-based-generation-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define and study a fully-convolutional neural network stochastic model, NN-Turb, which generates 1-dimensional fields with turbulent velocity statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-based-generation-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutually-Regularized Dual Collaborative Variational Auto-encoder for Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutually-regularized-dual-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, since latent item variables are not modeled in UAE, it is difficult to utilize the widely available item content information when ratings are sparse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutually-regularized-dual-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multitask Vision-Language Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-vision-language-prompt-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, (i) we demonstrate the effectiveness of learning a single transferable prompt from multiple source tasks to initialize the prompt for each target task; (ii) we show many target tasks can benefit each other from sharing prompt vectors and thus can be jointly learned via multitask prompt tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-vision-language-prompt-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Crisis-Related Tweet Classification with Entity-Masked Language Modeling and Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-crisis-related-tweet-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Social media has become an important information source for crisis management and provides quick access to ongoing developments and critical information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-crisis-related-tweet-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowLens: Seeing Beyond the FoV via Flow-guided Clip-Recurrent Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowlens-seeing-beyond-the-fov-via-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Limited by hardware cost and system size, camera's Field-of-View (FoV) is not always satisfactory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowlens-seeing-beyond-the-fov-via-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normalizing Flow with Variational Latent Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flow-with-variational-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting method is significantly more powerful than the standard normalization flow approach for generating data distributions with multiple modes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalizing-flow-with-variational-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyQMIX: Distributed Access Control for mMTC via Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyqmix-distributed-access-control-for-mmtc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, the trained agents are able to quickly adapt to dynamic traffic and provide low access delay.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyqmix-distributed-access-control-for-mmtc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-Based Scene Graph to Image Generation with Masked Contrastive Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-scene-graph-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating images from graph-structured inputs, such as scene graphs, is uniquely challenging due to the difficulty of aligning nodes and connections in graphs with objects and their relations in images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-scene-graph-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural networks trained with SGD learn distributions of increasing complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-trained-with-sgd-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability of deep neural networks to generalise well even when they interpolate their training data has been explained using various "simplicity biases".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-trained-with-sgd-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Masked Autoencoders for Self-Supervised Video Hashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-masked-autoencoders-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To capture video semantic information for better hashing learning, we adopt an encoder-decoder structure to reconstruct the video from its temporal-masked frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-masked-autoencoders-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointCLIP V2: Adapting CLIP for Powerful 3D Open-world Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointclip-v2-adapting-clip-for-powerful-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP) has shown promising open-world performance on 2D image tasks, while its transferred capacity on 3D point clouds, i. e., PointCLIP, is still far from satisfactory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointclip-v2-adapting-clip-for-powerful-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bursting the Burden Bubble? An Assessment of Sharma et al.'s Counterfactual-based Fairness Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bursting-the-burden-bubble-an-assessment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Metrics are needed to evaluate the fairness of a model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bursting-the-burden-bubble-an-assessment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mean Shift Mask Transformer for Unseen Object Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-shift-mask-transformer-for-unseen-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To illustrate the effectiveness of our method, we apply MSMFormer to Unseen Object Instance Segmentation, which yields a new state-of-the-art of 87. 3 Boundary F-meansure on the real-world Object Clutter Indoor Dataset (OCID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-shift-mask-transformer-for-unseen-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motor Imagery Decoding Using Ensemble Curriculum Learning and Collaborative Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motor-imagery-decoding-using-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first loss applies curriculum learning, forcing each feature extractor to specialize to a subset of the training subjects and promoting feature diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motor-imagery-decoding-using-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug and Play Active Learning for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-active-learning-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesise that this is because: (1) it is difficult to quantify uncertainty for object detection as it consists of both localisation and classification, where some classes are harder to localise, and others are harder to classify; (2) it is difficult to measure similarities for diversity-based AL when images contain different numbers of objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-active-learning-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering Fine Details for Neural Implicit Surface Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-fine-details-for-neural-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works on implicit neural representations have made significant strides.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-fine-details-for-neural-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-specific and Model-adaptive Supervision for Semi-supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-specific-and-model-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relying on the model's performance, iMAS employs a class-weighted symmetric intersection-over-union to evaluate quantitative hardness of each unlabeled instance and supervises the training on unlabeled data in a model-adaptive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-specific-and-model-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAILD: Towards Leveraging Relation Features for Inductive Link Prediction In Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raild-towards-leveraging-relation-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a novel Relation Aware Inductive Link preDiction (RAILD) is proposed for KG completion which learns representations for both unseen entities and unseen relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raild-towards-leveraging-relation-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges and Applications of Automated Extraction of Socio-political Events from Text (CASE 2022): Workshop and Shared Task Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-and-applications-of-automated-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a summary of the fifth edition of the CASE workshop that is held in the scope of EMNLP 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-and-applications-of-automated-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Segmentation for Fully Automated Macrofouling Analysis on Coatings after Field Exposure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-for-fully-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biofouling is a major challenge for sustainable shipping, filter membranes, heat exchangers, and medical devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-segmentation-for-fully-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceiver-VL: Efficient Vision-and-Language Modeling with Iterative Latent Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceiver-vl-efficient-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Perceiver-VL, a vision-and-language framework that efficiently handles high-dimensional multimodal inputs such as long videos and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceiver-vl-efficient-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatiotemporal Modeling of Multivariate Signals With Graph Neural Networks and Structured State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-modeling-of-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate signals are prevalent in various domains, such as healthcare, transportation systems, and space sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-modeling-of-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expectation-Maximization Contrastive Learning for Compact Video-and-Language Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expectation-maximization-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most video-and-language representation learning approaches employ contrastive learning, e. g., CLIP, to project the video and text features into a common latent space according to the semantic similarities of text-video pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expectation-maximization-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RobustLoc: Robust Camera Pose Regression in Challenging Driving Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustloc-robust-camera-pose-regression-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments demonstrate that RobustLoc surpasses current state-of-the-art camera pose regression models and achieves robust performance in various environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustloc-robust-camera-pose-regression-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniMSE: Towards Unified Multimodal Sentiment Analysis and Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimse-towards-unified-multimodal-sentiment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal sentiment analysis (MSA) and emotion recognition in conversation (ERC) are key research topics for computers to understand human behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimse-towards-unified-multimodal-sentiment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are All Combinations Equal? Combining Textual and Visual Features with Multiple Space Learning for Text-Based Video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-all-combinations-equal-combining-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we tackle the cross-modal video retrieval problem and, more specifically, we focus on text-to-video retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-all-combinations-equal-combining-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation, Classification, and Quality Assessment of UW-OCTA Images for the Diagnosis of Diabetic Retinopathy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-classification-and-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diabetic Retinopathy (DR) is a severe complication of diabetes that can cause blindness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-classification-and-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Efficacy of Pre-trained Checkpoints in Text-to-Music Generation Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-efficacy-of-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from large-scale datasets and pre-trained models, the field of generative models has recently gained significant momentum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-efficacy-of-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directed Acyclic Graph Factorization Machines for CTR Prediction via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-graph-factorization-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some recent knowledge distillation based methods transfer knowledge from complex teacher models to shallow student models for accelerating the online model inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-graph-factorization-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Generalization Improvement Guided by Random Weight Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-generalization-improvement-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fully uncover the great potential of deep neural networks (DNNs), various learning algorithms have been developed to improve the model's generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-generalization-improvement-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Knowledge Distillation for Robust Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-knowledge-distillation-for-robust-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Blind Knowledge Distillation - a novel teacher-student approach for learning with noisy labels by masking the ground truth related teacher output to filter out potentially corrupted knowledge and to estimate the tipping point from generalizing to overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-knowledge-distillation-for-robust-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Place Recognition under Occlusion and Changing Appearance via Disentangled Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/place-recognition-under-occlusion-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Place recognition is a critical and challenging task for mobile robots, aiming to retrieve an image captured at the same place as a query image from a database.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/place-recognition-under-occlusion-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel transfer learning schemes based on Siamese networks and synthetic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-transfer-learning-schemes-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We make the data sets available at https://pub. uni-bielefeld. de/record/2960030.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-transfer-learning-schemes-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last-Mile Embodied Visual Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/last-mile-embodied-visual-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Realistic long-horizon tasks like image-goal navigation involve exploratory and exploitative phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/last-mile-embodied-visual-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Contrastive Learning for Robust Reasoning in VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-contrastive-learning-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For each positive pair, we regard the images from different graphs as negative samples and deduct the version of multi-positive contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-contrastive-learning-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhaustive Symbolic Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exhaustive-symbolic-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues we introduce a new method for SR -- Exhaustive Symbolic Regression (ESR) -- which systematically and efficiently considers all possible equations and is therefore guaranteed to find not only the true optimum but also a complete function ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exhaustive-symbolic-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orientation recognition and correction of Cardiac MRI with deep neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-recognition-and-correction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, the problem of orientation correction in cardiac MRI images is investigated and a framework for orientation recognition via deep neural networks is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-recognition-and-correction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS-Transformer: Learning Sparse Photometric Stereo Network using Self-Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-transformer-learning-sparse-photometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While they are effective with the dense capture, simple first-order operations often fail to capture the high-order interactions among observations under small number of different lights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-transformer-learning-sparse-photometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Parametric Classification Baseline for Generalized Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-parametric-classification-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works in GCD argue that a non-parametric classifier formed using semi-supervised $k$-means can outperform strong baselines which use parametric classifiers as it can alleviate the over-fitting to seen categories in the labelled set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-parametric-classification-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Improving Visual Prompting: A Label-Mapping Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-visual-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As highlighted below, we show that when reprogramming an ImageNet-pretrained ResNet-18 to 13 target tasks, our method outperforms baselines by a substantial margin, e. g., 7. 9% and 6. 7% accuracy improvements in transfer learning to the target Flowers102 and CIFAR100 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-visual-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Lagrangian Neural Networks with Automatic Symmetry Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-lagrangian-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By one of the most fundamental principles in physics, a dynamical system will exhibit those motions which extremise an action functional.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-lagrangian-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogenous Ensemble of Models for Molecular Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogenous-ensemble-of-models-for-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous works have demonstrated the importance of considering different modalities on molecules, each of which provide a varied granularity of information for downstream property prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogenous-ensemble-of-models-for-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Single-Pass Contrastive Learning Work for Both Homophilic and Heterophilic Graph?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-single-pass-contrastive-learning-work-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer this, we analyze the concentration property of features obtained by neighborhood aggregation on both homophilic and heterophilic graphs, introduce the single-pass graph contrastive learning loss based on the property, and provide performance guarantees of the minimizer of the loss on downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-single-pass-contrastive-learning-work-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VER: Learning Natural Language Representations for Verbalizing Entities and Relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ver-learning-natural-language-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entities and relationships between entities are vital in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ver-learning-natural-language-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Adversarial Training for Robust Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-adversarial-training-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we seek to address these challenges and propose Spectral Adversarial Training (SAT), a simple yet effective adversarial training approach for GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-adversarial-training-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniMASK: Unified Inference in Sequential Decision Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimask-unified-inference-in-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Randomly masking and predicting word tokens has been a successful approach in pre-training language models for a variety of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimask-unified-inference-in-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Embedding Predictive Architectures Focus on Slow Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-embedding-predictive-architectures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many common methods for learning a world model for pixel-based environments use generative architectures trained with pixel-level reconstruction objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-embedding-predictive-architectures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Fine-grained Information via Knowledge-aware Hierarchical Graph for Zero-shot Entity Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-fine-grained-information-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extract the knowledge units from the corresponding context and then construct a mention/entity centralized graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-fine-grained-information-via</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
