<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 21:06:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SUG: Single-dataset Unified Generalization for 3D Point Cloud Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sug-single-dataset-unified-generalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, different from previous 2D DG works, we focus on the 3D DG problem and propose a Single-dataset Unified Generalization (SUG) framework that only leverages a single source dataset to alleviate the unforeseen domain differences faced by a well-trained source model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sug-single-dataset-unified-generalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Built-in Autoregressive Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-built-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this limitation, recent autoregressive search engines replace the dual-encoder architecture by directly generating identifiers for relevant documents in the candidate pool.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-built-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xPQA: Cross-Lingual Product Question Answering across 12 Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpqa-cross-lingual-product-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study this practical industrial task, we present xPQA, a large-scale annotated cross-lingual PQA dataset in 12 languages across 9 branches, and report results in (1) candidate ranking, to select the best English candidate containing the information to answer a non-English question; and (2) answer generation, to generate a natural-sounding non-English answer based on the selected English candidate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpqa-cross-lingual-product-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMario: Experimental Approach to Reptile Algorithm -- Reinforcement Learning for Mario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramario-experimental-approach-to-reptile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research paper presents an experimental approach to using the Reptile algorithm for reinforcement learning to train a neural network to play Super Mario Bros. We implement the Reptile algorithm using the Super Mario Bros Gym library and TensorFlow in Python, creating a neural network model with a single convolutional layer, a flatten layer, and a dense layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ramario-experimental-approach-to-reptile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ContrastNet: A Contrastive Learning Framework for Few-Shot Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastnet-a-contrastive-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot text classification has recently been promoted by the meta-learning paradigm which aims to identify target classes with knowledge transferred from source classes with sets of small tasks named episodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastnet-a-contrastive-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Misclassification and Out-of-Distribution Detection for Semantic Segmentation via Energy-Based Normalizing Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-misclassification-and-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FlowEneDet achieves promising results on Cityscapes, Cityscapes-C, FishyScapes and SegmentMeIfYouCan benchmarks in IDM/OOD detection when applied to pretrained DeepLabV3+ and SegFormer semantic segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-misclassification-and-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishing Shared Query Understanding in an Open Multi-Agent System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-shared-query-understanding-in-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we demonstrate a use-case where our method can be applied for the task of cooperative query answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-shared-query-understanding-in-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satisfiability-Aided Language Models Using Declarative Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satisfiability-aided-language-models-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new satisfiability-aided language modeling approach for improving the reasoning capabilities of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satisfiability-aided-language-models-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid and Collaborative Passage Reranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-and-collaborative-passage-reranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In passage retrieval system, the initial passage retrieval results may be unsatisfactory, which can be refined by a reranking scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-and-collaborative-passage-reranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniSafe: An Infrastructure for Accelerating Safe Reinforcement Learning Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnisafe-an-infrastructure-for-accelerating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI systems empowered by reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms harbor the immense potential to catalyze societal advancement, yet their deployment is often impeded by significant safety concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnisafe-an-infrastructure-for-accelerating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Diffusion Probabilistic Models for Symbolic Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-diffusion-probabilistic-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models (DDPMs) have made great strides in generating high-quality samples in both discrete and continuous domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-diffusion-probabilistic-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wavelet-based Unsupervised Label-to-Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-based-unsupervised-label-to-image-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic Image Synthesis (SIS) is a subclass of image-to-image translation where a semantic layout is used to generate a photorealistic image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-based-unsupervised-label-to-image-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Generative Framework for Cross-domain Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-generative-framework-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain aspect-based sentiment analysis (ABSA) aims to perform various fine-grained sentiment analysis tasks on a target domain by transferring knowledge from a source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-generative-framework-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Level Global Context Cross Consistency Model for Semi-Supervised Ultrasound Image Segmentation with Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-global-context-cross-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach enables the effective transfer of probability distribution knowledge to the segmentation network, resulting in improved segmentation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-global-context-cross-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Optimal Strategies for Wordle and General Guessing Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-optimal-strategies-for-wordle-and-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent popularity of Wordle has revived interest in guessing games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-optimal-strategies-for-wordle-and-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise robust neural network architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-robust-neural-network-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In which we propose neural network architecture (dune neural network) for recognizing general noisy image without adding any artificial noise in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-robust-neural-network-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on Google Research Football Multi-agent Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-google-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) research on Google Research Football (GRF) focus on the 11v11 multi-agent full-game scenario and to the best of our knowledge, no open benchmark on this scenario has been released to the public.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-google-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPI-rical: Data-Driven MPI Distributed Parallelism Assistance with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-rical-data-driven-mpi-distributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic source-to-source parallelization of serial code for shared and distributed memory systems is a challenging task in high-performance computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-rical-data-driven-mpi-distributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Alignment Pre-training for Cross-lingual Sentence Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-alignment-pre-training-for-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have shown that dual encoder models trained with the sentence-level translation ranking task are effective methods for cross-lingual sentence embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-alignment-pre-training-for-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Self-Knowledge Distillation with Multi-source Information Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-self-knowledge-distillation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a Distillation with Reverse Guidance (DRG) method that considers different levels of information extracted by the model, including edge, shape, and detail of the input data, to construct a more informative teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-self-knowledge-distillation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Continual Learning Without the Storage Constraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-without-the-storage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online continual learning (OCL) research has primarily focused on mitigating catastrophic forgetting with fixed and limited storage allocation throughout the agent's lifetime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-without-the-storage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Image Quality Assessment via Transformer Predicted Error Map and Perceptual Quality Token</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we firstly generate the predicted error map by pre-training one model consisting of a Transformer encoder and decoder, in which the objective difference between the distorted and the reference images is used as supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-image-quality-assessment-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content-Adaptive Downsampling in Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-adaptive-downsampling-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many convolutional neural networks (CNNs) rely on progressive downsampling of their feature maps to increase the network's receptive field and decrease computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-adaptive-downsampling-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view MERA Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-mera-subspace-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from multiple interactions among orthogonal/semi-orthogonal (low-rank) factors, the low-rank MERA has a strong representation power to capture the complex inter/intra-view information in the self-representation tensor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-mera-subspace-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Global Interaction and Local Alignment for Audio-Visual Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-global-interaction-and-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most existing AVSR approaches simply fuse the audio and visual features by concatenation, without explicit interactions to capture the deep correlations between them, which results in sub-optimal multimodal representations for downstream speech recognition task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-global-interaction-and-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Implicit Bias Using SHAP Feature Importance and Fuzzy Cognitive Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-implicit-bias-using-shap-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we integrate the concepts of feature importance with implicit bias in the context of pattern classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-implicit-bias-using-shap-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Translation: Improving Domain Robustness of Neural Machine Translation with Intermediate Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-translation-improving-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we introduce a full-permutation multi-task learning to alleviate the spurious causal relations from intermediate sequences to the target, which results from exposure bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-translation-improving-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics of niche construction in adaptable populations evolving in diverse environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-of-niche-construction-in-adaptable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study NC in simulation environments that consist of multiple, diverse niches and populations that evolve their plasticity, evolvability and niche-constructing behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-of-niche-construction-in-adaptable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Weighted Möbius Score: A Unified Framework for Feature Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-weighted-mobius-score-a-unified-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature attribution aims to explain the reasoning behind a black-box model's prediction by identifying the impact of each feature on the prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-weighted-mobius-score-a-unified-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIFT: Graph-Induced Fine-Tuning for Multi-Party Conversation Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gift-graph-induced-fine-tuning-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing the issues of who saying what to whom in multi-party conversations (MPCs) has recently attracted a lot of research attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gift-graph-induced-fine-tuning-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Training to Learn in Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-to-learn-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-context learning, where pre-trained language models learn to perform tasks from task examples and instructions in their contexts, has attracted much attention in the NLP community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-to-learn-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Reinforcement Learning for Network Control via Bi-Level Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-reinforcement-learning-for-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization problems over dynamic networks have been extensively studied and widely used in the past decades to formulate numerous real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-reinforcement-learning-for-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Instructions to Student's Learning Levels Boosts Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-instructions-to-student-s-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been commonly observed that a teacher model with superior performance does not necessarily result in a stronger student, highlighting a discrepancy between current teacher training practices and effective knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-instructions-to-student-s-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperDialseg: A Large-scale Dataset for Supervised Dialogue Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superdialseg-a-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a feasible definition of dialogue segmentation points with the help of document-grounded dialogues and release a large-scale supervised dataset called SuperDialseg, containing 9K dialogues based on two prevalent document-grounded dialogue corpora, and also inherit their useful dialogue-related annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superdialseg-a-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Sentence Representation Learning with Frequency-induced Adversarial Tuning and Incomplete Sentence Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-sentence-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the problems, we fine-tune PLMs by leveraging the frequency information of words and propose a novel USRL framework, namely Sentence Representation Learning with Frequency-induced Adversarial tuning and Incomplete sentence filtering (SLT-FAI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-sentence-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ensemble Approach for Automated Theorem Proving Based on Efficient Name Invariant Graph Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-automated-theorem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NIAGRA addresses this problem by using 1) improved Graph Neural Networks for learning name-invariant formula representations that is tailored for their unique characteristics and 2) an efficient ensemble approach for automated theorem proving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-approach-for-automated-theorem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MV-Map: Offboard HD-Map Generation with Multi-view Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-map-offboard-hd-map-generation-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance multi-view consistency, we augment the uncertainty network with the global 3D structure optimized by a voxelized neural radiance field (Voxel-NeRF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mv-map-offboard-hd-map-generation-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CQE: A Comprehensive Quantity Extractor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to other information extraction approaches, interestingly only a few works exist that describe methods for a proper extraction and representation of quantities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cqe-a-comprehensive-quantity-extractor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Consistency in Text-based Financial Forecasting Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using FinTrust, we show that the consistency of state-of-the-art NLP models for financial forecasting is poor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-consistency-in-text-based-financial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL4F: Generating Natural Language Feedback with Reinforcement Learning for Repairing Model Outputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4f-generating-natural-language-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their unprecedented success, even the largest language models make mistakes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4f-generating-natural-language-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mode Approximation Makes Good Vision-Language Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advance of large-scale model technologies, parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL) has swept across various fields of Artificial Intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mode-approximation-makes-good-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Semantic Variation Prediction using the Distribution of Sibling Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, some of the previously associated meanings of a target word can become obsolete over time (e. g. meaning of gay as happy), while novel usages of existing words are observed (e. g. meaning of cell as a mobile phone).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-semantic-variation-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal Extractive Summarization of U.S. Court Opinions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-extractive-summarization-of-u-s-court</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper tackles the task of legal extractive summarization using a dataset of 430K U. S. court opinions with key passages annotated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-extractive-summarization-of-u-s-court</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBRACE: Evaluation and Modifications for Boosting RACE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embrace-evaluation-and-modifications-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When training and evaluating machine reading comprehension models, it is very important to work with high-quality datasets that are also representative of real-world reading comprehension tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embrace-evaluation-and-modifications-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reproducible Extraction of Training Images from Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-extraction-of-training-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release code to verify our extraction attack, perform the attack, as well as all extracted prompts at \url{https://github. com/ryanwebster90/onestep-extraction}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-extraction-of-training-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse Rendering of Translucent Objects using Physical and Neural Renderers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-rendering-of-translucent-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the supervision of the proposed neural renderer, we also propose an augmented loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-rendering-of-translucent-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMEx: Intrinsic Rewards from Masked Input Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimex-intrinsic-rewards-from-masked-input</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show how this perspective naturally leads to a unified view on existing intrinsic reward approaches: they are special cases of conditional prediction, where the estimation of novelty can be seen as pseudo-likelihood estimation with different mask distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimex-intrinsic-rewards-from-masked-input</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five A$^{+}$ Network: You Only Need 9K Parameters for Underwater Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/five-a-network-you-only-need-9k-parameters</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the Five A$^{+}$ Network (FA$^{+}$Net), a highly efficient and lightweight real-time underwater image enhancement network with only $\sim$ 9k parameters and $\sim$ 0. 01s processing time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/five-a-network-you-only-need-9k-parameters</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Models for Plug-and-Play Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-plug-and-play</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although diffusion models have shown impressive performance for high-quality image synthesis, their potential to serve as a generative denoiser prior to the plug-and-play IR methods remains to be further explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-models-for-plug-and-play</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Better Contrastive View from Radiologist's Gaze</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-better-contrastive-view-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose a novel augmentation method, i. e., FocusContrast, to learn from radiologists' gaze in diagnosis and generate contrastive views for medical images with guidance from radiologists' visual attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-better-contrastive-view-from</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
