<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 09:13:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Overlapping Biclusterings and Boolean Matrix Factorizations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-overlapping-biclusterings-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of visualizing \emph{a given clustering} of overlapping clusters in bipartite graphs and the related problem of visualizing Boolean Matrix Factorizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-overlapping-biclusterings-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Spatiotemporal Token Attention Network for Skeleton-based General Interactive Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-spatiotemporal-token-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose an Interactive Spatiotemporal Token Attention Network (ISTA-Net), which simultaneously model spatial, temporal, and interactive relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-spatiotemporal-token-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Monotonic Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-monotonic-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The monotonic dependence of the outputs of a neural network on some of its inputs is a crucial inductive bias in many scenarios where domain knowledge dictates such behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-monotonic-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A testing-based approach to assess the clusterability of categorical data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-testing-based-approach-to-assess-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of clusterability evaluation is to check whether a clustering structure exists within the data set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-testing-based-approach-to-assess-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Different Is Stereotypical Bias Across Languages?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-different-is-stereotypical-bias-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have demonstrated how to assess the stereotypical bias in pre-trained English language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-different-is-stereotypical-bias-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Efficient Training Data via LLM-based Attribute Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-efficient-training-data-via-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel method, Chain-of-Thoughts Attribute Manipulation (CoTAM), to guide few-shot learning by carefully crafted data from Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-efficient-training-data-via-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Context-Aware Cutting Plane Selection Algorithm for Mixed-Integer Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-context-aware-cutting-plane-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current cut selection algorithm used in mixed-integer programming solvers has remained largely unchanged since its creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-context-aware-cutting-plane-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Region Selection for Active Learning in Whole Slide Image Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-region-selection-for-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the efficiency of this method highly depends on the choice of AL step size (i. e., the combination of region size and the number of selected regions per WSI), and a suboptimal AL step size can result in redundant annotation requests or inflated computation costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-region-selection-for-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeCOS: Self-Supervised Learning from Fractals and Unlabeled Images for Curvilinear Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freecos-self-supervised-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Curvilinear object segmentation is critical for many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freecos-self-supervised-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightFormer: An End-to-End Model for Intersection Right-of-Way Recognition Using Traffic Light Signals and an Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightformer-an-end-to-end-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For smart vehicles driving through signalised intersections, it is crucial to determine whether the vehicle has right of way given the state of the traffic lights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightformer-an-end-to-end-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarks and Custom Package for Electrical Load Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarks-and-custom-package-for-electrical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we conducted extensive experiments on load data at different levels, providing a reference for researchers to compare different load forecasting models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarks-and-custom-package-for-electrical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Dimensional Ability Diagnosis for Machine Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-ability-diagnosis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithms have become ubiquitous in a number of applications (e. g. image classification).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-ability-diagnosis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C3: Zero-shot Text-to-SQL with ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c3-zero-shot-text-to-sql-with-chatgpt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a ChatGPT-based zero-shot Text-to-SQL method, dubbed C3, which achieves 82. 3\% in terms of execution accuracy on the holdout test set of Spider and becomes the state-of-the-art zero-shot Text-to-SQL method on the Spider Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c3-zero-shot-text-to-sql-with-chatgpt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Empower Molecular Property Prediction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-empower-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular property prediction has gained significant attention due to its transformative potential in multiple scientific disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-empower-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Domain Adversarial Training for Robust Volumetric Medical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-adversarial-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent advances in deep learning have improved the performance of volumetric medical image segmentation models, these models cannot be deployed for real-world applications immediately due to their vulnerability to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-adversarial-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMSD2.0: Towards a Reliable Multi-modal Sarcasm Detection System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmsd2-0-towards-a-reliable-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal sarcasm detection has attracted much recent attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmsd2-0-towards-a-reliable-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Positional and Structural Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-positional-and-structural-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positional and structural encodings (PSE) enable better identifiability of nodes within a graph, as in general graphs lack a canonical node ordering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-positional-and-structural-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dynamic Points Removal Benchmark in Point Cloud Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-points-removal-benchmark-in-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of robotics, the point cloud has become an essential map representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-points-removal-benchmark-in-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioInceptionNeXt: TCL AI LAB Submission to EPIC-SOUND Audio-Based-Interaction-Recognition Challenge 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioinceptionnext-tcl-ai-lab-submission-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report presents the technical details of our submission to the 2023 Epic-Kitchen EPIC-SOUNDS Audio-Based Interaction Recognition Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioinceptionnext-tcl-ai-lab-submission-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAL-SWIN: A Vision Transformer On The Sphere</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heal-swin-a-vision-transformer-on-the-sphere</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-resolution wide-angle fisheye images are becoming more and more important for robotics applications such as autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heal-swin-a-vision-transformer-on-the-sphere</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drive Like a Human: Rethinking Autonomous Driving with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drive-like-a-human-rethinking-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the potential of using a large language model (LLM) to understand the driving environment in a human-like manner and analyze its ability to reason, interpret, and memorize when facing complex scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drive-like-a-human-rethinking-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achelous: A Fast Unified Water-surface Panoptic Perception Framework based on Fusion of Monocular Camera and 4D mmWave Radar</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achelous-a-fast-unified-water-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current perception models for different tasks usually exist in modular forms on Unmanned Surface Vehicles (USVs), which infer extremely slowly in parallel on edge devices, causing the asynchrony between perception results and USV position, and leading to error decisions of autonomous navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achelous-a-fast-unified-water-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variance-reduced accelerated methods for decentralized stochastic double-regularized nonconvex strongly-concave minimax problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduced-accelerated-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coupling this with variance-reduction (VR) techniques, our proposed method, entitled VRLM, by a single neighbor communication per iteration, is able to achieve an $\mathcal{O}(\kappa^3\varepsilon^{-3})$ sample complexity under the general stochastic setting, with either a big-batch or small-batch VR option, where $\kappa$ is the condition number of the problem and $\varepsilon$ is the desired solution accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduced-accelerated-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gloss Attention for Gloss-free Sign Language Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gloss-attention-for-gloss-free-sign-language-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that it can provide two aspects of information for the model, 1) it can help the model implicitly learn the location of semantic boundaries in continuous sign language videos, 2) it can help the model understand the sign language video globally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gloss-attention-for-gloss-free-sign-language-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linking vision and motion for self-supervised object-centric perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-vision-and-motion-for-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object-centric representations enable autonomous driving algorithms to reason about interactions between many independent agents and scene features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-vision-and-motion-for-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternVid: A Large-scale Video-Text Dataset for Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvid-a-large-scale-video-text-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we utilize a multi-scale approach to generate video-related descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvid-a-large-scale-video-text-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAN is superior to GraphRNN: node orderings, kernel- and graph embeddings-based metrics for graph generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gran-is-superior-to-graphrnn-node-orderings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use these metrics to compare GraphRNN and GRAN, two well-known generative models for graphs, and unveil the influence of node orderings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gran-is-superior-to-graphrnn-node-orderings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliGraphs: Datasets for Benchmarking Knowledge Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligraphs-datasets-for-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, Knowledge Graphs are not just sets of links but also have semantics underlying their structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligraphs-datasets-for-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regression-Oriented Knowledge Distillation for Lightweight Ship Orientation Angle Prediction with Optical Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regression-oriented-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Four tiny SOAP models are also created by replacing the convolutional blocks in Mobile-SOAP with four small-scale networks, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regression-oriented-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Supervised Deep Learning MRI Reconstruction to Multiple and Unseen Contrasts using Meta-Learning Hypernetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-supervised-deep-learning-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hypernetworks and the reconstruction network in the GBML setting provide discriminative mode-specific features and low-level image features, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-supervised-deep-learning-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Factored Action Spaces for Off-Policy Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-factored-action-spaces-for-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new family of "decomposed" importance sampling (IS) estimators based on factored action spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-factored-action-spaces-for-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptive Process Monitoring Under Resource Constraints: A Reinforcement Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prescriptive-process-monitoring-under-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper argues that, in the presence of resource constraints, a key dilemma in the field of prescriptive process monitoring is to trigger interventions based not only on predictions of their necessity, timeliness, or effect but also on the uncertainty of these predictions and the level of resource utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prescriptive-process-monitoring-under-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classical Out-of-Distribution Detection Methods Benchmark in Text Classification Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classical-out-of-distribution-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This highlights the need for future work to develop more effective OOD detection approaches for the NLP problems, and our work provides a well-defined foundation for further research in this area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classical-out-of-distribution-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mBLIP: Efficient Bootstrapping of Multilingual Vision-LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mblip-efficient-bootstrapping-of-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we \textit{re-align} an image encoder previously tuned to an English LLM to a new, multilingual LLM -- for this, we leverage multilingual data from a mix of vision-and-language tasks, which we obtain by machine-translating high-quality English data to 95 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mblip-efficient-bootstrapping-of-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-based end-to-end classification of variable-length volumetric data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-end-to-end-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that varying the slice-wise resolution of the input during training results in more informative volume representation as compared to training with fixed number of slices per volume.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-end-to-end-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animate-A-Story: Storytelling with Retrieval-Augmented Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animate-a-story-storytelling-with-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first module, we leverage an off-the-shelf video retrieval system and extract video depths as motion structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animate-a-story-storytelling-with-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Denoising and the Generative Accumulation of Photons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-denoising-and-the-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This new perspective allows us to make three contributions: We present a new strategy for self-supervised denoising, We present a new method for sampling from the posterior of possible solutions by iteratively sampling and adding small numbers of photons to the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-denoising-and-the-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dominant text generation models compose the output by sequentially selecting words from a fixed vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LimSim: A Long-term Interactive Multi-scenario Traffic Simulator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limsim-a-long-term-interactive-multi-scenario</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the growing popularity of digital twin and autonomous driving in transportation, the demand for simulation systems capable of generating high-fidelity and reliable scenarios is increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limsim-a-long-term-interactive-multi-scenario</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Functional Structured Data Generators Rooted in Out-of-Equilibrium Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-functional-structured-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address the challenge of using energy-based models to produce high-quality, label-specific data in complex structured datasets, such as population genetics, RNA or protein sequences data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-functional-structured-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-State-Space Learning: An Identification Approach for Stochastic Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-state-space-learning-an-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Available methods for identification of stochastic dynamical systems from input-output data generally impose restricting structural assumptions on either the noise structure in the data-generating system or the possible state probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-state-space-learning-an-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DecompEval: Evaluating Generated Texts as Unsupervised Decomposed Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decompeval-evaluating-generated-texts-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing evaluation metrics for natural language generation (NLG) tasks face the challenges on generalization ability and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decompeval-evaluating-generated-texts-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frameless Graph Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frameless-graph-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation (KD) has shown great potential for transferring knowledge from a complex teacher model to a simple student model in which the heavy learning task can be accomplished efficiently and without losing too much prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frameless-graph-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Vision-Language Foundation Models for Fine-Grained Downstream Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-vision-language-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language foundation models such as CLIP have shown impressive zero-shot performance on many tasks and datasets, especially thanks to their free-text inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-vision-language-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negated Complementary Commonsense using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negated-complementary-commonsense-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Larger language models, such as GPT-3, have shown to be excellent in many tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negated-complementary-commonsense-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-FocalNets: Spatio-Temporal Focal Modulation for Video Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-focalnets-spatio-temporal-focal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video transformer designs are based on self-attention that can model global context at a high computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-focalnets-spatio-temporal-focal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Beyond Local: Global Graph-Enhanced Personalized News Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-local-global-graph-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precisely recommending candidate news articles to users has always been a core challenge for personalized news recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-local-global-graph-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaterScenes: A Multi-Task 4D Radar-Camera Fusion Dataset and Benchmark for Autonomous Driving on Water Surfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterscenes-a-multi-task-4d-radar-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents WaterScenes, the first multi-task 4D radar-camera fusion dataset for autonomous driving on water surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterscenes-a-multi-task-4d-radar-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSV: An Alignment Validation Loss for Self-supervised Outlier Model Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsv-an-alignment-validation-loss-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DSV captures the alignment between an augmentation function and the anomaly-generating mechanism with surrogate losses, which approximate the discordance and separability of test data, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsv-an-alignment-validation-loss-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aeolus Ocean -- A simulation environment for the autonomous COLREG-compliant navigation of Unmanned Surface Vehicles using Deep Reinforcement Learning and Maritime Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeolus-ocean-a-simulation-environment-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[USV control systems must, safely and reliably, be able to adhere to the international regulations for preventing collisions at sea (COLREGs) in encounters with other vessels as they navigate to a given waypoint while being affected by realistic weather conditions, either during the day or at night.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeolus-ocean-a-simulation-environment-for-the</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
