<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 21:08:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Pose-Agnostic Change Localization with Zero Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-pose-agnostic-change-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous agents often require accurate methods for detecting and localizing changes in their environment, particularly when observations are captured from unconstrained and inconsistent viewpoints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-pose-agnostic-change-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florence-VL: Enhancing Vision-Language Models with Generative Vision Encoder and Depth-Breadth Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/florence-vl-enhancing-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Florence-VL, a new family of multimodal large language models (MLLMs) with enriched visual representations produced by Florence-2, a generative vision foundation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/florence-vl-enhancing-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training MLPs on Graphs without Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-mlps-on-graphs-without-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a comprehensive theoretical analysis, demonstrating the equivalence between SimMLP and GNNs based on mutual information and inductive bias, highlighting SimMLP's advanced structural learning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-mlps-on-graphs-without-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Branch Subpixel-Guided Network for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-branch-subpixel-guided-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) has been widely applied into hyperspectral image (HSI) classification owing to its promising feature learning and representation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-branch-subpixel-guided-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAM: Generalization in Deep RL with a Robust Adaptation Module</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gram-generalization-in-deep-rl-with-a-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reliable deployment of deep reinforcement learning in real-world settings requires the ability to generalize across a variety of conditions, including both in-distribution scenarios seen during training as well as novel out-of-distribution scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gram-generalization-in-deep-rl-with-a-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning in Mobile Networks: A Comprehensive Case Study on Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-in-mobile-networks-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing demand for efficient resource allocation in mobile networks has catalyzed the exploration of innovative solutions that could enhance the task of real-time cellular traffic prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-in-mobile-networks-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Hash for Recommendation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-hash-for-recommendation-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we present a comprehensive review of current HashRec algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-hash-for-recommendation-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixed-Mean Gaussian Processes for Post-hoc Bayesian Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-mean-gaussian-processes-for-post-hoc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there has been an increasing interest in performing post-hoc uncertainty estimation about the predictions of pre-trained deep neural networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixed-mean-gaussian-processes-for-post-hoc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Generative Multiphysics and Multi-component Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generative-multiphysics-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiphysics simulation, which models the interactions between multiple physical processes, and multi-component simulation of complex structures are critical in fields like nuclear and aerospace engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-generative-multiphysics-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supertoroid fitting of objects with holes for robotic grasping and scene generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supertoroid-fitting-of-objects-with-holes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The result is a supergeometric modeling that can be used for symmetric objects with and without holes with a simple distance function for the fitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supertoroid-fitting-of-objects-with-holes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransAdapter: Vision Transformer for Feature-Centric Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transadapter-vision-transformer-for-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (UDA) aims to utilize labeled data from a source domain to solve tasks in an unlabeled target domain, often hindered by significant domain gaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transadapter-vision-transformer-for-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Targeted Clean-Label Poisoning Attacks Generalize?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-targeted-clean-label-poisoning-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a common clean-label setting, they are achieved by slightly perturbing a subset of training samples given access to those specific targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-targeted-clean-label-poisoning-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the Limits of Segment Anything Model: Analyzing Challenges in Segmenting Tree-Like and Low-Contrast Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-limits-of-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM) has shown impressive performance in interactive and zero-shot segmentation across diverse domains, suggesting that they have learned a general concept of "objects" from their large-scale training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-limits-of-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaserGuider: A Laser Based Physical Backdoor Attack against Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laserguider-a-laser-based-physical-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the laser-based backdoor triggers, we present a physical backdoor attack, called LaserGuider, which possesses remote control ability and achieves high temporal stealthiness, flexibility, and mobility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laserguider-a-laser-based-physical-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Machine Translation with Unstructured Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-machine-translation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In machine translation (MT), previous work typically retrieves in-context examples from paired MT corpora, or domain-specific knowledge from knowledge graphs, to enhance models' MT ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-machine-translation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding Descriptions in Images informs Zero-Shot Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-descriptions-in-images-informs-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose GRAIN, a new pretraining strategy aimed at aligning representations at both fine and coarse levels simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-descriptions-in-images-informs-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User-item fairness tradeoffs in recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-item-fairness-tradeoffs-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically, we develop a model of recommendations with user and item fairness objectives and characterize the solutions of fairness-constrained optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-item-fairness-tradeoffs-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MegaCOIN: Enhancing Medium-Grained Color Perception for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megacoin-enhancing-medium-grained-color</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MegaCOIN consists of two parts: MegaCOIN-Instruct, which serves as a supervised fine-tuning (SFT) dataset for VLMs; and MegaCOIN-Bench, an annotated test set that can be used as a stand-alone QA dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megacoin-enhancing-medium-grained-color</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JANUS: A Difference-Oriented Analyzer For Financial Centralization Risks in Smart Contracts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-a-difference-oriented-analyzer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focusing on the impact of risks rather than behaviors, JANUS achieves improved accuracy compared to existing tools and can uncover centralization risks with unknown patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/janus-a-difference-oriented-analyzer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDG2Seq: Periodic Dynamic Graph to Sequence Model for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdg2seq-periodic-dynamic-graph-to-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these findings, this paper proposes a Periodic Dynamic Graph to Sequence Model (PDG2Seq) for traffic flow prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdg2seq-periodic-dynamic-graph-to-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M$^{3}$D: A Multimodal, Multilingual and Multitask Dataset for Grounded Document-level Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-d-a-multimodal-multilingual-and-multitask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, in order to promote the development of multimodal IE, we constructed a multimodal multilingual multitask dataset, named M$^{3}$D, which has the following features: (1) It contains paired document-level text and video to enrich multimodal information; (2) It supports two widely-used languages, namely English and Chinese; (3) It includes more multimodal IE tasks such as entity recognition, entity chain extraction, relation extraction and visual grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-d-a-multimodal-multilingual-and-multitask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact: Exploring Space-Time Perceptive Clues for Weakly Supervised Satellite Image Time Series Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-exploring-space-time-perceptive-clues</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, the segmentation network trained on Exact-generated masks achieves 95% of its fully supervised performance, showing the bright promise of weakly supervised paradigm in crop mapping scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-exploring-space-time-perceptive-clues</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Similarity and Dissimilarity Guided Symmetric Non-Negative Matrix Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-similarity-and-dissimilarity-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we construct the similarity matrix as a weighted $k$-NN graph with learnable weight that reflects the reliability of each $k$-th NN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-similarity-and-dissimilarity-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safeguarding Text-to-Image Generation via Inference-Time Prompt-Noise Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safeguarding-text-to-image-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method introduces a novel optimization framework that leverages both the continuous prompt embedding and the injected noise trajectory in the sampling process to generate safe images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safeguarding-text-to-image-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANGAEA: A Global and Inclusive Benchmark for Geospatial Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pangaea-a-global-and-inclusive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these challenges, we introduce PANGAEA, a standardized evaluation protocol that covers a diverse set of datasets, tasks, resolutions, sensor modalities, and temporalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pangaea-a-global-and-inclusive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDUAL: A Dual-Strategy with Adaptive Loss and Dynamic Aggregation for Mitigating Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddual-a-dual-strategy-with-adaptive-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our findings, we then introduce an innovative dual-strategy approach designed to effectively resolve these issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddual-a-dual-strategy-with-adaptive-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEFL: Balancing Energy Consumption in Federated Learning for Mobile Edge IoT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/befl-balancing-energy-consumption-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing research primarily focuses on reducing overall energy consumption, but this may inadvertently create energy consumption imbalances, leading to the premature dropout of energy-sensitive devices. To address these challenges, we propose BEFL, a joint optimization framework aimed at balancing three objectives: enhancing global model accuracy, minimizing total energy consumption, and reducing energy usage disparities among devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/befl-balancing-energy-consumption-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stereo Anywhere: Robust Zero-Shot Deep Stereo Matching Even Where Either Stereo or Mono Fail</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-anywhere-robust-zero-shot-deep-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Stereo Anywhere, a novel stereo-matching framework that combines geometric constraints with robust priors from monocular depth Vision Foundation Models (VFMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-anywhere-robust-zero-shot-deep-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samudra: An AI Global Ocean Emulator for Climate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samudra-an-ai-global-ocean-emulator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI emulators for forecasting have emerged as powerful tools that can outperform conventional numerical predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samudra-an-ai-global-ocean-emulator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A History of Philosophy in Colombia through Topic Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-history-of-philosophy-in-colombia-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analyzing the evolution of topics across the journal's history, we identify various trends and specific dynamics in philosophical discourse within the Colombian and Latin American context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-history-of-philosophy-in-colombia-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Gaussian Superposition for Efficient 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-gaussian-superposition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a probabilistic Gaussian superposition model which interprets each Gaussian as a probability distribution of its neighborhood being occupied and conforms to probabilistic multiplication to derive the overall geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-gaussian-superposition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashSloth: Lightning Multimodal Large Language Models via Embedded Visual Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashsloth-lightning-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite a big leap forward in capability, multimodal large language models (MLLMs) tend to behave like a sloth in practical use, i. e., slow response and large latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashsloth-lightning-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D SlingBAG: spatial-temporal coupled Gaussian ball for large-scale dynamic 3D photoacoustic iterative reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-slingbag-spatial-temporal-coupled-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, for existing IR algorithms, multi-frame 3D reconstruction leads to extremely high memory consumption and prolonged computation time, with limited consideration of the spatial-temporal continuity between data frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-slingbag-spatial-temporal-coupled-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Various Software Artifacts for Better LLM-based Bug Localization and Program Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-various-software-artifacts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that while issue content is particularly effective in assisting LLMs with fault localization and program repair, different types of software artifacts complement each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-various-software-artifacts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generalizable Autonomous Penetration Testing via Domain Randomization and Meta-Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalizable-autonomous-penetration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we are among the first to apply domain randomization in autonomous pentesting and propose a large language model-powered domain randomization method for synthetic environment generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalizable-autonomous-penetration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult Glioma Segmentation in Sub-Saharan Africa using Transfer Learning on Stratified Finetuning Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adult-glioma-segmentation-in-sub-saharan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gliomas, a kind of brain tumor characterized by high mortality, present substantial diagnostic challenges in low- and middle-income countries, particularly in Sub-Saharan Africa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adult-glioma-segmentation-in-sub-saharan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does your model understand genes? A benchmark of gene properties for biological and text models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-your-model-understand-genes-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that text-based models and protein language models generally outperform expression-based models in genomic properties and regulatory functions tasks, whereas expression-based models demonstrate superior performance in localization tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-your-model-understand-genes-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEIM: DETR with Improved Matching for Fast Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deim-detr-with-improved-matching-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce DEIM, an innovative and efficient training framework designed to accelerate convergence in real-time object detection with Transformer-based architectures (DETR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deim-detr-with-improved-matching-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZipAR: Accelerating Autoregressive Image Generation through Spatial Locality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipar-accelerating-autoregressive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ZipAR, a training-free, plug-and-play parallel decoding framework for accelerating auto-regressive (AR) visual generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipar-accelerating-autoregressive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Causal Inference for Point-referenced Spatial Data with Continuous Treatments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-causal-inference-for-point-referenced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal reasoning is often challenging with spatial data, particularly when handling high-dimensional inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-causal-inference-for-point-referenced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISR: Measuring Instrumental Self-Reasoning in Frontier Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misr-measuring-instrumental-self-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a suite of tasks to evaluate the instrumental self-reasoning ability of large language model (LLM) agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misr-measuring-instrumental-self-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LossVal: Efficient Data Valuation for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossval-efficient-data-valuation-for-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessing the importance of individual training samples is a key challenge in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossval-efficient-data-valuation-for-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divot: Diffusion Powers Video Tokenizer for Comprehension and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divot-diffusion-powers-video-tokenizer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We posit that if a video diffusion model can effectively de-noise video clips by taking the features of a video tokenizer as the condition, then the tokenizer has successfully captured robust spatial and temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divot-diffusion-powers-video-tokenizer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynFinTabs: A Dataset of Synthetic Financial Tables for Information and Table Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synfintabs-a-dataset-of-synthetic-financial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the effectiveness of our dataset in training models to extract information from table images, we create FinTabQA, a layout large language model trained on an extractive question-answering task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synfintabs-a-dataset-of-synthetic-financial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bench-CoE: a Framework for Collaboration of Experts from Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bench-coe-a-framework-for-collaboration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are key technologies driving intelligent systems to handle multiple tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bench-coe-a-framework-for-collaboration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monet: Mixture of Monosemantic Experts for Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monet-mixture-of-monosemantic-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the internal computations of large language models (LLMs) is crucial for aligning them with human values and preventing undesirable behaviors like toxic content generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monet-mixture-of-monosemantic-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-Sequential Alignment and Uniformity: Toward Enhanced Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sequential-alignment-and-uniformity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph-based and sequential methods are two popular recommendation paradigms, each excelling in its domain but lacking the ability to leverage signals from the other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sequential-alignment-and-uniformity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffSign: AI-Assisted Generation of Customizable Sign Language Videos With Enhanced Realism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsign-ai-assisted-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to make media content more accessible to the DHH community by generating sign language videos with synthetic signers that are realistic and expressive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsign-ai-assisted-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary-Guided Learning for Gene Expression Prediction in Spatial Transcriptomics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-guided-learning-for-gene-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the spot and in-context branches, boundary information, including edge and nuclei characteristics, is extracted using pretrained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-guided-learning-for-gene-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmbodiedOcc: Embodied 3D Occupancy Prediction for Vision-based Online Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodiedocc-embodied-3d-occupancy-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D occupancy prediction provides a comprehensive description of the surrounding scenes and has become an essential task for 3D perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodiedocc-embodied-3d-occupancy-prediction</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
