<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 21:08:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-temporal collaborative multiple-stream transformer network for liver lesion classification on multiple-sequence magnetic resonance imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-collaborative-multiple-stream</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate identification of focal liver lesions is essential for determining the appropriate therapeutic approach in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-collaborative-multiple-stream</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Valuation using Neural Networks for Efficient Instruction Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-using-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, recent works have proposed various metrics and algorithms to calculate the influence of data using language models, which do not scale well with large models and datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-valuation-using-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISSIR: Beam Codebooks with Self-Interference Reduction Guarantees for Integrated Sensing and Communication Beyond 5G</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cissir-beam-codebooks-with-self-interference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a beam codebook design to reduce self-interference (SI) in integrated sensing and communication (ISAC) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cissir-beam-codebooks-with-self-interference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Study of Machine Unlearning Techniques for Computer Vision and NLP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-of-machine-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine unlearning is an emerging field in machine learning that focuses on efficiently removing the influence of specific data from a trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-of-machine-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Anomaly Detection via Tensor Chidori Pseudoskeleton Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-anomaly-detection-via-tensor-chidori</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results underscore the potential of Tensor Chidori pseudoskeleton decomposition to enhance anomaly detection for large-scale, high-dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-anomaly-detection-via-tensor-chidori</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QMaxViT-Unet+: A Query-Based MaxViT-Unet with Edge Enhancement for Scribble-Supervised Segmentation of Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qmaxvit-unet-a-query-based-maxvit-unet-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this approach, we propose QMaxViT-Unet+, a novel framework for scribble-supervised medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qmaxvit-unet-a-query-based-maxvit-unet-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Performance of TAAF for image classification models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-performance-of-taaf-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the results of testing a custom activation function, The Analog Activation Function (TAAF), on both the MNIST and CIFAR-10 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-performance-of-taaf-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Judge-free LLM Open-ended Generation Benchmark Based on the Distributional Hypothesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-judge-free-llm-open-ended-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the open-ended text generation of large language models (LLMs) is challenging because of the lack of a clear ground truth and the high cost of human or LLM-based assessments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-judge-free-llm-open-ended-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQuARE: Sequential Question Answering Reasoning Engine for Enhanced Chain-of-Thought in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/square-sequential-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving field of Natural Language Processing, Large Language Models (LLMs) are tasked with increasingly complex reasoning challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/square-sequential-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CopySpec: Accelerating LLMs with Speculative Copy-and-Paste Without Compromising Quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copyspec-accelerating-llms-with-speculative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CopySpec, an innovative technique designed to tackle the inefficiencies LLMs face when generating responses that closely resemble previous outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copyspec-accelerating-llms-with-speculative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Deep Regression with Tightness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-deep-regression-with-tightness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For deep regression, preserving the ordinality of the targets with respect to the feature representation improves performance across various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-deep-regression-with-tightness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholly-WOOD: Wholly Leveraging Diversified-quality Labels for Weakly-supervised Oriented Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wholly-wood-wholly-leveraging-diversified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately estimating the orientation of visual objects with compact rotated bounding boxes (RBoxes) has become a prominent demand, which challenges existing object detection paradigms that only use horizontal bounding boxes (HBoxes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wholly-wood-wholly-leveraging-diversified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This looks like what? Challenges and Future Research Directions for Part-Prototype Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-looks-like-what-challenges-and-future</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing interest in eXplainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI) has prompted research into models with built-in interpretability, the most prominent of which are part-prototype models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-looks-like-what-challenges-and-future</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SigGate: Enhancing Recurrent Neural Networks with Signature-Based Gating Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siggate-enhancing-recurrent-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach that enhances recurrent neural networks (RNNs) by incorporating path signatures into their gating mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siggate-enhancing-recurrent-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel-Level Reasoning Segmentation via Multi-turn Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-level-reasoning-segmentation-via-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To establish a benchmark for this novel task, we build a Pixel-level ReasonIng Segmentation Dataset Based on Multi-Turn Conversations (PRIST), comprising 24k utterances from 8. 3k multi-turn conversational scenarios with segmentation targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-level-reasoning-segmentation-via-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTZ-Calib: Robust Pan-Tilt-Zoom Camera Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptz-calib-robust-pan-tilt-zoom-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present PTZ-Calib, a robust two-stage PTZ camera calibration method, that efficiently and accurately estimates camera parameters for arbitrary viewpoints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptz-calib-robust-pan-tilt-zoom-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Language In-Context Learning Driven Few-Shot Visual Inspection Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-in-context-learning-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose general visual inspection model using Vision-Language Model~(VLM) with few-shot images of non-defective or defective products, along with explanatory texts that serve as inspection criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-in-context-learning-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyGFM: Graph Foundation Model for Zero/Few-shot Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygfm-graph-foundation-model-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose AnomalyGFM, a GAD-oriented graph foundation model that supports zero-shot inference and few-shot prompt tuning for GAD in diverse graph datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygfm-graph-foundation-model-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Jensen Gap for Max-Min Group Fairness Optimization in Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-jensen-gap-for-max-min-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we first theoretically demonstrate that the MMF-constrained objective can be essentially reformulated as a group-weighted optimization objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-jensen-gap-for-max-min-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use of Air Quality Sensor Network Data for Real-time Pollution-Aware POI Suggestion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/use-of-air-quality-sensor-network-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This demo paper presents AirSense-R, a privacy-preserving mobile application that provides real-time, pollution-aware recommendations for points of interest (POIs) in urban environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/use-of-air-quality-sensor-network-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communicating Likelihoods with Normalising Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communicating-likelihoods-with-normalising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a machine-learning-based workflow to model an unbinned likelihood from its samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communicating-likelihoods-with-normalising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eidetic Learning: an Efficient and Provable Solution to Catastrophic Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eidetic-learning-an-efficient-and-provable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show with a variety of network architectures and sets of tasks that EideticNets are immune to forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eidetic-learning-an-efficient-and-provable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Classic GNNs for Graph-level Tasks: Simple Architectures Meet Excellence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-classic-gnns-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Message-passing Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are often criticized for their limited expressiveness, issues like over-smoothing and over-squashing, and challenges in capturing long-range dependencies, while Graph Transformers (GTs) are considered superior due to their global attention mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-classic-gnns-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stochastic Parrot on LLM's Shoulder: A Summative Assessment of Physical Concept Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stochastic-parrot-on-llm-s-shoulder-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a systematic way, we investigate a widely asked question: Do LLMs really understand what they say?, which relates to the more familiar term Stochastic Parrot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stochastic-parrot-on-llm-s-shoulder-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LP-LM: No Hallucinations in Question Answering with Logic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lp-lm-no-hallucinations-in-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are able to generate human-like responses to user queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lp-lm-no-hallucinations-in-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models for Molecules: A Survey of Methods and Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-molecules-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey aims to facilitate understanding and further flourishing development in this area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-molecules-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Coordinate with Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-coordinate-with-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a fundamental coordination problem called Learning to Yield and Request Control (YRC), where the objective is to learn a strategy that determines when to act autonomously and when to seek expert assistance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-coordinate-with-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiSA: Leveraging Link Recommender to Attack Graph Neural Networks via Subgraph Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lisa-leveraging-link-recommender-to-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have demonstrated remarkable proficiency in modeling data with graph structures, yet recent research reveals their susceptibility to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lisa-leveraging-link-recommender-to-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMS: Diffusion Generation of Molecules Conditioned on Mass Spectra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffms-diffusion-generation-of-molecules</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on established benchmarks show that DiffMS outperforms existing models on $\textit{de novo}$ molecule generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffms-diffusion-generation-of-molecules</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Package Bids in Combinatorial Electricity Auctions: Selection, Welfare Losses, and Alternatives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/package-bids-in-combinatorial-electricity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge in combinatorial auctions is designing bid formats that accurately capture agents' preferences while remaining computationally feasible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/package-bids-in-combinatorial-electricity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reevaluating Policy Gradient Methods for Imperfect-Information Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reevaluating-policy-gradient-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past decade, motivated by the putative failure of naive self-play deep reinforcement learning (DRL) in adversarial imperfect-information games, researchers have developed numerous DRL algorithms based on fictitious play (FP), double oracle (DO), and counterfactual regret minimization (CFR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reevaluating-policy-gradient-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Physics-Informed Deep Learning Model for MRI Brain Motion Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-deep-learning-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On MR-ART, PI-MoCoNet achieved PSNR gains of ~10 dB and SSIM improvements of up to 0. 20, with NMSE reductions of ~6%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-deep-learning-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DexTrack: Towards Generalizable Neural Tracking Control for Dexterous Manipulation from Human References</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dextrack-towards-generalizable-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the challenge of developing a generalizable neural tracking controller for dexterous manipulation from human references.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dextrack-towards-generalizable-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of Tabular Transformer Architectures for Operating System Fingerprinting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-tabular-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Operating System (OS) fingerprinting is essential for network management and cybersecurity, enabling accurate device identification based on network traffic analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-tabular-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Contextual-Aware Position Encoding for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-contextual-aware-position-encoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we propose a novel Contextual-Aware Position Encoding method for sequential recommendation, abbreviated as CAPE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-contextual-aware-position-encoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redistribute Ensemble Training for Mitigating Memorization in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistribute-ensemble-training-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel method for diffusion models from the perspective of visual modality, which is more generic and fundamental for mitigating memorization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistribute-ensemble-training-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Do Not Fully Utilize Transformer's Representation Capacity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-do-not-fully-utilize-transformer-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to RNNs, which compress previous tokens into a single hidden state, Transformers can attend to all previous tokens directly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-do-not-fully-utilize-transformer-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Importance of Embedding Norms in Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-embedding-norms-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While this seemingly implies that embedding norms cannot play any role in SSL, a few recent works have suggested that embedding norms have properties related to network convergence and confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-embedding-norms-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censor Dependent Variational Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-dependent-variational-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides a comprehensive analysis of variational inference in latent variable models for survival analysis, emphasizing the distinctive challenges associated with applying variational methods to survival data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-dependent-variational-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelfCite: Self-Supervised Alignment for Context Attribution in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfcite-self-supervised-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SelfCite, a novel self-supervised approach that aligns LLMs to generate high-quality, fine-grained, sentence-level citations for the statements in their generated responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfcite-self-supervised-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Vision Models for Time Series Analysis: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-vision-models-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series analysis has witnessed the inspiring development from traditional autoregressive models, deep learning models, to recent Transformers and Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-vision-models-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Potential of Encoder-free Architectures in 3D LMMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-encoder-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the first comprehensive investigation into the potential of encoder-free architectures to overcome the challenges of encoder-based 3D Large Multimodal Models (LMMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-encoder-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Images are Gaussians: High-Quality Large Image Representation with Levels of 2D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-images-are-gaussians-high-quality-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Implicit Neural Representations (INRs) have demonstrated significant success in image representation, they are often hindered by large training memory and slow decoding speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-images-are-gaussians-high-quality-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EventSTR: A Benchmark Dataset and Baselines for Event Stream based Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventstr-a-benchmark-dataset-and-baselines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mainstream Scene Text Recognition (STR) algorithms are developed based on RGB cameras which are sensitive to challenging factors such as low illumination, motion blur, and cluttered backgrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventstr-a-benchmark-dataset-and-baselines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Evaluation of Generative Models on Tabular Transportation Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work underscores the potential need to develop generative models specifically tailored to take advantage of the unique characteristics of emerging domains, such as transportation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-evaluation-of-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenSynth: A Token-based Neural Synthesizer for Instrument Cloning and Text-to-Instrument</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokensynth-a-token-based-neural-synthesizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in neural audio codecs have enabled the use of tokenized audio representations in various audio generation tasks, such as text-to-speech, text-to-audio, and text-to-music generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokensynth-a-token-based-neural-synthesizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDCrow: Automating Molecular Dynamics Workflows with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdcrow-automating-molecular-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce MDCrow, an agentic LLM assistant capable of automating MD workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdcrow-automating-molecular-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing the Utility of Higher-Order Information in Relational Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-utility-of-higher-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we systematically evaluate a selection of hypergraph-level and graph-level architectures, to determine their effectiveness in leveraging higher-order information in relational learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-utility-of-higher-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-based Ensemble Learning in CMR Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-based-ensemble-learning-in-cmr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing models typically segment either the entire 3D frame or 2D slices independently to derive clinical functional metrics from ventricular segmentation in cardiac cine sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-based-ensemble-learning-in-cmr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Switching Not Guaranteed</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-switching-not-guaranteed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hadfield-Menell et al. (2017) propose the Off-Switch Game, a model of Human-AI cooperation in which AI agents always defer to humans because they are uncertain about our preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-switching-not-guaranteed</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
