<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 21:09:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MMASD+: A Novel Dataset for Privacy-Preserving Behavior Analysis of Children with Autism Spectrum Disorder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmasd-a-novel-dataset-for-privacy-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework achieves an accuracy of 95. 03% for predicting action types and 96. 42% for predicting ASD presence, demonstrating over a 10% improvement compared to models trained on single data modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmasd-a-novel-dataset-for-privacy-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning effective pruning at initialization from iterative pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-effective-pruning-at-initialization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To validate the accuracy and generalization of our method, we performed PaI across various models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-effective-pruning-at-initialization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2SQL is Not Enough: Unifying AI and Databases with TAG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2sql-is-not-enough-unifying-ai-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such systems would allow users to leverage the powerful reasoning and knowledge capabilities of language models (LMs) alongside the scalable computational power of data management systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2sql-is-not-enough-unifying-ai-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Temporal Alignment for Event-guided Video Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-temporal-alignment-for-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we aim to solve the video deblurring task by leveraging an event camera with micro-second temporal resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-temporal-alignment-for-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone-assisted Road Gaussian Splatting with Cross-view Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drone-assisted-road-gaussian-splatting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust and realistic rendering for large-scale road scenes is essential in autonomous driving simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drone-assisted-road-gaussian-splatting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Graph Interaction Transformer with Dynamic Token Clustering for Camouflaged Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-graph-interaction-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a hierarchical graph interaction network termed HGINet for camouflaged object detection, which is capable of discovering imperceptible objects via effective graph interaction among the hierarchical tokenized features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-graph-interaction-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM &amp; SAM 2 in 3D Slicer: SegmentWithSAM Extension for Annotating Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-sam-2-in-3d-slicer-segmentwithsam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we adapt this model to the annotation of 3D medical images and offer our implementation in the form of an extension to the popular annotation software: 3D Slicer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-sam-2-in-3d-slicer-segmentwithsam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAW-Adapter: Adapting Pre-trained Visual Model to Camera RAW Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-adapter-adapting-pre-trained-visual-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[sRGB images are now the predominant choice for pre-training visual models in computer vision research, owing to their ease of acquisition and efficient storage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-adapter-adapting-pre-trained-visual-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mamba in the Llama: Distilling and Accelerating Hybrid Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mamba-in-the-llama-distilling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear RNN architectures, like Mamba, can be competitive with Transformer models in language modeling while having advantageous deployment characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mamba-in-the-llama-distilling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIFR3CT: Latent Diffusion for Probabilistic 3D CT Reconstruction from Few Planar X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difr3ct-latent-diffusion-for-probabilistic-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computed Tomography (CT) scans are the standard-of-care for the visualization and diagnosis of many clinical ailments, and are needed for the treatment planning of external beam radiotherapy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difr3ct-latent-diffusion-for-probabilistic-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRL-Based Federated Self-Supervised Learning for Task Offloading and Resource Allocation in ISAC-Enabled Vehicle Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drl-based-federated-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our improved algorithm offloads partial task to RSU and optimizes energy consumption by adjusting transmission power, CPU frequency, and task assignment ratios, balancing local and RSU-based training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drl-based-federated-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust Reward Machines from Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-reward-machines-from-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents PROB-IRM, an approach that learns robust reward machines (RMs) for reinforcement learning (RL) agents from noisy execution traces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-reward-machines-from-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Surgical Instrument Segmentation Without Human Intervention: A Graph Partitioning View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-surgical-instrument-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an unsupervised method by reframing the video frame segmentation as a graph partitioning problem and regarding image pixels as graph nodes, which is significantly different from the previous efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-surgical-instrument-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPU-Accelerated Counterfactual Regret Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpu-accelerated-counterfactual-regret</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual regret minimization (CFR) is a family of algorithms of no-regret learning dynamics capable of solving large-scale imperfect information games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpu-accelerated-counterfactual-regret</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAT: Pruning-Aware Tuning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pat-pruning-aware-tuning-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the model fine-tuning refines the general and chaotic knowledge in pre-trained models, we aim to incorporate structural pruning with the fine-tuning, and propose the Pruning-Aware Tuning (PAT) paradigm to eliminate model redundancy while preserving the model performance to the maximum extend.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pat-pruning-aware-tuning-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Force-Guided Bridge Matching for Full-Atom Time-Coarsened Dynamics of Peptides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/force-guided-bridge-matching-for-full-atom</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular Dynamics (MD) simulations are irreplaceable and ubiquitous in fields of materials science, chemistry, pharmacology just to name a few.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/force-guided-bridge-matching-for-full-atom</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTMamba++: Enhancing Multi-Task Dense Scene Understanding via Mamba-Based Decoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtmamba-enhancing-multi-task-dense-scene-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-task dense scene understanding, which trains a model for multiple dense prediction tasks, has a wide range of application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtmamba-enhancing-multi-task-dense-scene-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Nonlinear Deformation Design of 3D-Printable Shells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-nonlinear-deformation-design-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trained on thousands of physical experiments, our network aids in both forward and inverse design to generate shells exhibiting desired elastoplastic and hyperelastic deformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-nonlinear-deformation-design-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alfie: Democratising RGBA Image Generation With No $$$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alfie-democratising-rgba-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designs and artworks are ubiquitous across various creative fields, requiring graphic design skills and dedicated software to create compositions that include many graphical elements, such as logos, icons, symbols, and art scenes, which are integral to visual storytelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alfie-democratising-rgba-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-world Event-guided Low-light Video Enhancement and Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-event-guided-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In low-light conditions, capturing videos with frame-based cameras often requires long exposure times, resulting in motion blur and reduced visibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-event-guided-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Writing in the Margins: Better Inference Pattern for Long Context Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/writing-in-the-margins-better-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Writing in the Margins (WiM), a new inference pattern for Large Language Models designed to optimize the handling of long input sequences in retrieval-oriented tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/writing-in-the-margins-better-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing License Plate Super-Resolution: A Layout-Aware and Character-Driven Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-license-plate-super-resolution-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advancements in License Plate Recognition (LPR) through deep learning, most improvements rely on high-resolution images with clear characters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-license-plate-super-resolution-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Regrets: Investigating and Improving Regret Approximations for Curriculum Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-regrets-investigating-and-improving-regret</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we instead directly train on levels with high learnability and find that this simple and intuitive approach outperforms UED methods and DR in several binary-outcome environments, including on our domain and the standard UED domain of Minigrid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-regrets-investigating-and-improving-regret</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Sign Language Communication: Integrating Sentiment and Semantics for Facial Expression Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-sign-language-communication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial expressions (non-manual), in particular, are responsible for encoding the grammar of the sentence to be spoken, applying punctuation, pronouns, or emphasizing signs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-sign-language-communication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OctFusion: Octree-based Diffusion Models for 3D Shape Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octfusion-octree-based-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have emerged as a popular method for 3D generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octfusion-octree-based-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSTeller: Scaling Up Visual Language Modeling in Remote Sensing with Rich Linguistic Semantics from Openly Available Data and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsteller-scaling-up-visual-language-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abundant, well-annotated multimodal data in remote sensing are pivotal for aligning complex visual remote sensing (RS) scenes with human language, enabling the development of specialized vision language models across diverse RS interpretation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsteller-scaling-up-visual-language-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platypus: A Generalized Specialist Model for Reading Text in Various Forms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/platypus-a-generalized-specialist-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, generalist models (such as GPT-4V), trained on tremendous data in a unified way, have shown enormous potential in reading text in various scenarios, but with the drawbacks of limited accuracy and low efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/platypus-a-generalized-specialist-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-FAKE: Synthesizing Thermal Images for Facial Landmarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-fake-synthesizing-thermal-images-for-facial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the creation of the dataset, we propose a novel RGB2Thermal loss function, which enables the transfer of thermal style to RGB faces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-fake-synthesizing-thermal-images-for-facial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERX: A Fast Real-Time Anomaly Detection Algorithm for Hyperspectral Line-Scanning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erx-a-fast-real-time-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting unexpected objects (anomalies) in real-time has great potential for monitoring, managing, and protecting the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erx-a-fast-real-time-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Budget Simulation-Based Inference with Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-budget-simulation-based-inference-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that Bayesian neural networks produce informative and well-calibrated posterior estimates with only a few hundred simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-budget-simulation-based-inference-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LyCon: Lyrics Reconstruction from the Bag-of-Words Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lycon-lyrics-reconstruction-from-the-bag-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the unique challenge of conducting research in lyric studies, where direct use of lyrics is often restricted due to copyright concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lycon-lyrics-reconstruction-from-the-bag-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applying ViT in Generalized Few-shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-vit-in-generalized-few-shot-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the capability of ViT-based models under the generalized few-shot semantic segmentation (GFSS) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-vit-in-generalized-few-shot-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GR-MG: Leveraging Partially Annotated Data via Multi-Modal Goal Conditioned Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gr-mg-leveraging-partially-annotated-data-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose GR-MG, a novel method which supports conditioning on both a language instruction and a goal image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gr-mg-leveraging-partially-annotated-data-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentMove: Predicting Human Mobility Anywhere Using Large Language Model based Agentic Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentmove-predicting-human-mobility-anywhere</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In AgentMove, we first decompose the mobility prediction task into three sub-tasks and then design corresponding modules to complete these subtasks, including spatial-temporal memory for individual mobility pattern mining, world knowledge generator for modeling the effects of urban structure and collective knowledge extractor for capturing the shared patterns among population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentmove-predicting-human-mobility-anywhere</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical Proportion Label Perturbation for Learning from Label Proportions in Large Bags</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-proportion-label-perturbation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our method, smaller bags (mini-bags) are generated by sampling instances from large-sized bags (original bags), and these mini-bags are used in place of the original bags.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-proportion-label-perturbation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynaSurfGS: Dynamic Surface Reconstruction with Planar-based Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynasurfgs-dynamic-surface-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that DynaSurfGS surpasses state-of-the-art methods in both high-fidelity surface reconstruction and photorealistic rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynasurfgs-dynamic-surface-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURE4Rec: A Benchmark for Recommendation Unlearning with Deeper Influence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cure4rec-a-benchmark-for-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we consider the deeper influence of unlearning on recommendation fairness and robustness towards data with varying impact levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cure4rec-a-benchmark-for-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Insulator Defect Detection Model Based on Drone Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-insulator-defect-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Initially, the backbone network of IDD-YOLO employs GhostNet for feature extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-insulator-defect-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2EBench: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Instruction-based Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i2ebench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We will open-source I2EBench, including all instructions, input images, human annotations, edited images from all evaluated methods, and a simple script for evaluating the results from new IIE models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i2ebench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Speech Representations Still Struggle with African American Vernacular English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-speech-representations-still</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underperformance of ASR systems for speakers of African American Vernacular English (AAVE) and other marginalized language varieties is a well-documented phenomenon, and one that reinforces the stigmatization of these varieties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-speech-representations-still</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAST-LIVO2: Fast, Direct LiDAR-Inertial-Visual Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-livo2-fast-direct-lidar-inertial-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fusion of both visual and LiDAR measurements is based on a single unified voxel map where the LiDAR module constructs the geometric structure for registering new LiDAR scans and the visual module attaches image patches to the LiDAR points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-livo2-fast-direct-lidar-inertial-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score-based change point detection via tracking the best of infinitely many experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-change-point-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We suggest a novel algorithm for online change point detection based on sequential score function estimation and tracking the best expert approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-change-point-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topological filtering of a signal over a network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-filtering-of-a-signal-over-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work bridges topological data analysis and signal processing, presenting a new application of persistent homology as a topological data processing tool.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-filtering-of-a-signal-over-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step-by-Step Unmasking for Parameter-Efficient Fine-tuning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-by-step-unmasking-for-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce $\text{ID}^3$, a novel selective PEFT method that calculates parameter importance continually and dynamically unmasks parameters by balancing exploration and exploitation in parameter selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-by-step-unmasking-for-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-Mix: Optimizing Data Mixtures for Large Scale Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-mix-optimizing-data-mixtures-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasingly large imitation learning datasets are being collected with the goal of training foundation models for robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-mix-optimizing-data-mixtures-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Centralized Critics in Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-centralized-critics-in-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Centralized Training for Decentralized Execution where agents are trained offline in a centralized fashion and execute online in a decentralized manner, has become a popular approach in Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-centralized-critics-in-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Analysis: Violence Recognition from Videos using Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-violence-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Action recognition has become a hot topic in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-violence-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURLoRA: Stable LLM Continual Fine-Tuning and Catastrophic Forgetting Mitigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curlora-stable-llm-continual-fine-tuning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method addresses two critical challenges in LLM fine-tuning: mitigating catastrophic forgetting during continual learning and reducing the number of trainable parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curlora-stable-llm-continual-fine-tuning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Tree-Structured Composition of Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-tree-structured-composition-of-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing augmentation methods such as RandAugment randomly sample from a list of pre-selected transformations, while methods such as AutoAugment apply advanced search to optimize over an augmentation set of size $k^d$, which is the number of transformation sequences of length $d$, given a list of $k$ transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-tree-structured-composition-of-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Knowledge Transfer in Learning Using Privileged Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-transfer-in-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research on learning using privileged information (LUPI) aims to transfer the knowledge captured in PI onto a model that can perform inference without PI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-transfer-in-learning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
