<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 09:14:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>V2C-CBM: Building Concept Bottlenecks with Vision-to-Concept Tokenizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2c-cbm-building-concept-bottlenecks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs) offer inherent interpretability by initially translating images into human-comprehensible concepts, followed by a linear combination of these concepts for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2c-cbm-building-concept-bottlenecks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Learning with Evolving Tasks and Performance Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-learning-with-evolving-tasks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing techniques for learning tasks that are in a sequence are tailored to specific scenarios, lacking adaptability to others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-learning-with-evolving-tasks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Portable Solution for Simultaneous Human Movement and Mobile EEG Acquisition: Readiness Potentials for Basketball Free-throw Shooting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-portable-solution-for-simultaneous-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we investigated whether the RP differs between successful and unsuccessful free-throw attempts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-portable-solution-for-simultaneous-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Needles in Emb(a)dding Haystacks: Legal Document Retrieval via Bagging and SVR Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-needles-in-emb-a-dding-haystacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a retrieval approach leveraging Support Vector Regression (SVR) ensembles, bootstrap aggregation (bagging), and embedding spaces on the German Dataset for Legal Information Retrieval (GerDaLIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-needles-in-emb-a-dding-haystacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Adaptive Ising Machines for Constrained Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adaptive-ising-machines-for-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a probabilistic-bit (p-bit) IM emulated in software, we benchmark our algorithm with multidimensional knapsack problems (MKP) and quadratic knapsack problems (QKP), the latter being an Ising problem with linear constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-adaptive-ising-machines-for-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpecTf: Transformers Enable Data-Driven Imaging Spectroscopy Cloud Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectf-transformers-enable-data-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Spectroscopic Transformer (SpecTf) addresses these challenges with a spectroscopy-specific deep learning architecture that performs cloud detection using only spectral information (no spatial or temporal data are required).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectf-transformers-enable-data-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Plagiarism Detection in Marathi with a Weighted Ensemble of TF-IDF and BERT Embeddings for Low-Resource Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-plagiarism-detection-in-marathi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Plagiarism involves using another person's work or concepts without proper attribution, presenting them as original creations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-plagiarism-detection-in-marathi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search-o1: Agentic Search-Enhanced Large Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-o1-agentic-search-enhanced-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce \textbf{Search-o1}, a framework that enhances LRMs with an agentic retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) mechanism and a Reason-in-Documents module for refining retrieved documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-o1-agentic-search-enhanced-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWE-Fixer: Training Open-Source LLMs for Effective and Efficient GitHub Issue Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-fixer-training-open-source-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The retrieval module employs BM25 along with a lightweight LLM model to achieve coarse-to-fine file retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-fixer-training-open-source-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GAN is dead; long live the GAN! A Modern GAN Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gan-is-dead-long-live-the-gan-a-modern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a widely-spread claim that GANs are difficult to train, and GAN architectures in the literature are littered with empirical tricks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gan-is-dead-long-live-the-gan-a-modern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving the Catastrophic Forgetting Problem in Generalized Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-catastrophic-forgetting-problem-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LER optimizes the distribution of potential known class samples in unlabeled data, thus ensuring the preservation of knowledge related to known categories while learning novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-the-catastrophic-forgetting-problem-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FSC-loss: A Frequency-domain Structure Consistency Learning Approach for Signal Data Recovery and Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsc-loss-a-frequency-domain-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A core challenge for signal data recovery is to model the distribution of signal matrix (SM) data based on measured low-quality data in biomedical engineering of magnetic particle imaging (MPI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsc-loss-a-frequency-domain-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Entity Detection from GitHub Leveraging Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-entity-detection-from-github</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper follows this recent trend and investigates the potential of leveraging Large Language Models (LLMs) in such scenarios to automatically detect datasets and software within textual content from GitHub repositories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-entity-detection-from-github</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Gaussian Test-Time Adaptation of Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-gaussian-test-time-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that OGA outperforms state-of-the-art methods on most datasets and runs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-gaussian-test-time-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimelineKGQA: A Comprehensive Question-Answer Pair Generator for Temporal Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timelinekgqa-a-comprehensive-question-answer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Question answering over temporal knowledge graphs (TKGs) is crucial for understanding evolving facts and relationships, yet its development is hindered by limited datasets and difficulties in generating custom QA pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timelinekgqa-a-comprehensive-question-answer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoDFL: A Scalable and Automated Reputation-Aware Decentralized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodfl-a-scalable-and-automated-reputation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reputation-aware BFL poses even more challenges, as blockchain validators are tasked with processing federated learning transactions along with the transactions that evaluate FL tasks and aggregate reputations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autodfl-a-scalable-and-automated-reputation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCIts -- Deep Convolutional Interpreter for time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcits-deep-convolutional-interpreter-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an interpretable deep learning model for multivariate time series forecasting that prioritizes both predictive performance and interpretability - key requirements for understanding complex physical phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcits-deep-convolutional-interpreter-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On weight and variance uncertainty in neural networks for regression tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-weight-and-variance-uncertainty-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variance uncertainty enhances the generalization of the model {by} considering the posterior distribution over the variance parameter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-weight-and-variance-uncertainty-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolution of Spots and Stripes in Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-spots-and-stripes-in-cellular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of engineering cellular automata, we propose evolving cellular automata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-spots-and-stripes-in-cellular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiGUIAgent: A Multimodal Generalist GUI Agent with Native Reasoning and Reflection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiguiagent-a-multimodal-generalist-gui</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphical User Interface (GUI) Agents, powered by multimodal large language models (MLLMs), have shown great potential for task automation on computing devices such as computers and mobile phones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiguiagent-a-multimodal-generalist-gui</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducing HotFlip for Corpus Poisoning Attacks in Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducing-hotflip-for-corpus-poisoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HotFlip is a topical gradient-based word substitution method for attacking language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducing-hotflip-for-corpus-poisoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semantic Partitioning Method for Large-Scale Training of Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-partitioning-method-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, knowledge graph embeddings have achieved great success.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-partitioning-method-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Coding for Both Human Perception and Generalized Machine Analytics with CLIP Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-coding-for-both-human-perception-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The image compression model has long struggled with adaptability and generalization, as the decoded bitstream typically serves only human or machine needs and fails to preserve information for unseen visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-coding-for-both-human-perception-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeFusion: An Effective Decoupling Fusion Network for Multi-Modal Pregnancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defusion-an-effective-decoupling-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal embryo images and parental fertility table indicators are both valuable for pregnancy prediction in \textbf{in vitro fertilization embryo transfer} (IVF-ET).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defusion-an-effective-decoupling-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planing It by Ear: Convolutional Neural Networks for Acoustic Anomaly Detection in Industrial Wood Planers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planing-it-by-ear-convolutional-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our convolutional autoencoder with skip connections (Skip-CAE) and our Skip-CAE transformer outperform the DCASE autoencoder baseline, one-class SVM, isolation forest and a published convolutional autoencoder architecture, respectively obtaining an area under the ROC curve of 0. 846 and 0. 875 on a dataset of real-factory planer sounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planing-it-by-ear-convolutional-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Derivative Free Gaussian Mixture Variational Inference for Bayesian Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-derivative-free-gaussian-mixture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is concerned with the approximation of probability distributions known up to normalization constants, with a focus on Bayesian inference for large-scale inverse problems in scientific computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-derivative-free-gaussian-mixture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MB-TaylorFormer V2: Improved Multi-branch Linear Transformer Expanded by Taylor Formula for Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mb-taylorformer-v2-improved-multi-branch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This variant leverages the Taylor expansion to approximate the Softmax-attention and utilizes the concept of norm-preserving mapping to approximate the remainder of the first-order Taylor expansion, resulting in a linear computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mb-taylorformer-v2-improved-multi-branch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAD-UV: The 1st INTERSPEECH Mice Autism Detection via Ultrasound Vocalization Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mad-uv-the-1st-interspeech-mice-autism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The findings suggest promising directions for vocalization analysis and highlight the potential value of audible and ultrasound vocalizations in ASD detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mad-uv-the-1st-interspeech-mice-autism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grokking at the Edge of Numerical Stability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokking-at-the-edge-of-numerical-stability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To validate our hypotheses, we introduce two key contributions that address the challenges in grokking tasks: StableMax, a new activation function that prevents SC and enables grokking without regularization, and $\perp$Grad, a training algorithm that promotes quick generalization in grokking tasks by preventing NLM altogether.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokking-at-the-edge-of-numerical-stability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum-inspired Embeddings Projection and Similarity Metrics for Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-inspired-embeddings-projection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the last decade, representation learning, which embeds complex information extracted from large amounts of data into dense vector spaces, has emerged as a key technique in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-inspired-embeddings-projection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking High-speed Image Reconstruction Framework with Spike Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-high-speed-image-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spike cameras, as innovative neuromorphic devices, generate continuous spike streams to capture high-speed scenes with lower bandwidth and higher dynamic range than traditional RGB cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-high-speed-image-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Parameter Estimation with Incomplete Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-estimation-with-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging their computational speed and flexibility, neural networks are also being used to facilitate fast, likelihood-free statistical inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-estimation-with-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ContextMRI: Enhancing Compressed Sensing MRI through Metadata Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextmri-enhancing-compressed-sensing-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose ContextMRI, a text-conditioned diffusion model for MRI that integrates granular metadata into the reconstruction process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextmri-enhancing-compressed-sensing-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Statistical Theory of Contrastive Pre-training and Multimodal Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-theory-of-contrastive-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal generative AI systems, such as those combining vision and language, rely on contrastive pre-training to learn representations across different modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-theory-of-contrastive-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM4SR: A Survey on Large Language Models for Scientific Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4sr-a-survey-on-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) has transformed the landscape of scientific research, offering unprecedented support across various stages of the research cycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm4sr-a-survey-on-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient License Plate Recognition in Videos Using Visual Rhythm and Accumulative Line Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-license-plate-recognition-in-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video-based Automatic License Plate Recognition (ALPR) involves extracting vehicle license plate text information from video captures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-license-plate-recognition-in-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOLBENCH: Benchmarking LLMs on Linguistic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iolbench-benchmarking-llms-on-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable advancements and widespread applications of deep neural networks, their ability to perform reasoning tasks remains limited, particularly in domains requiring structured, abstract thought.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iolbench-benchmarking-llms-on-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Low-Cost Video Editing with Lightweight Adaptors and Temporal-Aware Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-low-cost-video-editing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in text-to-image (T2I) generation using diffusion models have enabled cost-effective video-editing applications by leveraging pre-trained models, eliminating the need for resource-intensive training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-low-cost-video-editing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Examination of Unrolled Networks for Linear Inverse Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-examination-of-unrolled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unrolled networks have become prevalent in various computer vision and imaging tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-examination-of-unrolled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look on Gender Stereotypes in Movie Recommender Systems and Their Implications with Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-on-gender-stereotypes-in-movie</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second phase, four inference algorithms were applied to detect gender stereotypes by combining the findings from the first phase with users' feedback data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-on-gender-stereotypes-in-movie</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Automated Mapping of Clouds on Titan With Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-automated-mapping-of-clouds-on-titan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite widespread adoption of deep learning models to address a variety of computer vision tasks, planetary science has yet to see extensive utilization of such tools to address its unique problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-automated-mapping-of-clouds-on-titan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Histologic Dataset of Normal and Atypical Mitotic Figures on Human Breast Cancer (AMi-Br)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-histologic-dataset-of-normal-and-atypical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessment of the density of mitotic figures (MFs) in histologic tumor sections is an important prognostic marker for many tumor types, including breast cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-histologic-dataset-of-normal-and-atypical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadGPT: Constructing 3D Image-Text Tumor Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radgpt-constructing-3d-image-text-tumor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With over 85 million CT scans performed annually in the United States, creating tumor-related reports is a challenging and time-consuming task for radiologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radgpt-constructing-3d-image-text-tumor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DispFormer: Pretrained Transformer for Flexible Dispersion Curve Inversion from Global Synthesis to Regional Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispformer-pretrained-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surface wave dispersion curve inversion is essential for estimating subsurface Shear-wave velocity ($v_s$), yet traditional methods often struggle to balance computational efficiency with inversion accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispformer-pretrained-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSAR: Restricted State Angle Resolver and Rotated SAR Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsar-restricted-state-angle-resolver-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach can effectively improve the performance of existing state-of-the-art weakly supervised methods and even surpasses fully supervised models on existing optical benchmarks (i. e., DOTA-v1. 0 dataset).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsar-restricted-state-angle-resolver-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Before Reasoning: Enhancing Chain-of-Thought with Iterative Summarization Pre-Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-before-reasoning-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-Thought (CoT) Prompting is a dominant paradigm in Large Language Models (LLMs) to enhance complex reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-before-reasoning-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Optimization for Domain Adaptive Open Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-optimization-for-domain-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Seg-TTO, a novel framework for zero-shot, open-vocabulary semantic segmentation (OVSS), designed to excel in specialized domain tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-optimization-for-domain-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSA: Neuro-symbolic ARC Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nsa-neuro-symbolic-arc-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus (ARC) evaluates general reasoning capabilities that are difficult for both machine learning models and combinatorial search methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nsa-neuro-symbolic-arc-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical artificial intelligence toolbox (MAIT): an explainable machine learning framework for binary classification, survival modelling, and regression analyses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-artificial-intelligence-toolbox-mait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While machine learning offers diverse techniques suitable for exploring various medical research questions, a cohesive synergistic framework can facilitate the integration and understanding of new approaches within unified model development and interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-artificial-intelligence-toolbox-mait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are They the Same? Exploring Visual Correspondence Shortcomings of Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-they-the-same-exploring-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in multimodal models have shown a strong ability in visual perception, reasoning abilities, and vision-language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-they-the-same-exploring-visual</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
