<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 21:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mathematical Introduction to Deep Learning: Methods, Implementations, and Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-introduction-to-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This book aims to provide an introduction to the topic of deep learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathematical-introduction-to-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-Helpful Multimodal Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-helpful-multimodal-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the extensive training set, EVA contains a video-helpful evaluation set in which subtitles are ambiguous, and videos are guaranteed helpful for disambiguation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-helpful-multimodal-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer-Based Model With Self-Distillation for Multimodal Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-model-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotion recognition in conversations (ERC), the task of recognizing the emotion of each utterance in a conversation, is crucial for building empathetic machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-model-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histopathological Image Analysis with Style-Augmented Feature Domain Mixing for Improved Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathological-image-analysis-with-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Style transfer-based data augmentation is an emerging technique that can be used to improve the generalizability of machine learning models for histopathological images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathological-image-analysis-with-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Act: Constraining Disparate Impact in Sparse Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-act-constraining-disparate-impact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model pruning is a popular approach to enable the deployment of large deep learning models on edge devices with restricted computational or storage capacities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-act-constraining-disparate-impact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Play Chess from Textbooks (LEAP): a Corpus for Evaluating Chess Moves based on Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-play-chess-from-textbooks-leap-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper examines chess textbooks as a new knowledge source for enabling machines to learn how to play chess -- a resource that has not been explored previously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-play-chess-from-textbooks-leap-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-like Flexible Visual Inference by Harnessing Feedback-Feedforward Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-like-flexible-visual-inference-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study presents FFA as a promising proof-of-concept for the mechanisms underlying how feedback connections in the visual cortex support flexible visual functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-like-flexible-visual-inference-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hybrid approach for solving the gravitational N-body problem with Artificial Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-approach-for-solving-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To increase the robustness of a method that uses neural networks, we propose a hybrid integrator that evaluates the prediction of the network and replaces it with the numerical solution if considered inaccurate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-approach-for-solving-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relative NN-Descent: A Fast Index Construction for Graph-Based Approximate Nearest Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-nn-descent-a-fast-index-construction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, in experiments on the GIST1M dataset, the construction of the proposed method is 2x faster than NSG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relative-nn-descent-a-fast-index-construction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Large Language Models Better Data Creators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-large-language-models-better-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments we demonstrate that instruction-following LLMs are highly cost-effective data creators, and that models trained with these data exhibit performance better than those trained with human-labeled data (by up to 17. 5%) on out-of-distribution evaluation, while maintaining comparable performance on in-distribution tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-large-language-models-better-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parametric Fairness with Statistical Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-fairness-with-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic fairness has gained prominence due to societal and regulatory concerns about biases in Machine Learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-fairness-with-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Transport: Toward Learning Causal Effects of Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-transport-toward-learning-causal-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we leverage the notion of distribution shift to describe an estimator that transports causal effects between domains, bypassing the need for strong assumptions in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-transport-toward-learning-causal-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amoeba: Circumventing ML-supported Network Censorship via Adversarial Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amoeba-circumventing-ml-supported-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we cast the problem of finding adversarial flows that will be misclassified as a sequence generation task, which we solve with Amoeba, a novel reinforcement learning algorithm that we design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amoeba-circumventing-ml-supported-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning From Mistakes Makes LLM Better Reasoner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-mistakes-makes-llm-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) recently exhibited remarkable reasoning capabilities on solving math problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-mistakes-makes-llm-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distil the informative essence of loop detector data set: Is network-level traffic forecasting hungry for more data?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distil-the-informative-essence-of-loop</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer this, we propose an uncertainty-aware traffic forecasting framework to explore how many samples of loop data are truly effective for training forecasting models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distil-the-informative-essence-of-loop</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate What You Prefer: Reshaping Sequential Recommendation via Guided Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-what-you-prefer-reshaping-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scrutinizing previous studies, we can summarize a common learning-to-classify paradigm -- given a positive item, a recommender model performs negative sampling to add negative items and learns to classify whether the user prefers them or not, based on his/her historical interaction sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-what-you-prefer-reshaping-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilitarian Algorithm Configuration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilitarian-algorithm-configuration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove upper bounds on the runtime of these procedures that are similar to theoretical lower bounds, while also demonstrating their performance empirically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilitarian-algorithm-configuration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linked Papers With Code: The Latest in Machine Learning as an RDF Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-papers-with-code-the-latest-in-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Linked Papers With Code (LPWC), an RDF knowledge graph that provides comprehensive, current information about almost 400, 000 machine learning publications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-papers-with-code-the-latest-in-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ling-CL: Understanding NLP Models through Linguistic Curricula</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ling-cl-understanding-nlp-models-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ a characterization of linguistic complexity from psycholinguistic and language acquisition research to develop data-driven curricula to understand the underlying linguistic knowledge that models learn to address NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ling-cl-understanding-nlp-models-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Field Discovery In Interacting Dynamical Systems With Neural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-field-discovery-in-interacting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Systems of interacting objects often evolve under the influence of field effects that govern their dynamics, yet previous works have abstracted away from such effects, and assume that systems evolve in a vacuum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-field-discovery-in-interacting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Impact of Companies on AI Research Based on Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-impact-of-companies-on-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) is one of the most momentous technologies of our time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-impact-of-companies-on-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEDNet: A Hierarchical Encoder-Decoder Network for 3D Object Detection in Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hednet-a-hierarchical-encoder-decoder-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce computational costs, these methods resort to submanifold sparse convolutions, which prevent the information exchange among spatially disconnected features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hednet-a-hierarchical-encoder-decoder-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HWD: A Novel Evaluation Score for Styled Handwritten Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwd-a-novel-evaluation-score-for-styled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experimental evaluation on different word-level and line-level datasets of handwritten text images, we demonstrate the suitability of the proposed HWD as a score for Styled HTG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwd-a-novel-evaluation-score-for-styled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GACE: Geometry Aware Confidence Enhancement for Black-Box 3D Object Detectors on LiDAR-Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gace-geometry-aware-confidence-enhancement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Widely-used LiDAR-based 3D object detectors often neglect fundamental geometric information readily available from the object proposals in their confidence estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gace-geometry-aware-confidence-enhancement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibration by Distribution Matching: Trainable Kernel Calibration Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-by-distribution-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Calibration ensures that probabilistic forecasts meaningfully capture uncertainty by requiring that predicted probabilities align with empirical frequencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-by-distribution-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsyCoT: Psychological Questionnaire as Powerful Chain-of-Thought for Personality Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psycot-psychological-questionnaire-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from Psychological Questionnaires, which are carefully designed by psychologists to evaluate individual personality traits through a series of targeted items, we argue that these items can be regarded as a collection of well-structured chain-of-thought (CoT) processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psycot-psychological-questionnaire-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Guided Visual Question Answering: Elevate Your Multimodal Language Model Using Knowledge-Enriched Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-visual-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual question answering (VQA) is the task of answering questions about an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-visual-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Compositionality in Sentiment: New Data and Analyses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-compositionality-in-sentiment-new-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When natural language phrases are combined, their meaning is often more than the sum of their parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-compositionality-in-sentiment-new-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information-Theoretic Trust Regions for Stochastic Gradient-Based Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-theoretic-trust-regions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Before each update, it solves the trust region problem for an optimal step size, resulting in a more stable and faster optimization process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-theoretic-trust-regions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilateral Network with Residual U-blocks and Dual-Guided Attention for Real-time Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-network-with-residual-u-blocks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be precise, we use the Dual-Guided Attention (DGA) module we proposed to replace some multi-scale transformations with the calculation of attention which means we only use several attention layers of near linear complexity to achieve performance comparable to frequently-used multi-layer fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-network-with-residual-u-blocks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General-Purpose Retrieval-Enhanced Medical Prediction Model Using Near-Infinite History</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-purpose-retrieval-enhanced-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach effectively eliminates the need for manual feature selection and enables an unrestricted observation window.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-purpose-retrieval-enhanced-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recaptured Raw Screen Image and Video Demoiréing via Channel and Spatial Modulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recaptured-raw-screen-image-and-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The spatial modulation utilizes the feature with large receptive field to modulate the feature with small receptive field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recaptured-raw-screen-image-and-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erato: Automatizing Poetry Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erato-automatizing-poetry-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Erato, a framework designed to facilitate the automated evaluation of poetry, including that generated by poetry generation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erato-automatizing-poetry-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting Entities of Interest from Comparative Product Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-entities-of-interest-from-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a deep learning based approach to extract product comparison information out of user reviews on various e-commerce websites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-entities-of-interest-from-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-Aware Adaptive Sampling for Self-Sustainability in Resource-Constrained IoT Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-aware-adaptive-sampling-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the ever-growing Internet of Things (IoT) landscape, smart power management algorithms combined with energy harvesting solutions are crucial to obtain self-sustainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-aware-adaptive-sampling-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning detects terminal singularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-detects-terminal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Together with the first sketch of the landscape of Q-Fanos in higher dimensions, this gives new evidence that machine learning can be an essential tool in developing mathematical conjectures and accelerating theoretical discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-detects-terminal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDAM-PS: Diligent Domain Adaptive Mixer for Person Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddam-ps-diligent-domain-adaptive-mixer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of the two bridge losses is to guide the moderate mixed-domain representations to maintain an appropriate distance from both the source and target domain representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddam-ps-diligent-domain-adaptive-mixer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Network Contention-Aware Cluster Scheduling with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-contention-aware-cluster-scheduling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With continuous advances in deep learning, distributed training is becoming common in GPU clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/network-contention-aware-cluster-scheduling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Denoising Training to Test-Time Adaptation: Enhancing Domain Generalization for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-denoising-training-to-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In medical image segmentation, domain generalization poses a significant challenge due to domain shifts caused by variations in data acquisition devices and other factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-denoising-training-to-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BasisFormer: Attention-based Time Series Forecasting with Learnable and Interpretable Basis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basisformer-attention-based-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bases have become an integral part of modern deep learning-based models for time series forecasting due to their ability to act as feature extractors or future references.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/basisformer-attention-based-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Difference Predictive Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-difference-predictive-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting and reasoning about the future lie at the heart of many time-series questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-difference-predictive-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructCoder: Empowering Language Models for Code Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructcoder-empowering-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the use of large language models (LLMs) to edit code based on user instructions, covering a broad range of implicit tasks such as comment insertion, code optimization, and code refactoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructcoder-empowering-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap Between Variational Inference and Wasserstein Gradient Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational inference is a technique that approximates a target distribution by optimizing within the parameter space of variational families.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Evaluation of Generative Models with Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-evaluation-of-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic evaluation of natural language generation has long been an elusive goal in NLP. A recent paradigm fine-tunes pre-trained language models to emulate human judgements for a particular task and evaluation criterion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-evaluation-of-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Examples to Annotate for In-Context Learning? Towards Effective and Efficient Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-examples-to-annotate-for-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) can adapt to new tasks via in-context learning (ICL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-examples-to-annotate-for-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIST: Medical Image Segmentation Transformer with Convolutional Attention Mixing (CAM) Decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mist-medical-image-segmentation-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the common and promising deep learning approaches used for medical image segmentation is transformers, as they can capture long-range dependencies among the pixels by utilizing self-attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mist-medical-image-segmentation-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Anchor Label Propagation for Transductive Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-anchor-label-propagation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our novel algorithm, Adaptive Anchor Label Propagation}, outperforms the standard label propagation algorithm by as much as 7% and 2% in the 1-shot and 5-shot settings respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-anchor-label-propagation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoCa: Measuring Human-Language Model Alignment on Causal and Moral Judgment Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moca-measuring-human-language-model-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A rich literature in cognitive science has studied people's causal and moral intuitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moca-measuring-human-language-model-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LitCab: Lightweight Calibration of Language Models on Outputs of Varied Lengths</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litcab-lightweight-calibration-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For evaluation, we construct CaT, a benchmark consisting of 7 text generation tasks, covering responses ranging from short phrases to paragraphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litcab-lightweight-calibration-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Attacks and Defenses in Large Language Models: Old and New Threats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-attacks-and-defenses-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, one major impediment has been the overestimation of the robustness of new defense approaches due to faulty defense evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-attacks-and-defenses-in-large</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
