<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 09:16:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Time Series is Worth Five Experts: Heterogeneous Mixture of Experts for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-five-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate traffic prediction faces significant challenges, necessitating a deep understanding of both temporal and spatial cues and their complex interactions across multiple variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-five-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-intensity knowledge distillation for robust medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-intensity-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to incorporate joint shape-intensity prior information into the segmentation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-intensity-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Quantum Creep In: Designing Quantum Neural Network Models by Gradually Swapping Out Classical Components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-quantum-creep-in-designing-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To provide a more fine-grained characterisation of the impact of quantum components on the performance of neural networks, we propose a framework where classical neural network layers are gradually replaced by quantum layers that have the same type of input and output while keeping the flow of information between layers unchanged, different from most current research in quantum neural network, which favours an end-to-end quantum model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-quantum-creep-in-designing-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving logical and functional dependencies in synthetic tabular data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-logical-and-functional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the existing notion of functional dependencies, we introduce the notion of logical dependencies among the attributes in this article.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-logical-and-functional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-bottleneck-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent concept-based interpretable models have succeeded in providing meaningful explanations by pre-defined concept sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-bottleneck-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Banking Dataset: Understanding Client Needs through Event Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-banking-dataset-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Financial organizations collect a huge amount of data about clients that typically has a temporal (sequential) structure and is collected from various sources (modalities).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-banking-dataset-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightAvatar: Efficient Head Avatar as Dynamic Neural Light Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightavatar-efficient-head-avatar-as-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have shown that neural radiance fields (NeRFs) on top of parametric models have reached SOTA quality to build photorealistic head avatars from a monocular video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightavatar-efficient-head-avatar-as-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control Industrial Automation System with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-industrial-automation-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a framework for integrating LLMs to achieve end-to-end control of industrial automation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-industrial-automation-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowTurbo: Towards Real-time Flow-Based Image Generation with Velocity Refiner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowturbo-towards-real-time-flow-based-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating FlowTurbo into different flow-based models, we obtain an acceleration ratio of 53. 1%$\sim$58. 3% on class-conditional generation and 29. 8%$\sim$38. 5% on text-to-image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowturbo-towards-real-time-flow-based-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimVG: A Simple Framework for Visual Grounding with Decoupled Multi-modal Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvg-a-simple-framework-for-visual-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual grounding is a common vision task that involves grounding descriptive sentences to the corresponding regions of an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvg-a-simple-framework-for-visual-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisit Anything: Visual Place Recognition via Image Segment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-anything-visual-place-recognition-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This poses a fundamental challenge in matching two images of the same place captured from different camera viewpoints: "the similarity of what overlaps can be dominated by the dissimilarity of what does not overlap".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-anything-visual-place-recognition-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Deep Ensemble Uncertainty for Enhanced Medical Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-ensemble-uncertainty-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we propose D2UE, a Diversified Dual-space Uncertainty Estimation framework for medical anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-ensemble-uncertainty-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Preference Optimization: Enhance Your Language Model with Preference Degree Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-preference-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there has been significant interest in replacing the reward model in Reinforcement Learning with Human Feedback (RLHF) methods for Large Language Models (LLMs), such as Direct Preference Optimization (DPO) and its variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-preference-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Rhinos without Finding Rhinos: Active Learning with Multimodal Imagery of South African Rhino Habitats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/find-rhinos-without-finding-rhinos-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much of Earth's charismatic megafauna is endangered by human activities, particularly the rhino, which is at risk of extinction due to the poaching crisis in Africa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/find-rhinos-without-finding-rhinos-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Time Series is Worth Five Experts: Heterogeneous Mixture of Experts for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-five-experts-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate traffic prediction faces significant challenges, necessitating a deep understanding of both temporal and spatial cues and their complex interactions across multiple variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-five-experts-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upper-Body Pose-based Gaze Estimation for Privacy-Preserving 3D Gaze Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-body-pose-based-gaze-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach to tackle this problem by utilizing the person's upper-body pose and available depth maps to extract a 3D gaze direction and employing a multi-stage or an end-to-end pipeline to predict the gazed target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-body-pose-based-gaze-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Diffusion Prior for Image Super-Resolution with Domain Shift SDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-prior-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present DoSSR, a Domain Shift diffusion-based SR model that capitalizes on the generative powers of pretrained diffusion models while significantly enhancing efficiency by initiating the diffusion process with low-resolution (LR) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-prior-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Hierarchy and Temporal Attention Guided Cross Masking for Self-supervised Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-hierarchy-and-temporal-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In self-supervised skeleton-based action recognition, the mask reconstruction paradigm is gaining interest in enhancing model refinement and robustness through effective masking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-hierarchy-and-temporal-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting Regression Models for Conditional Uncertainty Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-regression-models-for-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal Prediction methods have finite-sample distribution-free marginal coverage guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-regression-models-for-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Pretraining for Cardiovascular Magnetic Resonance Cine Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, short-axis cine stacks of 296 subjects (90618 2D slices) were used for unlabeled pretraining with four SSP methods; SimCLR, positional contrastive learning, DINO, and masked image modeling (MIM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype based Masked Audio Model for Self-Supervised Learning of Sound Event Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-masked-audio-model-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant challenge in sound event detection (SED) is the effective utilization of unlabeled data, given the limited availability of labeled data due to high annotation costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-masked-audio-model-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Modeling of Molecular Dynamics Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-molecular-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce generative modeling of molecular trajectories as a paradigm for learning flexible multi-task surrogate models of MD from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-molecular-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkSAM: Fooling Segment Anything Model to Segment Nothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darksam-fooling-segment-anything-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the spatial domain, we disrupt the semantics of both the foreground and background in the image to confuse SAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darksam-fooling-segment-anything-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGN: The RNN's New Successor is Effective for Long-Range Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgn-the-rnn-s-new-successor-is-effective-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The other branch employs patches to capture short-term information and aggregate the global representation of the series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgn-the-rnn-s-new-successor-is-effective-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskLLM: Learnable Semi-Structured Sparsity for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskllm-learnable-semi-structured-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach facilitates end-to-end training on large-scale datasets and offers two notable advantages: 1) High-quality Masks - our method effectively scales to large datasets and learns accurate masks; 2) Transferability - the probabilistic modeling of mask distribution enables the transfer learning of sparsity across domains or tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskllm-learnable-semi-structured-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Open-Set Domain Generalization Using Evidential Bi-Level Hardest Domain Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-open-set-domain-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe that an adaptive domain scheduler benefits more in OSDG compared with prefixed sequential and random domain schedulers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-open-set-domain-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DALDA: Data Augmentation Leveraging Diffusion Model and LLM with Adaptive Guidance Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dalda-data-augmentation-leveraging-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an effective data augmentation framework leveraging the Large Language Model (LLM) and Diffusion Model (DM) to tackle the challenges inherent in data-scarce scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dalda-data-augmentation-leveraging-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSBP: Improving Object Detection in Histology Images via Test-time Self-guided Bounding-box Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsbp-improving-object-detection-in-histology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of this, using a preset global threshold (e. g., 0. 5) applied to all the bounding box candidates may lead to suboptimal solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsbp-improving-object-detection-in-histology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVT: A Comprehensive Vision Framework for Learning in Non-Euclidean Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvt-a-comprehensive-vision-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data representation in non-Euclidean spaces has proven effective for capturing hierarchical and complex relationships in real-world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvt-a-comprehensive-vision-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MorphoSeg: An Uncertainty-Aware Deep Learning Method for Biomedical Segmentation of Complex Cellular Morphologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphoseg-an-uncertainty-aware-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel benchmark dataset of Ntera-2 (NT2) cells, a pluripotent carcinoma cell line, exhibiting diverse morphologies across multiple stages of differentiation, capturing the intricate and heterogeneous cellular structures that complicate segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphoseg-an-uncertainty-aware-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statewide Visual Geolocalization in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statewide-visual-geolocalization-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a method that is able to predict the geolocation of a street-view photo taken in the wild within a state-sized search region by matching against a database of aerial reference imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statewide-visual-geolocalization-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model aggregation: minimizing empirical variance outperforms minimizing empirical error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-aggregation-minimizing-empirical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is non-intrusive - treating models as black-box functions - model-agnostic, requires minimal assumptions, and can combine outputs from a wide range of models, including those from machine learning and numerical solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-aggregation-minimizing-empirical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Robot Informative Path Planning for Efficient Target Mapping using Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-robot-informative-path-planning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel deep reinforcement learning approach for multi-robot informative path planning to map targets-of-interest in an unknown 3D environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-robot-informative-path-planning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitQ: Tailoring Block Floating Point Precision for Improved DNN Efficiency on Resource-Constrained Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitq-tailoring-block-floating-point-precision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) are powerful for cognitive tasks such as image classification, object detection, and scene segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitq-tailoring-block-floating-point-precision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Comic Generation: Integrating Visual Narrative Theories with AI Models for Enhanced Creativity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-comic-generation-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our system combines human creativity with AI models to support parts of the generative process, providing a collaborative platform for creating comic content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-comic-generation-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Nighttime UAV Tracking with Light Distribution Suppression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-nighttime-uav-tracking-with-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the state-of-the-art (SOTA) enhancers for nighttime UAV tracking always neglect the uneven light distribution in low-light images, inevitably leading to excessive enhancement in scenarios with complex illumination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-nighttime-uav-tracking-with-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodonMPNN for Organism Specific and Codon Optimal Inverse Folding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codonmpnn-for-organism-specific-and-codon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, CodonMPNN has a higher likelihood of generating high-fitness codon sequences than low-fitness codon sequences for the same protein sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codonmpnn-for-organism-specific-and-codon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 BRAVO Challenge Track 1 1st Place Report: Evaluating Robustness of Vision Foundation Models for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2024-bravo-challenge-track-1-1st-place-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present our solution for Track 1 of the 2024 BRAVO Challenge, where a model is trained on Cityscapes and its robustness is evaluated on several out-of-distribution datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2024-bravo-challenge-track-1-1st-place-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FineZip : Pushing the Limits of Large Language Models for Practical Lossless Text Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finezip-pushing-the-limits-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare traditional text compression systems with neural network and LLM-based text compression methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finezip-pushing-the-limits-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeInsight: A Curated Dataset of Practical Coding Solutions from Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codeinsight-a-curated-dataset-of-practical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel dataset tailored for code generation, aimed at aiding developers in common tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codeinsight-a-curated-dataset-of-practical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Representation Learning for Real-Time UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-representation-learning-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, PRL-Track is divided into coarse representation learning and fine representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-representation-learning-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTQ4RIS: Post-Training Quantization for Referring Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptq4ris-post-training-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first conduct an in-depth analysis of the root causes of performance degradation in RIS model quantization and propose dual-region quantization (DRQ) and reorder-based outlier-retained quantization (RORQ) to address the quantization difficulties in visual and text encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptq4ris-post-training-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress Detection from Photoplethysmography in a Virtual Reality Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stress-detection-from-photoplethysmography-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized virtual reality exposure therapy is a therapeutic practice that can adapt to an individual patient, leading to better health outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stress-detection-from-photoplethysmography-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiders Based on Anxiety: How Reinforcement Learning Can Deliver Desired User Experience in Virtual Reality Personalized Arachnophobia Treatment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiders-based-on-anxiety-how-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The need to generate a spider to provoke a desired anxiety response arises in the context of personalized virtual reality exposure therapy (VRET), a treatment approach for arachnophobia.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiders-based-on-anxiety-how-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacewalker: Traversing Representation Spaces for Fast Interactive Exploration and Annotation of Unstructured Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spacewalker-traversing-representation-spaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unstructured data in industries such as healthcare, finance, and manufacturing presents significant challenges for efficient analysis and decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spacewalker-traversing-representation-spaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-SQL: Direct Schema Linking via Question Enrichment in Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-sql-direct-schema-linking-via-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce E-SQL, a novel pipeline specifically designed to address these challenges through direct schema linking and candidate predicate augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-sql-direct-schema-linking-via-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlCity: A Multimodal Diffusion Model Based Approach for Accurate Geospatial Data Generation and Urban Morphology Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlcity-a-multimodal-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study confirms the effectiveness of our approach in generating urban building footprint data and capturing complex city characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlcity-a-multimodal-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Prompting on Image for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-prompting-on-image-for-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, in this work, we propose a new prompting technique named Attention Prompting on Image, which just simply overlays a text-query-guided attention heatmap on the original input image and effectively enhances LVLM on various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-prompting-on-image-for-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VPTQ: Extreme Low-bit Vector Post-Training Quantization for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vptq-extreme-low-bit-vector-post-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the redundancy in LLM weights, recent research has focused on pushing weight-only quantization to extremely low-bit (even down to 2 bits).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vptq-extreme-low-bit-vector-post-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying Issues, Causes and Solutions in LLM Open-Source Projects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-issues-causes-and-solutions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advancements of Large Language Models (LLMs), an increasing number of open-source software projects are using LLMs as their core functional component.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-issues-causes-and-solutions-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
