<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2024 09:13:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-Semantic Collaborative Cropping for User Generated Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-semantic-collaborative-cropping-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A large amount of User Generated Content (UGC) is uploaded to the Internet daily and displayed to people world-widely through the client side (e. g., mobile and PC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-semantic-collaborative-cropping-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-lingual neural fuzzy matching for exploiting target-language monolingual corpora in computer-aided translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-neural-fuzzy-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper presents an automatic evaluation of these techniques on four language pairs that shows that our approach can successfully exploit monolingual texts in a TM-based CAT environment, increasing the amount of useful translation proposals, and that our neural model for estimating the post-editing effort enables the combination of translation proposals obtained from monolingual corpora and from TMs in the usual way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-neural-fuzzy-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JustiLM: Few-shot Justification Generation for Explainable Fact-Checking of Real-world Claims</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/justilm-few-shot-justification-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Justification is an explanation that supports the veracity assigned to a claim in fact-checking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/justilm-few-shot-justification-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferflow: an Efficient and Highly Configurable Inference Engine for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferflow-an-efficient-and-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Inferflow, an efficient and highly configurable inference engine for large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferflow-an-efficient-and-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reproducibility Study of Goldilocks: Just-Right Tuning of BERT for TAR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducibility-study-of-goldilocks-just</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this context, we show that there is no need for further pre-training if a domain-specific BERT backbone is used within the active learning pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducibility-study-of-goldilocks-just</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Test for Attention Map in Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-test-for-attention-map-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a statistical test for ViT's attentions, enabling us to use the attentions as reliable quantitative evidence indicators for ViT's decision-making with a rigorously controlled error rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-test-for-attention-map-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forging Vision Foundation Models for Autonomous Driving: Challenges, Methodologies, and Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forging-vision-foundation-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of large foundation models, trained on extensive datasets, is revolutionizing the field of AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forging-vision-foundation-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UV-SAM: Adapting Segment Anything Model for Urban Village Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uv-sam-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Urban villages, defined as informal residential areas in or around urban centers, are characterized by inadequate infrastructures and poor living conditions, closely related to the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) on poverty, adequate housing, and sustainable cities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uv-sam-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenDPD: An Open-Source End-to-End Learning &amp; Benchmarking Framework for Wideband Power Amplifier Modeling and Digital Pre-Distortion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opendpd-an-open-source-end-to-end-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise in communication capacity, deep neural networks (DNN) for digital pre-distortion (DPD) to correct non-linearity in wideband power amplifiers (PAs) have become prominent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opendpd-an-open-source-end-to-end-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calpric: Inclusive and Fine-grain Labeling of Privacy Policies with Crowdsourcing and Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calpric-inclusive-and-fine-grain-labeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we present Calpric , which combines automatic text selection and segmentation, active learning and the use of crowdsourced annotators to generate a large, balanced training set for privacy policies at low cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calpric-inclusive-and-fine-grain-labeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AesBench: An Expert Benchmark for Multimodal Large Language Models on Image Aesthetics Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesbench-an-expert-benchmark-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An obvious obstacle lies in the absence of a specific benchmark to evaluate the effectiveness of MLLMs on aesthetic perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesbench-an-expert-benchmark-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Resource-efficient LLM and Multimodal Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-resource-efficient-llm-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large foundation models, including large language models (LLMs), vision transformers (ViTs), diffusion, and LLM-based multimodal models, are revolutionizing the entire machine learning lifecycle, from training to deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-resource-efficient-llm-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devil is in the Details: Boosting Guided Depth Super-Resolution via Rethinking Cross-Modal Alignment and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-details-boosting-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Guided depth super-resolution (GDSR) involves restoring missing depth details using the high-resolution RGB image of the same scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-details-boosting-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMF: Small-Area-Aware Multi-focus Image Fusion for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samf-small-area-aware-multi-focus-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing multi-focus image fusion (MFIF) methods often fail to preserve the uncertain transition region and detect small focus areas within large defocused regions accurately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samf-small-area-aware-multi-focus-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ModelNet-O: A Large-Scale Synthetic Dataset for Occlusion-Aware Point Cloud Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelnet-o-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experiments, we demonstrate that our PointMLS achieves state-of-the-art results on ModelNet-O and competitive results on regular datasets, and it is robust and effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelnet-o-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KADEL: Knowledge-Aware Denoising Learning for Commit Message Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kadel-knowledge-aware-denoising-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, previous methods are trained on the entire dataset without considering the fact that a portion of commit messages adhere to good practice (i. e., good-practice commits), while the rest do not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kadel-knowledge-aware-denoising-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DurFlex-EVC: Duration-Flexible Emotional Voice Conversion with Parallel Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/durflex-evc-duration-flexible-emotional-voice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Emotional voice conversion (EVC) seeks to modify the emotional tone of a speaker's voice while preserving the original linguistic content and the speaker's unique vocal characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/durflex-evc-duration-flexible-emotional-voice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoraemonGPT: Toward Understanding Dynamic Scenes with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doraemongpt-toward-understanding-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of AI agents is advancing at an unprecedented rate due to the capabilities of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doraemongpt-toward-understanding-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Denoise Distillation: Simple Stochastic Noises Induce Efficient Knowledge Transfer for Dense Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-denoise-distillation-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation is the process of transferring knowledge from a more powerful large model (teacher) to a simpler counterpart (student).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-denoise-distillation-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask the experts: sourcing high-quality datasets for nutritional counselling through Human-AI collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-the-experts-sourcing-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release HAI-coaching, the first expert-annotated nutrition counselling dataset containing ~2. 4K dietary struggles from crowd workers, and ~97K related supportive texts generated by ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-the-experts-sourcing-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Imagine: Effective Unimodal Reasoning with Multimodal Models using Self-Imagination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-imagine-effective-unimodal-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The potential of Vision-Language Models (\textsc{vlm}s) often remains underutilized in handling complex text-based problems, particularly when these problems could benefit from visual representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-imagine-effective-unimodal-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn What You Need in Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-what-you-need-in-personalized-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized federated learning aims to address data heterogeneity across local clients in federated learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-what-you-need-in-personalized-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Completely Occluded and Dense Object Instance Segmentation Using Box Prompt-Based Segmentation Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completely-occluded-and-dense-object-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CFNet, a coarse-to-fine IS framework for completely occluded and dense objects, which is based on box prompt-based segmentation foundation models (BSMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completely-occluded-and-dense-object-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2HQV: High-Quality Video Generation from Event Camera via Theory-Inspired Model-Aided Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2hqv-high-quality-video-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose \textbf{E2HQV}, a novel E2V paradigm designed to produce high-quality video frames from events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2hqv-high-quality-video-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question Translation Training for Better Multilingual Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-translation-training-for-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models show compelling performance on reasoning tasks but they tend to perform much worse in languages other than English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-translation-training-for-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carrying over algorithm in transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carrying-over-algorithm-in-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first layer is mostly responsible for adding digits in the same position.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carrying-over-algorithm-in-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparsity-based background removal for STORM super-resolution images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-based-background-removal-for-storm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a sparsity-based background removal method by adapting a neural network (SLNet) from a different microscopy domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-based-background-removal-for-storm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CascadeV-Det: Cascade Point Voting for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascadev-det-cascade-point-voting-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, since model training can suffer from a lack of proposal points with high centerness, we have developed the CPA module to narrow down the positive assignment threshold with cascade stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascadev-det-cascade-point-voting-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JumpCoder: Go Beyond Autoregressive Coder via Online Modification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jumpcoder-go-beyond-autoregressive-coder-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing code large language models (code LLMs) exhibit impressive capabilities in code generation, their autoregressive sequential generation inherently lacks reversibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jumpcoder-go-beyond-autoregressive-coder-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Perceptual Quality: Evaluating the Impact of Severe Lossy Compression on Audio and Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-perceptual-quality-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results indicate three key findings: (1) using generative compression, it is feasible to leverage highly compressed data while incurring a negligible impact on machine perceptual quality; (2) machine perceptual quality correlates strongly with deep similarity metrics, indicating a crucial role of these metrics in the development of machine-oriented codecs; and (3) using lossy compressed datasets, (e. g. ImageNet) for pre-training can lead to counter-intuitive scenarios where lossy compression increases machine perceptual quality rather than degrading it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-perceptual-quality-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activations and Gradients Compression for Model-Parallel Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activations-and-gradients-compression-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze compression methods such as quantization and TopK compression, and also experiment with error compensation techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activations-and-gradients-compression-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical Evidence for the Fragment level Understanding on Drug Molecular Structure of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-evidence-for-the-fragment-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AI for drug discovery has been a research hotspot in recent years, and SMILES-based language models has been increasingly applied in drug molecular design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-evidence-for-the-fragment-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E3x: $\mathrm{E}(3)$-Equivariant Deep Learning Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e3x-mathrm-e-3-equivariant-deep-learning-made</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces E3x, a software package for building neural networks that are equivariant with respect to the Euclidean group $\mathrm{E}(3)$, consisting of translations, rotations, and reflections of three-dimensional space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e3x-mathrm-e-3-equivariant-deep-learning-made</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the importance of Data Scale in Pretraining Arabic Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-data-scale-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretraining monolingual language models have been proven to be vital for performance in Arabic Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-data-scale-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compute-Efficient Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compute-efficient-active-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active learning, a powerful paradigm in machine learning, aims at reducing labeling costs by selecting the most informative samples from an unlabeled dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compute-efficient-active-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Neural-Operator Backstepping Control of a Benchmark Hyperbolic PDE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-neural-operator-backstepping-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This requires an adaptive approach to PDE control, i. e., an estimation of the plant coefficients conducted concurrently with control, where a separate PDE for the gain kernel must be solved at each timestep upon the update in the plant coefficient function estimate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-neural-operator-backstepping-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Nonparametric Tensor Decomposition for Binary and Count Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-nonparametric-tensor-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, to address the computational issue of GPs, we enhance the model by incorporating sparse orthogonal variational inference of inducing points, which offers a more effective covariance approximation within GPs and stochastic natural gradient updates for nonparametric models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-nonparametric-tensor-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias-Conflict Sample Synthesis and Adversarial Removal Debias Strategy for Temporal Sentence Grounding in Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-conflict-sample-synthesis-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal Sentence Grounding in Video (TSGV) is troubled by dataset bias issue, which is caused by the uneven temporal distribution of the target moments for samples with similar semantic components in input videos or query texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-conflict-sample-synthesis-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Assimilation using ERA5, ASOS, and the U-STN model for Weather Forecasting over the UK</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-assimilation-using-era5-asos-and-the-u</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the convergence of data-driven machine learning models with Data Assimilation (DA) offers a promising avenue for enhancing weather forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-assimilation-using-era5-asos-and-the-u</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoNuS: Boundary Mining for Nuclei Segmentation with Partial Point Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bonus-boundary-mining-for-nuclei-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this problem, in this paper, we propose a weakly-supervised nuclei segmentation method that only requires partial point labels of nuclei.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bonus-boundary-mining-for-nuclei-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Approach To Gaussian Process Surrogate Evaluation With Coverage Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-approach-to-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian processes (GPs) are a Bayesian machine learning approach widely used to construct surrogate models for the uncertainty quantification of computer simulation codes in industrial applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-approach-to-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency of semi-supervised learning, stochastic tug-of-war games, and the p-Laplacian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-of-semi-supervised-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we give a broad overview of the intersection of partial differential equations (PDEs) and graph-based semi-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-of-semi-supervised-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-light Stereo Image Enhancement and De-noising in the Low-frequency Information Enhanced Image Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-stereo-image-enhancement-and-de</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, to reduce unwanted noise interference, a low-frequency information enhanced module (IEM) is proposed to suppress noise and produce a new image space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-stereo-image-enhancement-and-de</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstantID: Zero-shot Identity-Preserving Generation in Seconds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantid-zero-shot-identity-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been significant progress in personalized image synthesis with methods such as Textual Inversion, DreamBooth, and LoRA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantid-zero-shot-identity-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Masked Autoencoders for Sensor-Agnostic Image Retrieval in Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-masked-autoencoders-for-sensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We finally derive a guideline to exploit masked image modeling for uni-modal and cross-modal CBIR problems in RS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-masked-autoencoders-for-sensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Any Omics: Towards genome-wide data integration for patient stratification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrate-any-omics-towards-genome-wide-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-throughput omics profiling advancements have greatly enhanced cancer patient stratification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrate-any-omics-towards-genome-wide-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMFSNet: Polarized Multi-scale Feature Self-attention Network For Lightweight Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmfsnet-polarized-multi-scale-feature-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose PMFSNet, a novel medical imaging segmentation model that effectively balances global and local feature processing while avoiding the computational redundancy typical in larger models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmfsnet-polarized-multi-scale-feature-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascaded Cross-Modal Transformer for Audio-Textual Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-cross-modal-transformer-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we combine language-specific Bidirectional Encoder Representations from Transformers (BERT) with Wav2Vec2. 0 audio features via a novel cascaded cross-modal transformer (CCMT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-cross-modal-transformer-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciGLM: Training Scientific Language Models with Self-Reflective Instruction Annotation and Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciglm-training-scientific-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We fine-tuned the ChatGLM family of language models with SciInstruct, enhancing their capabilities in scientific and mathematical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciglm-training-scientific-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Globally Convergent Algorithm for Neural Network Parameter Optimization Based on Difference-of-Convex Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-globally-convergent-algorithm-for-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we mathematically analyze the convergence rate of parameters and the convergence rate in value (i. e., the training loss).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-globally-convergent-algorithm-for-neural</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
