<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2022 21:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Embracing Consistency: A One-Stage Approach for Spatio-Temporal Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embracing-consistency-a-one-stage-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatio-Temporal video grounding (STVG) focuses on retrieving the spatio-temporal tube of a specific object depicted by a free-form textual expression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embracing-consistency-a-one-stage-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Algorithm-Dependent Generalization of AUPRC Optimization with List Stability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-algorithm-dependent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic optimization of the Area Under the Precision-Recall Curve (AUPRC) is a crucial problem for machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-algorithm-dependent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Laws For Deep Learning Based Image Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-laws-for-deep-learning-based-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current methods are only trained on a few hundreds or thousands of images as opposed to the millions of examples deep networks are trained on in other domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-laws-for-deep-learning-based-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Panning: Screening the Optimal Sparse Network Before Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-panning-screening-the-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pruning on neural networks before training not only compresses the original models, but also accelerates the network training phase, which has substantial application value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-panning-screening-the-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Affective Vocal Bursts with Finetuned wav2vec 2.0</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-affective-vocal-bursts-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The studies of predicting affective states from human voices have relied heavily on speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-affective-vocal-bursts-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeightedSHAP: analyzing and improving Shapley based feature attributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weightedshap-analyzing-and-improving-shapley</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On several real-world datasets, we demonstrate that the influential features identified by WeightedSHAP are better able to recapitulate the model's predictions compared to the features identified by the Shapley value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weightedshap-analyzing-and-improving-shapley</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OBBStacking: An Ensemble Method for Remote Sensing Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obbstacking-an-ensemble-method-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trying to address these problems, this paper proposes OBBStacking, an ensemble method that is compatible with OBBs and combines the detection results in a learned fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obbstacking-an-ensemble-method-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Globally Optimal Event-Based Divergence Estimation for Ventral Landing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-optimal-event-based-divergence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is achieved by estimating divergence (inverse TTC), which is the rate of radial optic flow, from the event stream generated during landing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-optimal-event-based-divergence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossDTR: Cross-view and Depth-guided Transformers for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossdtr-cross-view-and-depth-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve accurate 3D object detection at a low cost for autonomous driving, many multi-camera methods have been proposed and solved the occlusion problem of monocular approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossdtr-cross-view-and-depth-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sauron U-Net: Simple automated redundancy elimination in medical image segmentation via filter pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sauron-u-net-simple-automated-redundancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Sauron, a filter pruning method that eliminates redundant feature maps by discarding the corresponding filters with automatically-adjusted layer-specific thresholds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sauron-u-net-simple-automated-redundancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draw Your Art Dream: Diverse Digital Art Synthesis with Multimodal Guided Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draw-your-art-dream-diverse-digital-art</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results on the quality and quantity of the generated digital art paintings confirm the effectiveness of the combination of the diffusion model and multimodal guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draw-your-art-dream-diverse-digital-art</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural parameter calibration for large-scale multi-agent models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-calibration-for-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computational models have become a powerful tool in the quantitative sciences to understand the behaviour of complex systems that evolve in time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-parameter-calibration-for-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization of Annealed Importance Sampling Hyperparameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-annealed-importance-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annealed Importance Sampling (AIS) is a popular algorithm used to estimates the intractable marginal likelihood of deep generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-annealed-importance-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EditEval: An Instruction-Based Benchmark for Text Improvements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editeval-an-instruction-based-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation of text generation to date has primarily focused on content created sequentially, rather than improvements on a piece of text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editeval-an-instruction-based-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Counter: Stochastic Feature-based Learning for Diverse Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-counter-stochastic-feature-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretable machine learning seeks to understand the reasoning process of complex black-box systems that are long notorious for lack of explainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-counter-stochastic-feature-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeSeg: Free Mask from Interpretable Contrastive Language-Image Pretraining for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseg-free-mask-from-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We call the proposed framework as FreeSeg, where the mask is freely available from raw feature map of pretraining model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseg-free-mask-from-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Digital Language Support on a Global Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-digital-language-support-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The users of endangered languages struggle to thrive in a digitally-mediated world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-digital-language-support-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperYOLO: Super Resolution Assisted Object Detection in Multimodal Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superyolo-super-resolution-assisted-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an accurate yet fast small object detection method for RSI, named SuperYOLO, which fuses multimodal data and performs high resolution (HR) object detection on multiscale objects by utilizing the assisted super resolution (SR) learning and considering both the detection accuracy and computation cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superyolo-super-resolution-assisted-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biologically-Plausible Determinant Maximization Neural Networks for Blind Separation of Correlated Sources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biologically-plausible-determinant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work on biologically-plausible BSS algorithms assumed that observed signals are linear mixtures of statistically independent or uncorrelated sources, limiting the domain of applicability of these algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biologically-plausible-determinant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formal Conceptual Views in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-conceptual-views-in-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explaining neural network models is a challenging task that remains unsolved in its entirety to this day.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-conceptual-views-in-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Decision Making Using Action Suggestions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decision-making-using-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The assumption of a collaborative environment enables us to use the agent's policy to estimate the distribution over action suggestions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decision-making-using-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Dataset for Evaluating and Alleviating Domain Shift for Human Detection in Agricultural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-dataset-for-evaluating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we evaluate the impact of domain shift on human detection models trained on well known object detection datasets when deployed on data outside the distribution of the training set, as well as propose methods to alleviate such phenomena based on the available annotations from the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-dataset-for-evaluating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Im2Oil: Stroke-Based Oil Painting Rendering with Linearly Controllable Fineness Via Adaptive Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/im2oil-stroke-based-oil-painting-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparison with existing state-of-the-art oil painting techniques shows that our results have higher fidelity and more realistic textures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/im2oil-stroke-based-oil-painting-rendering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleMask: Disentangling the Style Space of StyleGAN2 for Neural Face Reenactment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylemask-disentangling-the-style-space-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we address the problem of neural face reenactment, where, given a pair of a source and a target facial image, we need to transfer the target's pose (defined as the head pose and its facial expressions) to the source image, by preserving at the same time the source's identity characteristics (e. g., facial shape, hair style, etc), even in the challenging case where the source and the target faces belong to different identities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylemask-disentangling-the-style-space-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier Suppression: Pushing the Limit of Low-bit Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-suppression-pushing-the-limit-of-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the trends of large NLP models, the increasing memory and computation costs hinder their efficient deployment on resource-limited devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-suppression-pushing-the-limit-of-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Blind Source Separation with Learned Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-blind-source-separation-with-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BSS problems being ill-posed, the resolution requires efficient regularization schemes to better distinguish between the sources and yield interpretable solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-blind-source-separation-with-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Transformer in Reinforcement Learning for Interpretable Temporal Logic Motion Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-transformer-in-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automaton based approaches have enabled robots to perform various complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-transformer-in-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiDes: A Wikipedia-Based Dataset for Generating Short Descriptions from Paragraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikides-a-wikipedia-based-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce WikiDes, a novel dataset to generate short descriptions of Wikipedia articles for the problem of text summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikides-a-wikipedia-based-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Acquisition of High Quality RGB Image and Polarization Information using a Sparse Polarization Sensor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-acquisition-of-high-quality-rgb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed network architecture consists of an RGB image refinement network and a polarization information compensation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-acquisition-of-high-quality-rgb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Transformer with Global Intention Localization and Local Movement Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transformer-with-global-intention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that MTR achieves state-of-the-art performance on both the marginal and joint motion prediction challenges, ranking 1st on the leaderboards of Waymo Open Motion Dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-transformer-with-global-intention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdeaReader: A Machine Reading System for Understanding the Idea Flow of Scientific Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideareader-a-machine-reading-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the origin and influence of the publication's idea is critical to conducting scientific research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideareader-a-machine-reading-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning State-Aware Visual Representations from Audible Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-state-aware-visual-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, learning representations from videos can be challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-state-aware-visual-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Based Dimensionality Reduction for Computing Compact and Effective Local Feature Descriptors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-dimensionality-reduction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A distinctive representation of image patches in form of features is a key component of many computer vision and robotics tasks, such as image matching, image retrieval, and visual localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-dimensionality-reduction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyRec: An easy-to-use, extendable and efficient framework for building industrial recommendation systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-an-easy-to-use-extendable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present EasyRec, an easy-to-use, extendable and efficient recommendation framework for building industrial recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-an-easy-to-use-extendable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heterogeneous group CNN for image super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-heterogeneous-group-cnn-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To prevent loss of original information, a multi-level enhancement mechanism guides a CNN to achieve a symmetric architecture for promoting expressive ability of HGSRCNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-heterogeneous-group-cnn-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dataset Training of Transformers for Robust Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dataset-training-of-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the task of robust feature representations, aiming to generalize well on multiple datasets for action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dataset-training-of-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural identifiability analysis of epidemic models based on differential equations: A Primer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-identifiability-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Structural identifiability analysis uncovers any existing parameter correlations that preclude their estimation from the observed variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-identifiability-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrinking unit: a Graph Convolution-Based Unit for CNN-like 3D Point Cloud Feature Extractors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrinking-unit-a-graph-convolution-based-unit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While part of this failure stems from the irregularity, unstructuredness, and disorder of point clouds, which makes the task of point cloud feature detection significantly more challenging than the image one, we argue that a lack of inspiration from the image domain might be the primary cause of such a gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrinking-unit-a-graph-convolution-based-unit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Parametric Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-parametric-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on theoretical analysis, we observe that supervised contrastive loss tends to bias high-frequency classes and thus increases the difficulty of imbalanced learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-parametric-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Image Clustering through Sample Ranking and Its Application to remote--sensing images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-clustering-through-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Performing our method on a variety of datasets from remote sensing, we show that our method can be effectively applied to remote--sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-clustering-through-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural State-Space Modeling with Latent Causal-Effect Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-modeling-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a novel neural formulation of state-space models (SSMs), we first introduce causal-effect modeling of the latent dynamics via a system of interacting neural ODEs that separately describes 1) the continuous-time dynamics of the internal intervention, and 2) its effect on the trajectory of the system's native state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-modeling-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOViS: Learning Orientation and Visual Signals for Vision and Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lovis-learning-orientation-and-visual-signals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding spatial and visual information is essential for a navigation agent who follows natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lovis-learning-orientation-and-visual-signals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-stage image denoising with the wavelet transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-image-denoising-with-the-wavelet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep convolutional neural networks (CNNs) are used for image denoising via automatically mining accurate structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-image-denoising-with-the-wavelet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Attention GAN for Vehicle Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-attention-gan-for-vehicle-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The design of a safe and reliable Autonomous Driving stack (ADS) is one of the most challenging tasks of our era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-attention-gan-for-vehicle-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPIC-KITCHENS VISOR Benchmark: VIdeo Segmentations and Object Relations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epic-kitchens-visor-benchmark-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[VISOR annotates videos from EPIC-KITCHENS, which comes with a new set of challenges not encountered in current video segmentation datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epic-kitchens-visor-benchmark-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Efficient Controllers via Analytic Policy Gradient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-efficient-controllers-via-analytic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversely, learning-based offline optimization approaches, such as Reinforcement Learning (RL), allow fast and efficient execution on the robot but hardly match the accuracy of MPC in trajectory tracking tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-efficient-controllers-via-analytic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-RawVSR: Real-World Raw Video Super-Resolution with a Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-rawvsr-real-world-raw-video-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our code and dataset are available at https://github. com/zmzhang1998/Real-RawVSR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-rawvsr-real-world-raw-video-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Detection with Hilbert-Schmidt Independence Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-hilbert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works attempt to solve the problem by explicitly imposing uncertainty on classifiers when OOD inputs are exposed to the classifier during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-hilbert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bounded Simplex-Structured Matrix Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounded-simplex-structured-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new low-rank matrix factorization model dubbed bounded simplex-structured matrix factorization (BSSMF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bounded-simplex-structured-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Projections to Linear Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-projections-to-linear-subspaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The merit of projecting data onto linear subspaces is well known from, e. g., dimension reduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-projections-to-linear-subspaces</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
