<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 21:07:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>UMERegRobust -- Universal Manifold Embedding Compatible Features for Robust Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umeregrobust-universal-manifold-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend the UME framework by introducing a UME-compatible feature extraction method augmented with a unique UME contrastive loss and a sampling equalizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umeregrobust-universal-manifold-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show-o: One Single Transformer to Unify Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o-one-single-transformer-to-unify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a unified transformer, i. e., Show-o, that unifies multimodal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o-one-single-transformer-to-unify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Foundation Model Adaptation: Pioneering Computer Vision Models for Geophysical Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-foundation-model-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore adapting foundation models (FMs) from the computer vision domain to geoscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-foundation-model-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized SAM: Efficient Fine-Tuning of SAM for Variable Input Image Sizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-sam-efficient-fine-tuning-of-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The input image size of SAM is fixed at 1024 x 1024, resulting in substantial computational demands during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-sam-efficient-fine-tuning-of-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ssProp: Energy-Efficient Training for Convolutional Neural Networks with Scheduled Sparse Back Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssprop-energy-efficient-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Back-propagation (BP) is a major source of computational expense during training deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssprop-energy-efficient-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPARK: Multi-Vision Sensor Perception and Reasoning Benchmark for Large-scale Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spark-multi-vision-sensor-perception-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we observe that current LVLMs view images taken from multi-vision sensors as if they were in the same RGB domain without considering the physical characteristics of multi-vision sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spark-multi-vision-sensor-perception-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning (Medical) LLMs for (Counterfactual) Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-medical-llms-for-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have emerged as promising solutions for a variety of medical and clinical decision support applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-medical-llms-for-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvalYaks: Instruction Tuning Datasets and LoRA Fine-tuned Models for Automated Scoring of CEFR B2 Speaking Assessment Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evalyaks-instruction-tuning-datasets-and-lora</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, new instruction-tuned datasets are developed from the English Vocabulary Profile (up to CEFR B2 level) and the CEFR-SP WikiAuto datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evalyaks-instruction-tuning-datasets-and-lora</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Video Generation with Pyramid Attention Broadcast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-video-generation-with-pyramid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Pyramid Attention Broadcast (PAB), a real-time, high quality and training-free approach for DiT-based video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-video-generation-with-pyramid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning via Loss Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the impact of data heterogeneity on FL performance, we start with analyzing how FL training influence FL performance by decomposing the global loss into three terms: local loss, distribution shift loss and aggregation loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Pattern Mining-based Multi-Behavior Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-pattern-mining-based-multi-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-behavior recommendation systems enhance effectiveness by leveraging auxiliary behaviors (such as page views and favorites) to address the limitations of traditional models that depend solely on sparse target behaviors like purchases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-pattern-mining-based-multi-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRExplainer: Quantifiable Interpretability in Drug Response Prediction with Directed Graph Convolutional Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drexplainer-quantifiable-interpretability-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DRExplainer constructs a directed bipartite network integrating multi-omics profiles of cell lines, the chemical structure of drugs and known drug response to achieve directed prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drexplainer-quantifiable-interpretability-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection Through Transfer Learning for Large-Scale Web services</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multivariate-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) excel at general question-answering (Q&A) but often fall short in specialized domains due to a lack of domain-specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multivariate-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Percolation Model of Emergence: Analyzing Transformers Trained on a Formal Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-percolation-model-of-emergence-analyzing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increase in data, size, or compute can lead to sudden learning of specific capabilities by a neural network -- a phenomenon often called "emergence".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-percolation-model-of-emergence-analyzing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrolled Decomposed Unpaired Learning for Controllable Low-Light Video Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrolled-decomposed-unpaired-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above challenge, we propose the Unrolled Decomposed Unpaired Network (UDU-Net) for enhancing low-light videos by unrolling the optimization functions into a deep network to decompose the signal into spatial and temporal-related factors, which are updated iteratively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrolled-decomposed-unpaired-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Evaluating and Building Versatile Large Language Models for Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-evaluating-and-building-versatile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To promote further advancements in the application of LLMs to clinical challenges, we have made the MedS-Ins dataset fully accessible and invite the research community to contribute to its expansion. Additionally, we have launched a dynamic leaderboard for MedS-Bench, which we plan to regularly update the test set to track progress and enhance the adaptation of general LLMs to the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-evaluating-and-building-versatile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UMAD: University of Macau Anomaly Detection Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umad-university-of-macau-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our best knowledge, this is the first benchmark dataset designed specifically for anomaly detection with reference in robotic patrolling scenarios, e. g., where an autonomous robot is employed to detect anomalous objects by comparing a reference and a query video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/umad-university-of-macau-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CODE: Confident Ordinary Differential Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-confident-ordinary-differential-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, conditioning on noisy or Out-of-Distribution (OoD) images poses significant challenges, particularly in balancing fidelity to the input and realism of the output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-confident-ordinary-differential-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive DualChecker for Mitigating Hallucinations in Distilling Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-dualchecker-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, current methods for knowledge distillation using LLMs often struggle to enhance the effectiveness of both teacher and student models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-dualchecker-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Spiking Neural Networks with Hybrid Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spiking-neural-networks-with-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Spiking Neural Network (SNN), due to its unique spiking-driven nature, is a more energy-efficient and effective neural network compared to Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spiking-neural-networks-with-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Retrieval Augmented Trustworthiness Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-retrieval-augmented-trustworthiness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trustworthiness reasoning is crucial in multiplayer games with incomplete information, enabling agents to identify potential allies and adversaries, thereby enhancing reasoning and decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-retrieval-augmented-trustworthiness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenderCARE: A Comprehensive Framework for Assessing and Reducing Gender Bias in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendercare-a-comprehensive-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By offering a realistic assessment and tailored reduction of gender biases, we hope that our GenderCARE can represent a significant step towards achieving fairness and equity in LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendercare-a-comprehensive-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISETHDR: A Physics-based Synthetic Radiance Dataset for High Dynamic Range Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isethdr-a-physics-based-synthetic-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a physics-based end-to-end software simulation for image systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isethdr-a-physics-based-synthetic-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexEdit: Marrying Free-Shape Masks to VLLM for Flexible Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexedit-marrying-free-shape-masks-to-vllm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach employs a VLLM in comprehending the image content, mask, and user instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexedit-marrying-free-shape-masks-to-vllm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDD-5k: A New Diagnostic Conversation Dataset for Mental Disorders Synthesized via Neuro-Symbolic LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdd-5k-a-new-diagnostic-conversation-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By applying the proposed framework, we develop the largest Chinese mental disorders diagnosis dataset MDD-5k, which is built upon 1000 cleaned real patient cases by cooperating with a pioneering psychiatric hospital, and contains 5000 high-quality long conversations with diagnosis results as labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdd-5k-a-new-diagnostic-conversation-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Augmentation for Graph Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-augmentation-for-graph-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite emerging regulations addressing fairness of automated systems, unfairness issues in graph collaborative filtering remain underexplored, especially from the consumer's perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-augmentation-for-graph-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accounts of using the Tustin-Net architecture on a rotary inverted pendulum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accounts-of-using-the-tustin-net-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report we investigate the use of the Tustin neural network architecture (Tustin-Net) for the identification of a physical rotary inverse pendulum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accounts-of-using-the-tustin-net-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Riemannian Approach for Spatiotemporal Analysis and Generation of 4D Tree-shaped Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-riemannian-approach-for-spatiotemporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel mathematical representation of the shape space of such trajectories, a Riemannian metric on that space, and computational tools for fast and accurate spatiotemporal registration and geodesics computation between 4D tree-shaped structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-riemannian-approach-for-spatiotemporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple testing for signal-agnostic searches of new physics with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-testing-for-signal-agnostic-searches</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the question of how to enhance signal-agnostic searches by leveraging multiple testing strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-testing-for-signal-agnostic-searches</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Attributes' Contribution to Successful Camouflage: A Combined Textual and VisualAnalysis Strategy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-attributes-contribution-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the domain of Camouflaged Object Segmentation (COS), despite continuous improvements in segmentation performance, the underlying mechanisms of effective camouflage remain poorly understood, akin to a black box.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-attributes-contribution-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WCEbleedGen: A wireless capsule endoscopy dataset and its benchmarking for automatic bleeding classification, detection, and segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wcebleedgen-a-wireless-capsule-endoscopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a medically annotated WCE dataset for training and evaluation of automatic classification, detection, and segmentation of bleeding and non-bleeding frames is currently lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wcebleedgen-a-wireless-capsule-endoscopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning Factual Knowledge in Structured Data with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-factual-knowledge-in-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This benchmark allows us to investigate the capability of LLMs across five factual tasks derived from the unique characteristics of structural facts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-factual-knowledge-in-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Text Generation for Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-generation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper systematically reviews the latest advancements in CTG for LLMs, offering a comprehensive definition of its core concepts and clarifying the requirements for control conditions and text quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-generation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Autoregressive Image Generation with Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-autoregressive-image-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the ImageNet1K 256*256 benchmark, our best AiM model achieves a FID of 2. 21, surpassing all existing AR models of comparable parameter counts and demonstrating significant competitiveness against diffusion models, with 2 to 10 times faster inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-autoregressive-image-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Embodied Learning for Object-Centric Robotic Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-embodied-learning-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodied learning for object-centric robotic manipulation is a rapidly developing and challenging area in embodied AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-embodied-learning-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critique-out-Loud Reward Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critique-out-loud-reward-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable reward models to reason explicitly about the quality of a response, we introduce Critique-out-Loud (CLoud) reward models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critique-out-loud-reward-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient Wisdom, Modern Tools: Exploring Retrieval-Augmented LLMs for Ancient Indian Philosophy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ancient-wisdom-modern-tools-exploring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop and benchmark a RAG model against a standard, non-RAG LLM, focusing on transcription, retrieval, and generation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ancient-wisdom-modern-tools-exploring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does It Look Sequential? An Analysis of Datasets for Evaluation of Sequential Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-it-look-sequential-an-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such systems aim to use the order of interactions in a user's history to predict future interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-it-look-sequential-an-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classification of Mitral Regurgitation from Cardiac Cine MRI using Clinically-Interpretable Morphological Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-mitral-regurgitation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new approach to identify MR which automatically extracts 4-dimensional (3D + Time) morphological features from the reconstructed mitral annulus (MA) using Cine long-axis (LAX) views MRI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-mitral-regurgitation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding Ordinality to Binary Loss Function for Improving Solar Flare Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-ordinality-to-binary-loss-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel loss function aimed at optimizing the binary flare prediction problem by embedding the intrinsic ordinal flare characteristics into the binary cross-entropy (BCE) loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-ordinality-to-binary-loss-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFID based Health Adherence Medicine Case Using Fair Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfid-based-health-adherence-medicine-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the effectiveness and personalization of the Smart Pill Case, we propose integrating federated learning into the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rfid-based-health-adherence-medicine-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Out-of-Distribution Data Handling and Corruption Resistance via Modern Hopfield Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-out-of-distribution-data-handling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we investigate the capability of MHN to converge to the original non-corrupted data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-out-of-distribution-data-handling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Deep Dissipative Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-dissipative-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By analytically proving the general solution to the nonlinear Kalman-Yakubovich-Popov (KYP) lemma, which is the necessary and sufficient condition for dissipativity, we propose a differentiable projection that transforms any dynamics represented by neural networks into dissipative ones and a learning method for the transformed dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-dissipative-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Adversarial Suffix Optimization Without Affirmative Phrases: Efficient Black-box Jailbreaking via LLM as Optimizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-adversarial-suffix-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, ECLIPSE is on par with template-based methods in ASR while offering superior attack efficiency, reducing the average attack overhead by 83%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-adversarial-suffix-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSTran: Joint Geometric and Semantic Coherence for Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gstran-joint-geometric-and-semantic-coherence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed network mainly consists of two principal components: a local geometric transformer and a global semantic transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gstran-joint-geometric-and-semantic-coherence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Interpretable Decision Tree Policies for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-interpretable-decision-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically show that DTPO is a competitive algorithm compared to imitation learning algorithms for optimizing decision tree policies in reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-interpretable-decision-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniFashion: A Unified Vision-Language Model for Multimodal Fashion Retrieval and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifashion-a-unified-vision-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present UniFashion, a unified framework that simultaneously tackles the challenges of multimodal generation and retrieval tasks within the fashion domain, integrating image generation with retrieval tasks and text generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifashion-a-unified-vision-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiating Choices via Commonality for Multiple-Choice Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiating-choices-via-commonality-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model captures token-level attention of each choice to the question, and separates tokens of the question attended to by all the choices (i. e., commonalities) from those by individual choices (i. e., nuances).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiating-choices-via-commonality-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHOTA: A Higher Order Accuracy Metric for Cell Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chota-a-higher-order-accuracy-metric-for-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that CHOTA is sensitive to all tracking errors and gives a good indication of the biologically relevant capability of a method to reconstruct the full lineage of cells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chota-a-higher-order-accuracy-metric-for-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NuSegDG: Integration of Heterogeneous Space and Gaussian Kernel for Domain-Generalized Nuclei Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusegdg-integration-of-heterogeneous-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the labor-intensive requirement of manual prompts, we introduce a Gaussian-Kernel Prompt Encoder (GKP-Encoder) to generate density maps driven by a single point, which guides segmentation predictions by mixing position prompts and semantic prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusegdg-integration-of-heterogeneous-space</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
