<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 21:09:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Vanishing Activations in Deep CapsNets Using Channel Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-vanishing-activations-in-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the backbone network and capsule layers are pruned with different pruning ratios to reduce the number of inactive capsules and achieve better model accuracy than the unpruned models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-vanishing-activations-in-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Generative AI for De Novo Design of Co-Crystals with Enhanced Tabletability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-generative-ai-for-de-novo-design-of-co</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Co-crystallization is an accessible way to control physicochemical characteristics of organic crystals, which finds many biomedical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-generative-ai-for-de-novo-design-of-co</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMScan: Causal Scan for LLM Misbehavior Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmscan-causal-scan-for-llm-misbehavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the success of Large Language Models (LLMs) across various fields, their potential to generate untruthful, biased and harmful responses poses significant risks, particularly in critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmscan-causal-scan-for-llm-misbehavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven Coreference-based Ontology Building</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-coreference-based-ontology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While coreference resolution is traditionally used as a component in individual document understanding, in this work we take a more global view and explore what can we learn about a domain from the set of all document-level coreference relations that are present in a large corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-coreference-based-ontology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SELA: Tree-Search Enhanced LLM Agents for Automated Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sela-tree-search-enhanced-llm-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Machine Learning (AutoML) approaches encompass traditional methods that optimize fixed pipelines for model selection and ensembling, as well as newer LLM-based frameworks that autonomously build pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sela-tree-search-enhanced-llm-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing and improving reliability of neighbor embedding methods: a map-continuity perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-and-improving-reliability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LOO-map extends the embedding over a discrete set of input points to the entire input space, enabling a systematic assessment of map continuity, and thus the reliability of the visualizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-and-improving-reliability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaChimp: Tracking and Behavior Recognition of Chimpanzees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphachimp-tracking-and-behavior-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding non-human primate behavior is crucial for improving animal welfare, modeling social behavior, and gaining insights into both distinctly human and shared behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphachimp-tracking-and-behavior-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dhoroni: Exploring Bengali Climate Change and Environmental Views with a Multi-Perspective News Dataset and Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhoroni-exploring-bengali-climate-change-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Climate change poses critical challenges globally, disproportionately affecting low-income countries that often lack resources and linguistic representation on the international stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhoroni-exploring-bengali-climate-change-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoPS: Empowering LLM Agents with Provable Cross-Task Experience Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cops-empowering-llm-agents-with-provable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In detail, CoPS leverages agents' experiences on previous tasks, selecting distribution-matched experiences via a provable pessimism-based strategy to maximize utility while minimizing risks from distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cops-empowering-llm-agents-with-provable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustworthy Alignment of Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Models via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trustworthy-alignment-of-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trustworthiness is an essential prerequisite for the real-world application of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trustworthy-alignment-of-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPVSoAP3D: A Second-order Average Pooling Approach to enhance 3D Place Recognition in Horticultural Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spvsoap3d-a-second-order-average-pooling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address this challenge by introducing SPVSoAP3D, a novel modeling approach that combines a voxel-based feature extraction network with an aggregation technique based on a second-order average pooling operator, complemented by a descriptor enhancement stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spvsoap3d-a-second-order-average-pooling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-LLM Hybrid Text Answer Aggregation for Crowd Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-llm-hybrid-text-answer-aggregation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the scenario of aggregation on text answers and the role of LLMs as aggregators are not yet well-studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-llm-hybrid-text-answer-aggregation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontiers in Intelligent Colonoscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frontiers-in-intelligent-colonoscopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Colonoscopy is currently one of the most sensitive screening methods for colorectal cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frontiers-in-intelligent-colonoscopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Point Cloud Upsampling and Cleaning with Octree-based CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-point-cloud-upsampling-and-cleaning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recovering dense and uniformly distributed point clouds from sparse or noisy data remains a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-point-cloud-upsampling-and-cleaning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correct after Answer: Enhancing Multi-Span Question Answering with Post-Processing Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correct-after-answer-enhancing-multi-span</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Span Question Answering (MSQA) requires models to extract one or multiple answer spans from a given context to answer a question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correct-after-answer-enhancing-multi-span</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Multi-Scene Fire and Smoke Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multi-scene-fire-and-smoke</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current irregularities in existing public Fire and Smoke Detection (FSD) datasets have become a bottleneck in the advancement of FSD technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multi-scene-fire-and-smoke</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniPLM: Knowledge Distillation for Pre-Training Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miniplm-knowledge-distillation-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For effectiveness, MiniPLM leverages the differences between large and small LMs to enhance the difficulty and diversity of the training data, helping student LMs acquire versatile and sophisticated knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miniplm-knowledge-distillation-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISImed: A Framework for Self-Supervised Learning using Intrinsic Spatial Information in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isimed-a-framework-for-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper demonstrates that spatial information can be used to learn interpretable representations in medical images using Self-Supervised Learning (SSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isimed-a-framework-for-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Science Out of Its Ivory Tower: Improving Accessibility with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/science-out-of-its-ivory-tower-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A vast amount of scholarly work is published daily, yet much of it remains inaccessible to the general public due to dense jargon and complex language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/science-out-of-its-ivory-tower-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdenBAT: Disentangled Representation Learning for Identity-Preserved Brain Age Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idenbat-disentangled-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain age transformation aims to convert reference brain images into synthesized images that accurately reflect the age-specific features of a target age group.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idenbat-disentangled-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Clustering for Conditional Diffusion in Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-clustering-for-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses this gap by introducing TreeDiffusion, a deep generative model that conditions Diffusion Models on hierarchical clusters to obtain high-quality, cluster-specific generations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-clustering-for-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A class of modular and flexible covariate-based covariance functions for nonstationary spatial modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-class-of-modular-and-flexible-covariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The assumptions of stationarity and isotropy often stated over spatial processes have not aged well during the last two decades, partly explained by the combination of computational developments and the increasing availability of high-resolution spatial data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-class-of-modular-and-flexible-covariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNAHLM -- DNA sequence and Human Language mixed large language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnahlm-dna-sequence-and-human-language-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are already many DNA large language models, but most of them still follow traditional uses, such as extracting sequence features for classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnahlm-dna-sequence-and-human-language-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Possibilities of AI-Powered Legal Assistance in Bangladesh through Large Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-possibilities-of-ai-powered-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research seeks to develop a specialized Large Language Model (LLM) to assist in the Bangladeshi legal system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-possibilities-of-ai-powered-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-guided Search for Efficient Program Repair with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-search-for-efficient-program</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike conventional methods that rely on beam search, FLAMES utilizes greedy decoding to enhance memory efficiency while steering the search to more potentially good repair candidates via a semantic-guided best-first search algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-guided-search-for-efficient-program</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Graph Sharpness-Aware Minimization for Enhancing and Accelerating Few-Shot Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-graph-sharpness-aware-minimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The standard SAM approach, however, consists of two forward-backward steps in each training iteration, doubling the computational cost compared to the base optimizer (e. g., Adam).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-graph-sharpness-aware-minimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement learning on structure-conditioned categorical diffusion for protein inverse folding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-on-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we present RL-DIF, a categorical diffusion model for inverse folding that is pre-trained on sequence recovery and tuned via reinforcement learning on structural consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-on-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xLSTM-Mixer: Multivariate Time Series Forecasting by Mixing via Scalar Memories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xlstm-mixer-multivariate-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series data is prevalent across numerous fields, necessitating the development of robust and accurate forecasting models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xlstm-mixer-multivariate-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttriPrompter: Auto-Prompting with Attribute Semantics for Zero-shot Nuclei Detection via Visual-Language Pre-trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attriprompter-auto-prompting-with-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, this work highlights the astonishing potential of VLPMs pre-trained on natural image-text pairs for downstream tasks in the medical field as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attriprompter-auto-prompting-with-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyramidDrop: Accelerating Your Large Vision-Language Models via Pyramid Visual Redundancy Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramiddrop-accelerating-your-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose PyramidDrop, a visual redundancy reduction strategy for LVLMs to boost their efficiency in both training and inference with neglectable performance loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramiddrop-accelerating-your-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just In Time Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-in-time-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precise energy load forecasting in residential households is crucial for mitigating carbon emissions and enhancing energy efficiency; indeed, accurate forecasting enables utility companies and policymakers, who advocate sustainable energy practices, to optimize resource utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-in-time-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Frameworks for Conditional Two-Sample Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-frameworks-for-conditional-two-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our first framework allows us to convert any conditional independence test into a conditional two-sample test in a black-box manner, while preserving the asymptotic properties of the original conditional independence test.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-frameworks-for-conditional-two-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Language Models via Self-Steering Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to automated alignment lies in providing learnable and accurate preference signals for preference learning without human annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math Neurosurgery: Isolating Language Models' Math Reasoning Abilities Using Only Forward Passes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/math-neurosurgery-isolating-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MathNeuro builds on existing work by using weights and activations to calculate parameter importance, but isolates math-specific parameters by removing those important for general language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/math-neurosurgery-isolating-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Effectiveness of Attack-Agnostic Features for Morphing Attack Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-effectiveness-of-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Morphing attacks have diversified significantly over the past years, with new methods based on generative adversarial networks (GANs) and diffusion models posing substantial threats to face recognition systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-effectiveness-of-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layered LA-MAPF: a decomposition of large agent MAPF instance to accelerate solving without compromising solvability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layered-la-mapf-a-decomposition-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When considering the shape and size of agents in MAPF, the computational complexity increases significantly as the number of agents grows, primarily due to the increased overhead in conflict detection between geometric agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layered-la-mapf-a-decomposition-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KANICE: Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks with Interactive Convolutional Elements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kanice-kolmogorov-arnold-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work contributes to research in adaptive neural networks, integrates mathematical theorems into deep learning architectures, and explores the trade-offs between model complexity and performance, advancing computer vision and pattern recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kanice-kolmogorov-arnold-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Two-Player Performance Through Single-Player Knowledge Transfer: An Empirical Study on Atari 2600 Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-two-player-performance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Playing two-player games using reinforcement learning and self-play can be challenging due to the complexity of two-player environments and the possible instability in the training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-two-player-performance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAPILLON: PrivAcy Preservation from Internet-based and Local Language MOdel ENsembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/papillon-privacy-preservation-from-internet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While open-source models, hosted locally on the user's machine, alleviate some concerns, models that users can host locally are often less capable than proprietary frontier models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/papillon-privacy-preservation-from-internet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLDR-LLM: Large Language Model from Power Law Decoder Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pldr-llm-large-language-model-from-power-law</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Large Language Model from Power Law Decoder Representations (PLDR-LLM), a language model that leverages non-linear and linear transformations through Power Law Graph Attention mechanism to generate well-defined deductive and inductive outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pldr-llm-large-language-model-from-power-law</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Spinal MRI Labelling from Reports Using a Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-spinal-mri-labelling-from-reports</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general pipeline to automate the extraction of labels from radiology reports using large language models, which we validate on spinal MRI reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-spinal-mri-labelling-from-reports</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiNeS: Post-training Layer Scaling Prevents Forgetting and Enhances Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lines-post-training-layer-scaling-prevents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained models exhibit impressive zero-shot performance across diverse tasks, but fine-tuning often leads to catastrophic forgetting, where improvements on a target domain degrade generalization on other tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lines-post-training-layer-scaling-prevents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracing the Development of the Virtual Particle Concept Using Semantic Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracing-the-development-of-the-virtual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the SCD metrics align well with qualitative research insights in the history and philosophy of science, as well as with the results obtained from Dependency Parsing to determine the frequency and connotations of the term "virtual."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracing-the-development-of-the-virtual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Memory Barrier: Near Infinite Batch Size Scaling for Contrastive Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-memory-barrier-near-infinite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive loss is a powerful approach for representation learning, where larger batch sizes enhance performance by providing more negative samples to better distinguish between similar and dissimilar data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-memory-barrier-near-infinite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Causal Reasoning in Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-causal-reasoning-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we provide a comprehensive review of research aimed at enhancing LLMs for causal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-causal-reasoning-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emphasizing Discriminative Features for Dataset Distillation in Complex Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emphasizing-discriminative-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hopefully, more researchers will be inspired and encouraged to improve the practicality and efficacy of DD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emphasizing-discriminative-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample-efficient Bayesian Optimisation Using Known Invariances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-bayesian-optimisation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We derive a bound on the maximum information gain of these invariant kernels, and provide novel upper and lower bounds on the number of observations required for invariance-aware BO algorithms to achieve $\epsilon$-optimality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-efficient-bayesian-optimisation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETHIC: Evaluating Large Language Models on Long-Context Tasks with High Information Coverage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ethic-evaluating-large-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To thoroughly examine the effectiveness of existing benchmarks, we introduce a new metric called information coverage (IC), which quantifies the proportion of the input context necessary for answering queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ethic-evaluating-large-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RKadiyala at SemEval-2024 Task 8: Black-Box Word-Level Text Boundary Detection in Partially Machine Generated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rkadiyala-at-semeval-2024-task-8-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing models and proprietary systems focus on identifying whether given text is entirely human written or entirely machine generated, only a few systems provide insights at sentence or paragraph level at likelihood of being machine generated at a non reliable accuracy level, working well only for a set of domains and generators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rkadiyala-at-semeval-2024-task-8-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAP: Concave Linear APproximation for Quadratic Graph Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clap-concave-linear-approximation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel linear model and solver designed to accelerate the computation of graph matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clap-concave-linear-approximation-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
