<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 21:06:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Neural Net with Dynamic Neuron Addition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-net-with-dynamic-neuron-addition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X as the input matrix with dimensions(m, n), where m is the number of samples (batch size), and n is the number of input features, W as the weight matrix for the layer with dimensions (n, k), where k is the number of neurons in the layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-net-with-dynamic-neuron-addition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepACO: Neural-enhanced Ant Systems for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepaco-neural-enhanced-ant-systems-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a Neural Combinatorial Optimization method, DeepACO performs better than or on par with problem-specific methods on canonical routing problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepaco-neural-enhanced-ant-systems-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHuman: Harnessing Multi-Source Data for High-Resolution Human Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitedhuman-harnessing-multi-source-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A holistic human dataset inevitably has insufficient and low-resolution information on local parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitedhuman-harnessing-multi-source-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINCERE: Supervised Information Noise-Contrastive Estimation REvisited</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sincere-supervised-information-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SINCERE is a theoretically justified solution for a supervised extension of InfoNCE that never causes images from the same class to repel one another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sincere-supervised-information-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReMasker: Imputing Tabular Data with Masked Autoencoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remasker-imputing-tabular-data-with-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ReMasker, a new method of imputing missing values in tabular data by extending the masked autoencoding framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remasker-imputing-tabular-data-with-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AsymFormer: Asymmetrical Cross-Modal Representation Learning for Mobile Platform Real-Time RGB-D Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymformer-asymmetrical-cross-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose AsymFormer, a novel network for real-time RGB-D semantic segmentation, which targets the minimization of superfluous parameters by optimizing the distribution of computational resources and introduces an asymmetrical backbone to allow for the effective fusion of multimodal features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymformer-asymmetrical-cross-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiModN- Multimodal, Multi-Task, Interpretable Modular Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodn-multimodal-multi-task-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting multiple real-world tasks in a single model often requires a particularly diverse feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodn-multimodal-multi-task-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-Bench: A Benchmark for General-Purpose Foundation Models on Low-level Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-bench-a-benchmark-for-general-purpose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we present Q-Bench, a holistic benchmark crafted to systematically evaluate potential abilities of MLLMs on three realms: low-level visual perception, low-level visual description, and overall visual quality assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-bench-a-benchmark-for-general-purpose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCF-Crime Annotation: A Benchmark for Surveillance Video-and-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucf-crime-annotation-a-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we benchmark the state-of-the-art models of multiple multimodal tasks on this newly created dataset, including temporal sentence grounding in videos, video captioning, and dense video captioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucf-crime-annotation-a-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provable Training for Graph Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-training-for-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose the PrOvable Training (POT) for GCL, which regularizes the training of GCL to encode node embeddings that follows the GCL principle better.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-training-for-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projected Randomized Smoothing for Certified Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projected-randomized-smoothing-for-certified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Randomized smoothing is the current state-of-the-art method for producing provably robust classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projected-randomized-smoothing-for-certified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IEBins: Iterative Elastic Bins for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iebins-iterative-elastic-bins-for-monocular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the possible error accumulation during the iterative process, we utilize a novel elastic target bin to replace the original target bin, the width of which is adjusted elastically based on the depth uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iebins-iterative-elastic-bins-for-monocular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting and Grounding Multi-Modal Media Manipulation and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-grounding-multi-modal-media-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HAMMER performs 1) manipulation-aware contrastive learning between two uni-modal encoders as shallow manipulation reasoning, and 2) modality-aware cross-attention by multi-modal aggregator as deep manipulation reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-grounding-multi-modal-media-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VidChapters-7M: Video Chapters at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidchapters-7m-video-chapters-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we present VidChapters-7M, a dataset of 817K user-chaptered videos including 7M chapters in total.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidchapters-7m-video-chapters-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinGCN: Structural Linearized Graph Convolutional Network for Homomorphically Encrypted Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lingcn-structural-linearized-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, LinGCN achieves a 14. 2x latency speedup relative to CryptoGCN, while preserving an inference accuracy of 75% and notably reducing multiplication depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lingcn-structural-linearized-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeCAM: Exploiting the Heterogeneity of Class Distributions in Exemplar-Free Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecam-exploiting-the-heterogeneity-of-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, when learning from non-stationary data, we observe that the Euclidean metric is suboptimal and that feature distributions are heterogeneous.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecam-exploiting-the-heterogeneity-of-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitstream-Corrupted Video Recovery: A Novel Benchmark Dataset and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitstream-corrupted-video-recovery-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The past decade has witnessed great strides in video recovery by specialist technologies, like video inpainting, completion, and error concealment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitstream-corrupted-video-recovery-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoIR: Box-Supervised Instance Representation for Multi-Person Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boir-box-supervised-instance-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our new instance embedding loss provides a learning signal on the entire area of the image with bounding box annotations, achieving globally consistent and disentangled instance representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boir-box-supervised-instance-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio classification with Dilated Convolution with Learnable Spacings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-classification-with-dilated-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dilated convolution with learnable spacings (DCLS) is a recent convolution method in which the positions of the kernel elements are learned throughout training by backpropagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-classification-with-dilated-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Impact of Serverless Computing on Peer To Peer Training Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-impact-of-serverless-computing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel architecture that combines serverless computing with P2P networks for distributed training and present a method for efficient parallel gradient computation under resource constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-impact-of-serverless-computing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Semantic Image Editing with Style Codes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-semantic-image-editing-with-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic image editing requires inpainting pixels following a semantic map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-semantic-image-editing-with-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniEvent: A Comprehensive, Fair, and Easy-to-Use Toolkit for Event Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnievent-a-comprehensive-fair-and-easy-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event understanding aims at understanding the content and relationship of events within texts, which covers multiple complicated information extraction tasks: event detection, event argument extraction, and event relation extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnievent-a-comprehensive-fair-and-easy-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised correspondence with combined geometric learning and imaging for radiotherapy applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-correspondence-with-combined</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then extended the original model to incorporate imaging information using two approaches: 1) extracting features directly from image patches, and 2) including the mean square error between patches as part of the loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-correspondence-with-combined</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perception-and-Energy-aware Motion Planning for UAV using Learning-based Model under Heteroscedastic Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-and-energy-aware-motion-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Global navigation satellite systems (GNSS) denied environments/conditions require unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs) to energy-efficiently and reliably fly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-and-energy-aware-motion-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing data efficiency in reinforcement learning: a novel imagination mechanism based on mesh information propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-data-efficiency-in-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms face the challenge of limited data efficiency, particularly when dealing with high-dimensional state spaces and large-scale problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-data-efficiency-in-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linked shrinkage to improve estimation of interaction effects in regression models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-shrinkage-to-improve-estimation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically show that borrowing strength between the amount of shrinkage for main effects and their interactions can strongly improve estimation of the regression coefficients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-shrinkage-to-improve-estimation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards End-User Development for IoT: A Case Study on Semantic Parsing of Cooking Recipes for Programming Kitchen Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-user-development-for-iot-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic parsing of user-generated instructional text, in the way of enabling end-users to program the Internet of Things (IoT), is an underexplored area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-user-development-for-iot-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRiSM: Enhancing Low-Resource Document-Level Relation Extraction with Relation-Aware Score Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-enhancing-low-resource-document-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document-level relation extraction (DocRE) aims to extract relations of all entity pairs in a document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-enhancing-low-resource-document-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Recurrent Grouping Attention Network for Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-recurrent-grouping-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design forward feature extraction module and backward feature extraction module to collect temporal information between consecutive frames from two directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-recurrent-grouping-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILNet: Low-level Matters for Salient Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ilnet-low-level-matters-for-salient-infrared</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the dearth of high-level semantic information, small infrared target features are weakened in the deep layers of the CNN, which underachieves the CNN's representation ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ilnet-low-level-matters-for-salient-infrared</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Reinforcement Learning for Image-to-Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-for-image-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key feature in the RL-I2IT framework is to decompose a monolithic learning process into small steps with a lightweight model to progressively transform a source image successively to a target image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-for-image-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Cooperation in Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning via Model-based Rollout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-cooperation-in-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we propose a one-step rollout-based planning to further facilitate inter-level cooperation, where the higher-level Q-function is used to guide the lower-level policy by estimating the value of future states so that global task information is transmitted downwards to avoid local pitfalls.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-cooperation-in-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Relations Classification using Imbalanced Predictions Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-relations-classification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this work is the first that recognizes the imbalanced predictions within the relation classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-relations-classification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal-DFQ: Causality Guided Data-free Network Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-dfq-causality-guided-data-free-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the causal understanding, we propose the Causality-guided Data-free Network Quantization method, Causal-DFQ, to eliminate the reliance on data via approaching an equilibrium of causality-driven intervened distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-dfq-causality-guided-data-free-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptation of the super resolution SOTA for Art Restoration in camera capture images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-the-super-resolution-sota-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the domain of art restoration, developing a computer vision model capable of effectively restoring deteriorated images of art pieces was difficult, but now we have a good computer vision state-of-art.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-the-super-resolution-sota-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerabilities in Video Quality Assessment Models: The Challenge of Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vulnerabilities-in-video-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, considering both the attack effect on quality score and the visual quality of adversarial video, the attack problem is formulated as misleading the estimated quality score under the constraint of just-noticeable difference (JND).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vulnerabilities-in-video-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skill Check: Some Considerations on the Evaluation of Gamemastering Models for Role-playing Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-check-some-considerations-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In role-playing games a Game Master (GM) is the player in charge of the game, who must design the challenges the players face and narrate the outcomes of their actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-check-some-considerations-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIS: Practical robust invertible network for image steganography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pris-practical-robust-invertible-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the existing image steganography methods have low hiding robustness when the container images affected by distortion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pris-practical-robust-invertible-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanopticNDT: Efficient and Robust Panoptic Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panopticndt-efficient-and-robust-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the application scenarios of mobile robots are getting more complex and challenging, scene understanding becomes increasingly crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panopticndt-efficient-and-robust-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speeding-up Evolutionary Algorithms to solve Black-Box Optimization Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speeding-up-evolutionary-algorithms-to-solve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these algorithms require a large number of evaluations to provide a quality solution, which might be computationally expensive when the evaluation cost is high.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speeding-up-evolutionary-algorithms-to-solve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOBER: Coherent Non-autoregressive Video Generation via GLOBal Guided Video DecodER</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glober-coherent-non-autoregressive-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a video auto-encoder, where a video encoder encodes videos into global features, and a video decoder, built on a diffusion model, decodes the global features and synthesizes video frames in a non-autoregressive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glober-coherent-non-autoregressive-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real3D-AD: A Dataset of Point Cloud Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real3d-ad-a-dataset-of-point-cloud-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-precision point cloud anomaly detection is the gold standard for identifying the defects of advancing machining and precision manufacturing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real3d-ad-a-dataset-of-point-cloud-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-Separation for Causal Self-Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-separation-for-causal-self-explanation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of attempting to rectify the issues of the MMI criterion, we propose a novel criterion to uncover the causal rationale, termed the Minimum Conditional Dependence (MCD) criterion, which is grounded on our finding that the non-causal features and the target label are \emph{d-separated} by the causal rationale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-separation-for-causal-self-explanation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexical Squad@Multimodal Hate Speech Event Detection 2023: Multimodal Hate Speech Detection using Fused Ensemble Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexical-squad-multimodal-hate-speech-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a surge in the usage of social media postings to express opinions, emotions, and ideologies, there has been a significant shift towards the calibration of social media as a rapid medium of conveying viewpoints and outlooks over the globe.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexical-squad-multimodal-hate-speech-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP-MVS: Multi-Scale Windows PatchMatch and Planar Prior Multi-View Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mp-mvs-multi-scale-windows-patchmatch-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design a multi-scale windows PatchMatch (mPM) to obtain reliable depth of untextured areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mp-mvs-multi-scale-windows-patchmatch-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WS-YOLO: Weakly Supervised Yolo Network for Surgical Tool Localization in Endoscopic Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ws-yolo-weakly-supervised-yolo-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being able to automatically detect and track surgical instruments in endoscopic video recordings would allow for many useful applications that could transform different aspects of surgery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ws-yolo-weakly-supervised-yolo-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mirror-Unet architecture for PET/CT lesion segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mirror-unet-architecture-for-pet-ct-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic lesion detection and segmentation from [${}^{18}$F]FDG PET/CT scans is a challenging task, due to the diversity of shapes, sizes, FDG uptake and location they may present, besides the fact that physiological uptake is also present on healthy tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mirror-unet-architecture-for-pet-ct-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Timeline Modeling For News Story Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-timeline-modeling-for-news-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We anticipate that this exploratory work will pave the way for further research in video timeline modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-timeline-modeling-for-news-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Amodal Video Segmentation from Learning Supervised Signals with Object-centric Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-amodal-video-segmentation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a multi-view fusion layer based temporal module which is equipped with a set of object slots and interacts with features from different views by attention mechanism to fulfill sufficient object representation completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-amodal-video-segmentation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ML Algorithm Synthesizing Domain Knowledge for Fungal Spores Concentration Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ml-algorithm-synthesizing-domain-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pulp and paper manufacturing industry requires precise quality control to ensure pure, contaminant-free end products suitable for various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ml-algorithm-synthesizing-domain-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
