<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 09:18:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SCoralDet: Efficient real-time underwater soft coral detection with YOLO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoraldet-efficient-real-time-underwater-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose SCoralDet, a soft coral detection model based on the YOLO architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoraldet-efficient-real-time-underwater-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Portfolio Optimization using GOPALS: Geospatial Optimization and Portfolio Allocation using Landscape Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-portfolio-optimization-using-gopals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces GOPALS: Geospatial Optimization and Portfolio Allocation using Landscape Segmentation, a simulation-based portfolio optimization framework designed to overcome these limitations and improve the robustness of the portfolio optimization process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-portfolio-optimization-using-gopals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-VL2: Mixture-of-Experts Vision-Language Models for Advanced Multimodal Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl2-mixture-of-experts-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DeepSeek-VL2, an advanced series of large Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) Vision-Language Models that significantly improves upon its predecessor, DeepSeek-VL, through two key major upgrades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl2-mixture-of-experts-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Action Models: From Inception to Implementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-action-models-from-inception-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As AI continues to advance, there is a growing demand for systems that go beyond language-based assistance and move toward intelligent agents capable of performing real-world actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-action-models-from-inception-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Identity Defenses against Malicious Personalization of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-identity-defenses-against-malicious</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized diffusion models, capable of synthesizing highly realistic images based on a few reference portraits, pose substantial social, ethical, and legal risks by enabling identity replication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-identity-defenses-against-malicious</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Multiple Choice Have a Future in the Age of Generative AI? A Posttest-only RCT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-multiple-choice-have-a-future-in-the-age</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a posttest-only randomized control design, we compare the performance of 234 tutors (790 lesson completions) across three conditions: MCQ only, open response only, and a combination of both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-multiple-choice-have-a-future-in-the-age</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPatent: A Multi-Agent Framework for Automatic Patent Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopatent-a-multi-agent-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) continue to advance, the field of patent processing has garnered increased attention within the natural language processing community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopatent-a-multi-agent-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-IIN: Semi-supervised Intra-inter modal Interaction Learning Network for Multimodal Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-iin-semi-supervised-intra-inter-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite multimodal sentiment analysis being a fertile research ground that merits further investigation, current approaches take up high annotation cost and suffer from label ambiguity, non-amicable to high-quality labeled data acquisition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-iin-semi-supervised-intra-inter-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaLoRAify: Calorie Estimation with Visual-Text Pairing and LoRA-Driven Visual Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caloraify-calorie-estimation-with-visual-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The obesity phenomenon, known as the heavy issue, is a leading cause of preventable chronic diseases worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caloraify-calorie-estimation-with-visual-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Integration with Fusion Searchlight: Classifying Brain States from Resting-state fMRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-integration-with-fusion-searchlight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our study, we present a fusion searchlight (FuSL) framework to combine the complementary information contained in different resting-state fMRI metrics and demonstrate how this can improve the decoding of brain states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-integration-with-fusion-searchlight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FM2S: Self-Supervised Fluorescence Microscopy Denoising With Single Noisy Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fm2s-self-supervised-fluorescence-microscopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fluorescence microscopy has significantly advanced biological research by visualizing detailed cellular structures and biological processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fm2s-self-supervised-fluorescence-microscopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Periodic Activation for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-periodic-activation-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the lack of research on activation functions for neural network models in time series tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-periodic-activation-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniMed-CLIP: Towards a Unified Image-Text Pretraining Paradigm for Diverse Medical Imaging Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimed-clip-towards-a-unified-image-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UniMed is developed using a data-collection framework that leverages Large Language Models (LLMs) to transform modality-specific classification datasets into image-text formats while incorporating existing image-text data from the medical domain, facilitating scalable VLM pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimed-clip-towards-a-unified-image-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Byte Latent Transformer: Patches Scale Better Than Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byte-latent-transformer-patches-scale-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Byte Latent Transformer (BLT), a new byte-level LLM architecture that, for the first time, matches tokenization-based LLM performance at scale with significant improvements in inference efficiency and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byte-latent-transformer-patches-scale-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RETQA: A Large-Scale Open-Domain Tabular Question Answering Dataset for Real Estate Sector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retqa-a-large-scale-open-domain-tabular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges, we propose the SLUTQA framework, which integrates large language models with spoken language understanding tasks to enhance retrieval and answering accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retqa-a-large-scale-open-domain-tabular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sims: An Interactive Tool for Geospatial Matching and Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sims-an-interactive-tool-for-geospatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acquiring, processing, and visualizing geospatial data requires significant computing resources, especially for large spatio-temporal domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sims-an-interactive-tool-for-geospatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROUTE: Robust Multitask Tuning and Collaboration for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/route-robust-multitask-tuning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a novel RObust mUltitask Tuning and collaboration mEthod (ROUTE) to improve the comprehensive capabilities of open-source LLMs for Text2SQL, thereby providing a more practical solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/route-robust-multitask-tuning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Multi-modal Spatiotemporal Expert for Zero-shot Action Recognition with CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-a-multi-modal-spatiotemporal-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot action recognition (ZSAR) requires collaborative multi-modal spatiotemporal understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-a-multi-modal-spatiotemporal-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt2Perturb (P2P): Text-Guided Diffusion-Based Adversarial Attacks on Breast Ultrasound Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2perturb-p2p-text-guided-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, diffusion-based attacks require pre-trained models, demanding substantial data when these models are unavailable, limiting practical use in data-scarce scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt2perturb-p2p-text-guided-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraSP: Simple yet Effective Graph Similarity Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grasp-simple-yet-effective-graph-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In GSC, graph edit distance (GED) and maximum common subgraph (MCS) are two important similarity metrics, both of which are NP-hard to compute.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grasp-simple-yet-effective-graph-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Pruning Can Do More: A Comprehensive Data Pruning Approach for Object Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-pruning-can-do-more-a-comprehensive-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous studies have demonstrated that not each sample in a dataset is of equal importance during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-pruning-can-do-more-a-comprehensive-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing the Reasoning Capabilities of Small Language Models via Solution Guidance Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-reasoning-capabilities-of-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, this paper introduce a new reasoning strategy Solution Guidance (SG) and a plug-and-play training paradigm Solution-Guidance Fine-Tuning (SGFT) for enhancing the reasoning capabilities of small language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-reasoning-capabilities-of-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaussianAD: Gaussian-Centric End-to-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianad-gaussian-centric-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We initialize the scene with uniform 3D Gaussians and use surrounding-view images to progressively refine them to obtain the 3D Gaussian scene representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianad-gaussian-centric-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Guidance Mechanisms for Discrete Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-guidance-mechanisms-for-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models for continuous data gained widespread adoption owing to their high quality generation and control mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-guidance-mechanisms-for-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Linguistic Diversity of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-linguistic-diversity-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development and evaluation of Large Language Models (LLMs) has primarily focused on their task-solving capabilities, with recent models even surpassing human performance in some areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-linguistic-diversity-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Head Encoding for Extreme Label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-encoding-for-extreme-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the training process, MHE decomposes extreme labels into the product of multiple short local labels, with each head trained on these local labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-encoding-for-extreme-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Visually Grounded Domain Ontologies via Embodied Conversation and Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visually-grounded-domain-ontologies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we offer a learning framework in which the agent's knowledge gaps are overcome through corrective feedback from a teacher whenever the agent explains its (incorrect) predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visually-grounded-domain-ontologies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs Convert Graphs to Text-Attributed Graphs?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-convert-graphs-to-text-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, recent approaches introduce text-attributed graphs, where each node is associated with a textual description, enabling the use of a shared textual encoder to project nodes from different graphs into a unified feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-convert-graphs-to-text-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Node One Model: Featuring the Missing-Half for Graph Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-node-one-model-featuring-the-missing-half</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing graph clustering methods primarily focus on exploiting topological structure, often neglecting the ``missing-half" node feature information, especially how these features can enhance clustering performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-node-one-model-featuring-the-missing-half</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaussianWorld: Gaussian World Model for Streaming 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianworld-gaussian-world-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D occupancy prediction is important for autonomous driving due to its comprehensive perception of the surroundings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussianworld-gaussian-world-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MST-R: Multi-Stage Tuning for Retrieval Systems and Metric Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mst-r-multi-stage-tuning-for-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regulatory documents are rich in nuanced terminology and specialized semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mst-r-multi-stage-tuning-for-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Multimodal Large Language Models Complex Reason via Similarity Computation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multimodal-large-language-models-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models have experienced rapid growth, and numerous different models have emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multimodal-large-language-models-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Named Entity Disambiguation for Low Resource Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-named-entity-disambiguation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of natural language processing and information retrieval, the need for robust and domain-specific entity linking algorithms has become increasingly apparent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-named-entity-disambiguation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RemDet: Rethinking Efficient Model Design for UAV Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remdet-rethinking-efficient-model-design-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are as follows: 1) Rethinking the challenges of existing detectors for small and dense UAV images, and proposing information loss as a design guideline for efficient models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remdet-rethinking-efficient-model-design-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Langevin Monte Carlo Beyond Lipschitz Gradient Continuity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-monte-carlo-beyond-lipschitz</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a significant advancement in the field of Langevin Monte Carlo (LMC) methods by introducing the Inexact Proximal Langevin Algorithm (IPLA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-monte-carlo-beyond-lipschitz</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reversing the Damage: A QP-Aware Transformer-Diffusion Approach for 8K Video Restoration under Codec Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversing-the-damage-a-qp-aware-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce DiQP; a novel Transformer-Diffusion model for restoring 8K video quality degraded by codec compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversing-the-damage-a-qp-aware-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural Entropy Guided Probabilistic Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-entropy-guided-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic embeddings have several advantages over deterministic embeddings as they map each data point to a distribution, which better describes the uncertainty and complexity of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-entropy-guided-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Music Generation with Explicit Bridges and Retrieval Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-music-generation-with-explicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal music generation aims to produce music from diverse input modalities, including text, videos, and images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-music-generation-with-explicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-Regressive Moving Diffusion Models for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-regressive-moving-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This design aligns the diffusion model's sampling procedure with the forecasting objective, resulting in an unconditional, continuous sequential diffusion TSF model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-regressive-moving-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Flexible Plug-and-Play Module for Generating Variable-Length</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-plug-and-play-module-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The NHL framework introduces a novel mechanism to simultaneously generate hash codes of varying lengths in a nested manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-plug-and-play-module-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2PE: Improving Multimodal Long-Context Capability of Vision-Language Models with Variable Visual Position Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2pe-improving-multimodal-long-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we first conduct an empirical analysis of the long-context capabilities of VLMs using our augmented long-context multimodal datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2pe-improving-multimodal-long-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDRL: Unified Skeleton-Based Dense Representation Learning with Multi-Grained Feature Decorrelation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usdrl-unified-skeleton-based-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we design a Dense Spatio-Temporal Encoder (DSTE) to capture fine-grained action representations effectively, thereby enhancing the performance of dense prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usdrl-unified-skeleton-based-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LatentSync: Audio Conditioned Latent Diffusion Models for Lip Sync</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentsync-audio-conditioned-latent-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since we did not change the overall training framework of SyncNet, our experience can also be applied to other lip sync and audio-driven portrait animation methods that utilize SyncNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentsync-audio-conditioned-latent-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Action Localization with Cross Layer Task Decoupling and Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-action-localization-with-cross-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal action localization (TAL) involves dual tasks to classify and localize actions within untrimmed videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-action-localization-with-cross-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskTerial: A Foundation Model for Automated 2D Material Flake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskterial-a-foundation-model-for-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection and classification of exfoliated two-dimensional (2D) material flakes from optical microscope images can be automated using computer vision algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskterial-a-foundation-model-for-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motif Guided Graph Transformer with Combinatorial Skeleton Prototype Learning for Skeleton-Based Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-guided-graph-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a generic Motif guided graph transformer with Combinatorial skeleton prototype learning (MoCos) that exploits structure-specific and gait-related body relations as well as combinatorial features of skeleton graphs to learn effective skeleton representations for person re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motif-guided-graph-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Owl-1: Omni World Model for Consistent Long Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owl-1-omni-world-model-for-consistent-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As videos are observations of the underlying evolving world, we propose to model the long-term developments in a latent space and use VGMs to film them into videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owl-1-omni-world-model-for-consistent-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Predictive Control with Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-predictive-control-with-constraints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have recently gained popularity for policy learning in robotics due to their ability to capture high-dimensional and multimodal distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-predictive-control-with-constraints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Foundation Models on Heterogeneous Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-foundation-models-on-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training a general-purpose time series foundation models with robust generalization capabilities across diverse applications from scratch is still an open challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-foundation-models-on-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filter-then-Generate: Large Language Models with Structure-Text Adapter for Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-then-generate-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fundamentally, applying LLMs on KGC introduces several critical challenges, including a vast set of entity candidates, hallucination issue of LLMs, and under-exploitation of the graph structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-then-generate-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
