<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 09:20:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Neural Kernel Embeddings for General Activations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-neural-kernel-embeddings-for-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, most prior works on neural kernels have focused on the ReLU activation, mainly due to its popularity but also due to the difficulty of computing such kernels for general activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-neural-kernel-embeddings-for-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoder Based Iterative Modeling and Multivariate Time-Series Subsequence Clustering Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-iterative-modeling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[No meaningful and coherent measurement data which could be used for training a CbM model would emerge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-iterative-modeling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Confidence-guided Shape Completion for Robotic Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-confidence-guided-shape-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many robotic tasks involving some form of 3D visual perception greatly benefit from a complete knowledge of the working environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-confidence-guided-shape-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Document Scientific Summarization from a Knowledge Graph-Centric View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-scientific-summarization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Document Scientific Summarization (MDSS) aims to produce coherent and concise summaries for clusters of topic-relevant scientific papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-scientific-summarization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathology Synthesis of 3D Consistent Cardiac MR Im-ages Using 2D VAEs and GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathology-synthesis-of-3d-consistent-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We devise an approach for label manipulation in the latent space of the trained VAE model, namely pathology synthesis, aiming to synthesize a series of pseudo-pathological synthetic subjects with characteristics of a desired heart disease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathology-synthesis-of-3d-consistent-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-Aware JPEG Image Compression: A Multi-Objective Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-aware-jpeg-image-compression-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, two Pareto-based methods, including a non-dominated sorting genetic algorithm (NSGA-II) and a reference-point-based NSGA-II (NSGA-III) are used for the embedding scheme, and two Pareto-based algorithms, EnNSGAII and EnNSGAIII, are presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-aware-jpeg-image-compression-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaxMatch-Dropout: Subword Regularization for WordPiece</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxmatch-dropout-subword-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a subword regularization method for WordPiece, which uses a maximum matching algorithm for tokenization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxmatch-dropout-subword-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>clusterBMA: Bayesian model averaging for clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clusterbma-bayesian-model-averaging-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we introduce clusterBMA, a method that enables weighted model averaging across results from multiple unsupervised clustering algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clusterbma-bayesian-model-averaging-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MassMIND: Massachusetts Maritime INfrared Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massmind-massachusetts-maritime-infrared</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the dataset focuses on the coastal terrain it can equally help deep sea use cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massmind-massachusetts-maritime-infrared</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Alignment of Multi-Task Feature and Label Spaces for Emotion Cause Pair Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-alignment-of-multi-task-feature-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first propose a feature-task alignment to explicitly model the specific emotion-&cause-specific features and the shared interactive feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-alignment-of-multi-task-feature-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F-COREF: Fast, Accurate and Easy to Use Coreference Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-coref-fast-accurate-and-easy-to-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce fastcoref, a python package for fast, accurate, and easy-to-use English coreference resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-coref-fast-accurate-and-easy-to-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Memory-Related Multi-Task Method Based on Task-Agnostic Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-memory-related-multi-task-method-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, for a new task, the action effect features stored in memory are used to generate candidate actions by a feature decomposition-based approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-memory-related-multi-task-method-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-grained Label Refinement Network with Dependency Structures for Joint Intent Detection and Slot Filling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-label-refinement-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To capture the semantic dependency between the syntactic information and task labels, we combine the task specific features with corresponding label embeddings by attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grained-label-refinement-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting to Non-Centered Languages for Zero-shot Multilingual Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-centered-languages-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual neural machine translation can translate unseen language pairs during training, i. e. zero-shot translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-centered-languages-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retinal Image Restoration and Vessel Segmentation using Modified Cycle-CBAM and CBAM-UNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retinal-image-restoration-and-vessel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The retinal vessel segmentation performance was compared with the ground-truth fundus images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retinal-image-restoration-and-vessel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Enhanced Scheme for Reducing the Complexity of Pointwise Convolutions in CNNs for Image Classification Based on Interleaved Grouped Filters without Divisibility Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-enhanced-scheme-for-reducing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The number of groups of filters and filters per group for layers K and L is determined by exact divisions of the original number of input channels and filters by Ch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-enhanced-scheme-for-reducing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Utility of Explainable AI in Ad Hoc Human-Machine Teaming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-utility-of-explainable-ai-in-ad-hoc-human-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, expert performance degrades with the addition of xAI-based support ($p<0. 05$), indicating that the cost of paying attention to the xAI outweighs the benefits obtained from being provided additional information to enhance SA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-utility-of-explainable-ai-in-ad-hoc-human-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Feedback Loops: Model-driven Amplification of Dataset Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-feedback-loops-model-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Datasets scraped from the internet have been critical to the successes of large-scale machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-feedback-loops-model-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni-Mol: A Universal 3D Molecular Representation Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-a-universal-3d-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uni-Mol is composed of two models with the same SE(3)-equivariant transformer architecture: a molecular pretraining model trained by 209M molecular conformations; a pocket pretraining model trained by 3M candidate protein pocket data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-a-universal-3d-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Effect of Sampling in GNNs on Individual Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effect-of-sampling-in-gnns-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate two popular GNN methods: Graph Convolutional Network (GCN), which trains on the entire graph, and GraphSAGE, which uses probabilistic random walks to create subgraphs for mini-batch training, and assess the effects of sub-sampling on individual fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effect-of-sampling-in-gnns-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simpler is better: Multilevel Abstraction with Graph Convolutional Recurrent Neural Network Cells for Traffic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpler-is-better-multilevel-abstraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, graph neural networks (GNNs) combined with variants of recurrent neural networks (RNNs) have reached state-of-the-art performance in spatiotemporal forecasting tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simpler-is-better-multilevel-abstraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AARGH! End-to-end Retrieval-Generation for Task-Oriented Dialog</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aargh-end-to-end-retrieval-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce AARGH, an end-to-end task-oriented dialog system combining retrieval and generative approaches in a single model, aiming at improving dialog management and lexical diversity of outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aargh-end-to-end-retrieval-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Evaluation of Posterior Sampling for Constrained Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-evaluation-of-posterior-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study a posterior sampling approach to efficient exploration in constrained reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-evaluation-of-posterior-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic gradient descent with gradient estimator for categorical features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-with-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Categorical data are present in key areas such as health or supply chain, and this data require specific treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-gradient-descent-with-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extractive is not Faithful: An Investigation of Broad Unfaithfulness Problems in Extractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extractive-is-not-faithful-an-investigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though extractive summarization is less prone to the common unfaithfulness issues of abstractive summaries, does that mean extractive is equal to faithful?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extractive-is-not-faithful-an-investigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Driven Program Synthesis via Adaptive Replacement Mutation and Auto-constructed Subprogram Archives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-program-synthesis-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the proposed method with PushGP, as well as a method using subprograms manually extracted by a human.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-program-synthesis-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Combination of a Genetic Algorithm and Novelty Search for Deep Neuroevolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-combination-of-a-genetic-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, Novelty Search (NS) has been shown to be able to outperform gradient-following optimizers in some cases, while under-performing in others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-combination-of-a-genetic-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R$^3$LIVE++: A Robust, Real-time, Radiance reconstruction package with a tightly-coupled LiDAR-Inertial-Visual state Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-3-live-a-robust-real-time-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LIO subsystem utilizes the measurements from a LiDAR for reconstructing the geometric structure (i. e., the positions of 3D points), while the VIO subsystem simultaneously recovers the radiance information of the geometric structure from the input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-3-live-a-robust-real-time-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aerial View Goal Localization with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aerial-view-goal-localization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many cases the rough location may be known and a UAV can be deployed to explore a given, confined area to precisely localize the missing people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aerial-view-goal-localization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIY-IPS: Towards an Off-the-Shelf Accurate Indoor Positioning System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diy-ips-towards-an-off-the-shelf-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DIY-IPS - Do It Yourself - Indoor Positioning System, an open-source real-time indoor positioning mobile application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diy-ips-towards-an-off-the-shelf-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Free Learning of a Natural Language Interface for Pretrained Face Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-free-learning-of-a-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Fast text2StyleGAN, a natural language interface that adapts pre-trained GANs for text-guided human face synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-free-learning-of-a-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized One-shot Domain Adaption of Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-one-shot-domain-adaption-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous works mainly focus on the style transfer, we propose a novel and concise framework\footnote{\url{https://github. com/thevoidname/Generalized-One-shot-GAN-Adaption}} to address the \textit{generalized one-shot adaption} task for both style and entity transfer, in which a reference image and its binary entity mask are provided.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-one-shot-domain-adaption-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Shapley Values to Generalized Additive Models and back</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-shapley-values-to-generalized-additive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then show that Shapley Values recover generalized additive models of order $n$, assuming that we allow for interaction terms up to order $n$ in the explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-shapley-values-to-generalized-additive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLaCLab at SocialDisNER: Using Medical Gazetteers for Named-Entity Recognition of Disease Mentions in Spanish Tweets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/claclab-at-socialdisner-using-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper summarizes the CLaC submission for SMM4H 2022 Task 10 which concerns the recognition of diseases mentioned in Spanish tweets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/claclab-at-socialdisner-using-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Training a Graph Recurrent Network for Language Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-a-graph-recurrent-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based pre-trained models have gained much advance in recent years, becoming one of the most important backbones in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-a-graph-recurrent-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eigenvalue Mapping-based Semi-implicit Discretization of the Generalized Super-Twisting Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenvalue-mapping-based-semi-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, an eigenvalue mapping-based semi-implicit discretization method is applied to discretize the generalized super-twisting algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenvalue-mapping-based-semi-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geolocation of Cultural Heritage using Multi-View Knowledge Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolocation-of-cultural-heritage-using-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graphs (KGs) have proven to be a reliable way of structuring data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolocation-of-cultural-heritage-using-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representing Camera Response Function by a Single Latent Variable and Fully Connected Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-camera-response-function-by-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a new high-performance camera response model that uses a single latent variable and fully connected neural network is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-camera-response-function-by-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KT-BT: A Framework for Knowledge Transfer Through Behavior Trees in Multi-Robot Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kt-bt-a-framework-for-knowledge-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically investigate the properties of the KT-BT framework in achieving homogeneity of high knowledge across the entire group compared to a heterogeneous system without the capability of sharing their knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kt-bt-a-framework-for-knowledge-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretations Steered Network Pruning via Amortized Inferred Saliency Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretations-steered-network-pruning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill in this gap, we propose to address the channel pruning problem from a novel perspective by leveraging the interpretations of a model to steer the pruning process, thereby utilizing information from both inputs and outputs of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretations-steered-network-pruning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficulty-Net: Learning to Predict Difficulty for Long-Tailed Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-net-learning-to-predict-difficulty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-tailed datasets, where head classes comprise much more training samples than tail classes, cause recognition models to get biased towards the head classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-net-learning-to-predict-difficulty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Crowd Counting via Density Agency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-crowd-counting-via-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new agency-guided semi-supervised counting approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-crowd-counting-via-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGStore: A Multimodal Extension to SPARQL for Querying RDF Scene Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgstore-a-multimodal-extension-to-sparql-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic Web technology has successfully facilitated many RDF models with rich data representation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgstore-a-multimodal-extension-to-sparql-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Interactive Learning for Text Classification: A Constructive Approach for Contextual Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-interactive-learning-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interactive Machine Learning (IML) shall enable intelligent systems to interactively learn from their end-users, and is quickly becoming more and more important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-interactive-learning-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiFuse++: Self-supervised and Efficient Bi-projection Fusion for 360 Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifuse-self-supervised-and-efficient-bi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, state-of-the-art frameworks for monocular 360 depth estimation such as bi-projection fusion in BiFuse are proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifuse-self-supervised-and-efficient-bi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Compact Biomedical Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-compact-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models pre-trained on biomedical corpora, such as BioBERT, have recently shown promising results on downstream biomedical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-compact-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSMDFusion: Fusing LiDAR and Camera at Multiple Scales with Multi-Depth Seeds for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msmdfusion-fusing-lidar-and-camera-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fusing LiDAR and camera information is essential for achieving accurate and reliable 3D object detection in autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msmdfusion-fusing-lidar-and-camera-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Neural Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-neural-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey aims to present a comprehensive review of NTs and attempts to identify how they enhance the model interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-neural-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantitative probing: Validating causal models using quantitative domain knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-probing-validating-causal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present quantitative probing as a model-agnostic framework for validating causal models in the presence of quantitative domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-probing-validating-causal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFACT: An Online Human Evaluation Framework for Conversational Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infact-an-online-human-evaluation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational recommender systems (CRS) are interactive agents that support their users in recommendation-related goals through multi-turn conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infact-an-online-human-evaluation-framework</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
