<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 21:09:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>REPA-E: Unlocking VAE for End-to-End Tuning of Latent Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repa-e-unlocking-vae-for-end-to-end-tuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that while diffusion loss is ineffective, end-to-end training can be unlocked through the representation-alignment (REPA) loss -- allowing both VAE and diffusion model to be jointly tuned during the training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repa-e-unlocking-vae-for-end-to-end-tuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation models for electronic health records: representation dynamics and transferability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-for-electronic-health</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models (FMs) trained on electronic health records (EHRs) have shown strong performance on a range of clinical prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-for-electronic-health</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Personalization: From RAG to Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-personalization-from-rag-to-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalization has become an essential capability in modern AI systems, enabling customized interactions that align with individual user preferences, contexts, and goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-personalization-from-rag-to-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade-offs in Privacy-Preserving Eye Tracking through Iris Obfuscation: A Benchmarking Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trade-offs-in-privacy-preserving-eye-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering all, in this paper, we benchmark blurring, noising, downsampling, rubber sheet model, and iris style transfer to obfuscate user identity, and compare their impact on image quality, privacy, utility, and risk of imposter attack on two datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trade-offs-in-privacy-preserving-eye-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OctGPT: Octree-based Multiscale Autoregressive Models for 3D Shape Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octgpt-octree-based-multiscale-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce OctGPT, a novel multiscale autoregressive model for 3D shape generation that dramatically improves the efficiency and performance of prior 3D autoregressive approaches, while rivaling or surpassing state-of-the-art diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octgpt-octree-based-multiscale-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-SRBench: A New Benchmark for Scientific Equation Discovery with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-srbench-a-new-benchmark-for-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific equation discovery is a fundamental task in the history of scientific progress, enabling the derivation of laws governing natural phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-srbench-a-new-benchmark-for-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamik: Syntactically-Driven Dynamic Font Sizing for Emphasis of Key Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamik-syntactically-driven-dynamic-font</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In today's globalized world, there are increasing opportunities for individuals to communicate using a common non-native language (lingua franca).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamik-syntactically-driven-dynamic-font</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D CoCa: Contrastive Learners are 3D Captioners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-coca-contrastive-learners-are-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D captioning, which aims to describe the content of 3D scenes in natural language, remains highly challenging due to the inherent sparsity of point clouds and weak cross-modal alignment in existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-coca-contrastive-learners-are-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Guided Refinement for Fine-Grained Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-refinement-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce the uncertainty guidance learning approach to SOD, intended to enhance the model's perception of uncertain regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-refinement-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explorer: Robust Collection of Interactable GUI Elements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explorer-robust-collection-of-interactable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We mostly assume that the target application is known in advance, so that data collection and ML-training can be personalized for the test-time target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explorer-robust-collection-of-interactable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting the Class-Incremental Learning in 3D Point Clouds via Zero-Collection-Cost Basic Shape Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-class-incremental-learning-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we propose a framework embedded with 3D geometry knowledge for incremental learning in point clouds, compatible with exemplar-free (-based) settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-class-incremental-learning-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-conditioned Ensemble of Expert Models for Continuous Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-conditioned-ensemble-of-expert-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The non-stationary environment results in distribution shifts and, consequently, a degradation in accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-conditioned-ensemble-of-expert-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Reconfiguration of LC-RISs: Modeling and Algorithm Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-reconfiguration-of-lc-riss-modeling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the slow phase-shifting limitation of LC by developing a physics-based model for the time response of an LC unit cell and proposing a novel phase-shift design framework to reduce the transition time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-reconfiguration-of-lc-riss-modeling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Methods for Detecting Thermal Runaway Events in Battery Production Lines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-methods-for-detecting-thermal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the use of deep learning for detecting thermal runaway in the battery production line of VDL Nedcar, a Dutch automobile manufacturer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-methods-for-detecting-thermal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CG-TGAN: Conditional Generative Adversarial Networks with Graph Neural Networks for Tabular Data Synthesizing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cg-tgan-conditional-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The synthesized tabular data should reflect the relational meaning between columns of tabular data, so modeling the probability distribution of tabular data is a non-trivial task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cg-tgan-conditional-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMNI: Pose-free Multi-view Normal Integration for Reflective and Textureless Surface Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmni-pose-free-multi-view-normal-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reflective and textureless surfaces remain a challenge in multi-view 3D reconstruction. Both camera pose calibration and shape reconstruction often fail due to insufficient or unreliable cross-view visual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pmni-pose-free-multi-view-normal-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genius: A Generalizable and Purely Unsupervised Self-Training Framework For Advanced Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genius-a-generalizable-and-purely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This motivates us to enhance LLM reasoning without the need for external supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genius-a-generalizable-and-purely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of Style: RAG's Fragility to Linguistic Variation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-style-rag-s-fragility-to-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impressive performance of Retrieval-augmented Generation (RAG) systems across various NLP benchmarks, their robustness in handling real-world user-LLM interaction queries remains largely underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-style-rag-s-fragility-to-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedRep: Medical Concept Representation for General Electronic Health Record Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medrep-medical-concept-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with this problem, we propose MedRep for EHR foundation models based on the observational medical outcome partnership (OMOP) common data model (CDM), providing the integrated medical concept representations and the basic data augmentation strategy for patient trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medrep-medical-concept-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealCam-Vid: High-resolution Video Dataset with Dynamic Scenes and Metric-scale Camera Movements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcam-vid-high-resolution-video-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in camera-controllable video generation have been constrained by the reliance on static-scene datasets with relative-scale camera annotations, such as RealEstate10K.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realcam-vid-high-resolution-video-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG-VR: Leveraging Retrieval-Augmented Generation for 3D Question Answering in VR Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-vr-leveraging-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) provide new opportunities for context understanding in virtual reality (VR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-vr-leveraging-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muon-Accelerated Attention Distillation for Real-Time Edge Synthesis via Optimized Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muon-accelerated-attention-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Muon-AD, a co-designed framework that integrates the Muon optimizer with attention distillation for real-time edge synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muon-accelerated-attention-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Diffusion Autoencoders: Toward Efficient and Meaningful Unsupervised Representation Learning in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-autoencoders-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents Latent Diffusion Autoencoder (LDAE), a novel encoder-decoder diffusion-based framework for efficient and meaningful unsupervised learning in medical imaging, focusing on Alzheimer disease (AD) using brain MR from the ADNI database as a case study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-autoencoders-toward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Background Bias of Post-Hoc Concept Embeddings in Computer Vision DNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-background-bias-of-post-hoc-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A dangerous performance degradation of the concept-corner cases of animals on the road could thus remain undiscovered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-background-bias-of-post-hoc-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchFX: A modern approach to Audio DSP with PyTorch and GPU acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchfx-a-modern-approach-to-audio-dsp-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response, we introduce TorchFX: a GPU-accelerated Python library for DSP, specifically engineered to facilitate sophisticated audio signal processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchfx-a-modern-approach-to-audio-dsp-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut-and-Splat: Leveraging Gaussian Splatting for Synthetic Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-splat-leveraging-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating synthetic images is a useful method for cheaply obtaining labeled data for training computer vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-splat-leveraging-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverberation-based Features for Sound Event Localization and Detection with Distance Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverberation-based-features-for-sound-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Only recently, SELD was extended to 3D by incorporating distance estimation, enabling the prediction of sound event positions in 3D space (3D SELD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverberation-based-features-for-sound-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SN-LiDAR: Semantic Neural Fields for Novel Space-time View LiDAR Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sn-lidar-semantic-neural-fields-for-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose SN-LiDAR, a method that jointly performs accurate semantic segmentation, high-quality geometric reconstruction, and realistic LiDAR synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sn-lidar-semantic-neural-fields-for-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RouterKT: Mixture-of-Experts for Knowledge Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routerkt-mixture-of-experts-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose RouterKT, a novel Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) architecture designed to capture heterogeneous learning patterns by enabling experts to specialize in different patterns without any handcrafted learning pattern bias such as forgetting decay.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routerkt-mixture-of-experts-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Memory Engine (TME): Enhancing State Awareness for Multi-Step LLM Agent Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-memory-engine-tme-enhancing-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the Task Memory Engine (TME), a lightweight and structured memory module that tracks task execution using a hierarchical Task Memory Tree (TMT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-memory-engine-tme-enhancing-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The More is not the Merrier: Investigating the Effect of Client Size on Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-more-is-not-the-merrier-investigating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find a significant deterioration of learning accuracy for FedAvg as the number of clients increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-more-is-not-the-merrier-investigating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>seeBias: A Comprehensive Tool for Assessing and Visualizing AI Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seebias-a-comprehensive-tool-for-assessing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fairness in artificial intelligence (AI) prediction models is increasingly emphasized to support responsible adoption in high-stakes domains such as health care and criminal justice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seebias-a-comprehensive-tool-for-assessing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TensorNEAT: A GPU-accelerated Library for NeuroEvolution of Augmenting Topologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorneat-a-gpu-accelerated-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to NEAT, the library supports variants such as CPPN and HyperNEAT, and integrates with benchmark environments like Gym, Brax, and gymnax.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorneat-a-gpu-accelerated-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Black-Box Predictions: Identifying Marginal Feature Effects in Tabular Transformer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-black-box-predictions-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this predictive power comes at the cost of intelligibility: Marginal feature effects are almost completely lost in the black-box nature of deep tabular transformer networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-black-box-predictions-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F$^3$Set: Towards Analyzing Fast, Frequent, and Fine-grained Events from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-3-set-towards-analyzing-fast-frequent-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analyzing Fast, Frequent, and Fine-grained (F$^3$) events presents a significant challenge in video analytics and multi-modal LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-3-set-towards-analyzing-fast-frequent-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Power Grid Topologies with Reinforcement Learning: A Survey of Methods and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-power-grid-topologies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Power grid operation is becoming increasingly complex due to the rising integration of renewable energy sources and the need for more adaptive control strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-power-grid-topologies-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBE-ARI: A Multimodal Dataset Mapping Bi-directional Engagement in Animal-Robot Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbe-ari-a-multimodal-dataset-mapping-bi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Animal-robot interaction (ARI) remains an unexplored challenge in robotics, as robots struggle to interpret the complex, multimodal communication cues of animals, such as body language, movement, and vocalizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbe-ari-a-multimodal-dataset-mapping-bi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MooseAgent: A LLM Based Multi-agent Framework for Automating Moose Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mooseagent-a-llm-based-multi-agent-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an automated solution framework, MooseAgent, for the multi-physics simulation framework MOOSE, which combines large-scale pre-trained language models (LLMs) with a multi-agent system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mooseagent-a-llm-based-multi-agent-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform Convergence of Lipschitz Functions with Dependent Gaussian Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-convergence-of-lipschitz-functions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many practical learning problems, training samples are not i. i. d., and there is an intrinsic dependency among samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-convergence-of-lipschitz-functions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probability Estimation and Scheduling Optimization for Battery Swap Stations via LRU-Enhanced Genetic Algorithm and Dual-Factor Decision System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probability-estimation-and-scheduling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges of limited Battery Swap Stations datasets, high operational costs, and fluctuating user charging demand, this research proposes a probability estimation model based on charging pile data and constructs nine scenario-specific battery swap demand datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probability-estimation-and-scheduling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modular Control of Discrete Event System for Modeling and Mitigating Power System Cascading Failures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-control-of-discrete-event-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In prior work, we developed a new approach for identifying and preventing cascading failures in power systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modular-control-of-discrete-event-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2Object: Single Point Supervised Object Detection and Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2object-single-point-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Point-to-Box Network (P2BNet), which constructs balanced \textbf{\textit{instance-level proposal bags}} by generating proposals in an anchor-like way and refining the proposals in a coarse-to-fine paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2object-single-point-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Time Series Forecasting via Multi-Level Text Alignment with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-time-series-forecasting-via-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adaptation of large language models (LLMs) to time series forecasting poses unique challenges, as time series data is continuous in nature, while LLMs operate on discrete tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-time-series-forecasting-via-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating quantum feature map design via large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-quantum-feature-map-design-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum feature maps are a key component of quantum machine learning, encoding classical data into quantum states to exploit the expressive power of high-dimensional Hilbert spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-quantum-feature-map-design-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRI: Reducing Cross-Task Interference in Multi-Task Low-Rank Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lori-reducing-cross-task-interference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose LoRA with Reduced Interference (LoRI), a simple yet effective approach that freezes the projection matrices $A$ as random projections and sparsifies the matrices $B$ using task-specific masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lori-reducing-cross-task-interference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness of Online Identification-based Policy Iteration to Noisy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-of-online-identification-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We integrate recursive least squares (RLS) for online model estimation within a certainty-equivalent framework, and employ PI to iteratively update the control policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-of-online-identification-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Selection using Smooth Sensitivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-selection-using-smooth-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differentially private selection mechanisms offer strong privacy guarantees for queries aiming to identify the top-scoring element r from a finite set R, based on a dataset-dependent utility function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-selection-using-smooth-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRVP: Strong Recollection Video Prediction Model Using Attention-Based Spatiotemporal Correlation Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srvp-strong-recollection-video-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video prediction (VP) generates future frames by leveraging spatial representations and temporal context from past frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srvp-strong-recollection-video-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Between Linear and Sinusoidal: Rethinking the Time Encoder in Dynamic Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/between-linear-and-sinusoidal-rethinking-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experiments on six dynamic graph datasets, we demonstrate that the linear time encoder improves the performance of TGAT and DyGFormer in most cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/between-linear-and-sinusoidal-rethinking-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOSAIC: Modeling Social AI for Content Dissemination and Regulation in Multi-Agent Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mosaic-modeling-social-ai-for-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel, open-source social network simulation framework, MOSAIC, where generative language agents predict user behaviors such as liking, sharing, and flagging content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mosaic-modeling-social-ai-for-content</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
