<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 09:15:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Secondary Protein Structure Prediction Using Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-protein-structure-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we test the impact of varying the length of protein sequence we input into the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-protein-structure-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeRFception: Perception using Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfception-perception-using-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent progress in implicit 3D representation, i. e., Neural Radiance Fields (NeRFs), has made accurate and photorealistic 3D reconstruction possible in a differentiable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfception-perception-using-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Substructure-Aware Network for Drug-Drug Interaction Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-substructure-aware-network-for-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concomitant administration of drugs can cause drug-drug interactions (DDIs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-substructure-aware-network-for-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Deep Learning Performance of Massive MIMO CSI Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a jigsaw puzzles aided training strategy (JPTS) to enhance the deep learning-based Massive MIMO CSI feedback approaches by maximizing mutual information between the original CSI and the compressed CSI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-deep-learning-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting Song Lyrics with an Audio-Informed Pre-trained Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-song-lyrics-with-an-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lyric interpretations can help people understand songs and their lyrics quickly, and can also make it easier to manage, retrieve and discover songs efficiently from the growing mass of music archives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-song-lyrics-with-an-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Induced Natural Language Rationales and Interleaved Markup Tokens Enable Extrapolation in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/induced-natural-language-rationales-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to extrapolate, i. e., to make predictions on sequences that are longer than those presented as training examples, is a challenging problem for current deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/induced-natural-language-rationales-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On a Built-in Conflict between Deep Learning and Systematic Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-a-built-in-conflict-between-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we hypothesize that internal function sharing is one of the reasons to weaken o. o. d.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-a-built-in-conflict-between-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bugs in the Data: How ImageNet Misrepresents Biodiversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bugs-in-the-data-how-imagenet-misrepresents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that many of the classes are ill-defined or overlapping, and that 12% of the images are incorrectly labeled, with some classes having >90% of images incorrect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bugs-in-the-data-how-imagenet-misrepresents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FactMix: Using a Few Labeled In-domain Examples to Generalize to Cross-domain Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factmix-using-a-few-labeled-in-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot Named Entity Recognition (NER) is imperative for entity tagging in limited resource domains and thus received proper attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factmix-using-a-few-labeled-in-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-Year Bankruptcy Prediction from Textual Data: Benchmark and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/next-year-bankruptcy-prediction-from-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models for bankruptcy prediction are useful in several real-world scenarios, and multiple research contributions have been devoted to the task, based on structured (numerical) as well as unstructured (textual) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/next-year-bankruptcy-prediction-from-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Learning Approach Using Masked Image Modeling for Reconstruction of Undersampled K-spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-using-masked-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model was evaluated through L1 loss, gradient normalization, and structural similarity values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-using-masked-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOPv2: Better, Faster, Stronger for Panoptic Driving Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolopv2-better-faster-stronger-for-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the last decade, multi-tasking learning approaches have achieved promising results in solving panoptic driving perception problems, providing both high-precision and high-efficiency performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolopv2-better-faster-stronger-for-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Human Criteria and Automatic Metrics: A Benchmark of the Evaluation of Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-human-criteria-and-automatic-metrics-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there is no consensus on which human evaluation criteria to use, and no analysis of how well automatic criteria correlate with them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-human-criteria-and-automatic-metrics-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPTDR: Deep Prompt Tuning for Dense Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dptdr-deep-prompt-tuning-for-dense-passage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe this work facilitates the industry, as it saves enormous efforts and costs of deployment and increases the utility of computing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dptdr-deep-prompt-tuning-for-dense-passage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjoint Optimisation for Wind Farm Flow Control with a Free-Vortex Wake Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjoint-optimisation-for-wind-farm-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The free-vortex wake model with gradient information shows potential for efficient optimisation and provides a promising way to further explore dynamic wind farm flow control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjoint-optimisation-for-wind-farm-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an Awareness of Time Series Anomaly Detection Models' Adversarial Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-awareness-of-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our understanding, we demonstrate, for the first time, the vulnerabilities of anomaly detection systems against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-awareness-of-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Nearest Convolution for Real-Time Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-nearest-convolution-for-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed nearest convolution has the same performance as the nearest upsampling but is much faster and more suitable for Android NNAPI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-nearest-convolution-for-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applying Eigencontours to PolarMask-Based Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-eigencontours-to-polarmask-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Eigencontours are the first data-driven contour descriptors based on singular value decomposition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-eigencontours-to-polarmask-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliding Window Recurrent Network for Efficient Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-window-recurrent-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from single image super-resolution, VSR can utilize frames' temporal information to reconstruct results with more details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-window-recurrent-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Filtering: A Noise-Aware Sample Selection for Label Noise with Confidence Penalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-filtering-a-noise-aware-sample-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sample selection is an effective strategy to mitigate the effect of label noise in robust learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-filtering-a-noise-aware-sample-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Design of Privacy-Aware Cameras: a Study on Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-design-of-privacy-aware-cameras-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the same time, we ensure that useful non-sensitive data can still be extracted from distorted images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-design-of-privacy-aware-cameras-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking by weakly-supervised learning and graph optimization for whole-embryo C. elegans lineages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-by-weakly-supervised-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work specifically addresses the following challenging properties of C. elegans embryo recordings: (1) Many cell divisions as compared to benchmark recordings of other organisms, and (2) the presence of polar bodies that are easily mistaken as cell nuclei.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-by-weakly-supervised-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RZSR: Reference-based Zero-Shot Super-Resolution with Depth Guided Self-Exemplars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rzsr-reference-based-zero-shot-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance ZSSR, we obtain reference image patches with rich textures and high-frequency details which are also extracted only from the input image using cross-scale matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rzsr-reference-based-zero-shot-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrestricted Black-box Adversarial Attack Using GAN with Limited Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrestricted-black-box-adversarial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we demonstrate that our targeted attack method is query-efficient to produce unrestricted adversarial examples for a facial identity recognition model that contains 307 identities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrestricted-black-box-adversarial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-Net: Query-Informed Few-Shot Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-net-query-informed-few-shot-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has achieved tremendous success in computer vision, while medical image segmentation (MIS) remains a challenge, due to the scarcity of data annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-net-query-informed-few-shot-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CitySim: A Drone-Based Vehicle Trajectory Dataset for Safety Oriented Research and Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citysim-a-drone-based-vehicle-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of safety-oriented research ideas and applications requires fine-grained vehicle trajectory data that not only has high accuracy but also captures a substantial number of critical safety events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citysim-a-drone-based-vehicle-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMPaSh: A Novel Domain-shift Resistant Representation for Colorectal Cancer Tissue Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impash-a-novel-domain-shift-resistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The appearance of histopathology images depends on tissue type, staining and digitization procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impash-a-novel-domain-shift-resistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-Aware Occlusion Detection with Focused Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-occlusion-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, (1) we propose a novel three-decoder architecture as the infrastructure for focused attention; 2) we use the generalized intersection box prediction task to effectively guide our model to focus on occlusion-specific regions; 3) our model achieves a new state-of-the-art performance on distance-aware relationship detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-aware-occlusion-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing User Behavior Sequence Modeling by Generative Tasks for Session Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-user-behavior-sequence-modeling-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help the encoding of the current user behavior sequence, we propose to use a decoder and the information of future sequences and a supplemental query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-user-behavior-sequence-modeling-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VILT: Video Instructions Linking for Complex Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilt-video-instructions-linking-for-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work addresses challenges in developing conversational assistants that support rich multimodal video interactions to accomplish real-world tasks interactively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilt-video-instructions-linking-for-complex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepInteraction: 3D Object Detection via Modality Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepinteraction-3d-object-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing top-performance 3D object detectors typically rely on the multi-modal fusion strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepinteraction-3d-object-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZoomNAS: Searching for Whole-body Human Pose Estimation in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoomnas-searching-for-whole-body-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a single-network approach, termed ZoomNet, to take into account the hierarchical structure of the full human body and solve the scale variation of different body parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoomnas-searching-for-whole-body-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIM 2022 Challenge on Super-Resolution of Compressed Image and Video: Dataset, Methods and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aim-2022-challenge-on-super-resolution-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The homepage of this challenge is at https://github. com/RenYang-home/AIM22_CompressSR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aim-2022-challenge-on-super-resolution-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-domain Learning for Updating Face Anti-spoofing Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-domain-learning-for-updating-face-anti</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study multi-domain learning for face anti-spoofing(MD-FAS), where a pre-trained FAS model needs to be updated to perform equally well on both source and target domains while only using target domain data for updating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-domain-learning-for-updating-face-anti</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks and Representation Embedding for Table Extraction in PDF Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-and-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tables are widely used in several types of documents since they can bring important information in a structured way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-and-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Computed Tomography (CT) Reconstruction via 3D Shape Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-computed-tomography-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chest computed tomography (CT) imaging adds valuable insight in the diagnosis and management of pulmonary infectious diseases, like tuberculosis (TB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-computed-tomography-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pystacked: Stacking generalization and machine learning in Stata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pystacked-stacking-generalization-and-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[pystacked implements stacked generalization (Wolpert, 1992) for regression and binary classification via Python's scikit-lear}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pystacked-stacking-generalization-and-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact Penalty Method for Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-penalty-method-for-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning has burgeoned recently in machine learning, giving rise to a variety of research topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-penalty-method-for-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data augmentation on graphs for table type classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-on-graphs-for-table-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tables are widely used in documents because of their compact and structured representation of information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-on-graphs-for-table-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting as Probing: Using Language Models for Knowledge Base Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-as-probing-using-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ProP implements a multi-step approach that combines a variety of prompting techniques to achieve this.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-as-probing-using-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency Regularization for Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-regularization-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collection of real world annotations for training semantic segmentation models is an expensive process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-regularization-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvSHAP(t): Time-dependent explanations of machine learning survival models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survshap-t-time-dependent-explanations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on synthetic and medical data confirm that SurvSHAP(t) can detect variables with a time-dependent effect, and its aggregation is a better determinant of the importance of variables for a prediction than SurvLIME.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survshap-t-time-dependent-explanations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Across Domains Gaze Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-across-domains-gaze-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the gaze target detection problem in single images captured from the third-person perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-across-domains-gaze-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Perceptual Noise Injection for Social Media Fingerprint Privacy Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-perceptual-noise-injection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The threat of fingerprint leakage from social media raises a strong desire for anonymizing shared images while maintaining image qualities, since fingerprints act as a lifelong individual biometric password.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-perceptual-noise-injection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULISSE: A Tool for One-shot Sky Exploration and its Application to Active Galactic Nuclei Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ulisse-a-tool-for-one-shot-sky-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on applying our method to the detection of AGN candidates in a Sloan Digital Sky Survey galaxy sample, since the identification and classification of Active Galactic Nuclei (AGN) in the optical band still remains a challenging task in extragalactic astronomy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ulisse-a-tool-for-one-shot-sky-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Anomaly Localization with Structural Feature-Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-localization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most commonly, the anomaly detection model generates a "normal" version of an input image, and the pixel-wise $l^p$-difference of the two is used to localize anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-localization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrative conformal p-values for powerful out-of-distribution testing with labeled outliers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrative-conformal-p-values-for-powerful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops novel conformal methods to test whether a new observation was sampled from the same distribution as a reference set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrative-conformal-p-values-for-powerful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchically Decomposed Graph Convolutional Networks for Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-decomposed-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph convolutional networks (GCNs) are the most commonly used method for skeleton-based action recognition and have achieved remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchically-decomposed-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Fitness Landscape Analysis of Permutation Problems: From Distance Metrics to Mutation Operator Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-fitness-landscape-analysis-of-permutation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our implementations of the permutation metrics, permutation mutation operators, and associated evolutionary algorithm, are available in a pair of open source Java libraries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-fitness-landscape-analysis-of-permutation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Feature Augmentation for Cross-domain Few-shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-feature-augmentation-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods based on meta-learning predict novel-class labels for (target domain) testing tasks via meta knowledge learned from (source domain) training tasks of base classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-feature-augmentation-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
