<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 21:07:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>KAN See In the Dark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-see-in-the-dark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing low-light image enhancement methods are difficult to fit the complex nonlinear relationship between normal and low-light images due to uneven illumination and noise effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-see-in-the-dark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexicon3D: Probing Visual Foundation Models for Complex 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicon3d-probing-visual-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we present a comprehensive study that probes various visual encoding models for 3D scene understanding, identifying the strengths and limitations of each model across different scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicon3d-probing-visual-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The representation landscape of few-shot learning and fine-tuning in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-representation-landscape-of-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More specifically, we compare how LLMs solve the same question-answering task, finding that ICL and SFT create very different internal structures, in both cases undergoing a sharp transition in the middle of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-representation-landscape-of-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCDiff: Triple Condition Diffusion Model with 3D Constraints for Stylizing Synthetic Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcdiff-triple-condition-diffusion-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Triple Condition Diffusion Model (TCDiff) to improve face style transfer from real to synthetic faces through 2D and 3D facial constraints, enhancing face identity consistency while keeping the necessary high intra-class variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcdiff-triple-condition-diffusion-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A method to benchmark high-dimensional process drift detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-to-benchmark-high-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Process curves are multi-variate finite time series data coming from manufacturing processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-method-to-benchmark-high-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Uncertainty-Error Correspondence in Deep Bayesian Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-uncertainty-error-correspondence-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work has investigated the correspondence between uncertainty and error, however, no work has been done on improving the "utility" of Bayesian uncertainty maps such that it is only present in inaccurate regions and not in the accurate ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-uncertainty-error-correspondence-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELO-Rated Sequence Rewards: Advancing Reinforcement Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elo-rated-sequence-rewards-advancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) is highly dependent on the meticulous design of the reward function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elo-rated-sequence-rewards-advancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning large language models for domain adaptation: Exploration of training strategies, scaling, model merging and synergistic capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-for-domain-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) for domain applications in fields such as materials science and engineering depends on the development of fine-tuning strategies that adapt models for specialized, technical capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-for-domain-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raw Speech Enhancement with Deep State Space Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-speech-enhancement-with-deep-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present aTENNuate, a simple deep state-space autoencoder configured for efficient online raw speech enhancement in an end-to-end fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-speech-enhancement-with-deep-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Autonomous Cybersecurity: An Intelligent AutoML Framework for Autonomous Intrusion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-cybersecurity-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, this paper proposes an Automated Machine Learning (AutoML)-based autonomous IDS framework towards achieving autonomous cybersecurity for next-generation networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-cybersecurity-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing Massive Activations of Attention Mechanism in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-massive-activations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Key contributions include (1) establishing the direct link between attention mechanisms and MAs generation in GNNs, (2) developing a robust definition and detection method for MAs based on activation ratio distributions, (3) introducing the Explicit Bias Term (EBT) as a potential countermeasure and exploring it as an adversarial framework to assess models robustness based on the presence or absence of MAs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-massive-activations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wind turbine condition monitoring based on intra- and inter-farm federated learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wind-turbine-condition-monitoring-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many AI applications in wind energy, such as in condition monitoring and power forecasting, may benefit from using operational data not only from individual wind turbines but from multiple turbines and multiple wind farms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wind-turbine-condition-monitoring-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Healthcare LLM Trust with Atypical Presentations Recalibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-healthcare-llm-trust-with-atypical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the miscalibration behavior of black-box LLMs within the healthcare setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-healthcare-llm-trust-with-atypical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-based multi-agent poetry generation in non-cooperative environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-based-multi-agent-poetry-generation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PROMPTING-BASED agents in our framework also benefit from non-cooperative environments and a more diverse ensemble of models with non-homogeneous agents has the potential to further enhance diversity, with an increase of 7. 0-17. 5 pp according to our experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-based-multi-agent-poetry-generation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Cyclists' Street Visual Preferences Through Multi-Source Big Data Using Deep Inverse Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-cyclists-street-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cycling has gained global popularity for its health benefits and positive urban impacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-cyclists-street-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC-Solver: Improving Predictor-Corrector Diffusion Sampler via Dynamic Compensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc-solver-improving-predictor-corrector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion probabilistic models (DPMs) have shown remarkable performance in visual synthesis but are computationally expensive due to the need for multiple evaluations during the sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc-solver-improving-predictor-corrector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Model or Finetune? Evaluation of few-shot semantic segmentation for river pollution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-or-finetune-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we compare the performance of FMs to finetuned pre-trained supervised models in the task of semantic segmentation on an entirely new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-or-finetune-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tissue Concepts: supervised foundation models in computational pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tissue-concepts-supervised-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is based on multi-task learning to train a joint encoder, by combining 16 different classification, segmentation, and detection tasks on a total of 912, 000 patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tissue-concepts-supervised-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMLT: Low-to-high Multi-Level Vision Transformer for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmlt-low-to-high-multi-level-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LMLT divides image features along the channel dimension, gradually reduces spatial size for lower heads, and applies self-attention to each head.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmlt-low-to-high-multi-level-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A practical approach to evaluating the adversarial distance for machine learning classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-approach-to-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robustness is critical for machine learning (ML) classifiers to ensure consistent performance in real-world applications where models may encounter corrupted or adversarial inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-approach-to-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Forecasting of Cryptocoins Timeseries using Correlation Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-forecasting-of-cryptocoins</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the causality between the trends, and exploit the derived correlations to understand the accuracy of state-of-the-art forecasting techniques for time series modeling (e. g., GBMs, LSTM and GRU) of correlated cryptocoins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-forecasting-of-cryptocoins</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iText2KG: Incremental Knowledge Graphs Construction Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itext2kg-incremental-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method demonstrates superior performance compared to baseline methods across three scenarios: converting scientific papers to graphs, websites to graphs, and CVs to graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itext2kg-incremental-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Labeled-to-Unlabeled Distribution Alignment for Partially-Supervised Multi-Organ Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/labeled-to-unlabeled-distribution-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the limited availability of labeled foreground organs and the absence of supervision to distinguish unlabeled foreground organs from the background pose a significant challenge, which leads to a distribution mismatch between labeled and unlabeled pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/labeled-to-unlabeled-distribution-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HGAMN: Heterogeneous Graph Attention Matching Network for Multilingual POI Retrieval at Baidu Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgamn-heterogeneous-graph-attention-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate challenge \#2, we construct edges between POI and query nodes based on the co-occurrences between queries and POIs, where queries in different languages and formulations can be aggregated for individual POIs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hgamn-heterogeneous-graph-attention-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Context-Related Anomalies: Knowledge Graph Empowered Decoupling of Scene and Action for Human-Related Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-context-related-anomalies-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In short, current methods struggle to integrate low-level visual and high-level action features, leading to poor anomaly detection in varied and complex scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-context-related-anomalies-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Mixup Towards Long-Tailed Image Categorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-mixup-towards-long-tailed-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many real-world applications, the frequency distribution of class labels for training data can exhibit a long-tailed distribution, which challenges traditional approaches of training deep neural networks that require heavy amounts of balanced data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-mixup-towards-long-tailed-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Uniform Illumination Attack for Fooling Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-uniform-illumination-attack-for-fooling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This strategy seeks to bolster CNN models' resilience against NUI attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-uniform-illumination-attack-for-fooling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iSeg: An Iterative Refinement-based Framework for Training-free Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iseg-an-iterative-refinement-based-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose an iterative refinement framework for training-free segmentation, named iSeg, having an entropy-reduced self-attention module which utilizes a gradient descent scheme to reduce the entropy of self-attention map, thereby suppressing the weak responses corresponding to irrelevant global information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iseg-an-iterative-refinement-based-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate on Graph: a Flexible and Reliable Reasoning Framework for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debate-on-graph-a-flexible-and-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the integration experiments with various LLMs on the mentioned datasets highlight the flexibility of DoG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debate-on-graph-a-flexible-and-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDM: A Reliable Metric for Fair and Accurate Formula Recognition Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdm-a-reliable-metric-for-fair-and-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a spatially-aware and character-matching method offers a more accurate and equitable evaluation compared with previous BLEU and Edit Distance metrics that rely solely on text-based character matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdm-a-reliable-metric-for-fair-and-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceptual-Distortion Balanced Image Super-Resolution is a Multi-Objective Optimization Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-distortion-balanced-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training Single-Image Super-Resolution (SISR) models using pixel-based regression losses can achieve high distortion metrics scores (e. g., PSNR and SSIM), but often results in blurry images due to insufficient recovery of high-frequency details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-distortion-balanced-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Heads of Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-heads-of-large-language-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, many researchers have begun exploring the potential internal mechanisms of LLMs, aiming to identify the essence of their reasoning bottlenecks, with most studies focusing on attention heads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-heads-of-large-language-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning In Natural Language Improves LLM Search For Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-in-natural-language-improves-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically demonstrate that this lack of diversity can be mitigated by searching over candidate plans for solving a problem in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-in-natural-language-improves-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPLUG-DocOwl2: High-resolution Compressing for OCR-free Multi-page Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-docowl2-high-resolution-compressing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodel Large Language Models(MLLMs) have achieved promising OCR-free Document Understanding performance by increasing the supported resolution of document images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-docowl2-high-resolution-compressing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AdEMAMix Optimizer: Better, Faster, Older</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ademamix-optimizer-better-faster-older</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work questions the use of a single EMA to accumulate past gradients and empirically demonstrates how this choice can be sub-optimal: a single EMA cannot simultaneously give a high weight to the immediate past, and a non-negligible weight to older gradients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ademamix-optimizer-better-faster-older</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LowFormer: Hardware Efficient Design for Convolutional Transformer Backbones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowformer-hardware-efficient-design-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyzed common modules and architectural design choices for backbones not in terms of MACs, but rather in actual throughput and latency, as the combination of the latter two is a better representation of the efficiency of models in real applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowformer-hardware-efficient-design-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-capacity Choquet Integral for Sensor Fusion with Label Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-capacity-choquet-integral-for-sensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows for extended non-linear interactions between the sensor sources and can lead to interesting fusion results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-capacity-choquet-integral-for-sensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surface-Centric Modeling for High-Fidelity Generalizable Neural Surface Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-centric-modeling-for-high-fidelity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose SuRF, a new Surface-centric framework that incorporates a new Region sparsification based on a matching Field, achieving good trade-offs between performance, efficiency and scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-centric-modeling-for-high-fidelity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurgTrack: CAD-Free 3D Tracking of Real-world Surgical Instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgtrack-cad-free-3d-tracking-of-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with 2D instrument tracking methods, 3D instrument tracking has broader value in clinical practice, but is also more challenging due to weak texture, occlusion, and lack of Computer-Aided Design (CAD) models for 3D registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgtrack-cad-free-3d-tracking-of-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pooling And Attention: What Are Effective Designs For LLM-Based Embedding Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pooling-and-attention-what-are-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these models, employing different pooling and attention strategies, have achieved state-of-the-art performance on public embedding benchmarks, questions still arise about what constitutes an effective design for LLM-based embedding models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pooling-and-attention-what-are-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look Into the LITE in Deep Learning for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-into-the-lite-in-deep-learning-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new architecture for TSC, the Light Inception with boosTing tEchnique (LITE) with only 2. 34% of the number of parameters of the state-of-the-art InceptionTime model, while preserving performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-into-the-lite-in-deep-learning-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Pre-training and Self-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-pre-training-and-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct experiments on six datasets, four data augmentation, and imbalanced data for sentiment analysis and natural language inference tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-pre-training-and-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongCite: Enabling LLMs to Generate Fine-grained Citations in Long-context QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcite-enabling-llms-to-generate-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though current long-context large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive capacities in answering user questions based on extensive text, the lack of citations in their responses makes user verification difficult, leading to concerns about their trustworthiness due to their potential hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcite-enabling-llms-to-generate-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Your Generative Model Detect Out-of-Distribution Covariate Shift?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-your-generative-model-detect-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models capture the ID data in an unsupervised manner, enabling them to effectively identify samples that deviate significantly from this learned distribution, irrespective of the downstream task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-your-generative-model-detect-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypothesizing Missing Causal Variables with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesizing-missing-causal-variables-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the scientific discovery process, in this work, we formulate a novel task where the input is a partial causal graph with missing variables, and the output is a hypothesis about the missing variables to complete the partial graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesizing-missing-causal-variables-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-VDM: Learning Single-Image 3D Human Gaussian Splatting from Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-vdm-learning-single-image-3d-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating lifelike 3D humans from a single RGB image remains a challenging task in computer vision, as it requires accurate modeling of geometry, high-quality texture, and plausible unseen parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-vdm-learning-single-image-3d-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Head Attention Residual Unfolded Network for Model-Based Pansharpening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-attention-residual-unfolded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of pansharpening and hypersharpening is to accurately combine a high-resolution panchromatic (PAN) image with a low-resolution multispectral (MS) or hyperspectral (HS) image, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-attention-residual-unfolded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Spurious Bias in Few-Shot Image Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-spurious-bias-in-few-shot-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a systematic and rigorous benchmark framework, termed FewSTAB, to fairly demonstrate and quantify varied degrees of robustness of few-shot classifiers to spurious bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-spurious-bias-in-few-shot-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Study on SAM 2 for Class-agnostic Instance-level Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-study-on-sam-2-for-class-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM) has demonstrated powerful zero-shot segmentation performance in natural scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-study-on-sam-2-for-class-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundless: Generating Photorealistic Synthetic Data for Object Detection in Urban Streetscapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundless-generating-photorealistic-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Boundless, a photo-realistic synthetic data generation system for enabling highly accurate object detection in dense urban streetscapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundless-generating-photorealistic-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
