<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 21:04:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>INSTRUCTSCORE: Towards Explainable Text Generation Evaluation with Automatic Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructscore-towards-explainable-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, since the advent of neural metrics, like COMET, BLEURT, and SEScore2, the newest generation of metrics show a high correlation with human judgment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructscore-towards-explainable-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Rationalization with Asymmetric Learning Rates: A Flexible Lipshitz Restraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-rationalization-with-asymmetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such a cooperative game may incur the degeneration problem where the predictor overfits to the uninformative pieces generated by a not yet well-trained generator and in turn, leads the generator to converge to a sub-optimal model that tends to select senseless pieces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-rationalization-with-asymmetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyglot or Not? Measuring Multilingual Encyclopedic Knowledge Retrieval from Foundation Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyglot-or-not-measuring-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we evaluate the capacity for foundation models to retrieve encyclopedic knowledge across a wide range of languages, topics, and contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyglot-or-not-measuring-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covariate balancing using the integral probability metric for causal inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covariate-balancing-using-the-integral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the existing weighting methods have desirable theoretical properties only when a certain model, either the propensity score or outcome regression model, is correctly specified.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covariate-balancing-using-the-integral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-CLIP: Semi-supervised Vision-Language Pre-training using Few Specialist Captions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-clip-semi-supervised-vision-language-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By combining these objectives, S-CLIP significantly enhances the training of CLIP using only a few image-text pairs, as demonstrated in various specialist domains, including remote sensing, fashion, scientific figures, and comics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-clip-semi-supervised-vision-language-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Heterogeneous Model Reuse by Density Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-heterogeneous-model-reuse-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies multiparty learning, aiming to learn a model using the private data of different participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-heterogeneous-model-reuse-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynosaur: A Dynamic Growth Paradigm for Instruction-Tuning Data Curation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynosaur-a-dynamic-growth-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a novel continual learning scenario for instruction tuning, selecting tasks based on instruction representations can be an effective replaying strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynosaur-a-dynamic-growth-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NORM: Knowledge Distillation via N-to-One Representation Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norm-knowledge-distillation-via-n-to-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By sequentially splitting the expanded student representation into N non-overlapping feature segments having the same number of feature channels as the teacher's, they can be readily forced to approximate the intact teacher representation simultaneously, formulating a novel many-to-one representation matching mechanism conditioned on a single teacher-student layer pair.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/norm-knowledge-distillation-via-n-to-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APPLS: A Meta-evaluation Testbed for Plain Language Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appls-a-meta-evaluation-testbed-for-plain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our research contributes the first meta-evaluation testbed for PLS and a comprehensive evaluation of existing metrics, offering insights with relevance to other text generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appls-a-meta-evaluation-testbed-for-plain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REC-MV: REconstructing 3D Dynamic Cloth from Monocular Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rec-mv-reconstructing-3d-dynamic-cloth-from-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above limitations, in this paper, we formulate this task as an optimization problem of 3D garment feature curves and surface reconstruction from monocular video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rec-mv-reconstructing-3d-dynamic-cloth-from-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophia: A Scalable Stochastic Second-order Optimizer for Language Model Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sophia-a-scalable-stochastic-second-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the massive cost of language model pre-training, a non-trivial improvement of the optimization algorithm would lead to a material reduction on the time and cost of training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sophia-a-scalable-stochastic-second-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clustering Indices based Automatic Classification Model Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-indices-based-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose an end-to-end Automated ML system for data classification based on our model selection method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-indices-based-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goodness of fit by Neyman-Pearson testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goodness-of-fit-by-neyman-pearson-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Neyman-Pearson strategy for hypothesis testing can be employed for goodness of fit if the alternative hypothesis $\rm H_1$ is generic enough not to introduce a significant bias while at the same time avoiding overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goodness-of-fit-by-neyman-pearson-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Prompting Assists Large Language Model on Web Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-prompting-assists-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) struggle on processing complicated observations in interactive decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-prompting-assists-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Prediction without Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-prediction-without-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Link prediction, which consists of predicting edges based on graph features, is a fundamental task in many graph applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-prediction-without-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Chat Language Models by Scaling High-quality Instructional Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chat-language-models-by-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning on instruction data has been widely validated as an effective practice for implementing chat language models like ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chat-language-models-by-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When the Music Stops: Tip-of-the-Tongue Retrieval for Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-the-music-stops-tip-of-the-tongue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a study of Tip-of-the-tongue (ToT) retrieval for music, where a searcher is trying to find an existing music entity, but is unable to succeed as they cannot accurately recall important identifying information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-the-music-stops-tip-of-the-tongue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind the spikes: Benign overfitting of kernels and neural networks in fixed dimension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-spikes-benign-overfitting-of-kernels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the smoothness of the estimators, and not the dimension, is the key: benign overfitting is possible if and only if the estimator's derivatives are large enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-spikes-benign-overfitting-of-kernels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Low-Resource Entity Recognition Through Translation and Annotation Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-low-resource-entity-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained multilingual language models have enabled significant advancements in cross-lingual transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-low-resource-entity-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Frame-level Directors for Zero-shot Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-frame-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the paradigm of AI-generated content (AIGC), there has been increasing attention in extending pre-trained text-to-image (T2I) models to text-to-video (T2V) generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-frame-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Focal Loss for Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-focal-loss-for-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While different variants of focal loss have been explored, it is difficult to find a balance between over-confidence and under-confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-focal-loss-for-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TVTSv2: Learning Out-of-the-box Spatiotemporal Visual Representations at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tvtsv2-learning-out-of-the-box-spatiotemporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that tuning a text encoder end-to-end, as done in previous work, is suboptimal since it may overfit in terms of styles, thereby losing its original generalization ability to capture the semantics of various language registers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tvtsv2-learning-out-of-the-box-spatiotemporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Detail Preservation for Customized Text-to-Image Generation: A Regularization-Free Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, generating images of novel concept provided by the user input image is still a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVA: A Dirichlet Process Based Incremental Deep Clustering Algorithm via Variational Auto-Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-a-dirichlet-process-based-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative model-based deep clustering frameworks excel in classifying complex data, but are limited in handling dynamic and complex features because they require prior knowledge of the number of clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-a-dirichlet-process-based-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterspeeches up my sleeve! Intent Distribution Learning and Persistent Fusion for Intent-Conditioned Counterspeech Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterspeeches-up-my-sleeve-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the complex and multifaceted nature of hate speech, utilizing multiple forms of counter-narratives with varying intents may be advantageous in different circumstances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterspeeches-up-my-sleeve-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Prompt Optimization via Constrained Generation for Zero-shot Re-ranker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-prompt-optimization-via-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along with highlighting the impact of optimization on the zero-shot re-ranker, we propose a novel discrete prompt optimization method, Constrained Prompt generation (Co-Prompt), with the metric estimating the optimum for re-ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-prompt-optimization-via-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Metrics for Medical Multi-Document Summarization Disagree with Human Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-metrics-for-medical-multi-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze how automated summarization evaluation metrics correlate with lexical features of generated summaries, to other automated metrics including several we propose in this work, and to aspects of human-assessed summary quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-metrics-for-medical-multi-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perception Test: A Diagnostic Benchmark for Multimodal Video Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-test-a-diagnostic-benchmark-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel multimodal video benchmark - the Perception Test - to evaluate the perception and reasoning skills of pre-trained multimodal models (e. g. Flamingo, BEiT-3, or GPT-4).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-test-a-diagnostic-benchmark-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Structure Modeling for Inductive Logical Reasoning Over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-structure-modeling-for-inductive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results demonstrate the effectiveness of our method on logical reasoning over KGs in both inductive and transductive settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-structure-modeling-for-inductive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning on Dynamic Graphs via Parameter Isolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-on-dynamic-graphs-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic graph learning methods commonly suffer from the catastrophic forgetting problem, where knowledge learned for previous graphs is overwritten by updates for new graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-on-dynamic-graphs-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-Mix Contrastive Learning with Audio Spectrogram Transformer on Respiratory Sound Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mix-contrastive-learning-with-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Respiratory sound contains crucial information for the early diagnosis of fatal lung diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mix-contrastive-learning-with-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Learning to Summarize with Large Language Models as References</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-to-summarize-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we investigate a new learning paradigm of text summarization models that considers the LLMs as the reference or the gold-standard oracle on commonly used summarization datasets such as the CNN/DailyMail dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-to-summarize-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPEECH: Structured Prediction with Energy-Based Event-Centric Hyperspheres</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-structured-prediction-with-energy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-centric structured prediction involves predicting structured outputs of events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-structured-prediction-with-energy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USB: A Unified Summarization Benchmark Across Tasks and Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usb-a-unified-summarization-benchmark-across</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that for some tasks, the amount of training data matters more than the domain where it comes from, while for other tasks training specifically on data from the target domain, even if limited, is more beneficial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usb-a-unified-summarization-benchmark-across</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QLoRA: Efficient Finetuning of Quantized LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our best model family, which we name Guanaco, outperforms all previous openly released models on the Vicuna benchmark, reaching 99. 3% of the performance level of ChatGPT while only requiring 24 hours of finetuning on a single GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Mutual Information for Disentangled Representations in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-mutual-information-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) environments can produce training data with spurious correlations between features due to the amount of training data or its limited feature coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-mutual-information-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting and Mitigating Hallucinations in Multilingual Summarisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-mitigating-hallucinations-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the existing faithful metrics focusing on English, even measuring the extent of this phenomenon in cross-lingual settings is hard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-mitigating-hallucinations-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parts of Speech-Grounded Subspaces in Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parts-of-speech-grounded-subspaces-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to separate representations of the different visual modalities in CLIP's joint vision-language space by leveraging the association between parts of speech and specific visual modes of variation (e. g. nouns relate to objects, adjectives describe appearance).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parts-of-speech-grounded-subspaces-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Remote Sensing Object Detection with Single Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-remote-sensing-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we make the first attempt to achieve RS object detection with single point supervision, and propose a PSOD framework tailored with RS images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-remote-sensing-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Adaptive Voxel-guided Sampling for Real-time Applications in Large-scale Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-adaptive-voxel-guided-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While point-based neural architectures have demonstrated their efficacy, the time-consuming sampler currently prevents them from performing real-time reasoning on scene-level point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-adaptive-voxel-guided-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Open Dataset and Model for Language Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-open-dataset-and-model-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve this by training on a curated dataset of monolingual data, the reliability of which we ensure by auditing a sample from each source and each language manually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-open-dataset-and-model-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype Adaption and Projection for Few- and Zero-shot 3D Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-adaption-and-projection-for-few-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the challenging task of few-shot and zero-shot 3D point cloud semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-adaption-and-projection-for-few-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Laplacian Pyramid Based Generative H&amp;E Stain Augmentation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-laplacian-pyramid-based-generative-h-e</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hematoxylin and Eosin (H&E) staining is a widely used sample preparation procedure for enhancing the saturation of tissue sections and the contrast between nuclei and cytoplasm in histology images for medical diagnostics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-laplacian-pyramid-based-generative-h-e</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TalkUp: A Novel Dataset Paving the Way for Understanding Empowering Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talkup-a-novel-dataset-paving-the-way-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empowering language is important in many real-world contexts, from education to workplace dynamics to healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talkup-a-novel-dataset-paving-the-way-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AxomiyaBERTa: A Phonologically-aware Transformer Model for Assamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axomiyaberta-a-phonologically-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we show that AxomiyaBERTa can leverage phonological signals for even more challenging tasks, such as a novel cross-document coreference task on a translated version of the ECB+ corpus, where we present a new SOTA result for an LRL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/axomiyaberta-a-phonologically-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IdEALS: Idiomatic Expressions for Advancement of Language Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideals-idiomatic-expressions-for-advancement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although significant progress has been made in developing methods for Grammatical Error Correction (GEC), addressing word choice improvements has been notably lacking and enhancing sentence expressivity by replacing phrases with advanced expressions is an understudied aspect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ideals-idiomatic-expressions-for-advancement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Speech Technology to 1,000+ Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expanding the language coverage of speech technology has the potential to improve access to information for many more people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Improving Optimization in Predictive Coding Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-optimization-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backpropagation (BP), the standard learning algorithm for artificial neural networks, is often considered biologically implausible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-optimization-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Kullback-Leibler Divergence Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-kullback-leibler-divergence-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve deeper into the Kullback-Leibler (KL) Divergence loss and observe that it is equivalent to the Doupled Kullback-Leibler (DKL) Divergence loss that consists of 1) a weighted Mean Square Error (wMSE) loss and 2) a Cross-Entropy loss incorporating soft labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-kullback-leibler-divergence-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP-SENet: A Speech Enhancement Model with Parallel Denoising of Magnitude and Phase Spectra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mp-senet-a-speech-enhancement-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes MP-SENet, a novel Speech Enhancement Network which directly denoises Magnitude and Phase spectra in parallel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mp-senet-a-speech-enhancement-model-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
