<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 09:15:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Enhance: A Deep Learning Approach to Extreme Deblurring of Text Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-enhance-a-deep-learning-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a novel deep-learning-based pipeline for the inverse problem of image deblurring, leveraging augmentation and pre-training with synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-enhance-a-deep-learning-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explaining Subjective Ground of Individuals on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-subjective-ground-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale language models have been reducing the gap between machines and humans in understanding the real world, yet understanding an individual's theory of mind and behavior from text is far from being resolved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-subjective-ground-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperbolic Sliced-Wasserstein via Geodesic and Horospherical Projections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-sliced-wasserstein-via-geodesic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been shown beneficial for many types of data which present an underlying hierarchical structure to be embedded in hyperbolic spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-sliced-wasserstein-via-geodesic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CITADEL: Conditional Token Interaction via Dynamic Lexical Routing for Efficient and Effective Multi-Vector Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citadel-conditional-token-interaction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we unify different multi-vector retrieval models from a token routing viewpoint and propose conditional token interaction via dynamic lexical routing, namely CITADEL, for efficient and effective multi-vector retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citadel-conditional-token-interaction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask4Help: Learning to Leverage an Expert for Embodied Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask4help-learning-to-leverage-an-expert-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embodied AI agents continue to become more capable every year with the advent of new models, environments, and benchmarks, but are still far away from being performant and reliable enough to be deployed in real, user-facing, applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask4help-learning-to-leverage-an-expert-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look More but Care Less in Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-more-but-care-less-in-video-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose Ample and Focal Network (AFNet), which is composed of two branches to utilize more frames but with less computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-more-but-care-less-in-video-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Losses Are Natural Criteria for Unsupervised Video Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-losses-are-natural-criteria-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video summarization aims to select the most informative subset of frames in a video to facilitate efficient video browsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-losses-are-natural-criteria-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmoothQuant: Accurate and Efficient Post-Training Quantization for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothquant-accurate-and-efficient-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SmoothQuant, a training-free, accuracy-preserving, and general-purpose post-training quantization (PTQ) solution to enable 8-bit weight, 8-bit activation (W8A8) quantization for LLMs that can be implemented efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothquant-accurate-and-efficient-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnostics for Deep Neural Networks with Automated Copy/Paste Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnostics-for-deep-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third, we compare this approach with other interpretability tools by attempting to rediscover trojans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnostics-for-deep-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowing What to Label for Few Shot Microscopy Image Cell Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowing-what-to-label-for-few-shot-microscopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we argue that the random selection of unlabelled training target images to be annotated and included in the support set may not enable an effective fine-tuning process, so we propose a new approach to optimise this image selection process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowing-what-to-label-for-few-shot-microscopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Gaussian Processes for Air Quality Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-gaussian-processes-for-air-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate, fine-grained air quality (AQ) monitoring is essential to control and reduce pollution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-gaussian-processes-for-air-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Knowledge Graph Error Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-knowledge-graph-error-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel framework - ContrAstive knowledge Graph Error Detection (CAGED).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-knowledge-graph-error-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Learning for Sparse Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-sparse-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this reason, we propose a multi-task learning network that can simultaneously predict the congestion classes and the speed of each road segment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-sparse-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to train your draGAN: A task oriented solution to imbalanced classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-your-dragan-a-task-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The long-standing challenge of building effective classification models for small and imbalanced datasets has seen little improvement since the creation of the Synthetic Minority Over-sampling Technique (SMOTE) over 20 years ago.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-your-dragan-a-task-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Persian ASR-based SER: Modification of Sharif Emotional Speech Database and Investigation of Persian Text Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-persian-asr-based-ser-modification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech Emotion Recognition (SER) is one of the essential perceptual methods of humans in understanding the situation and how to interact with others, therefore, in recent years, it has been tried to add the ability to recognize emotions to human-machine communication systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-persian-asr-based-ser-modification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Multi-stream Information Fusion for Trajectory Prediction in Low-illumination Scenarios: A Multi-channel Graph Convolutional Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multi-stream-information-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The optical flow channel is applied to capture the pattern of relative motion between adjacent camera frames and modelled by Spatial-Temporal Graph Convolutional Network (ST-GCN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multi-stream-information-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-based Causal Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-causal-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose model-based causal Bayesian optimization (MCBO), an algorithm that learns a full system model instead of only modeling intervention-reward pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-causal-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Residual for Tuning Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-residual-for-tuning-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale vision-language models (VLMs) pre-trained on billion-level data have learned general visual representations and broad visual concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-residual-for-tuning-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Adaptive Discriminative Feature Localization with Statistically Guaranteed Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-adaptive-discriminative-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply the proposed method to the MNIST dataset and the MIT-BIH dataset with a convolutional auto-encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-adaptive-discriminative-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Conditioned Reinforcement Learning to Solve Misunderstandings with Action Corrections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-conditioned-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate our approach, we propose a collection of benchmark environments for action correction in language-conditioned reinforcement learning, utilizing a synthetic instructor to generate language goals and their corresponding corrections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-conditioned-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNS: A generalizable Graph Neural Network-based simulator for particulate and fluid modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gns-a-generalizable-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The predictions are 5, 000x faster than traditional MPM simulations (2. 5 hours for MPM simulations versus 20 s for GNS simulation of granular flow).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gns-a-generalizable-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GENIUS: Sketch-based Language Model Pre-training via Extreme and Selective Masking for Text Generation and Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genius-sketch-based-language-model-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GENIUS: a conditional text generation model using sketches as input, which can fill in the missing contexts for a given sketch (key information consisting of textual spans, phrases, or words, concatenated by mask tokens).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genius-sketch-based-language-model-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Positive Sample Propagation along the Audio-Visual Event Line</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-positive-sample-propagation-along</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual and audio signals often coexist in natural environments, forming audio-visual events (AVEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-positive-sample-propagation-along</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGD-cGAN: A Dual Generator for Image Dewatering and Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgd-cgan-a-dual-generator-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our Dual Generator Dewatering cGAN (DGD-cGAN) removes the haze and colour cast induced by the water column and restores the true colours of underwater scenes whereby the effects of various attenuation and scattering phenomena that occur in underwater images are tackled by the two generators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgd-cgan-a-dual-generator-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Inference for Coadded Astronomical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-coadded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coadded astronomical images are created by stacking multiple single-exposure images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-coadded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalized Latent Factor Model Approach to Mixed-data Matrix Completion with Entrywise Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-latent-factor-model-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Matrix completion is a class of machine learning methods that concerns the prediction of missing entries in a partially observed matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-latent-factor-model-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bird's-eye View of Reranking: from List Level to Page Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bird-s-eye-view-of-reranking-from-list</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, simply applying a shared network for all the lists fails to capture the commonalities and distinctions in user behaviors on different lists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bird-s-eye-view-of-reranking-from-list</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Deep Learning Generalizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-deep-learning-generalizes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Very large deep learning models trained using gradient descent are remarkably resistant to memorization given their huge capacity, but are at the same time capable of fitting large datasets of pure noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-deep-learning-generalizes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aiMotive Dataset: A Multimodal Dataset for Robust Autonomous Driving with Long-Range Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aimotive-dataset-a-multimodal-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset consists of 176 scenes with synchronized and calibrated LiDAR, camera, and radar sensors covering a 360-degree field of view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aimotive-dataset-a-multimodal-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Good Practices in Evaluating Transfer Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-good-practices-in-evaluating-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation reveals new important insights: 1) Transferability is highly contextual, and some white-box defenses may give a false sense of security since they are actually vulnerable to (black-box) transfer attacks; 2) All transfer attacks are less stealthy, and their stealthiness can vary dramatically under the same $L_{\infty}$ bound.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-good-practices-in-evaluating-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientTrain: Exploring Generalized Curriculum Learning for Training Visual Backbones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-exploring-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is inspired by the phenomenon that deep networks mainly learn to recognize some 'easier-to-learn' discriminative patterns within each example at earlier stages of training, e. g., the lower-frequency components of images and the original information before data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-exploring-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTRv2: Bootstrapping End-to-End Multi-Object Tracking by Pretrained Object Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motrv2-bootstrapping-end-to-end-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose MOTRv2, a simple yet effective pipeline to bootstrap end-to-end multi-object tracking with a pretrained object detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motrv2-bootstrapping-end-to-end-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring machine learning (ML)-based risk prediction algorithms in the presence of confounding medical interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monitoring-machine-learning-ml-based-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitoring the performance of machine learning (ML)-based risk prediction models in healthcare is complicated by the issue of confounding medical interventions (CMI): when an algorithm predicts a patient to be at high risk for an adverse event, clinicians are more likely to administer prophylactic treatment and alter the very target that the algorithm aims to predict.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monitoring-machine-learning-ml-based-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Transformers with Dynamic Token Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformers-with-dynamic-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers achieve unrivalled performance in modelling language, but remain inefficient in terms of memory and time complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformers-with-dynamic-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSumm: Unified Few-shot Summarization with Multi-Task Pre-Training and Prefix-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisumm-unified-few-shot-summarization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diverse demands of different summarization tasks and their high annotation costs are driving a need for few-shot summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisumm-unified-few-shot-summarization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Building Text-To-Speech Systems for the Next Billion Users</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-text-to-speech-systems-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We open-source all models on the Bhashini platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-building-text-to-speech-systems-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstractive Summarization Guided by Latent Hierarchical Document Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstractive-summarization-guided-by-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential abstractive neural summarizers often do not use the underlying structure in the input article or dependencies between the input sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstractive-summarization-guided-by-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conffusion: Confidence Intervals for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conffusion-confidence-intervals-for-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have become the go-to method for many generative tasks, particularly for image-to-image generation tasks such as super-resolution and inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conffusion-confidence-intervals-for-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automated Design of Bayesian Optimization via Exploratory Landscape Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-design-of-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian optimization (BO) algorithms form a class of surrogate-based heuristics, aimed at efficiently computing high-quality solutions for numerical black-box optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-design-of-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Trajectory Representation Learning with Temporal Regularities and Travel Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-trajectory-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TRL aims to convert complicated raw trajectories into low-dimensional representation vectors, which can be applied to various downstream tasks, such as trajectory classification, clustering, and similarity computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-trajectory-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Tree-Structured Prototype Network for End-to-End Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tree-structured-prototype-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design a novel embedding method called tree-structured prototype, producing a set of hierarchical representative embeddings which capture the hierarchical semantic structure in textual space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tree-structured-prototype-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepPrivacy2: Towards Realistic Full-Body Anonymization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepprivacy2-towards-realistic-full-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) are widely adapted for anonymization of human figures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepprivacy2-towards-realistic-full-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Arbitrary Keypoints on Limbs and Skis with Sparse Partly Correct Segmentation Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-arbitrary-keypoints-on-limbs-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze different training techniques for freely selected and standard keypoints, including pseudo labels, and show in our experiments that only a few partly correct segmentation masks are sufficient for learning to detect arbitrary keypoints on limbs and skis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-arbitrary-keypoints-on-limbs-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternVideo-Ego4D: A Pack of Champion Solutions to Ego4D Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-ego4d-a-pack-of-champion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present our champion solutions to five tracks at Ego4D challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-ego4d-a-pack-of-champion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVDistill: Cross-Modal BEV Distillation for Multi-View 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevdistill-cross-modal-bev-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of directly training a depth prediction network, we unify the image and LiDAR features in the Bird-Eye-View (BEV) space and adaptively transfer knowledge across non-homogenous representations in a teacher-student paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevdistill-cross-modal-bev-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Commonsense-aware Representation Network for Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-commonsense-aware-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating consecutive descriptions for videos, i. e., Video Captioning, requires taking full advantage of visual representation along with the generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-commonsense-aware-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Vocal Quality Feature Embeddings for Dysphonic Voice Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-vocal-quality-feature-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a deep learning framework for generating acoustic feature embeddings sensitive to vocal quality and robust across different corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-vocal-quality-feature-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ignore Previous Prompt: Attack Techniques For Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignore-previous-prompt-attack-techniques-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based large language models (LLMs) provide a powerful foundation for natural language tasks in large-scale customer-facing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignore-previous-prompt-attack-techniques-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComMU: Dataset for Combinatorial Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commu-dataset-for-combinatorial-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Commercial adoption of automatic music composition requires the capability of generating diverse and high-quality music suitable for the desired context (e. g., music for romantic movies, action games, restaurants, etc.).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/commu-dataset-for-combinatorial-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effect of Pre-training for Transformer in Different Modality on Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effect-of-pre-training-for-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically investigate how pre-training on data of different modalities, such as language and vision, affects fine-tuning of Transformer-based models to Mujoco offline reinforcement learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effect-of-pre-training-for-transformer</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
