<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 21:06:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sampling is Matter: Point-guided 3D Human Mesh Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-is-matter-point-guided-3d-human-mesh-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though those approaches have shown the remarkable progress in 3D human mesh reconstruction, it is still difficult to directly infer the relationship between features, which are encoded from the 2D input image, and 3D coordinates of each vertex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-is-matter-point-guided-3d-human-mesh-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TieFake: Title-Text Similarity and Emotion-Aware Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiefake-title-text-similarity-and-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a scale-dot product attention mechanism to capture the similarity between title features and textual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiefake-title-text-similarity-and-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging RL Theory and Practice with the Effective Horizon</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-rl-theory-and-practice-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that prior bounds do not correlate well with when deep RL succeeds vs. fails, but discover a surprising property that does.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-rl-theory-and-practice-with-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Corpora for Germanic Low-Resource Languages and Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-corpora-for-germanic-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we instead focus on low-resource languages and in particular non-standardized low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-corpora-for-germanic-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Neuron Representations with Concept Vectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-neuron-representations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mechanistic interpretability aims to understand how models store representations by breaking down neural networks into interpretable units.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-neuron-representations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Multi-Camera People Tracking with Anchor-Guided Clustering and Spatio-Temporal Consistency ID Re-Assignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multi-camera-people-tracking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-camera multiple people tracking has become an increasingly important area of research due to the growing demand for accurate and efficient indoor people tracking systems, particularly in settings such as retail, healthcare centers, and transit hubs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multi-camera-people-tracking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density-Insensitive Unsupervised Domain Adaption on 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-insensitive-unsupervised-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, few works attempt to tackle the domain gap in objects, but still fail to adapt to the gap of varying beam-densities between two domains, which is critical to mitigate the characteristic differences of the LiDAR collectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-insensitive-unsupervised-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any-to-Any Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-to-any-style-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing approaches either apply the holistic style of the style image in a global manner, or migrate local colors and textures of the style image to the content counterparts in a pre-defined way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-to-any-style-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Semantic Segmentation with Semantic Boundaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-semantic-segmentation-with-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the recent development in improving semantic segmentation by incorporating boundaries as auxiliary tasks, we propose a multi-task framework that uses semantic boundary detection (SBD) as an auxiliary task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-semantic-segmentation-with-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Resource Scheduling with High Priority Users using Deep Deterministic Policy Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-resource-scheduling-with-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in mobile communication capabilities open the door for closer integration of pre-hospital and in-hospital care processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-resource-scheduling-with-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMT: All-Pairs Multi-Field Transforms for Efficient Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amt-all-pairs-multi-field-transforms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is based on two essential designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amt-all-pairs-multi-field-transforms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Adaptive Fusion Network for Hyperspectral Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-adaptive-fusion-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two key components contribute to improving the hyperspectral image denoising: A progressively multiscale information aggregation network and a co-attention fusion module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-adaptive-fusion-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMID: A Unified Self-Supervised Learning Framework for Remote Sensing Image Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmid-a-unified-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that this learning strategy is suboptimal in the realm of RS, since the required representations for different RS downstream tasks are often varied and complex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmid-a-unified-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://arxiv.org/abs/2304.09797</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-abs-2304-09797</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) in reasoning tasks depends heavily on prompt design, with Chain-of-Thought (CoT) and self-consistency being critical methods that enhance this ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-abs-2304-09797</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank-Based Learning and Local Model Based Evolutionary Algorithm for High-Dimensional Expensive Multi-Objective Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-based-learning-and-local-model-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a novel Classifier-assisted rank-based learning and Local Model based multi-objective Evolutionary Algorithm (CLMEA) is proposed for high-dimensional expensive multi-objective optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-based-learning-and-local-model-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rehabilitation Exercise Repetition Segmentation and Counting using Skeletal Body Joints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rehabilitation-exercise-repetition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach for segmenting and counting the repetitions of rehabilitation exercises performed by patients, based on their skeletal body joints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rehabilitation-exercise-repetition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chameleon: Plug-and-Play Compositional Reasoning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chameleon-plug-and-play-compositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have achieved remarkable progress in various natural language processing tasks with emergent abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chameleon-plug-and-play-compositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointerformer: Deep Reinforced Multi-Pointer Transformer for the Traveling Salesman Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointerformer-deep-reinforced-multi-pointer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traveling Salesman Problem (TSP), as a classic routing optimization problem originally arising in the domain of transportation and logistics, has become a critical task in broader domains, such as manufacturing and biology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointerformer-deep-reinforced-multi-pointer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Nature of 3D Generalization in Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-nature-of-3d-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern deep learning architectures for object recognition generalize well to novel views, but the mechanisms are not well understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-nature-of-3d-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Based Visual Segmentation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-visual-segmentation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, transformers, a type of neural network based on self-attention originally designed for natural language processing, have considerably surpassed previous convolutional or recurrent approaches in various vision processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-visual-segmentation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LipsFormer: Introducing Lipschitz Continuity to Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipsformer-introducing-lipschitz-continuity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous practical tricks that address training instability by learning rate warmup, layer normalization, attention formulation, and weight initialization, we show that Lipschitz continuity is a more essential property to ensure training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipsformer-introducing-lipschitz-continuity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust Visual-Semantic Embedding for Generalizable Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-visual-semantic-embedding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Multi-Modal Equivalent Transformer called MMET for more robust visual-semantic embedding learning on visual, textual and visual-textual tasks respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-visual-semantic-embedding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Verifiability in Generative Search Engines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-verifiability-in-generative-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative search engines directly generate responses to user queries, along with in-line citations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-verifiability-in-generative-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Earth Parser: Discovering 3D Prototypes in Aerial Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-earth-parser-discovering-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our goal is to provide a practical tool for analyzing 3D scenes with unique characteristics in the context of aerial surveying and mapping, without relying on application-specific user annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-earth-parser-discovering-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPMQA: Multimodal Question Answering on Product Manuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpmqa-multimodal-question-answering-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Taking into account the length of product manuals and the fact that a question is always related to a small number of pages, MPMQA can be naturally split into two subtasks: retrieving most related pages and then generating multimodal answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpmqa-multimodal-question-answering-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models Enable Simple Systems for Generating Structured Views of Heterogeneous Data Lakes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-enable-simple-systems-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code synthesis is cheap, but far less accurate than directly processing each document with the LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-enable-simple-systems-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling keywords and their positions in text generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-keywords-and-their-positions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle a novel task of controlling not only keywords but also the position of each keyword in the text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-keywords-and-their-positions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximate non-linear model predictive control with safety-augmented neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-non-linear-model-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method requires a single evaluation of the NN and forward integration of the input sequence online, which is fast to compute on resource-constrained systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-non-linear-model-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Carbon Storage Operations for Long-Term Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-carbon-storage-operations-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address these issues by modeling the decision-making process for carbon storage operations as a partially observable Markov decision process (POMDP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-carbon-storage-operations-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Offline Metric for the Debiasedness of Click Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-offline-metric-for-the-debiasedness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that debiasedness is a necessary condition for recovering unbiased and consistent relevance scores and for the invariance of click prediction under covariate shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-offline-metric-for-the-debiasedness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big-Little Adaptive Neural Networks on Low-Power Near-Subthreshold Processors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-little-adaptive-neural-networks-on-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the energy savings that near-subthreshold processors can obtain in edge AI applications and proposes strategies to improve them while maintaining the accuracy of the application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/big-little-adaptive-neural-networks-on-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Geometrically Generalized Covariate Shift Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-geometrically-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, the phenomenon that the marginal distribution of the data changes is called covariate shift, one of the most important research topics in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-geometrically-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Enhanced Hybrid Attention Network for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-enhanced-hybrid-attention-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, many recent studies represent that current self-attention based models are low-pass filters and are inadequate to capture high-frequency information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-enhanced-hybrid-attention-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Architecture Search for Visual Anomaly Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-architecture-search-for-visual-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents AutoPatch, the first application of neural architecture search to the complex task of segmenting visual anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-architecture-search-for-visual-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Unrestricted Document Image Rectification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unrestricted-document-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our best knowledge, this is the first learning-based method for the rectification of unrestricted document images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unrestricted-document-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeKGC: Code Language Model for Generative Knowledge Graph Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codekgc-code-language-model-for-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, large generative language model trained on structured data such as code has demonstrated impressive capability in understanding natural language for structural prediction and reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codekgc-code-language-model-for-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Language Model Based Textual Adversarial Example Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-language-model-based-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explore how to use the masked language model in adversarial detection, we propose a novel textual adversarial example detection method, namely Masked Language Model-based Detection (MLMD), which can produce clearly distinguishable signals between normal examples and adversarial examples by exploring the changes in manifolds induced by the masked language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-language-model-based-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling and unraveling aggregation and dispersion fallacies in group MCDM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-and-unraveling-aggregation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also discuss the errors in computing measures of dispersion, including standard deviation and distance functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-and-unraveling-aggregation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Situation Hyper-Graphs for Video Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-situation-hyper-graphs-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is trained in an end-to-end manner and optimized by a VQA loss with the cross-entropy function and a Hungarian matching loss for the situation graph prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-situation-hyper-graphs-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness of Visual Explanations to Common Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-of-visual-explanations-to-common</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the use of deep neural networks continues to grow, understanding their behaviour has become more crucial than ever.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-of-visual-explanations-to-common</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Fuse Monocular and Multi-view Cues for Multi-frame Depth Estimation in Dynamic Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-fuse-monocular-and-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To let the geometric perception learned from multi-view cues in static areas propagate to the monocular representation in dynamic areas and let monocular cues enhance the representation of multi-view cost volume, we propose a cross-cue fusion (CCF) module, which includes the cross-cue attention (CCA) to encode the spatially non-local relative intra-relations from each source to enhance the representation of the other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-fuse-monocular-and-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data and Knowledge Co-driving for Cancer Subtype Classification on Multi-Scale Histopathological Slides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-and-knowledge-co-driving-for-cancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Data and Knowledge Co-driving (D&K) model to replicate the process of cancer subtype classification on a histopathological slide like a pathologist.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-and-knowledge-co-driving-for-cancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saliency-aware Stereoscopic Video Retargeting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-aware-stereoscopic-video-retargeting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use 1D convolution for shifting the salient objects and design a stereo video Transformer to assist the retargeting process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-aware-stereoscopic-video-retargeting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of Image Denoising Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-image-denoising-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to investigate the applicability of existing denoising techniques, we compare a variety of denoising methods on both synthetic and real-world datasets for different applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-image-denoising-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Coarse-to-Fine Learning for Oriented Tiny Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-coarse-to-fine-learning-for-oriented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the exploration of adaptive label assignment in recent oriented object detectors, the extreme geometry shape and limited feature of oriented tiny objects still induce severe mismatch and imbalance issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-coarse-to-fine-learning-for-oriented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MER 2023: Multi-label Learning, Modality Robustness, and Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mer-2023-multi-label-learning-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past few decades, multimodal emotion recognition has made remarkable progress with the development of deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mer-2023-multi-label-learning-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting k-NN for Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-k-nn-for-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Language Models (PLMs), as parametric-based eager learners, have become the de-facto choice for current paradigms of Natural Language Processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-k-nn-for-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Need Two Detectors to Achieve Multi-Modal 3D Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-need-two-detectors-to-achieve-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, a new multi-object tracking framework is proposed in this paper based on multi-modal fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-need-two-detectors-to-achieve-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking Through the Glass: Neural Surface Reconstruction Against High Specular Reflections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-through-the-glass-neural-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this issue, we present a novel surface reconstruction framework, NeuS-HSR, based on implicit neural rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-through-the-glass-neural-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phase-Retrieval with Incomplete Autocorrelations Using Deep Convolutional Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase-retrieval-with-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Phase-retrieval techniques aim to recover the original signal from just the modulus of its Fourier transform, which is usually much easier to measure than its phase, but the standard iterative techniques tend to fail if only part of the modulus information is available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phase-retrieval-with-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
