<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 21:06:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning by Asking for Embodied Visual Navigation and Task Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-by-asking-for-embodied-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The research community has shown increasing interest in designing intelligent embodied agents that can assist humans in accomplishing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-by-asking-for-embodied-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Likelihood Score: Evaluating Generalization of Generative Models Using Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-likelihood-score-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indeed, likelihood-based metrics do not apply in many cases while pure sample-based metrics such as FID fail to capture known failure modes such as overfitting on training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-likelihood-score-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation for Robust Character Detection in Fantasy Novels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-for-robust-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named Entity Recognition (NER) is a low-level task often used as a foundation for solving higher level NLP problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-for-robust-character</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trading Information between Latents in Hierarchical Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trading-information-between-latents-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational Autoencoders (VAEs) were originally motivated (Kingma & Welling, 2014) as probabilistic generative models in which one performs approximate Bayesian inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trading-information-between-latents-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuKron: Constant-Size Lossy Compression of Sparse Reorderable Matrices and Tensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neukron-constant-size-lossy-compression-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The updates take time linear in the number of non-zeros in the input matrix, and the approximation of each entry can be retrieved in logarithmic time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neukron-constant-size-lossy-compression-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Visual Feedback to Guide Benchmark Creation: A Human-and-Metric-in-the-Loop Workflow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-visual-feedback-to-guide-benchmark-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In pursuit of creating better benchmarks, we propose VAIDA, a novel benchmark creation paradigm for NLP, that focuses on guiding crowdworkers, an under-explored facet of addressing benchmark idiosyncrasies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-visual-feedback-to-guide-benchmark-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Generalizability of Collaborative Dialogue Analysis with Multi-Feature Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-generalizability-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this problem, this paper introduces a multi-feature embedding (MFeEmb) that improves the generalizability of conflict prediction models trained on dialogue sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-generalizability-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reversible Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversible-vision-transformers-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reversible Vision Transformers achieve a reduced memory footprint of up to 15. 5x at roughly identical model complexity, parameters and accuracy, demonstrating the promise of reversible vision transformers as an efficient backbone for hardware resource limited training regimes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversible-vision-transformers-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REIN: A Comprehensive Benchmark Framework for Data Cleaning Methods in ML Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rein-a-comprehensive-benchmark-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a comprehensive benchmark, called REIN1, to thoroughly investigate the impact of data cleaning methods on various ML models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rein-a-comprehensive-benchmark-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Node Representation Learning via Node-to-Neighbourhood Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-node-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the excessive memory overheads of contrastive learning, we further propose a negative-free solution, where the main contribution is a Graph Signal Decorrelation (GSD) constraint to avoid representation collapse and over-smoothing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-node-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FrameBERT: Conceptual Metaphor Detection with Frame Embedding Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framebert-conceptual-metaphor-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FrameBERT, a RoBERTa-based model that can explicitly learn and incorporate FrameNet Embeddings for concept-level metaphor detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framebert-conceptual-metaphor-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rMultiNet: An R Package For Multilayer Networks Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmultinet-an-r-package-for-multilayer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper develops an R package rMultiNet to analyze multilayer network data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmultinet-an-r-package-for-multilayer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is This Loss Informative? Speeding Up Textual Inversion with Deterministic Objective Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-loss-informative-speeding-up-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generation models represent the next step of evolution in image synthesis, offering natural means of flexible yet fine-grained control over the result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-loss-informative-speeding-up-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gentlest ascent dynamics on manifolds defined by adaptively sampled point-clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gentlest-ascent-dynamics-on-manifolds-defined</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finding saddle points of dynamical systems is an important problem in practical applications such as the study of rare events of molecular systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gentlest-ascent-dynamics-on-manifolds-defined</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robot Synesthesia: A Sound and Emotion Guided AI Painter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-synesthesia-a-sound-and-emotion-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For speech, we decouple speech into its transcribed text and the tone of the speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robot-synesthesia-a-sound-and-emotion-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Perceive or Not to Perceive: Lightweight Stacked Hourglass Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-perceive-or-not-to-perceive-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human pose estimation (HPE) is a classical task in computer vision that focuses on representing the orientation of a person by identifying the positions of their joints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-perceive-or-not-to-perceive-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drawing Attention to Detail: Pose Alignment through Self-Attention for Fine-Grained Object Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drawing-attention-to-detail-pose-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intra-class variations in the open world lead to various challenges in classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drawing-attention-to-detail-pose-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global and Preference-based Optimization with Mixed Variables using Piecewise Affine Surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-preference-based-optimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization problems involving mixed variables, i. e., variables of numerical and categorical nature, can be challenging to solve, especially in the presence of complex constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-preference-based-optimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offsite-Tuning: Transfer Learning without Full Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offsite-tuning-transfer-learning-without-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Offsite-Tuning, a privacy-preserving and efficient transfer learning framework that can adapt billion-parameter foundation models to downstream data without access to the full model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offsite-tuning-transfer-learning-without-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Diffusion Models Further Improve Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-diffusion-models-further-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been recognized that the data generated by the denoising diffusion probabilistic model (DDPM) improves adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-diffusion-models-further-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Anomaly Detection: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly detection (AD) is a crucial task in machine learning with various applications, such as detecting emerging diseases, identifying financial frauds, and detecting fake news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Learning for Requirements Classification: An Exploratory Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-learning-for-requirements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Principal ideas-results: To address this challenge, this paper proposes an approach that employs the embedding-based unsupervised Zero-Shot Learning (ZSL) technique to perform requirements classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-learning-for-requirements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principled and Efficient Motif Finding for Structure Learning in Lifted Graphical Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-and-efficient-motif-finding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first principled approach for mining structural motifs in lifted graphical models, languages that blend first-order logic with probabilistic models, which uses a stochastic process to measure the similarity of entities in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-and-efficient-motif-finding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating a Structured Summary of Numerous Academic Papers: Dataset and Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-a-structured-summary-of-numerous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing MDS datasets usually focus on producing the structureless summary covering a few input documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-a-structured-summary-of-numerous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManiSkill2: A Unified Benchmark for Generalizable Manipulation Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maniskill2-a-unified-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizable manipulation skills, which can be composed to tackle long-horizon and complex daily chores, are one of the cornerstones of Embodied AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maniskill2-a-unified-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multilingual Language Models for Cross Lingual Fact Extraction from Low Resource Indian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multilingual-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross Lingual Information Extraction aims at extracting factual information in the form of English triples from low resource Indian Language text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multilingual-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Generative Adversarial Imitation Learning with Mid-level Input Generation for Autonomous Driving on Urban Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-generative-adversarial-imitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed hGAIL consists of an hierarchical Adversarial Imitation Learning architecture composed of two main modules: the GAN (Generative Adversarial Nets) which generates the Bird's-Eye View (BEV) representation mainly from the images of three frontal cameras of the vehicle, and the GAIL which learns to control the vehicle based mainly on the BEV predictions from the GAN as input. Our experiments have shown that GAIL exclusively from cameras (without BEV) fails to even learn the task, while hGAIL, after training, was able to autonomously navigate successfully in all intersections of the city.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-generative-adversarial-imitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RayNet: A Simulation Platform for Developing Reinforcement Learning-Driven Network Protocols</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raynet-a-simulation-platform-for-developing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce RayNet, a scalable and adaptable simulation framework for the development of learning-based network protocols.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raynet-a-simulation-platform-for-developing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transformer-based Response Evaluator for Open-Domain Spoken Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-response-evaluator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we collect a corpus of Athena conversations with live human traffic, where potential responses from all enabled response generators are logged and subsequently annotated for response quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transformer-based-response-evaluator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Intra-Image Contrastive Learning for Weakly Supervised One-Step Person Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-intra-image-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope that our simple intra-image contrastive learning can provide more paradigms on weakly supervised person search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-intra-image-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Extremely Lightweight Distracted Driver Recognition With Distillation-Based Neural Architecture Search and Knowledge Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-extremely-lightweight-distracted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on the Statefarm Distracted Driver Detection Dataset and AUC Distracted Driver Dataset show that the proposed approach is highly effective for recognizing distracted driving behaviors from photos: (1) the teacher network's accuracy surpasses the previous best accuracy; (2) the student network achieves very high accuracy with only 0. 42M parameters (around 55% of the previous most lightweight model).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-extremely-lightweight-distracted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Sampling with Approximate Transport Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-sampling-with-approximate-transport-maps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transport maps can ease the sampling of distributions with non-trivial geometries by transforming them into distributions that are easier to handle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-sampling-with-approximate-transport-maps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust and Scalable Bayesian Online Changepoint Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-scalable-bayesian-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an online, provably robust, and scalable Bayesian approach for changepoint detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-scalable-bayesian-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Human Motion Prediction Guided by Multi-Level Spatial-Temporal Anchors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-human-motion-prediction-guided-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting diverse human motions given a sequence of historical poses has received increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-human-motion-prediction-guided-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniPC: A Unified Predictor-Corrector Framework for Fast Sampling of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipc-a-unified-predictor-corrector-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining UniP and UniC, we propose a unified predictor-corrector framework called UniPC for the fast sampling of DPMs, which has a unified analytical form for any order and can significantly improve the sampling quality over previous methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipc-a-unified-predictor-corrector-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Constraints with Prompting for Zero-Shot Event Argument Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-constraints-with-prompting-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to use global constraints with prompting to effectively tackles event argument classification without any annotation and task-specific training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-constraints-with-prompting-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Select Pivotal Samples for Meta Re-weighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-pivotal-samples-for-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study how to learn to identify such a meta sample set from a large, imperfect training set, that is subsequently cleaned and used to optimize performance in the meta re-weighting setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-select-pivotal-samples-for-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey on Multimodal Recommender Systems: Taxonomy, Evaluation, and Future Directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation systems have become popular and effective tools to help users discover their interesting items by modeling the user preference and item property based on implicit interactions (e. g., purchasing and clicking).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Contextomized Quotes in News Headlines by Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-contextomized-quotes-in-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quotes are critical for establishing credibility in news articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-contextomized-quotes-in-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Question Answering against Distribution Shifts with Test-Time Adaptation: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-question-answering-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer this question, we evaluate test-time adaptation (TTA) to improve a model after deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-question-answering-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polynomial Neural Fields for Subband Decomposition and Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polynomial-neural-fields-for-subband</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this framework to design Fourier PNFs, which match state-of-the-art performance in signal representation tasks that use neural fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polynomial-neural-fields-for-subband</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybrIK-Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrik-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HybrIK relies on a combination of analytical inverse kinematics and deep learning to produce more accurate 3D pose estimation from 2D monocular images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrik-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Attention via Control Variates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-via-control-variates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Built upon previous progress of RFA, we characterize this gap through the lens of control variates and show that RFA can be decomposed into a sum of multiple control variate estimators for each element in the sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-via-control-variates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rehabilitating Homeless: Dataset and Key Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rehabilitating-homeless-dataset-and-key</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a large anonymized dataset of homelessness alongside insights into the data-driven rehabilitation of homeless people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rehabilitating-homeless-dataset-and-key</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark on Uncertainty Quantification for Deep Learning Prognostics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-on-uncertainty-quantification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The assessment includes RUL prediction accuracy, the quality of predictive uncertainty, and the possibility to break down the total predictive uncertainty into its aleatoric and epistemic parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-on-uncertainty-quantification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMBO: A Complete Benchmark for Open KG Canonicalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combo-a-complete-benchmark-for-open-kg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The subject and object noun phrases and the relation in open KG have severe redundancy and ambiguity and need to be canonicalized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combo-a-complete-benchmark-for-open-kg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Trained to Identify Words Provide a Good Account of Visual Form Priming Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-trained-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models tend to include hand-coded orthographic representations with single unit coding for specific forms of knowledge (e. g., units coding for a letter in a given position or a letter sequence).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-trained-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictable MDP Abstraction for Unsupervised Model-Based RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictable-mdp-abstraction-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key component of model-based reinforcement learning (RL) is a dynamics model that predicts the outcomes of actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictable-mdp-abstraction-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inefficiency of CFMs: hedging perspective and agent-based simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inefficiency-of-cfms-hedging-perspective-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate whether the fee income from trades on the CFM is sufficient for the liquidity providers to hedge away the exposure to market risk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inefficiency-of-cfms-hedging-perspective-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channelformer: Attention based Neural Solution for Wireless Channel Estimation and Effective Online Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channelformer-attention-based-neural-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an encoder-decoder neural architecture (called Channelformer) to achieve improved channel estimation for orthogonal frequency-division multiplexing (OFDM) waveforms in downlink scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channelformer-attention-based-neural-solution</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
