<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 09:13:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling the Mystery of Artifacts in Machine Generated Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-the-mystery-of-artifacts-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As neural Text Generation Models (TGM) have become more and more capable of generating text indistinguishable from human-written ones, the misuse of text generation technologies can have serious ramifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-the-mystery-of-artifacts-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Two-way Partial AUC with an End-to-end Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-two-way-partial-auc-with-an-end-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The critical challenge along this course lies in the difficulty of performing gradient-based optimization with end-to-end stochastic training, even with a proper choice of surrogate loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-two-way-partial-auc-with-an-end-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Clinically Assisted Colorectal Polyp Recognition via Structured Cross-modal Representation Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-clinically-assisted-colorectal-polyp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By aligning the class tokens and spatial attention maps of paired NBI and WL images at different levels, the Transformer achieves the ability to keep both global and local representation consistency for the above two modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-clinically-assisted-colorectal-polyp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Surgical Instrument Segmentation: A Background Image Can Be All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-surgical-instrument-segmentation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data diversity and volume are crucial to the success of training deep learning models, while in the medical imaging field, the difficulty and cost of data collection and annotation are especially huge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-surgical-instrument-segmentation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Spatio-temporal Aggregation for Insubstantial Object Detection: Benchmark Dataset and Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-spatio-temporal-aggregation-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We endeavor on a rarely explored task named Insubstantial Object Detection (IOD), which aims to localize the object with following characteristics: (1) amorphous shape with indistinct boundary; (2) similarity to surroundings; (3) absence in color.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-spatio-temporal-aggregation-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGAR: Critic Guided Action Redistribution in Reinforcement Leaning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgar-critic-guided-action-redistribution-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As discussed in this paper, under the settings of the off-policy actor critic algorithms, we demonstrate that the critic can bring more expected discounted rewards than or at least equal to the actor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgar-critic-guided-action-redistribution-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICOS Protein Expression Segmentation: Can Transformer Networks Give Better Results?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icos-protein-expression-segmentation-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biomarkers identify a patients response to treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icos-protein-expression-segmentation-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Error Templates for Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-error-templates-for-grammatical-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have accumulated 1, 119 error templates for Chinese GEC based on this method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-error-templates-for-grammatical-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theory-Grounded Measurement of U.S. Social Stereotypes in English Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theory-grounded-measurement-of-u-s-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NLP models trained on text have been shown to reproduce human stereotypes, which can magnify harms to marginalized groups when systems are deployed at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theory-grounded-measurement-of-u-s-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complementary datasets to COCO for object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-datasets-to-coco-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For nearly a decade, the COCO dataset has been the central test bed of research in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complementary-datasets-to-coco-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Sensing and Measurements Reuse for Image Compressed Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-sensing-and-measurements-reuse-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods obtain measurements only from partial features in the network and use them only once for image reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-sensing-and-measurements-reuse-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence fusion with contextual discounting for multi-modality medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidence-fusion-with-contextual-discounting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As information sources are usually imperfect, it is necessary to take into account their reliability in multi-source information fusion tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidence-fusion-with-contextual-discounting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warped Convolution Networks for Homography Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warped-convolution-networks-for-homography</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Warped Convolution Networks (WCN) to effectively estimate the homography transformation by SL(3) group and sl(3) algebra with group convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warped-convolution-networks-for-homography</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-in-the-Loop Large-Scale Predictive Maintenance of Workstations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-large-scale-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a human-in-the-loop PdM approach in which a machine learning system predicts future problems in sets of workstations (computers, laptops, and servers).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-large-scale-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Generalizability and Predictability of Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalizability-and-predictability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By using far more meta-training data than prior work, RecZilla is able to substantially reduce the level of human involvement when faced with a new recommender system application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalizability-and-predictability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An adaptive graph learning method for automated molecular interactions and properties predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-graph-learning-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In fact, the pursuit of high prediction performance on a limited number of datasets has crystallized their architectures and hyperparameters, making them lose advantage in repurposing to new data generated in drug discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-graph-learning-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waypoint Generation in Row-based Crops with Deep Learning and Contrastive Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waypoint-generation-in-row-based-crops-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a learning-based approach to tackle waypoint generation for planning a navigation path for row-based crops, starting from a top-view map of the region-of-interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waypoint-generation-in-row-based-crops-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Domain Adaptation via Normalizing Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-domain-adaptation-via-normalizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose using normalizing flows to mitigate this problem while maintaining the framework of unsupervised domain adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-domain-adaptation-via-normalizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source FPGA-ML codesign for the MLPerf Tiny Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-fpga-ml-codesign-for-the-mlperf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present our development experience and recent results for the MLPerf Tiny Inference Benchmark on field-programmable gate array (FPGA) platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-fpga-ml-codesign-for-the-mlperf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NovelCraft: A Dataset for Novelty Detection and Discovery in Open Worlds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novelcraft-a-dataset-for-novelty-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results suggest an opportunity for future research: models aware of task-specific costs of different types of mistakes could more effectively detect and adapt to novelty in open worlds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novelcraft-a-dataset-for-novelty-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RetroGraph: Retrosynthetic Planning with Graph Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrograph-retrosynthetic-planning-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the same intermediate molecules are visited many times in the searching process, and they are usually independently treated in previous tree-based methods (e. g., AND-OR tree search, Monte Carlo tree search).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrograph-retrosynthetic-planning-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-dimensional total absorption spectroscopy with conditional generative adversarial networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-dimensional-total-absorption-spectroscopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the use of machine learning techniques to remove the response of large volume $\gamma$-ray detectors from experimental spectra.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-dimensional-total-absorption-spectroscopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Geometric Method for Improved Uncertainty Estimation in Real-time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-method-for-improved-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the probability of a specific input to be correct is called uncertainty (or confidence) estimation and is crucial for risk management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-geometric-method-for-improved-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilizing Expert Features for Contrastive Learning of Time-Series Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-expert-features-for-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We therefore devise ExpCLR, a novel contrastive learning approach built on an objective that utilizes expert features to encourage both properties for the learned representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-expert-features-for-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>plingo: A system for probabilistic reasoning in clingo based on lpmln</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plingo-a-system-for-probabilistic-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present plingo, an extension of the ASP system clingo with various probabilistic reasoning modes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plingo-a-system-for-probabilistic-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Topological characterisation of Weisfeiler-Leman equivalence classes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-topological-characterisation-of-weisfeiler</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we rely on the theory of covering spaces to fully characterize the classes of graphs that GNNs cannot distinguish.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-topological-characterisation-of-weisfeiler</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing Change Detection (Segmentation) using Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-change-detection-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human civilization has an increasingly powerful influence on the earth system, and earth observations are an invaluable tool for assessing and mitigating the negative impacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-change-detection-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shilling Black-box Recommender Systems by Learning to Generate Fake User Profiles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shilling-black-box-recommender-systems-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leg-UP learns user behavior patterns from real users in the sampled ``templates'' and constructs fake user profiles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shilling-black-box-recommender-systems-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Dependent Sound Event Detection for DCASE 2022 Challenge Task 4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-dependent-sound-event-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many deep learning methods on other domains have been applied to sound event detection (SED), differences between original domains of the methods and SED have not been appropriately considered so far.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-dependent-sound-event-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Informed Statistical Modeling for Wildfire Aerosols Process Using Multi-Source Geostationary Satellite Remote-Sensing Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-statistical-modeling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasingly frequent wildfires significantly affect solar energy production as the atmospheric aerosols generated by wildfires diminish the incoming solar radiation to the earth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-statistical-modeling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundamental limitations on the control of lossless systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fundamental-limitations-on-the-control-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we derive fundamental limitations on the levels of $H_2$ and $H_\infty{}$ performance that can be achieved when controlling lossless systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fundamental-limitations-on-the-control-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReuseKNN: Neighborhood Reuse for Privacy-Aware Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reuseknn-neighborhood-reuse-for-privacy-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[User-based KNN recommender systems (UserKNN) utilize the rating data of a target user's k nearest neighbors in the recommendation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reuseknn-neighborhood-reuse-for-privacy-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical-VQA: Visual Question Answering in Surgical Scenes using Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqa-visual-question-answering-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This overload often limits their time answering questionnaires from patients, medical students or junior residents related to surgical procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqa-visual-question-answering-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Physical Metric For 6-DoF Grasp Pose Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-physical-metric-for-6-dof-grasp-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[6-DoF grasp pose detection of multi-grasp and multi-object is a challenge task in the field of intelligent robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-physical-metric-for-6-dof-grasp-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical Contrastive Language Image Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-contrastive-language-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show a representation grouping effect during this process: the InfoNCE objective indirectly groups semantically similar representations together via randomly emerged within-modal anchors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-contrastive-language-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Vocabulary Object Detection with Proposal Mining and Prediction Equalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary object detection (OVD) aims to scale up vocabulary size to detect objects of novel categories beyond the training vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-based Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-based-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AgentNet is inspired by sublinear algorithms, featuring a computational complexity that is independent of the graph size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-based-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>reStructured Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restructured-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we test our model in the 2022 College Entrance Examination English that happened a few days ago (2022. 06. 08), and it gets a total score of 134 (v. s.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restructured-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Type Clustering using Markov Directly-Follow Multigraph in Object-Centric Process Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-type-clustering-using-markov-directly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This graph is used to calculate a similarity matrix for discovering clusters of similar case notions based on a threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-type-clustering-using-markov-directly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenXAI: Towards a Transparent Evaluation of Model Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openxai-towards-a-transparent-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenXAI comprises of the following key components: (i) a flexible synthetic data generator and a collection of diverse real-world datasets, pre-trained models, and state-of-the-art feature attribution methods, (ii) open-source implementations of twenty-two quantitative metrics for evaluating faithfulness, stability (robustness), and fairness of explanation methods, and (iii) the first ever public XAI leaderboards to benchmark explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openxai-towards-a-transparent-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facke: a Survey on Generative Models for Face Swapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facke-a-survey-on-generative-models-for-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate into the performance of mainstream neural generative models on the very task of swapping faces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facke-a-survey-on-generative-models-for-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Resolution, Multi-Horizon Distributed Solar PV Power Forecasting with Forecast Combinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-multi-horizon-distributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a forecast combination approach based on particle swarm optimization (PSO) that will enable a forecaster to produce accurate forecasts for the task at hand by weighting the forecasts produced by individual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-multi-horizon-distributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoccerCPD: Formation and Role Change-Point Detection in Soccer Matches Using Spatiotemporal Tracking Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soccercpd-formation-and-role-change-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In fluid team sports such as soccer and basketball, analyzing team formation is one of the most intuitive ways to understand tactics from domain participants' point of view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soccercpd-formation-and-role-change-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-LexSum: Real-World Summaries of Civil Rights Lawsuits at Multiple Granularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-lexsum-real-world-summaries-of-civil</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of large language models, methods for abstractive summarization have made great strides, creating potential for use in applications to aid knowledge workers processing unwieldy document collections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-lexsum-real-world-summaries-of-civil</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2TNet: Spatio-Temporal Transformer Networks for Trajectory Prediction in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2tnet-spatio-temporal-transformer-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To safely and rationally participate in dense and heterogeneous traffic, autonomous vehicles require to sufficiently analyze the motion patterns of surrounding traffic-agents and accurately predict their future trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2tnet-spatio-temporal-transformer-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-optimal control of dynamical systems with neural ordinary differential equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-control-of-dynamical-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimal control problems naturally arise in many scientific applications where one wishes to steer a dynamical system from a certain initial state $\mathbf{x}_0$ to a desired target state $\mathbf{x}^*$ in finite time $T$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-control-of-dynamical-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecting a French Dictionary from the Beginning of the 20th Century to Wikidata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-a-french-dictionary-from-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe a new lexical resource, where we connected all the dictionary entries of the history and geography part to current data sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-a-french-dictionary-from-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated GI tract segmentation using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-gi-tract-segmentation-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a time-consuming and labor-intensive process that can easily prolong treatments from 15 minutes to an hour a day unless deep learning methods can automate the segmentation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-gi-tract-segmentation-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Context Tagging for Utterance Rewriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-tagging-for-utterance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HCT (i) tags the source string with token-level edit actions and slotted rules and (ii) fills in the resulting rule slots with spans from the dialogue context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-tagging-for-utterance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A view of mini-batch SGD via generating functions: conditions of convergence, phase transitions, benefit from negative momenta</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-view-of-mini-batch-sgd-via-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mini-batch SGD with momentum is a fundamental algorithm for learning large predictive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-view-of-mini-batch-sgd-via-generating</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
