<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 21:06:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BLT: Can Large Language Models Handle Basic Legal Text?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blt-can-large-language-models-handle-basic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the best publicly available LLMs like GPT-4 and PaLM 2 currently perform poorly at basic text handling required of lawyers or paralegals, such as looking up the text at a line of a witness deposition or at a subsection of a contract.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blt-can-large-language-models-handle-basic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Constitutes a Faithful Summary? Preserving Author Perspectives in News Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-constitutes-a-faithful-summary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a first step towards designing summarization systems that are faithful to the author's opinions and perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-constitutes-a-faithful-summary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICXML: An In-Context Learning Framework for Zero-Shot Extreme Multi-Label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icxml-an-in-context-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the task of Extreme Multi-Label Classification (XMC) whose goal is to predict multiple labels for each instance from an extremely large label space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icxml-an-in-context-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Symbolic Integration Brings Causal and Reliable Reasoning Proofs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-integration-brings-causal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though prompting LLMs with various reasoning structures produces reasoning proofs along with answers, these proofs are not ensured to be causal and reliable due to the inherent defects of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-integration-brings-causal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLNet: Scale-Modulated Query and Localization Network for Few-Shot Class-Agnostic Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlnet-scale-modulated-query-and-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the localization stage, the Scale-aware Multi-head Localization (SAML) module utilizes the query tensor to predict the confidence, location, and size of each potential object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlnet-scale-modulated-query-and-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PWISeg: Point-based Weakly-supervised Instance Segmentation for Surgical Instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwiseg-point-based-weakly-supervised-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel yet effective weakly-supervised surgical instrument instance segmentation approach, named Point-based Weakly-supervised Instance Segmentation (PWISeg).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwiseg-point-based-weakly-supervised-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center Focusing Network for Real-Time LiDAR Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-focusing-network-for-real-time-lidar-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR panoptic segmentation facilitates an autonomous vehicle to comprehensively understand the surrounding objects and scenes and is required to run in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-focusing-network-for-real-time-lidar-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JaxMARL: Multi-Agent RL Environments in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxmarl-multi-agent-rl-environments-in-jax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This not only enables GPU acceleration, but also provides a more flexible MARL environment, unlocking the potential for self-play, meta-learning, and other future applications in MARL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxmarl-multi-agent-rl-environments-in-jax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvTimeSurvival: Survival Analysis On The Patient With Multiple Visits/Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survtimesurvival-survival-analysis-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces "SurvTimeSurvival: Survival Analysis On Patients With Multiple Visits/Records", utilizing the Transformer model to not only handle the complexities of time-varying covariates but also covariates data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survtimesurvival-survival-analysis-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining the Laparoscopic Spatial Sense: AI-based Intra- and Postoperative Measurement from Stereoimages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redefining-the-laparoscopic-spatial-sense-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant challenge in image-guided surgery is the accurate measurement task of relevant structures such as vessel segments, resection margins, or bowel lengths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redefining-the-laparoscopic-spatial-sense-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don't need a personality test to know these models are unreliable: Assessing the Reliability of Large Language Models on Psychometric Instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-don-t-need-a-personality-test-to-know</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The versatility of Large Language Models (LLMs) on natural language understanding tasks has made them popular for research in social sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-don-t-need-a-personality-test-to-know</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facilitating the sharing of electrophysiology data analysis results through in-depth provenance capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facilitating-the-sharing-of-electrophysiology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Alpaca (Automated Lightweight Provenance Capture), a tool that captures fine-grained provenance information with minimal user intervention when running data analysis pipelines implemented in Python scripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facilitating-the-sharing-of-electrophysiology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedFusion: Manifold Driven Federated Learning for Multi-satellite and Multi-modality Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfusion-manifold-driven-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-satellite, multi-modality in-orbit fusion is a challenging task as it explores the fusion representation of complex high-dimensional data under limited computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfusion-manifold-driven-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFPS: A unified framework for partially-annotated federated segmentation in heterogeneous data distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufps-a-unified-framework-for-partially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Unified Federated Partially-labeled Segmentation (UFPS) framework to segment pixels within all classes for partially-annotated datasets by training a totipotential global model without class collision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufps-a-unified-framework-for-partially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARES: An Automated Evaluation Framework for Retrieval-Augmented Generation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-an-automated-evaluation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) systems traditionally relies on hand annotations for input queries, passages to retrieve, and responses to generate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-an-automated-evaluation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Your Work with Confidence: Confidence Bands for Tuning Curves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-your-work-with-confidence-confidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The choice of hyperparameters greatly impacts performance in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-your-work-with-confidence-confidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reevaluation of Event Extraction: Past, Present, and Future Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reevaluation-of-event-extraction-past</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first identify and discuss these evaluation challenges, including the unfair comparisons resulting from different assumptions about data or different data preprocessing steps, the incompleteness of the current evaluation framework leading to potential dataset bias or data split bias, and low reproducibility of prior studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reevaluation-of-event-extraction-past</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Evaluation and Insights into the Use of Deep Neural Networks to Detect and Quantify Lymphoma Lesions in PET/CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-and-insights-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study performs comprehensive evaluation of four neural network architectures (UNet, SegResNet, DynUNet, and SwinUNETR) for lymphoma lesion segmentation from PET/CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-and-insights-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning with Whom? Large Language Models Have Gender and Racial Biases in Subjective NLP Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-with-whom-large-language-models-have</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that for both tasks, model predictions are closer to the labels from White and female participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-with-whom-large-language-models-have</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUQL: Conversational Search over Structured and Unstructured Data with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suql-conversational-search-over-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over 51% of the questions in the dataset require both structured and unstructured data, suggesting that it is a common phenomenon.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suql-conversational-search-over-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inherently Interpretable Time Series Classification via Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherently-interpretable-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional Time Series Classification (TSC) methods are often black boxes that obscure inherent interpretation of their decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherently-interpretable-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging LLMs in Scholarly Knowledge Graph Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-llms-in-scholarly-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a scholarly Knowledge Graph Question Answering (KGQA) that answers bibliographic natural language questions by leveraging a large language model (LLM) in a few-shot manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-llms-in-scholarly-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-data Learning for Bayesian Additive Regression Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-data-learning-for-bayesian-additive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose to incorporate co-data, i. e. external information on the covariates, into Bayesian additive regression trees (BART), a sum-of-trees prediction model that utilizes priors on the tree parameters to prevent overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-data-learning-for-bayesian-additive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAM-E: Mammographic synthetic image generation with diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mam-e-mammographic-synthetic-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we propose using stable diffusion models for the inpainting of synthetic lesions on healthy mammograms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mam-e-mammographic-synthetic-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAIA: Delving into Gradient-based Attribution Abnormality for Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaia-delving-into-gradient-based-attribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This perspective is motivated by our observation that gradient-based attribution methods encounter challenges in assigning feature importance to OOD data, thereby yielding divergent explanation patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaia-delving-into-gradient-based-attribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pachinko: Patching Interpretable QA Models through Natural Language Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pachinko-patching-interpretable-qa-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first one, we present users with incorrect answers and corresponding rationales of various formats and ask them to provide natural language feedback to revise the rationale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pachinko-patching-interpretable-qa-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Song Describer Dataset: a Corpus of Audio Captions for Music-and-Language Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-song-describer-dataset-a-corpus-of-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Song Describer dataset (SDD), a new crowdsourced corpus of high-quality audio-caption pairs, designed for the evaluation of music-and-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-song-describer-dataset-a-corpus-of-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention-Based Denoising Framework for Personality Detection in Social Media Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-denoising-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In social media networks, users produce a large amount of text content anytime, providing researchers with a valuable approach to digging for personality-related information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-denoising-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Can We Extract Diverse Perspectives from Large Language Models? Criteria-Based Diversity Prompting!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-extract-diverse-perspectives</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate this problem as diversity extraction in LLMs and propose a criteria-based prompting technique to ground diverse opinions and measure perspective diversity from the generated criteria words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-extract-diverse-perspectives</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On some elusive aspects of databases hindering AI based discovery: A case study on superconducting materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-some-elusive-aspects-of-databases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It stands to reason that the amount and the quality of big data is of key importance for setting up accurate AI-driven models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-some-elusive-aspects-of-databases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepEMD: A Transformer-based Fast Estimation of the Earth Mover's Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepemd-a-transformer-based-fast-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an attention-based model to compute an accurate approximation of the EMD that can be used as a training loss for generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepemd-a-transformer-based-fast-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of a block structure on the Lotka-Volterra model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-a-block-structure-on-the-lotka</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the important case of two communities of interacting species, study how interactions affect their respective equilibrium.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-a-block-structure-on-the-lotka</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Basics: A Simple Recipe for Improving Out-of-Domain Retrieval in Dense Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-to-basics-a-simple-recipe-for-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prevailing research practice today often relies on training dense retrievers on existing large datasets such as MSMARCO and then experimenting with ways to improve zero-shot generalization capabilities to unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-to-basics-a-simple-recipe-for-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group-Aware Interest Disentangled Dual-Training for Personalized Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-aware-interest-disentangled-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The users' group participation on social platforms reveals their interests and can be utilized as side information to mitigate the data sparsity and cold-start problem in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-aware-interest-disentangled-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongBoX: Evaluating Transformers on Long-Sequence Clinical Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longbox-evaluating-transformers-on-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessing these models on long sequences is crucial since prior work in the general domain has demonstrated performance degradation of LLMs on longer texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longbox-evaluating-transformers-on-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Differentiable Logics for Learning Systems: A Research Preview</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-differentiable-logics-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive research on formal verification of machine learning (ML) systems indicates that learning from data alone often fails to capture underlying background knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-differentiable-logics-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Anomaly Detection for Chest X-Ray Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-for-chest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chest X-Ray (CXR) examination is a common method for assessing thoracic diseases in clinical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-for-chest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-Former: Memory-Supported Transformer for Weakly Supervised Change Detection with Patch-Level Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-former-memory-supported-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to capture the semantic variations associated with the changed and unchanged regions from the patch-level annotations to obtain promising change results is the critical challenge for the weakly supervised change detection task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-former-memory-supported-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-Map-Guided Adaptive Domain Generalization for Cross Modality MRI Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-map-guided-adaptive-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal MRI segmentation is of great value for computer-aided medical diagnosis, enabling flexible data acquisition and model generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-map-guided-adaptive-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RED-DOT: Multimodal Fact-checking via Relevant Evidence Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-dot-multimodal-fact-checking-via-relevant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online misinformation is often multimodal in nature, i. e., it is caused by misleading associations between texts and accompanying images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-dot-multimodal-fact-checking-via-relevant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Source Domain Expansion for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-source-domain-expansion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) tries to overcome the need for a large labeled dataset by transferring knowledge from a source dataset, with lots of labeled data, to a target dataset, that has no labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-source-domain-expansion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LymphoML: An interpretable artificial intelligence-based method identifies morphologic features that correlate with lymphoma subtype</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lymphoml-an-interpretable-artificial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accurate classification of lymphoma subtypes using hematoxylin and eosin (H&E)-stained tissue is complicated by the wide range of morphological features these cancers can exhibit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lymphoml-an-interpretable-artificial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDMPP: A Device-Model Agnostic Framework for Latency Prediction of Tensor Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdmpp-a-device-model-agnostic-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the large space of DNN models and devices that impede direct profiling of all combinations, recent efforts focus on building a predictor to model the performance of DNN models on different devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdmpp-a-device-model-agnostic-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do People Tell Stories Online? Story Detection Across Online Communities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-do-people-tell-stories-online-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People share stories online for a myriad of purposes, whether as a means of self-disclosure, processing difficult personal experiences, providing needed information or entertainment, or persuading others to share their beliefs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-do-people-tell-stories-online-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-bayesian-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show that a single SBNN can be used to represent a variety of spatial processes often used in practice, such as Gaussian processes and lognormal processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-bayesian-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfriMTE and AfriCOMET: Empowering COMET to Embrace Under-resourced African Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrimte-and-africomet-empowering-comet-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we develop AfriCOMET, a COMET evaluation metric for African languages by leveraging DA training data from high-resource languages and African-centric multilingual encoder (AfroXLM-Roberta) to create the state-of-the-art evaluation metric for African languages MT with respect to Spearman-rank correlation with human judgments (+0. 406).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrimte-and-africomet-empowering-comet-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenkai -- Framework For Exploring Beyond Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenkai-framework-for-exploring-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zenkai aims to make it easier to get around these limitations and help researchers more easily explore new frontiers in deep learning that do not strictly adhere to the backpropagation framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenkai-framework-for-exploring-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERVENOR: Prompt the Coding Ability of Large Language Models with the Interactive Chain of Repairing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervenor-prompt-the-coding-ability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Code Learner is asked to generate and repair code according to the instructions from the Code Teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervenor-prompt-the-coding-ability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token Prediction as Implicit Classification to Identify LLM-Generated Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-prediction-as-implicit-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach for identifying the possible large language models (LLMs) involved in text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-prediction-as-implicit-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-shot Visual Question Answering via Large Language Models with Reasoning Question Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-visual-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This results in a set of candidate answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-visual-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
