<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:15:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Conversational Search Behavior For Domain Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-conversational-search-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational search has evolved as a new information retrieval paradigm, marking a shift from traditional search systems towards interactive dialogues with intelligent search agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-conversational-search-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Mandarin-Cantonese Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-mandarin-cantonese-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advancements in unsupervised machine translation have enabled the development of machine translation systems that can translate between languages for which there is not an abundance of parallel data available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-mandarin-cantonese-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RedMule: A Mixed-Precision Matrix-Matrix Operation Engine for Flexible and Energy-Efficient On-Chip Linear Algebra and TinyML Training Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redmule-a-mixed-precision-matrix-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing interest in TinyML, i. e., near-sensor machine learning on power budgets of a few tens of mW, is currently pushing toward enabling TinyML-class training as opposed to inference only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redmule-a-mixed-precision-matrix-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look Beyond Bias with Entropic Adversarial Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-beyond-bias-with-entropic-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks do not discriminate between spurious and causal patterns, and will only learn the most predictive ones while ignoring the others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-beyond-bias-with-entropic-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why People Skip Music? On Predicting Music Skips using Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-people-skip-music-on-predicting-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the utility of users' historical data for the task of sequentially predicting users' skipping behaviour.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-people-skip-music-on-predicting-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Data Scientists Review the Scholarly Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-data-scientists-review-the-scholarly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keeping up with the research literature plays an important role in the workflow of scientists - allowing them to understand a field, formulate the problems they focus on, and develop the solutions that they contribute, which in turn shape the nature of the discipline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-data-scientists-review-the-scholarly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There is No Big Brother or Small Brother: Knowledge Infusion in Language Models for Link Prediction and Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/there-is-no-big-brother-or-small-brother</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this context, we infuse knowledge in large and small language models and study their performance, and find the performance to be similar.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/there-is-no-big-brother-or-small-brother</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Grained Encoder for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-grained-encoder-for-vision-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a Dynamic Grained Encoder for vision transformers, which can adaptively assign a suitable number of queries to each spatial region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-grained-encoder-for-vision-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hint assisted reinforcement learning: an application in radio astronomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hint-assisted-reinforcement-learning-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, the construction of a dynamics model in model based reinforcement learning has increased complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hint-assisted-reinforcement-learning-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Semantic Segmentation with Inter-Frame Feature Fusion and Inner-Frame Feature Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-semantic-segmentation-with-inter-frame</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to tackle the misalignment issue, we propose a spatial-temporal fusion (STF) module to model dense pairwise relationships among multi-frame features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-semantic-segmentation-with-inter-frame</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Transferability of Machine-Learned Force Fields for Material Property Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-transferability-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine-learned force fields have generated significant interest in recent years as a tool for molecular dynamics (MD) simulations, with the aim of developing accurate and efficient models that can replace classical interatomic potentials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-transferability-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Voxelization and Classification for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-voxelization-and-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main challenge in 3D object detection from LiDAR point clouds is achieving real-time performance without affecting the reliability of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-voxelization-and-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBUSfT: Robust Real-Time Shape-from-Template, a C++ Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robusft-robust-real-time-shape-from-template</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking the 3D shape of a deforming object using only monocular 2D vision is a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robusft-robust-real-time-shape-from-template</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with minimal effort: leveraging in silico labeling for cell and nucleus segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-minimal-effort-leveraging-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning provides us with powerful methods to perform nucleus or cell segmentation with unprecedented quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-minimal-effort-leveraging-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-Time Panoptic Narrative Grounding by an End-to-End Grounding Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-panoptic-narrative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the PNG benchmark dataset demonstrate the effectiveness and efficiency of our method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-panoptic-narrative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Medical Image Analysis with Vision Transformers: A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-medical-image-analysis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The remarkable performance of the Transformer architecture in natural language processing has recently also triggered broad interest in Computer Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-medical-image-analysis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyRSM++: Hybrid Relation Guided Temporal Set Matching for Few-shot Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyrsm-hybrid-relation-guided-temporal-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be specific, HyRSM++ consists of two key components, a hybrid relation module and a temporal set matching metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyrsm-hybrid-relation-guided-temporal-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Functional Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-functional-connectivity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most generally, dynamic functional connectivity (FC) refers to the non-instantaneous couplings across timeseries from a set of brain areas, here as measured by fMRI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-functional-connectivity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Algonauts Project 2023 Challenge: How the Human Brain Makes Sense of Natural Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-algonauts-project-2023-challenge-how-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The sciences of biological and artificial intelligence are ever more intertwined.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-algonauts-project-2023-challenge-how-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers as Policies for Variable Action Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-as-policies-for-variable-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this project we demonstrate the effectiveness of the transformer encoder as a viable architecture for policies in variable action environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-as-policies-for-variable-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topologically Regularized Data Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topologically-regularized-data-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In some cases, users may have prior topological knowledge about the data, such as a known cluster structure or the fact that the data is known to lie along a tree- or graph-structured topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topologically-regularized-data-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Discovery using Natural Language Questions via a Self-Supervised Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-discovery-using-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a self-supervised approach to assemble training datasets and train learned discovery systems without human intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-discovery-using-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Open-Set Video Domain Adaptation with Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-open-set-video-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we address a more realistic scenario, called open-set video domain adaptation (OUVDA), where the target dataset contains "unknown" semantic categories that are not shared with the source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-open-set-video-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution Cloud Removal with Multi-Modal and Multi-Resolution Data Fusion: A New Baseline and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-cloud-removal-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Planet-CR, a benchmark dataset for high-resolution cloud removal with multi-modal and multi-resolution data fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-cloud-removal-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Me Intrigued: Quantifying Usage of Colors in Fiction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-me-intrigued-quantifying-usage-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present preliminary results in quantitative analyses of color usage in selected authors' works from LitBank.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-me-intrigued-quantifying-usage-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Shape Perception Integrates Intuitive Physics and Analysis-by-Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-shape-perception-integrates-intuitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many surface cues support three-dimensional shape perception, but people can sometimes still see shape when these features are missing -- in extreme cases, even when an object is completely occluded, as when covered with a draped cloth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-shape-perception-integrates-intuitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Performance Aspirations Matter for Guiding Software Configuration Tuning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-performance-aspirations-matter-for-guiding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Before we design better optimizers, a crucial engineering decision to make therein is how to handle the performance requirements with clear aspirations in the tuning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-performance-aspirations-matter-for-guiding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doc2Query--: When Less is More</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doc2query-when-less-is-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Doc2Query -- the process of expanding the content of a document before indexing using a sequence-to-sequence model -- has emerged as a prominent technique for improving the first-stage retrieval effectiveness of search engines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doc2query-when-less-is-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subset verification and search algorithms for causal DAGs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subset-verification-and-search-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the problem of learning the causal relationships of a subset of edges (target edges) in a graph with as few interventions as possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subset-verification-and-search-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDebug: Systematic Debugging for Federated Learning Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddebug-systematic-debugging-for-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When a global model's performance deteriorates, finding the round and the clients responsible is a major pain point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddebug-systematic-debugging-for-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing BERT for Convolutional Networks: Sparse and Hierarchical Masked Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-bert-for-convolutional-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is the first use of sparse convolution for 2D masked modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-bert-for-convolutional-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind Reasoning Manners: Enhancing Type Perception for Generalized Zero-shot Logical Reasoning over Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-reasoning-manners-enhancing-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) How to enhance the perception of reasoning types for the models?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-reasoning-manners-enhancing-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RobArch: Designing Robust Architectures against Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robarch-designing-robust-architectures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial Training is the most effective approach for improving the robustness of Deep Neural Networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robarch-designing-robust-architectures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Injective Prior for Inverse Scattering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-injective-prior-for-inverse-scattering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In electromagnetic inverse scattering, we aim to reconstruct object permittivity from scattered waves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-injective-prior-for-inverse-scattering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRTransNet: HRFormer-Driven Two-Modality Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtransnet-hrformer-driven-two-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the second problem, a dual-direction short connection fusion module is used to optimize the output features of HRFormer, thereby enhancing the detailed representation of objects at the output level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtransnet-hrformer-driven-two-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Time Series Forecasting with Diffusion, Denoise, and Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-time-series-forecasting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to address the time series forecasting problem with generative modeling and propose a bidirectional variational auto-encoder (BVAE) equipped with diffusion, denoise, and disentanglement, namely D3VAE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-time-series-forecasting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Batch Normalization Damage Federated Learning on Non-IID Data?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-batch-normalization-damage-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In view of this, we develop a new FL algorithm that is tailored to BN, called FedTAN, which is capable of achieving robust FL performance under a variety of data distributions via iterative layer-wise parameter aggregation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-batch-normalization-damage-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topic Modelling of Swedish Newspaper Articles about Coronavirus: a Case Study using Latent Dirichlet Allocation Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topic-modelling-of-swedish-newspaper-articles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, from the social-media and healthcare domain, we apply popular Latent Dirichlet Allocation (LDA) methods to model the topic changes in Swedish newspaper articles about Coronavirus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topic-modelling-of-swedish-newspaper-articles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGB-T Multi-Modal Crowd Counting Based on Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-multi-modal-crowd-counting-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better excavate multi-modal information, we use count-guided multi-modal fusion and modal-guided count enhancement to achieve the impressive performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-multi-modal-crowd-counting-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepMatcher: A Deep Transformer-based Network for Robust and Accurate Local Feature Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmatcher-a-deep-transformer-based-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose DeepMatcher, a deep Transformer-based network built upon our investigation of local feature matching in detector-free methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmatcher-a-deep-transformer-based-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FGAHOI: Fine-Grained Anchors for Human-Object Interaction Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgahoi-fine-grained-anchors-for-human-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HSAM and TAM semantically align and merge the extracted features and query embeddings in the hierarchical spatial and task perspectives in turn.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgahoi-fine-grained-anchors-for-human-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoAC: Towards Automated Attribute Completion for Heterogeneous Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoac-towards-automated-attribute-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to improve the performance of the downstream graph learning task, attribute completion and the training of the heterogeneous GNN should be jointly optimized rather than viewed as two separate processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoac-towards-automated-attribute-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foldsformer: Learning Sequential Multi-Step Cloth Manipulation With Space-Time Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foldsformer-learning-sequential-multi-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foldformer can complete multi-step cloth manipulation tasks even when configurations of the cloth (e. g., size and pose) vary from configurations in the general demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foldsformer-learning-sequential-multi-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing 3D finger knuckle recognition via deep feature learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-3d-finger-knuckle-recognition-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this approach results in a large feature dimension, and the trained classification layer is required for comparing probe samples, which limits the introduction of new classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-3d-finger-knuckle-recognition-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Local Feature Aggregation for Learning on Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-local-feature-aggregation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing point cloud learning methods aggregate features from neighbouring points relying on constructing graph in the spatial domain, which results in feature update for each point based on spatially-fixed neighbours throughout layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-local-feature-aggregation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Review Driven Collaborative Bug Finding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/app-review-driven-collaborative-bug-finding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our novelty is that we guide the bug finding process by considering that existing bugs have been hinted within app reviews.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/app-review-driven-collaborative-bug-finding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistic-style-aware Neural Networks for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-style-aware-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the hierarchical recursive neural network (HERO) to predict fake news by learning its linguistic style, which is distinguishable from the truth, as psychological theories reveal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-style-aware-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized Greedy Algorithms and Composable Coreset for k-Center Clustering with Outliers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-greedy-algorithms-and-composable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though a number of methods have been developed in the past decades, it is still quite challenging to design quality guaranteed algorithm with low complexity for this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-greedy-algorithms-and-composable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Salient Object Detection in Optical Remote Sensing Images via Semantic Matching and Edge Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-salient-object-detection-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, semantic kernels are used to activate salient object locations in two groups of high-level features through dynamic convolution operations in DSMM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-salient-object-detection-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Poster: Laying out Stylized Texts on Retrieved Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2poster-laying-out-stylized-texts-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Poster generation is a significant task for a wide range of applications, which is often time-consuming and requires lots of manual editing and artistic experience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2poster-laying-out-stylized-texts-on</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
