<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 21:06:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap Masked Visual Modeling via Hard Patches Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrap-masked-visual-modeling-via-hard</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To empower the model as a teacher, we propose Hard Patches Mining (HPM), predicting patch-wise losses and subsequently determining where to mask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrap-masked-visual-modeling-via-hard</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Splitting Algorithm with Color and Opacity Depended on Viewing Direction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-splitting-algorithm-with-color-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the caveats of both models, we propose a hybrid model that uses GS representation of the 3D object's shape and NeRF-based encoding of color and opacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-splitting-algorithm-with-color-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapt &amp; Align: Continual Learning with Generative Models Latent Space Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-align-continual-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Adapt & Align, a method for continual learning of neural networks by aligning latent representations in generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-align-continual-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropic Open-set Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-open-set-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active Learning (AL) aims to enhance the performance of deep models by selecting the most informative samples for annotation from a pool of unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-open-set-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT as a commenter to the news: can LLMs generate human-like opinions?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-as-a-commenter-to-the-news-can-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ChatGPT, GPT-3. 5, and other large language models (LLMs) have drawn significant attention since their release, and the abilities of these models have been investigated for a wide variety of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-as-a-commenter-to-the-news-can-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Foreground and Background Separation in Weakly-supervised Temporal Action Localization: A Clustering-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-foreground-and-background-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It comprises two core components: a snippet clustering component that groups the snippets into multiple latent clusters and a cluster classification component that further classifies the cluster as foreground or background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-foreground-and-background-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPGroup3D: Superpoint Grouping Network for Indoor 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgroup3d-superpoint-grouping-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel superpoint grouping network for indoor anchor-free one-stage 3D object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgroup3d-superpoint-grouping-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation for Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, the proposed method achieves 51. 8\% mIoU on the Cityscapes test dataset, showcasing its potential as a strong WSSS baseline on driving scene datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upper Bounding Barlow Twins: A Novel Filter for Multi-Relational Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-bounding-barlow-twins-a-novel-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this drawback, we propose to learn a graph filter motivated by the theoretical analysis of Barlow Twins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-bounding-barlow-twins-a-novel-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Sensitive Stochastic Optimal Control as Rao-Blackwellized Markovian Score Climbing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-stochastic-optimal-control-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic optimal control of dynamical systems is a crucial challenge in sequential decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-stochastic-optimal-control-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LingoQA: Video Question Answering for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lingoqa-video-question-answering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we introduce LingoQA, a benchmark specifically for autonomous driving Video QA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lingoqa-video-question-answering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Attention U-Net with Feature Infusion: Pushing the Boundaries of Multiclass Defect Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-attention-u-net-with-feature-infusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed architecture, Dual Attentive U-Net with Feature Infusion (DAU-FI Net), addresses challenges in semantic segmentation, particularly on multiclass imbalanced datasets with limited samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-attention-u-net-with-feature-infusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFABA: A More Faithful and Accelerated Boundary-based Attribution Method for Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfaba-a-more-faithful-and-accelerated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better understand the output of deep neural networks (DNN), attribution based methods have been an important approach for model interpretability, which assign a score for each input dimension to indicate its importance towards the model outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfaba-a-more-faithful-and-accelerated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Task Performance and Model Calibration with Supervised and Self-Ensembled In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-task-performance-and-model-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following the standard supervised fine-tuning (SFT) paradigm, in-context learning (ICL) has become an efficient approach propelled by the recent advancements in large language models (LLMs), yielding promising performance across various tasks in few-shot data setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-task-performance-and-model-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning Graph Neural Networks by Preserving Graph Generative Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-graph-neural-networks-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we identify the fundamental cause of structural divergence as the discrepancy of generative patterns between the pre-training and downstream graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-graph-neural-networks-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinySAM: Pushing the Envelope for Efficient Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinysam-pushing-the-envelope-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first propose a full-stage knowledge distillation method with online hard prompt sampling strategy to distill a lightweight student model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinysam-pushing-the-envelope-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Noise Annotation: Unveiling the Impact of Noisy annotation on Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-noise-annotation-unveiling-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For object detection task with noisy labels, it is important to consider not only categorization noise, as in image classification, but also localization noise, missing annotations, and bogus bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-noise-annotation-unveiling-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Semantic Space is Worth 256 Language Descriptions: Make Stronger Segmentation Models with Descriptive Properties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-space-is-worth-256-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of relying solely on category-specific annotations, ProLab uses descriptive properties grounded in common sense knowledge for supervising segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-semantic-space-is-worth-256-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysRFANet: Physics-Guided Neural Network for Real-Time Prediction of Thermal Effect During Radiofrequency Ablation Treatment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physrfanet-physics-guided-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiofrequency ablation (RFA) is a widely used minimally invasive technique for ablating solid tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physrfanet-physics-guided-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argue with Me Tersely: Towards Sentence-Level Counter-Argument Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argue-with-me-tersely-towards-sentence-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show the competitiveness of our proposed framework and evaluator in counter-argument generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argue-with-me-tersely-towards-sentence-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HD-Painter: High-Resolution and Prompt-Faithful Text-Guided Image Inpainting with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd-painter-high-resolution-and-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in text-guided image inpainting, based on the unprecedented success of text-to-image diffusion models, has led to exceptionally realistic and visually plausible results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd-painter-high-resolution-and-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchoring Path for Inductive Relation Prediction in Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchoring-path-for-inductive-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose Anchoring Path Sentence Transformer (APST) by introducing Anchoring Paths (APs) to alleviate the reliance of CPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchoring-path-for-inductive-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable 3D Face Generation with Conditional Style Code Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-face-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For 3D GAN inversion, we introduce two methods which aim to enhance the representation of style codes and alleviate 3D inconsistencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-3d-face-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive End-to-End Computer Vision Framework for Restoration and Recognition of Low-Quality Engineering Drawings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-end-to-end-computer-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing computer vision approaches for digitizing engineering drawings typically assume the input drawings have high quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-end-to-end-computer-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SE(3)-Equivariant and Noise-Invariant 3D Motion Tracking in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-3-equivariant-and-noise-invariant-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose EquiTrack, the first method that uses recent steerable SE(3)-equivariant CNNs (E-CNN) for motion tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-3-equivariant-and-noise-invariant-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Probabilistic Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-probabilistic-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By extracting compact and informative representations from input related to the target task, SPC can enhance the generalization ability of pre-trained language models for better language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-probabilistic-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paint3D: Paint Anything 3D with Lighting-Less Texture Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint3d-paint-anything-3d-with-lighting-less</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Paint3D, a novel coarse-to-fine generative framework that is capable of producing high-resolution, lighting-less, and diverse 2K UV texture maps for untextured 3D meshes conditioned on text or image inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint3d-paint-anything-3d-with-lighting-less</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Visual Supervision for Array-based Active Speaker Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-visual-supervision-for-array-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The multichannel audio ``student'' network is trained to generate the same results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-visual-supervision-for-array-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Pose Estimation of Two Interacting Hands from a Monocular Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pose-estimation-of-two-interacting-hands</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D hand tracking from a monocular video is a very challenging problem due to hand interactions, occlusions, left-right hand ambiguity, and fast motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pose-estimation-of-two-interacting-hands</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards More Faithful Natural Language Explanation Using Multi-Level Contrastive Learning in VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-faithful-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above issues, we propose a novel self-supervised \textbf{M}ulti-level \textbf{C}ontrastive \textbf{L}earning based natural language \textbf{E}xplanation model (MCLE) for VQA with semantic-level, image-level, and instance-level factual and counterfactual samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-more-faithful-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveLM: Driving with Graph Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivelm-driving-with-graph-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiments demonstrate that Graph VQA provides a simple, principled framework for reasoning about a driving scene, and DriveLM-Data provides a challenging benchmark for this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivelm-driving-with-graph-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth is in There: Improving Reasoning in Language Models with Layer-Selective Rank Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-truth-is-in-there-improving-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs) have become a fixture in modern machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-truth-is-in-there-improving-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Point Cloud Diffusion for Disentangled 3D Shape and Appearance Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-point-cloud-diffusion-for-disentangled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, none of the existing models enable disentangled generation to control the shape and appearance separately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-point-cloud-diffusion-for-disentangled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Eval: Evaluating the Tool Utilization Capability Step by Step</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eval-evaluating-the-tool-utilization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous works that evaluate models holistically, we comprehensively decompose the tool utilization into multiple sub-processes, including instruction following, planning, reasoning, retrieval, understanding, and review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eval-evaluating-the-tool-utilization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable artificial intelligence approaches for brain-computer interfaces: a review and design space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-artificial-intelligence-5</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a design space for XAI4BCI, considering the evolving need to visualize and investigate predictive model outcomes customised for various stakeholders in the BCI development and deployment lifecycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-artificial-intelligence-5</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeLL: A Lifelong Learning Dataset to Support the Co-Evolution of Data and Language Models of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codell-a-lifelong-learning-dataset-to-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by recent work on lifelong learning applications for language models (LMs) of code, we introduce CodeLL, a lifelong learning dataset focused on code changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codell-a-lifelong-learning-dataset-to-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models With Learned Adaptive Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-learned-adaptive-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have gained traction as powerful algorithms for synthesizing high-quality images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-learned-adaptive-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Machine Learning Algorithms by Union-Free Generic Depth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-machine-learning-algorithms-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a framework for descriptively analyzing sets of partial orders based on the concept of depth functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-machine-learning-algorithms-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Deep Generalized Canonical Correlation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-generalized-canonical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Others overload the problem by also seeking to reveal what is not common among the views -- i. e., the private components that are needed to fully reconstruct each view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-generalized-canonical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiFAR: A Fraud Detection Dataset for Learning to Defer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fifar-a-fraud-detection-dataset-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Financial fraud detection is a high-stakes setting where algorithms and human experts often work in tandem; however, there are no publicly available datasets for L2D concerning this important application of human-AI teaming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fifar-a-fraud-detection-dataset-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Deep Learning: A BP-Free Approach for Parallel Block-Wise Training of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-deep-learning-a-bp-free-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This includes decisions on how to decouple network blocks and which auxiliary networks to use for each block.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-deep-learning-a-bp-free-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repaint123: Fast and High-quality One Image to 3D Generation with Progressive Controllable 2D Repainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repaint123-fast-and-high-quality-one-image-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea is to combine the powerful image generation capability of the 2D diffusion model and the texture alignment ability of the repainting strategy for generating high-quality multi-view images with consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repaint123-fast-and-high-quality-one-image-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Lane-Level Maps from Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-lane-level-maps-from-aerial-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce for the first time a large-scale aerial image dataset built for lane detection, with high-quality polyline lane annotations on high-resolution images of around 80 kilometers of road.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-lane-level-maps-from-aerial-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning with Versatile Loss Geometries for Fast Adaptation Using Mirror Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-versatile-loss-geometries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing task-invariant prior knowledge extracted from related tasks, meta-learning is a principled framework that empowers learning a new task especially when data records are limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-versatile-loss-geometries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Verification of Quantized Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-verification-of-quantized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantization replaces floating point arithmetic with integer arithmetic in deep neural network models, providing more efficient on-device inference with less power and memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-verification-of-quantized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGCLUSTER: A Neural Framework for Attributed Graph Clustering via Modularity Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgcluster-a-neural-framework-for-attributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph clustering is a fundamental and challenging task in the field of graph mining where the objective is to group the nodes into clusters taking into consideration the topology of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgcluster-a-neural-framework-for-attributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assaying on the Robustness of Zero-Shot Machine-Generated Text Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assaying-on-the-robustness-of-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an effort to address these issues, we delve into the realm of zero-shot machine-generated text detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assaying-on-the-robustness-of-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at the Few-Shot Adaptation of Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-few-shot-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient transfer learning (ETL) is receiving increasing attention to adapt large pre-trained language-vision models on downstream tasks with a few labeled samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-few-shot-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Response Enhanced Semi-Supervised Dialogue Query Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-enhanced-semi-supervised-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the observation that the search query is typically related to the topic of dialogue response, we train a response-augmented query producer (RA) to provide rich and effective training signals for QP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-enhanced-semi-supervised-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSPy Assertions: Computational Constraints for Self-Refining Language Model Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspy-assertions-computational-constraints-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our reference implementation of LM Assertions is integrated into DSPy at https://github. com/stanfordnlp/dspy]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspy-assertions-computational-constraints-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
