<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 09:14:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed Deep Super-resolution for Spatiotemporal Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-deep-super-resolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-fidelity simulation of complex physical systems is exorbitantly expensive and inaccessible across spatiotemporal scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-deep-super-resolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIPCaD-Bench: Continuous Industrial Process datasets for benchmarking Causal Discovery methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cipcad-bench-continuous-industrial-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces two novel public datasets for CD in continuous manufacturing processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cipcad-bench-continuous-industrial-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Normalization for Accelerating and Stabilizing Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-normalization-for-accelerating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we propose Unified Normalization (UN), which can speed up the inference by being fused with other linear operations and achieve comparable performance on par with LN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-normalization-for-accelerating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Late Fusion Multi-view Clustering via Global and Local Alignment Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/late-fusion-multi-view-clustering-via-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It optimally fuses multiple source information in partition level from each individual view, and maximally aligns the consensus partition with these weighted base ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/late-fusion-multi-view-clustering-via-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Cluster Validity Measures (In)valid?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-cluster-validity-measures-in-valid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Internal cluster validity measures (such as the Calinski-Harabasz, Dunn, or Davies-Bouldin indices) are frequently used for selecting the appropriate number of partitions a dataset should be split into.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-cluster-validity-measures-in-valid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Hand Pose Estimation and Pin Inspection for Insertion of Through-Hole Components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-hand-pose-estimation-and-pin-inspection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A deep learning segmentation of the pins is performed and the inspection pose is found by simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-hand-pose-estimation-and-pin-inspection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSR -- A dual subspace re-projection network for surface anomaly detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsr-a-dual-subspace-re-projection-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The state-of-the-art in discriminative unsupervised surface anomaly detection relies on external datasets for synthesizing anomaly-augmented training images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsr-a-dual-subspace-re-projection-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiview Regenerative Morphing with Dual Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-regenerative-morphing-with-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to address a new task of image morphing under a multiview setting, which takes two sets of multiview images as the input and generates intermediate renderings that not only exhibit smooth transitions between the two input sets but also ensure visual consistency across different views at any transition state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiview-regenerative-morphing-with-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyABSA: Open Framework for Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyabsa-open-framework-for-aspect-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, previous efforts usually neglect the precursor aspect term extraction (ASC) subtask and focus on the aspect sentiment classification (ATE) subtask.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyabsa-open-framework-for-aspect-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image is Worth One Word: Personalizing Text-to-Image Generation using Textual Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-is-worth-one-word-personalizing-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, it is unclear how such freedom can be exercised to generate images of specific unique concepts, modify their appearance, or compose them in new roles and novel scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-is-worth-one-word-personalizing-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Individual Decision-Making Style: Exploring Behavioral Stylometry in Chess</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-individual-decision-making-style-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a transformer-based approach to behavioral stylometry in the context of chess, where one attempts to identify the player who played a set of games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-individual-decision-making-style-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Deep Networks with Linear Competing Units for Model-Agnostic Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-deep-networks-with-linear-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work addresses meta-learning (ML) by considering deep networks with stochastic local winner-takes-all (LWTA) activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-deep-networks-with-linear-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ferret: a Framework for Benchmarking Explainers on Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-a-framework-for-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many interpretability tools allow practitioners and researchers to explain Natural Language Processing systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-a-framework-for-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T4DT: Tensorizing Time for Learning Temporal 3D Visual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t4dt-tensorizing-time-for-learning-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that low-rank tensor compression is extremely compact to store and query time-varying signed distance functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t4dt-tensorizing-time-for-learning-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Comparison of Deep RL Algorithms for Energy Systems Optimal Scheduling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-comparison-of-deep-rl-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This trade-off introduces extra hyperparameters that impact the DRL algorithms' performance and capability of providing feasible solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-comparison-of-deep-rl-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Can Transformers Learn In-Context? A Case Study of Simple Function Classes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-transformers-learn-in-context-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make progress towards understanding in-context learning, we consider the well-defined problem of training a model to in-context learn a function class (e. g., linear functions): that is, given data derived from some functions in the class, can we train a model to in-context learn "most" functions from this class?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-transformers-learn-in-context-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XOOD: Extreme Value Based Out-Of-Distribution Detection For Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xood-extreme-value-based-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting out-of-distribution (OOD) data at inference time is crucial for many applications of machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xood-extreme-value-based-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransDeepLab: Convolution-Free Transformer-based DeepLab v3+ for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transdeeplab-convolution-free-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Especially, deep neural networks based on seminal architectures such as U-shaped models with skip-connections or atrous convolution with pyramid pooling have been tailored to a wide range of medical image analysis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transdeeplab-convolution-free-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Adversarial Robustness of Vision Transformers via Cauchy Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-adversarial-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research on the robustness of deep learning has shown that Vision Transformers (ViTs) surpass the Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) under some perturbations, e. g., natural corruption, adversarial attacks, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-adversarial-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacking Adversarial Defences by Smoothing the Loss Landscape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-adversarial-defences-by-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates a family of methods for defending against adversarial attacks that owe part of their success to creating a noisy, discontinuous, or otherwise rugged loss landscape that adversaries find difficult to navigate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacking-adversarial-defences-by-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Attention Based Style Distribution for Controllable Person Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-based-style-distribution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a cross attention based style distribution module that computes between the source semantic styles and target pose for pose transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-based-style-distribution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBAG: An Efficient Genetic Algorithm for the Graph Burning Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbag-an-efficient-genetic-algorithm-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph burning is a simplified deterministic model for how information spreads within networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbag-an-efficient-genetic-algorithm-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoF-NeRF: Depth-of-Field Meets Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dof-nerf-depth-of-field-meets-neural-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we introduce DoF-NeRF, a novel neural rendering approach that can deal with shallow DoF inputs and can simulate DoF effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dof-nerf-depth-of-field-meets-neural-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Package for Automated Analysis of Lung Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-package-for-automated-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the recent past with the rapid surge of COVID-19 infections, lung ultrasound has emerged as a fast and powerful diagnostic tool particularly for continuous and periodic monitoring of the lung.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/software-package-for-automated-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Future Mosquito Habitats Using Time Series Climate Forecasting and Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-future-mosquito-habitats-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mosquito habitat ranges are projected to expand due to climate change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-future-mosquito-habitats-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Scaling Approach for Metabolomics Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-scaling-approach-for-metabolomics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the performance of the proposed method in comparison to the other existing conventional scaling techniques using metabolomics data analysis in both the absence and presence of different percentages of outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-scaling-approach-for-metabolomics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Document Summarization with Centroid-Based Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-summarization-with-centroid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multi-document summarization (MDS), the input is a cluster of documents, and the output is the cluster summary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-summarization-with-centroid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FrOoDo: Framework for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/froodo-framework-for-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FrOoDo is an easy-to-use and flexible framework for Out-of-Distribution detection tasks in digital pathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/froodo-framework-for-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Product Retrieval with Weakly Supervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-product-retrieval-with-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale weakly supervised product retrieval is a practically useful yet computationally challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-product-retrieval-with-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do Deep Neural Networks Learn in Medical Images?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-deep-neural-networks-learn-in-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning is increasingly gaining rapid adoption in healthcare to help improve patient outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-deep-neural-networks-learn-in-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint covariate-alignment and concept-alignment: a framework for domain generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-covariate-alignment-and-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, our framework proposes to jointly minimize both the covariate-shift as well as the concept-shift between the seen domains for a better performance on the unseen domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-covariate-alignment-and-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Fine-Grained Visual Recognition in Low Data Regimes via Self-Boosting Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fine-grained-visual-recognition-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In low data regimes, a network often struggles to choose the correct regions for recognition and tends to overfit spurious correlated patterns from the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fine-grained-visual-recognition-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Polygonal Mapping of Buildings in Satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-polygonal-mapping-of-buildings-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We addressed such an issue by exploiting the hierarchical supervision (of bottom-level vertices, mid-level line segments and the high-level regional masks) and proposed a novel interaction mechanism of feature embedding sourced from different levels of supervision signals to obtain reversible building masks for polygonal mapping of buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-polygonal-mapping-of-buildings-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Perception-Aware Transformer for Aerial Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-perception-aware-transformer-for-aerial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, with local-modeling to global-search mechanism, the proposed tracker replaces the global encoder by a novel local-recognition encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-perception-aware-transformer-for-aerial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSLA: Dynamic smooth label assignment for efficient anchor-free object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsla-dynamic-smooth-label-assignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dynamic smooth label is assigned to supervise the classification branch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsla-dynamic-smooth-label-assignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIFF: Carrying Location Information in Full Frames into Human Pose and Shape Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliff-carrying-location-information-in-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Top-down methods dominate the field of 3D human pose and shape estimation, because they are decoupled from human detection and allow researchers to focus on the core problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliff-carrying-location-information-in-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic failure of cell infection post viral entry: Implications for infection outcomes and antiviral therapy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-failure-of-cell-infection-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that infections wherein virus is release by an infected cell as a single burst, rather than at a constant rate over the cell's infectious lifespan, has the same probability of infection extinction, despite previous claims to this effect [Pearson 2011, doi:10. 1371/journal. pcbi. 1001058].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-failure-of-cell-infection-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Collection and Analysis of French Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-collection-and-analysis-of-french</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper discusses creating and analysing a new dataset for data mining and text analytics research, contributing to a joint Leeds University research project for the Corpus of National Dialects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-collection-and-analysis-of-french</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Computing an Optimal Abstraction for Structural Causal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-computing-an-optimal-abstraction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Working with causal models at different levels of abstraction is an important feature of science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-computing-an-optimal-abstraction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Grasp on the Moon from 3D Octree Observations with Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-grasp-on-the-moon-from-3d-octree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain randomization improves the generalization of learned policies to novel scenes with previously unseen objects and different illumination conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-grasp-on-the-moon-from-3d-octree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Adaptation Works with UnpredicTable Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-adaptation-works-with-unpredictable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finetuning on the resulting dataset leads to improved FSL performance on Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks, but not proportionally to dataset scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-adaptation-works-with-unpredictable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Discovering Novel Visual Categories with Self-supervised Prototype Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-discovering-novel-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, we obtain a robust feature extractor, which could serve for all images with base and novel categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-discovering-novel-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Trainability of Deep Neural Networks through Layerwise Batch-Entropy Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-trainability-of-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show empirically that we can therefore train a "vanilla" fully connected network and convolutional neural network -- no skip connections, batch normalization, dropout, or any other architectural tweak -- with 500 layers by simply adding the batch-entropy regularization term to the loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-trainability-of-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Policy Correction for Actor-Critic Algorithms in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-correction-for-actor-critic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the well-studied importance sampling and off-policy policy gradient techniques were proposed to compensate for this discrepancy, they usually require a collection of long trajectories that increases the computational complexity and induce additional problems such as vanishing or exploding gradients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-correction-for-actor-critic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCOA: Cross Modality Contrastive Learning for Sensor Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cocoa-cross-modality-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Learning (CL) is one of the most well-known approaches in SSL that attempts to learn general, informative representations of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cocoa-cross-modality-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Dough Shaping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robotic-dough-shaping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of shaping a piece of dough-like deformable material into a 2D target shape presented upfront.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robotic-dough-shaping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggretriever: A Simple Approach to Aggregate Textual Representation for Robust Dense Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggretriever-a-simple-approach-to-aggregate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work demonstrates that MLM pre-trained transformers can be used to effectively encode text information into a single-vector for dense retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggretriever-a-simple-approach-to-aggregate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>eco2AI: carbon emissions tracking of machine learning models as the first step towards sustainable AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eco2ai-carbon-emissions-tracking-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The size and complexity of deep neural networks continue to grow exponentially, significantly increasing energy consumption for training and inference by these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eco2ai-carbon-emissions-tracking-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSightR-Net: Interpretable Neural Network for Regression using Similarity-based Comparisons to Prototypical Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insightr-net-interpretable-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional neural networks (CNNs) have shown exceptional performance for a range of medical imaging tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insightr-net-interpretable-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Edge Offloading for Image Classification Under Rate Limit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-edge-offloading-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of limited computing capacity, embedded devices rely on a parsimonious classification model with uneven accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-edge-offloading-for-image</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
