<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 21:06:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>E4SRec: An Elegant Effective Efficient Extensible Solution of Large Language Models for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e4srec-an-elegant-effective-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, practical ID-based recommendation strategies, reliant on a huge number of unique identities (IDs) to represent users and items, have gained prominence in real-world recommender systems due to their effectiveness and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e4srec-an-elegant-effective-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Measuring Representational Similarity of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-measuring-representational-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the similarity of the numerous released large language models (LLMs) has many uses, e. g., simplifying model selection, detecting illegal model reuse, and advancing our understanding of what makes LLMs perform well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-measuring-representational-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Initialization of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-initialization-of-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze the variance of forward and backward propagation across GNN layers and show that the variance instability of GNN initializations comes from the combined effect of the activation function, hidden dimension, graph structure and message passing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-initialization-of-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-Assisted Remote Sensing Imagery Semantic Segmentation with Object and Boundary Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-assisted-remote-sensing-imagery-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the boundary loss capitalizes on the distinctive features of SGB by directing the model's attention to the boundary information of the object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-assisted-remote-sensing-imagery-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaRA: Aligning Large Language Models with Sequential Recommenders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llara-aligning-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To harness the complementary strengths of traditional recommenders (which encode user behavioral knowledge) and LLMs (which possess world knowledge about items), we propose LLaRA -- a Large Language and Recommendation Assistant framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llara-aligning-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Agents: Empowering Agents with Imagination for Creative Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-agents-empowering-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We benchmark creative tasks with the challenging open-world game Minecraft, where the agents are asked to create diverse buildings given free-form language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-agents-empowering-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast non-autoregressive inverse folding with discrete diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-non-autoregressive-inverse-folding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating protein sequences that fold into a intended 3D structure is a fundamental step in de novo protein design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-non-autoregressive-inverse-folding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Describing Differences in Image Sets with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describing-differences-in-image-sets-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aid in this discovery process, we explore the task of automatically describing the differences between two $\textbf{sets}$ of images, which we term Set Difference Captioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describing-differences-in-image-sets-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEDD: The MineRL BASALT Evaluation and Demonstrations Dataset for Training and Benchmarking Agents that Solve Fuzzy Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bedd-the-minerl-basalt-evaluation-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the completion of two years of BASALT competitions, we offer to the community a formalized benchmark through the BASALT Evaluation and Demonstrations Dataset (BEDD), which serves as a resource for algorithm development and performance assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bedd-the-minerl-basalt-evaluation-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C-NERF: Representing Scene Changes as Directional Consistency Difference-based NeRF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-nerf-representing-scene-changes-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach surpasses state-of-the-art 2D change detection and NeRF-based methods by a significant margin.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-nerf-representing-scene-changes-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synchronization is All You Need: Exocentric-to-Egocentric Transfer for Temporal Action Segmentation with Unlabeled Synchronized Video Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synchronization-is-all-you-need-exocentric-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we propose a novel methodology which performs the adaptation leveraging existing labeled exocentric videos and a new set of unlabeled, synchronized exocentric-egocentric video pairs, for which temporal action segmentation annotations do not need to be collected.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synchronization-is-all-you-need-exocentric-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniswap Daily Transaction Indices by Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniswap-daily-transaction-indices-by-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeFi is transforming financial services by removing intermediaries and producing a wealth of open-source data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniswap-daily-transaction-indices-by-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Granularity-Aware Aspect Learning Model for Multi-Aspect Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-granularity-aware-aspect-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense retrieval methods have been mostly focused on unstructured text and less attention has been drawn to structured data with various aspects, e. g., products with aspects such as category and brand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-granularity-aware-aspect-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models on Graphs: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-on-graphs-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, although LLMs have shown their pure text-based reasoning ability, it is underexplored whether such ability can be generalized to graph scenarios (i. e., graph-based reasoning).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-on-graphs-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lenna: Language Enhanced Reasoning Detection Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lenna-language-enhanced-reasoning-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the reasoning capability of Lenna, we construct a ReasonDet dataset to measure its performance on reasoning-based detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lenna-language-enhanced-reasoning-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeNIe: Generative Hard Negative Images Through Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genie-generative-hard-negative-images-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation is crucial in training deep models, preventing them from overfitting to limited data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genie-generative-hard-negative-images-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMONets: Multiple-Input-Multiple-Output Neural Networks Exploiting Computation in Superposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimonets-multiple-input-multiple-output-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MIMONets augment various deep neural network architectures with variable binding mechanisms to represent an arbitrary number of inputs in a compositional data structure via fixed-width distributed representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimonets-multiple-input-multiple-output-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expert-guided Bayesian Optimisation for Human-in-the-loop Experimental Design of Known Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expert-guided-bayesian-optimisation-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain experts often possess valuable physical insights that are overlooked in fully automated decision-making processes such as Bayesian optimisation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expert-guided-bayesian-optimisation-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clustering Pseudo Language Family in Multilingual Translation Models with Fisher Information Matrix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-pseudo-language-family-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multilingual translation research, the comprehension and utilization of language families are of paramount importance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clustering-pseudo-language-family-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DanZero+: Dominating the GuanDan Game through Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/danzero-dominating-the-guandan-game-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The utilization of artificial intelligence (AI) in card games has been a well-explored subject within AI research for an extensive period.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/danzero-dominating-the-guandan-game-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Vision Transformers More Data Hungry Than Newborn Visual Systems?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-transformers-more-data-hungry-than-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, ViTs were not more data hungry than newborn visual systems: both learned view invariant object representations in impoverished visual environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-transformers-more-data-hungry-than-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-SS3D: Diffusion Model for Semi-supervised 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-ss3d-diffusion-model-for-semi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised object detection is crucial for 3D scene understanding, efficiently addressing the limitation of acquiring large-scale 3D bounding box annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-ss3d-diffusion-model-for-semi-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIT-Net: Generalized Integral Transform for Operator Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/git-net-generalized-integral-transform-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces GIT-Net, a deep neural network architecture for approximating Partial Differential Equation (PDE) operators, inspired by integral transform operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/git-net-generalized-integral-transform-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchLMM: Benchmarking Cross-style Visual Capability of Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchlmm-benchmarking-cross-style-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) such as GPT-4V and LLaVA have shown remarkable capabilities in visual reasoning with common image styles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchlmm-benchmarking-cross-style-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Fast and Stable Federated Learning: Confronting Heterogeneity via Knowledge Anchor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fast-and-stable-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assuming that all clients have a single shared sample for each class, the knowledge anchor is constructed before each local training stage by extracting shared samples for missing classes and randomly selecting one sample per class for non-dominant classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-fast-and-stable-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIND: Multi-Task Incremental Network Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-multi-task-incremental-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent surge in pervasive devices generating dynamic data streams has underscored the necessity for learning systems to adapt to data distributional shifts continually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-multi-task-incremental-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MKA: A Scalable Medical Knowledge Assisted Mechanism for Generative Models on Medical Conversation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mka-a-scalable-medical-knowledge-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation of our method is carried out on two typical medical datasets, MedDG and MedDialog-CN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mka-a-scalable-medical-knowledge-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Vision Therapy: Multimodal Large Language Models Can Enhance Visual Robustness via Denoising In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-vision-therapy-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, by estimating a transition matrix that captures the probability of one class being confused with another, an instruction containing a correct exemplar and an erroneous one from the most probable noisy class can be constructed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-vision-therapy-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Neural Network Training Under Class Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-neural-network-training-under-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world datasets are often highly class-imbalanced, which can adversely impact the performance of deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-neural-network-training-under-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankZephyr: Effective and Robust Zero-Shot Listwise Reranking is a Breeze!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankzephyr-effective-and-robust-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In information retrieval, proprietary large language models (LLMs) such as GPT-4 and open-source counterparts such as LLaMA and Vicuna have played a vital role in reranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankzephyr-effective-and-robust-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WoVoGen: World Volume-aware Diffusion for Controllable Multi-camera Driving Scene Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wovogen-world-volume-aware-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating multi-camera street-view videos is critical for augmenting autonomous driving datasets, addressing the urgent demand for extensive and varied data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wovogen-world-volume-aware-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PEFA: Parameter-Free Adapters for Large-scale Embedding-based Retrieval Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pefa-parameter-free-adapters-for-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For product search, PEFA improves the Recall@100 of the fine-tuned ERMs by an average of 5. 3% and 14. 5%, for PEFA-XS and PEFA-XL, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pefa-parameter-free-adapters-for-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the LLMs Talk: Simulating Human-to-Human Conversational QA via Zero-Shot LLM-to-LLM Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-llms-talk-simulating-human-to-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework involves two LLMs interacting on a specific topic, with the first LLM acting as a student, generating questions to explore a given search topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-llms-talk-simulating-human-to-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LExCI: A Framework for Reinforcement Learning with Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexci-a-framework-for-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in artificial intelligence (AI) have led to its application in many areas of everyday life.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexci-a-framework-for-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Think Outside the Box: Exploring Leap-of-Thought in Large Language Models with Creative Humor Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-think-outside-the-box-exploring-leap-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we study LLMs on the popular Oogiri game which needs participants to have good creativity and strong associative thinking for responding unexpectedly and humorously to the given image, text, or both, and thus is suitable for LoT study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-think-outside-the-box-exploring-leap-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GauHuman: Articulated Gaussian Splatting from Monocular Human Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gauhuman-articulated-gaussian-splatting-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present, GauHuman, a 3D human model with Gaussian Splatting for both fast training (1 ~ 2 minutes) and real-time rendering (up to 189 FPS), compared with existing NeRF-based implicit representation modelling frameworks demanding hours of training and seconds of rendering per frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gauhuman-articulated-gaussian-splatting-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-Grounding: Grounded Visual Chat with Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-grounding-grounded-visual-chat-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we have created GVC data that allows for the combination of grounding and chat capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-grounding-grounded-visual-chat-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panoptica -- instance-wise evaluation of 3D semantic and instance segmentation maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptica-instance-wise-evaluation-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces panoptica, a versatile and performance-optimized package designed for computing instance-wise segmentation quality metrics from 2D and 3D segmentation maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoptica-instance-wise-evaluation-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magicoder: Source Code Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicoder-source-code-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magicoder models are trained on 75K synthetic instruction data using OSS-Instruct, a novel approach to enlightening LLMs with open-source code snippets to generate high-quality instruction data for code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicoder-source-code-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Multi-Modal Fusion for Image Manipulation Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-multi-modal-fusion-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent image manipulation localization and detection techniques usually leverage forensic artifacts and traces that are produced by a noise-sensitive filter, such as SRM and Bayar convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-multi-modal-fusion-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STADEE: STAtistics-based DEEp Detection of Machine Generated Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stadee-statistics-based-deep-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present STADEE, a \textbf{STA}tistics-based \textbf{DEE}p detection method to identify machine-generated text, addressing the limitations of current methods that rely heavily on fine-tuning pre-trained language models (PLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stadee-statistics-based-deep-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Viability of Synthetic Audio Data for Audio-Based Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-viability-of-synthetic-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address this by investigating synthetic audio data for audio-based DST.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-viability-of-synthetic-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Urban Mobility Prediction: A Super-Multivariate Time Series Forecasting Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-urban-mobility-prediction-a-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we present the Super-Multivariate Urban Mobility Transformer (SUMformer), which utilizes a specially designed attention mechanism to calculate temporal and cross-variable correlations and reduce computational costs stemming from a large number of time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-urban-mobility-prediction-a-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation and Unintended Biases on Univariate and Multivariate Decision Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-and-unintended-biases-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decision Trees are accessible, interpretable, and well-performing classification models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-and-unintended-biases-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffiT: Diffusion Vision Transformers for Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffit-diffusion-vision-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce latent DiffiT which consists of transformer model with the proposed self-attention layers, for high-resolution image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffit-diffusion-vision-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good Questions Help Zero-Shot Image Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/good-questions-help-zero-shot-image-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[QVix enables a wider exploration of visual scenes, improving the LVLMs' reasoning accuracy and depth in tasks such as visual question answering and visual entailment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/good-questions-help-zero-shot-image-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Confidence Threshold for ByteTrack in Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-confidence-threshold-for-bytetrack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ByteTrack, a simple tracking algorithm, enables the simultaneous tracking of multiple objects by strategically incorporating detections with a low confidence threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-confidence-threshold-for-bytetrack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing Large Language Model Geometry Solves Toxicity Detection and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-large-language-model-geometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We obtain in closed form (i) the intrinsic dimension in which the Multi-Head Attention embeddings are constrained to exist and (ii) the partition and per-region affine mappings of the per-layer feedforward networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-large-language-model-geometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEREOFOG -- Computational DeFogging via Image-to-Image Translation on a real-world Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereofog-computational-defogging-via-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-to-Image translation (I2I) is a subtype of Machine Learning (ML) that has tremendous potential in applications where two domains of images and the need for translation between the two exist, such as the removal of fog.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereofog-computational-defogging-via-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNN2R: Weakly-Supervised Rationale-Providing Question Answering over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn2r-weakly-supervised-rationale-providing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most current methods for multi-hop question answering (QA) over knowledge graphs (KGs) only provide final conclusive answers without explanations, such as a set of KG entities that is difficult for normal users to review and comprehend.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn2r-weakly-supervised-rationale-providing</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
