<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:11:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed neural networks for highly compressible flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This thesis shows that physics-informed neural networks struggle with highly compressible problems for two independent reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Warm-Start Fixed-Point Optimization Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-warm-start-fixed-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a machine-learning framework to warm-start fixed-point optimization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-warm-start-fixed-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A DenseNet-based method for decoding auditory spatial attention with EEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-densenet-based-method-for-decoding-auditory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ASAD methods are inspired by the brain lateralization of cortical neural responses during the processing of auditory spatial attention, and show promising performance for the task of auditory attention decoding (AAD) with neural recordings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-densenet-based-method-for-decoding-auditory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some notes concerning a generalized KMM-type optimization method for density ratio estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-notes-concerning-a-generalized-kmm-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present paper we introduce new optimization algorithms for the task of density ratio estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-notes-concerning-a-generalized-kmm-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-Preserving Transformers for Sequences of SPD Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Transformer-based auto-attention mechanisms have been successfully applied to the analysis of a variety of context-reliant data types, from texts to images and beyond, including data from non-Euclidean geometries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Prompt Learning with Distilled Connective Knowledge for Implicit Discourse Relation Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-prompt-learning-with-distilled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit discourse relation recognition (IDRR) aims at recognizing the discourse relation between two text segments without an explicit connective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-prompt-learning-with-distilled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client-side Gradient Inversion Against Federated Learning from Poisoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-side-gradient-inversion-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first time, we show the feasibility of a client-side adversary with limited knowledge being able to recover the training samples from the aggregated global model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-side-gradient-inversion-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMICL: Empowering Vision-language Model with Multi-Modal In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmicl-empowering-vision-language-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the current VLMs primarily emphasize utilizing multi-modal data with a single image some, rather than multi-modal prompts with interleaved multiple images and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmicl-empowering-vision-language-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMEAD: MS MARCO Entity Annotations and Disambiguations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmead-ms-marco-entity-annotations-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MMEAD, or MS MARCO Entity Annotations and Disambiguations, is a resource for entity links for the MS MARCO datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmead-ms-marco-entity-annotations-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Potential of Large Language Model Based Agents: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-rise-and-potential-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a long time, humanity has pursued artificial intelligence (AI) equivalent to or surpassing the human level, with AI agents considered a promising vehicle for this pursuit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-rise-and-potential-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Adversarial Attacks via Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-adversarial-attacks-via-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then there are two variants of this framework: 1) the Semantic Transformation (ST) approach fine-tunes the latent space of the generated image and/or the diffusion model itself; 2) the Latent Masking (LM) approach masks the latent space with another target image and local backpropagation-based interpretation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-adversarial-attacks-via-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Conversation is Worth A Thousand Recommendations: A Survey of Holistic Conversational Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-conversation-is-worth-a-thousand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, not all CRS approaches use human conversations as their source of interaction data; the majority of prior CRS work simulates interactions by exchanging entity-level information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-conversation-is-worth-a-thousand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIB-200: A Simple, Inclusive, and Big Evaluation Dataset for Topic Classification in 200+ Languages and Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sib-200-a-simple-inclusive-and-big-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the progress we have recorded in the last few years in multilingual natural language processing, evaluation is typically limited to a small set of languages with available datasets which excludes a large number of low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sib-200-a-simple-inclusive-and-big-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents: An Open-source Framework for Autonomous Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-an-open-source-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances on large language models (LLMs) enable researchers and developers to build autonomous language agents that can automatically solve various tasks and interact with environments, humans, and other agents using natural language interfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-an-open-source-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Text Summarization: Adapting Large Language Models Can Outperform Human Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinical-text-summarization-adapting-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sifting through vast textual data and summarizing key information imposes a substantial burden on how clinicians allocate their time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinical-text-summarization-adapting-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Human-Scene Interaction via Prompted Chain-of-Contacts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-human-scene-interaction-via-prompted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the definition, UniHSI constitutes a Large Language Model (LLM) Planner to translate language prompts into task plans in the form of CoC, and a Unified Controller that turns CoC into uniform task execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-human-scene-interaction-via-prompted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGT: Hierarchical Interaction Graph-Transformer for Whole Slide Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higt-hierarchical-interaction-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that the information from different resolutions is complementary and can benefit each other during the learning process, we further design a novel Bidirectional Interaction block to establish communication between different levels within the WSI pyramids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higt-hierarchical-interaction-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Diffusion with Task-awareness for Procedure Planning in Instructional Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-diffusion-with-task-awareness-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The introduced mask acts akin to a task-oriented attention filter, enabling the diffusion/denoising process to concentrate on a subset of action types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-diffusion-with-task-awareness-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Spatial and Temporal Learning for Efficient Image-to-Video Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-spatial-and-temporal-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When pre-training on the large-scale Kinetics-710, we achieve 89. 7% on Kinetics-400 with a frozen ViT-L model, which verifies the scalability of DiST.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-spatial-and-temporal-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DePT: Decoupled Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dept-decoupled-prompt-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, through an in-depth analysis of the learned features of the base and new tasks, we observe that the BNT stems from a channel bias issue, i. e., the vast majority of feature channels are occupied by base-specific knowledge, resulting in the collapse of taskshared knowledge important to new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dept-decoupled-prompt-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRE: Vision-Language Prompt Learning with Reparameterization Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-vision-language-prompt-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Prompt Learning with Reparameterization Encoder (PRE) - a simple and efficient method that enhances the generalization ability of the learnable prompt to unseen classes while maintaining the capacity to learn Base classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-vision-language-prompt-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpertQA: Expert-Curated Questions and Attributed Answers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertqa-expert-curated-questions-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As language models are adapted by a more sophisticated and diverse set of users, the importance of guaranteeing that they provide factually correct information supported by verifiable sources is critical across fields of study & professions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertqa-expert-curated-questions-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C-Pack: Packaged Resources To Advance General Chinese Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-pack-packaged-resources-to-advance-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along with our resources on general Chinese embedding, we release our data and models for English text embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-pack-packaged-resources-to-advance-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Dross Into Gold Loss: is BERT4Rec really better than SASRec?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-dross-into-gold-loss-is-bert4rec</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we show that SASRec could be effectively trained with negative sampling and still outperform BERT4Rec, but the number of negative examples should be much larger than one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-dross-into-gold-loss-is-bert4rec</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnCodecMAE: Leveraging neural codecs for universal audio representation learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encodecmae-leveraging-neural-codecs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of universal audio representation learning is to obtain foundational models that can be used for a variety of downstream tasks involving speech, music or environmental sounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encodecmae-leveraging-neural-codecs-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nucleus-aware Self-supervised Pretraining Using Unpaired Image-to-image Translation for Histopathology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nucleus-aware-self-supervised-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised pretraining attempts to enhance model performance by obtaining effective features from unlabeled data, and has demonstrated its effectiveness in the field of histopathology images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nucleus-aware-self-supervised-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EP2P-Loc: End-to-End 3D Point to 2D Pixel Localization for Large-Scale Visual Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ep2p-loc-end-to-end-3d-point-to-2d-pixel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual localization is the task of estimating a 6-DoF camera pose of a query image within a provided 3D reference map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ep2p-loc-end-to-end-3d-point-to-2d-pixel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PILOT: A Pre-Trained Model-Based Continual Learning Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pilot-a-pre-trained-model-based-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While traditional machine learning can effectively tackle a wide range of problems, it primarily operates within a closed-world setting, which presents limitations when dealing with streaming data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pilot-a-pre-trained-model-based-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTD: Multi-Timestep Detector for Delayed Streaming Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtd-multi-timestep-detector-for-delayed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving systems require real-time environmental perception to ensure user safety and experience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtd-multi-timestep-detector-for-delayed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniBrain: Universal Brain MRI Diagnosis with Hierarchical Knowledge-enhanced Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unibrain-universal-brain-mri-diagnosis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging~(MRI) have played a crucial role in brain disease diagnosis, with which a range of computer-aided artificial intelligence methods have been proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unibrain-universal-brain-mri-diagnosis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCSPNet-Joint: Efficient Joint Training Method for Traffic Sign Detection Under Extreme Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccspnet-joint-efficient-joint-training-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic sign detection is an important research direction in intelligent driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccspnet-joint-efficient-joint-training-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable JPEG: The Devil is in the Details</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-jpeg-the-devil-is-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[the input image, the JPEG quality, the quantization tables, and the color conversion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-jpeg-the-devil-is-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transparent Object Tracking with Enhanced Fusion Module</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transparent-object-tracking-with-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, with the existing fusion techniques, the addition of new features causes a change in the latent space making it impossible to incorporate transparency awareness on trackers with fixed latent spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transparent-object-tracking-with-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limited-Angle Tomography Reconstruction via Deep End-To-End Learning on Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limited-angle-tomography-reconstruction-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A CT scanner consists of an X-ray source that is spun around an object of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limited-angle-tomography-reconstruction-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated segmentation of rheumatoid arthritis immunohistochemistry stained synovial tissue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-segmentation-of-rheumatoid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model obtains a DICE score of 0. 865 and successfully segments different types of IHC staining, as well as dealing with variance in colours, intensity and common WSIs artefacts from the different clinical centres.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-segmentation-of-rheumatoid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConR: Contrastive Regularizer for Deep Imbalanced Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conr-contrastive-regularizer-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ConR minds the continuous nature of label space with two main strategies in a contrastive manner: incorrect proximities are penalized proportionate to the label similarities and the correct ones are encouraged to model local similarities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conr-contrastive-regularizer-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLSlice: Interactive Vision-and-Language Slice Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlslice-interactive-vision-and-language-slice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work in vision-and-language demonstrates that large-scale pretraining can learn generalizable models that are efficiently transferable to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlslice-interactive-vision-and-language-slice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of hyperparameters on variable selection in random forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-hyperparameters-on-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conclusion, the default values of the hyperparameters will not always be suitable for identifying important variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-hyperparameters-on-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ungar $\unicode{x2013}$ A C++ Framework for Real-Time Optimal Control Using Template Metaprogramming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ungar-unicode-x2013-a-c-framework-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Ungar, an open-source library to aid the implementation of high-dimensional optimal control problems (OCPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ungar-unicode-x2013-a-c-framework-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Infringement Detection via Feature Disentanglement and Mutual Information Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-infringement-detection-via-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically analyzed the mutual information between the label and the disentangled features, arriving at a loss that maximizes the extraction of task-relevant information from the original feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-infringement-detection-via-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Fatigue Crack Growth via Path Slicing and Re-Weighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-fatigue-crack-growth-via-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting potential risks associated with the fatigue of key structural components is crucial in engineering design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-fatigue-crack-growth-via-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aggregating Long-term Sharp Features via Hybrid Transformers for Video Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-long-term-sharp-features-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aggregate long-term sharp features from detected sharp frames, we utilize a global Transformer with multi-scale matching capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aggregating-long-term-sharp-features-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SupFusion: Supervised LiDAR-Camera Fusion for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supfusion-supervised-lidar-camera-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel training strategy called SupFusion, which provides an auxiliary feature level supervision for effective LiDAR-Camera fusion and significantly boosts detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supfusion-supervised-lidar-camera-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Reinforcement Learning for Jumping Monopods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-jumping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the complex control problem of making a monopod reach a target with a jump.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-jumping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Résumé Parsing as Hierarchical Sequence Labeling: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resume-parsing-as-hierarchical-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting information from r\'esum\'es is typically formulated as a two-stage problem, where the document is first segmented into sections and then each section is processed individually to extract the target entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resume-parsing-as-hierarchical-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNNShifter: An Efficient DNN Pruning System for Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnnshifter-an-efficient-dnn-pruning-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to sparse models, the pruned model variants are up to 5. 14x smaller and have a 1. 67x inference latency speedup, with no compromise to sparse model accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnnshifter-an-efficient-dnn-pruning-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Mirage: A Review of Hallucinations in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-mirage-a-review-of-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contribution are threefold: (1) We provide a detailed and complete taxonomy for hallucinations appearing in text generation tasks; (2) We provide theoretical analyses of hallucinations in LLMs and provide existing detection and improvement methods; (3) We propose several research directions that can be developed in the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-mirage-a-review-of-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Refined Large Language Model as Automated Reward Function Designer for Deep Reinforcement Learning in Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-refined-large-language-model-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, the performance of the reward function is assessed, and the results are presented back to the LLM for guiding its self-refinement process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-refined-large-language-model-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Hallucinations and Off-target Machine Translation with Source-Contrastive and Language-Contrastive Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucinations-and-off-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucinations and off-target translation remain unsolved problems in machine translation, especially for low-resource languages and massively multilingual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucinations-and-off-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image Dataset for Benchmarking Recommender Systems with Raw Pixels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-dataset-for-benchmarking-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, to show the effectiveness of the dataset's image features, we substitute the itemID embeddings (from IDNet) with a powerful vision encoder that represents items using their raw image pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-dataset-for-benchmarking-recommender</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
