<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2022 09:18:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Trustworthy Multi-Modal Motion Prediction: Evaluation and Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-trustworthy-multi-modal-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we comprehensively analyse the evaluation metrics, identify the main gaps of current benchmarks, and propose a new holistic evaluation framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-trustworthy-multi-modal-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven discovery of Green's functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-discovery-of-green-s-functions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, theoretical results on Green's functions and rational NNs are combined to design a human-understandable deep learning method for discovering Green's functions from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-discovery-of-green-s-functions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-Shot Multilingual Translation with Universal Representations and Cross-Mappings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-multilingual-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The many-to-many multilingual neural machine translation can translate between language pairs unseen during training, i. e., zero-shot translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-multilingual-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Directional Iterative Prompt-Tuning for Event Argument Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-iterative-prompt-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, prompt-tuning has attracted growing interests in event argument extraction (EAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-iterative-prompt-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESUS: Warm-Up Cold Users via Meta-Learning Residual User Preferences in CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resus-warm-up-cold-users-via-meta-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we employ a shared predictor to infer basis user preferences, which acquires global preference knowledge from the interactions of different users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resus-warm-up-cold-users-via-meta-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Handwriting Trajectory Recovery: Evaluation Metrics and Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-handwriting-trajectory-recovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many important tasks such as forensic signature verification, calligraphy synthesis, etc, rely on handwriting trajectory recovery of which, however, even an appropriate evaluation metric is still missing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-handwriting-trajectory-recovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NNSVS: A Neural Network-Based Singing Voice Synthesis Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsvs-a-neural-network-based-singing-voice</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the design of NNSVS, an open-source software for neural network-based singing voice synthesis research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnsvs-a-neural-network-based-singing-voice</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoChBert: Towards Robust BERT Fine-tuning for Chinese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rochbert-towards-robust-bert-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite of the superb performance on a wide range of tasks, pre-trained language models (e. g., BERT) have been proved vulnerable to adversarial texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rochbert-towards-robust-bert-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLT: Vision-Language Transformer and Query Generation for Referring Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlt-vision-language-transformer-and-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Vision-Language Transformer (VLT) framework for referring segmentation to facilitate deep interactions among multi-modal information and enhance the holistic understanding to vision-language features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlt-vision-language-transformer-and-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning with Multi-View Rendering for 3D Point Cloud Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the success of deep learning in the image domain, we devise a novel pre-training technique for better model initialization by utilizing the multi-view rendering of the 3D data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-with-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Lipschitz-Constrained Neural Networks by Learning Activation Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lipschitz-constrained-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lipschitz-constrained neural networks have several advantages compared to unconstrained ones and can be applied to various different problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lipschitz-constrained-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORE: Document Ordered Relation Extraction based on Generative Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dore-document-ordered-relation-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the root cause of the underwhelming performance of the existing generative DocRE models and discover that the culprit is the inadequacy of the training paradigm, instead of the capacities of the models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dore-document-ordered-relation-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Measuring Calibration When Humans Disagree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-measuring-calibration-when-humans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Calibration is a popular framework to evaluate whether a classifier knows when it does not know - i. e., its predictive probabilities are a good indication of how likely a prediction is to be correct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-measuring-calibration-when-humans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM-TCNet: Gated Multi-scale Temporal Convolutional Network using Emotion Causality for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gm-tcnet-gated-multi-scale-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Gated Multi-scale Temporal Convolutional Network (GM-TCNet) to construct a novel emotional causality representation learning component with a multi-scale receptive field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gm-tcnet-gated-multi-scale-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goal Exploration Augmentation via Pre-trained Skills for Sparse-Reward Long-Horizon Goal-Conditioned Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-exploration-augmentation-via-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In GCRL, exploring novel sub-goals is essential for the agent to ultimately find the pathway to the desired goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goal-exploration-augmentation-via-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Analog Quantum Computing for Optimization and Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-analog-quantum-computing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate the first differentiable analog quantum computing framework with a specific parameterization design at the analog signal (pulse) level to better exploit near-term quantum devices via variational methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-analog-quantum-computing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preferential Subsampling for Stochastic Gradient Langevin Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preferential-subsampling-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic gradient MCMC (SGMCMC) offers a scalable alternative to traditional MCMC, by constructing an unbiased estimate of the gradient of the log-posterior with a small, uniformly-weighted subsample of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preferential-subsampling-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight and High-Fidelity End-to-End Text-to-Speech with Multi-Band Generation and Inverse Short-Time Fourier Transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-high-fidelity-end-to-end-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a lightweight end-to-end text-to-speech model using multi-band generation and inverse short-time Fourier transform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-high-fidelity-end-to-end-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Segmentation of Cluttered Airborne LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-segmentation-of-cluttered-airborne</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Airborne topographic LiDAR is an active remote sensing technology that emits near-infrared light to map objects on the Earth's surface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-segmentation-of-cluttered-airborne</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Generalization through the Lens of Angular Invariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-through-the-lens-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the proposed term of invariance, we propose a novel deep DG method called Angular Invariance Domain Generalization Network (AIDGN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-through-the-lens-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Learning in Fourier Complex Field for VHR Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-learning-in-fourier-complex-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By stacking various layers of CSA blocks, we propose the Fourier Complex Transformer (FCT) model to learn global contextual information from VHR aerial images following the hierarchical manners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-learning-in-fourier-complex-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Label Correlations in a Multi-label Setting: A Case Study in Emotion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-label-correlations-in-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we develop two modeling approaches to the problem in order to capture word associations of the emotion words themselves, by either including the emotions in the input, or by leveraging Masked Language Modeling (MLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-label-correlations-in-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cRedAnno+: Annotation Exploitation in Self-Explanatory Lung Nodule Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credanno-annotation-exploitation-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, attempts have been made to reduce annotation requirements in feature-based self-explanatory models for lung nodule diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credanno-annotation-exploitation-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Spatial-Temporal Features for Deepfake Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-spatial-temporal-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Spatial-Temporal Deepfake Detection and Localization (ST-DDL) network that simultaneously explores spatial and temporal features for detecting and localizing forged regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-spatial-temporal-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Aware Bid Optimization for Online Display Advertisement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-bid-optimization-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research focuses on the bid optimization problem in the real-time bidding setting for online display advertisements, where an advertiser, or the advertiser's agent, has access to the features of the website visitor and the type of ad slots, to decide the optimal bid prices given a predetermined total advertisement budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-bid-optimization-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Use of Modality-Specific Large-Scale Pre-Trained Encoders for Multimodal Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-modality-specific-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the effectiveness and implementation of modality-specific large-scale pre-trained encoders for multimodal sentiment analysis~(MSA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-modality-specific-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vox-Fusion: Dense Tracking and Mapping with Voxel-based Neural Implicit Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vox-fusion-dense-tracking-and-mapping-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a dense tracking and mapping system named Vox-Fusion, which seamlessly fuses neural implicit representations with traditional volumetric fusion methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vox-fusion-dense-tracking-and-mapping-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Space is Feature Space: Regularization Term for GANs Training on Limited Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-is-feature-space-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, a large amount of data is required, or the model would prone to generate images with similar patterns (mode collapse) and bad quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-is-feature-space-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handwashing Action Detection System for an Autonomous Social Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handwashing-action-detection-system-for-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Young children are at an increased risk of contracting contagious diseases such as COVID-19 due to improper hand hygiene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handwashing-action-detection-system-for-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisson Reweighted Laplacian Uncertainty Sampling for Graph-based Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisson-reweighted-laplacian-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that uncertainty sampling is sufficient to achieve exploration versus exploitation in graph-based active learning, as long as the measure of uncertainty properly aligns with the underlying model and the model properly reflects uncertainty in unexplored regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisson-reweighted-laplacian-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditioning and Sampling in Variational Diffusion Models for Speech Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditioning-and-sampling-in-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, by coupling the proposed sampling method with an unconditional DM, i. e., a DM with no auxiliary inputs to its noise predictor, we can generalize it to a wide range of SR setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditioning-and-sampling-in-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACES: Translation Accuracy Challenge Sets for Evaluating Machine Translation Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aces-translation-accuracy-challenge-sets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As machine translation (MT) metrics improve their correlation with human judgement every year, it is crucial to understand the limitations of such metrics at the segment level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aces-translation-accuracy-challenge-sets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRTF Field: Unifying Measured HRTF Magnitude Representation with Neural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtf-field-unifying-measured-hrtf-magnitude</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to use neural fields, a differentiable representation of functions through neural networks, to model HRTFs with arbitrary spatial sampling schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrtf-field-unifying-measured-hrtf-magnitude</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structuring User-Generated Content on Social Media with Multimodal Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structuring-user-generated-content-on-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People post their opinions and experiences on social media, yielding rich databases of end users' sentiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structuring-user-generated-content-on-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Wikidata's edit history in knowledge graph refinement tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-wikidata-s-edit-history-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A number of solutions have been proposed to that end, ranging from rule-based approaches to the use of probabilistic methods, but there is an element that has not been considered yet: the edit history of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-wikidata-s-edit-history-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Voxel Adaptive Feature Abstraction for Robust Point Cloud Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-voxel-adaptive-feature-abstraction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the proposed framework iteratively voxelize the point cloud and extract point-voxel feature with shared local encoding and Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-voxel-adaptive-feature-abstraction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Multi-Person Body Detection and Orientation Estimation via One Unified Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-person-body-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the paper, we propose a single-stage end-to-end trainable framework for tackling the HBOE problem with multi-persons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multi-person-body-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Decoding: Open-ended Text Generation as Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-decoding-open-ended-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose contrastive decoding (CD), a more reliable search objective that returns the difference between likelihood under a large LM (called the expert, e. g. OPT-13b) and a small LM (called the amateur, e. g. OPT-125m).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-decoding-open-ended-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards High-Quality Neural TTS for Low-Resource Languages by Learning Compact Speech Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-quality-neural-tts-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we optimize the training strategy by leveraging more audio to learn MSMCRs better for low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-quality-neural-tts-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeVC: Towards High-Quality Text-Free One-Shot Voice Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freevc-towards-high-quality-text-free-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice conversion (VC) can be achieved by first extracting source content information and target speaker information, and then reconstructing waveform with these information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freevc-towards-high-quality-text-free-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Reverse-engineering of Trojan Triggers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-reverse-engineering-of-trojan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On average, the detection accuracy of our method is 93\%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-reverse-engineering-of-trojan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Visual Attention and Distraction During Visual Search Using Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-visual-attention-and-distraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our second approach is object-based and predicts the distractor and target objects during visual search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-visual-attention-and-distraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-MDS Framework for Recovering the 3D Shape of 2D Landmarks from a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-mds-framework-for-recovering-the-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a low parameter deep learning framework utilizing the Non-metric Multi-Dimensional scaling (NMDS) method, is proposed to recover the 3D shape of 2D landmarks on a human face, in a single input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-mds-framework-for-recovering-the-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaitMixer: skeleton-based gait representation learning via wide-spectrum multi-axial mixer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitmixer-skeleton-based-gait-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing gait recognition methods are appearance-based, which rely on the silhouettes extracted from the video data of human walking activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitmixer-skeleton-based-gait-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TASA: Deceiving Question Answering Models by Twin Answer Sentences Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tasa-deceiving-question-answering-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Twin Answer Sentences Attack (TASA), an adversarial attack method for question answering (QA) models that produces fluent and grammatical adversarial contexts while maintaining gold answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tasa-deceiving-question-answering-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Language Model to Train if You Have One Million GPU Hours?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-language-model-to-train-if-you-have-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All our models and code are open-sourced at https://huggingface. co/bigscience .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-language-model-to-train-if-you-have-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Feature Distillation via Projector Ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-feature-distillation-via-projector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the positive effect of the projector in feature distillation, we propose an ensemble of projectors to further improve the quality of student features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-feature-distillation-via-projector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting modality-invariant feature for robust multimodal emotion recognition with missing modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-modality-invariant-feature-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal emotion recognition leverages complementary information across modalities to gain performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-modality-invariant-feature-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion-based Few-Shot Morphing Attack Detection and Fingerprinting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-based-few-shot-morphing-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our technical contributions include: 1) We propose a fusion-based few-shot learning (FSL) method to learn discriminative features that can generalize to unseen morphing attack types from predefined presentation attacks; 2) The proposed FSL based on the fusion of the PRNU model and Noiseprint network is extended from binary MAD to multiclass morphing attack fingerprinting (MAF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-based-few-shot-morphing-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deformable Temporal Convolutional Networks for Monaural Noisy Reverberant Speech Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-temporal-convolutional-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work deformable convolution is proposed as a solution to allow TCN models to have dynamic RFs that can adapt to various reverberation times for reverberant speech separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-temporal-convolutional-networks</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
