<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:06:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Conventions for Human-AI Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-conventions-for-human-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventions are crucial for strong performance in cooperative multi-agent games, because they allow players to coordinate on a shared strategy without explicit communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-conventions-for-human-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variator: Accelerating Pre-trained Models with Plug-and-Play Compression Modules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variator-accelerating-pre-trained-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained language models (PLMs) have achieved remarkable results on NLP tasks but at the expense of huge parameter sizes and the consequent computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variator-accelerating-pre-trained-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuSR: Testing the Limits of Chain-of-thought with Multistep Soft Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musr-testing-the-limits-of-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate a range of LLMs and prompting techniques on this dataset and characterize the gaps that remain for techniques like chain-of-thought to perform robust reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musr-testing-the-limits-of-chain-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-HATERS: A Hate Speech Detection Corpus in Korean with Target-Specific Ratings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-haters-a-hate-speech-detection-corpus-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This resource is the largest offensive language corpus in Korean and is the first to offer target-specific ratings on a three-point Likert scale, enabling the detection of hate expressions in Korean across varying degrees of offensiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-haters-a-hate-speech-detection-corpus-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLFMF: Data Sets for Machine Learning for Mathematical Formalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlfmf-data-sets-for-machine-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The collection includes the largest Lean~4 library Mathlib, and some of the largest Agda libraries: the standard library, the library of univalent mathematics Agda-unimath, and the TypeTopology library.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlfmf-data-sets-for-machine-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tagE: Enabling an Embodied Agent to Understand Human Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tage-enabling-an-embodied-agent-to-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At its core, our system employs an inventive neural network model designed to extract a series of tasks from complex task instructions expressed in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tage-enabling-an-embodied-agent-to-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTRASTE: Supervised Contrastive Pre-training With Aspect-based Prompts For Aspect Sentiment Triplet Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contraste-supervised-contrastive-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then (pre)train an encoder-decoder model by applying contrastive learning on the decoder-generated aspect-aware sentiment representations of the masked terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contraste-supervised-contrastive-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Attention-based Deep Reinforcement Learning for solving the Chinese Postman Problem with Load-dependent costs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-attention-based-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release our C++ implementations for metaheuristics such as EA, ILS and VNS along with the code for data generation and our generated data at https://github. com/HySonLab/Chinese_Postman_Problem]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-attention-based-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Medical Image Classification using Prototype Learning and Privileged Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-medical-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability is often an essential requirement in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-medical-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScanDL: A Diffusion Model for Generating Synthetic Scanpaths on Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scandl-a-diffusion-model-for-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, scarcity of eye movement data and its unavailability at application time poses a major challenge for this line of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scandl-a-diffusion-model-for-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SequenceMatch: Revisiting the design of weak-strong augmentations for Semi-supervised learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequencematch-revisiting-the-design-of-weak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By taking advantage of different augmentations and the consistency constraints between each pair of augmented examples, SequenceMatch helps reduce the divergence between the prediction distribution of the model for weakly and strongly augmented examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequencematch-revisiting-the-design-of-weak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accented Speech Recognition With Accent-specific Codebooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accented-speech-recognition-with-accent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel accent adaptation approach for end-to-end ASR systems using cross-attention with a trainable set of codebooks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accented-speech-recognition-with-accent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BianQue: Balancing the Questioning and Suggestion Ability of Health LLMs with Multi-turn Health Conversations Polished by ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bianque-balancing-the-questioning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have performed well in providing general and extensive health suggestions in single-turn conversations, exemplified by systems such as ChatGPT, ChatGLM, ChatDoctor, DoctorGLM, and etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bianque-balancing-the-questioning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G2-MonoDepth: A General Framework of Generalized Depth Inference from Monocular RGB+X Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2-monodepth-a-general-framework-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates a unified task of monocular depth inference, which infers high-quality depth maps from all kinds of input raw data from various robots in unseen scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g2-monodepth-a-general-framework-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Diffusion Weighted Graph Framework for New Intent Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-diffusion-weighted-graph-framework-for-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[New Intent Discovery (NID) aims to recognize both new and known intents from unlabeled data with the aid of limited labeled data containing only known intents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-diffusion-weighted-graph-framework-for-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating View Conditions for Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-view-conditions-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of image processing, applying intricate semantic modifications within existing images remains an enduring challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-view-conditions-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimewarpVAE: Simultaneous Time-Warping and Representation Learning of Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timewarpvae-simultaneous-time-warping-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human demonstrations of trajectories are an important source of training data for many machine learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timewarpvae-simultaneous-time-warping-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Sequences Prediction via Fourier Transform for Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-sequences-prediction-via-fourier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we theoretically analyze the existence of structural information in state sequences, which is closely related to policy performance and signal regularity, and then propose to predict the Fourier transform of infinite-step future state sequences to extract such information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-sequences-prediction-via-fourier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-driven Scene Synthesis using Multi-conditional Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-scene-synthesis-using-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a language-driven scene synthesis task, which is a new task that integrates text prompts, human motion, and existing objects for scene synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-scene-synthesis-using-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind the Gap Between Conversations for Improved Long-Term Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-gap-between-conversations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowing how to end and resume conversations over time is a natural part of communication, allowing for discussions to span weeks, months, or years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-the-gap-between-conversations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nominality Score Conditioned Time Series Anomaly Detection by Point/Sequential Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nominality-score-conditioned-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework for unsupervised time series anomaly detection that utilizes point-based and sequence-based reconstruction models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nominality-score-conditioned-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Convolutional Neural Networks as Efficient Pre-trained Audio Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-convolutional-neural-networks-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio Spectrogram Transformers are excellent at exploiting large datasets, creating powerful pre-trained models that surpass CNNs when fine-tuned on downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-convolutional-neural-networks-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transitivity Recovering Decompositions: Interpretable and Robust Fine-Grained Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transitivity-recovering-decompositions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We begin by theoretically showing that abstract relational representations are nothing but a way of recovering transitive relationships among local views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transitivity-recovering-decompositions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Detection of LLMs-Generated Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-detection-of-llms-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The burgeoning capabilities of advanced large language models (LLMs) such as ChatGPT have led to an increase in synthetic content generation with implications across a variety of sectors, including media, cybersecurity, public discourse, and education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-detection-of-llms-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-aware Debiased Self-supervised Graph Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-debiased-self-supervised-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, given a user (item), we construct its negative pairs by selecting users (items) which embed different semantic structures to ensure the semantic difference between the given user (item) and its negatives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-debiased-self-supervised-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a silver standard for patent simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-a-silver-standard-for-patent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Patents are legal documents that aim at protecting inventions on the one hand and at making technical knowledge circulate on the other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-a-silver-standard-for-patent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woodpecker: Hallucination Correction for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/woodpecker-hallucination-correction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucination is a big shadow hanging over the rapidly evolving Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs), referring to the phenomenon that the generated text is inconsistent with the image content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/woodpecker-hallucination-correction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A statistical significance testing approach for measuring term burstiness with applications to domain-specific terminology extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-significance-testing-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To test these waters, we propose as our main contribution a multinomial language model-based exact test of statistical significance for term burstiness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-significance-testing-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DALE: Generative Data Augmentation for Low-Resource Legal NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dale-generative-data-augmentation-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DALE, a novel and effective generative Data Augmentation framework for low-resource LEgal NLP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dale-generative-data-augmentation-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoAnnotating: Uncertainty-Guided Work Allocation between Human and Large Language Models for Data Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coannotating-uncertainty-guided-work</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annotated data plays a critical role in Natural Language Processing (NLP) in training models and evaluating their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coannotating-uncertainty-guided-work</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Language Models into Direct Speech Translation: An Inference-Time Solution to Control Gender Inflection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-language-models-into-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When translating words referring to the speaker, speech translation (ST) systems should not resort to default masculine generics nor rely on potentially misleading vocal traits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-language-models-into-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetry-preserving graph attention network to solve routing problems at multiple resolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-preserving-graph-attention-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Travelling Salesperson Problems (TSPs) and Vehicle Routing Problems (VRPs) have achieved reasonable improvement in accuracy and computation time with the adaptation of Machine Learning (ML) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-preserving-graph-attention-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual directed acyclic graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-directed-acyclic-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating the structure of directed acyclic graphs (DAGs) from observational data remains a significant challenge in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-directed-acyclic-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's Left? Concept Grounding with Logic-Enhanced Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-s-left-concept-grounding-with-logic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the Logic-Enhanced Foundation Model (LEFT), a unified framework that learns to ground and reason with concepts across domains with a differentiable, domain-independent, first-order logic-based program executor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-s-left-concept-grounding-with-logic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptiX -- A Transitional XR Framework for Development and Evaluation of Shared Control Applications in Assistive Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptix-a-transitional-xr-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the ongoing efforts to empower people with mobility impairments and the increase in technological acceptance by the general public, assistive technologies, such as collaborative robotic arms, are gaining popularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptix-a-transitional-xr-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking of brightness consistency in optical flow with a lightweight CNN network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-of-brightness-consistency-in-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modifying the typical brightness consistency of the optical flow method to the convolutional feature consistency yields the light-robust hybrid optical flow method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-of-brightness-consistency-in-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble of Task-Specific Language Models for Brain Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-of-task-specific-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models have been shown to be rich enough to encode fMRI activations of certain Regions of Interest in our Brains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-of-task-specific-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expression Syntax Information Bottleneck for Math Word Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expression-syntax-information-bottleneck-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we design an Expression Syntax Information Bottleneck method for MWP (called ESIB) based on variational information bottleneck, which extracts essential features of expression syntax tree while filtering latent-specific redundancy containing syntax-irrelevant features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expression-syntax-information-bottleneck-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MUSER: A Multi-View Similar Case Retrieval Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muser-a-multi-view-similar-case-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the case similarities are typically measured solely by the textual semantics of the fact descriptions, which may fail to capture the full complexity of legal cases from the perspective of legal knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muser-a-multi-view-similar-case-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUPNet++: Geometry Uncertainty Propagation Network for Monocular 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gupnet-geometry-uncertainty-propagation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It models the uncertainty propagation relationship of the geometry projection during training, improving the stability and efficiency of the end-to-end model learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gupnet-geometry-uncertainty-propagation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nighttime Thermal Infrared Image Colorization with Feedback-based Object Appearance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nighttime-thermal-infrared-image-colorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments illustrate that the proposed FoalGAN is not only effective for appearance learning of small objects, but also outperforms other image translation methods in terms of semantic preservation and edge consistency for the NTIR2DC task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nighttime-thermal-infrared-image-colorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is not a Dataset: A Large Negation Benchmark to Challenge Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-is-not-a-dataset-a-large-negation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have used our dataset with the largest available open LLMs in a zero-shot approach to grasp their generalization and inference capability and we have also fine-tuned some of the models to assess whether the understanding of negation can be trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-is-not-a-dataset-a-large-negation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Failures Pave the Way: Enhancing Large Language Models through Tuning-free Rule Accumulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/failures-pave-the-way-enhancing-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have showcased impressive performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/failures-pave-the-way-enhancing-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NuTrea: Neural Tree Search for Context-guided Multi-hop KGQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nutrea-neural-tree-search-for-context-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-hop Knowledge Graph Question Answering (KGQA) is a task that involves retrieving nodes from a knowledge graph (KG) to answer natural language questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nutrea-neural-tree-search-for-context-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Biomedical Abstractive Summarisation with Knowledge Aggregation from Citation Papers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-biomedical-abstractive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstracts derived from biomedical literature possess distinct domain-specific characteristics, including specialised writing styles and biomedical terminologies, which necessitate a deep understanding of the related literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-biomedical-abstractive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Language Pseudo-Labels for Single-Positive Multi-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-pseudo-labels-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In general multi-label learning, a model learns to predict multiple labels or categories for a single input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-pseudo-labels-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Mason-Alberta Phonetic Segmenter: A forced alignment system based on deep neural networks and interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mason-alberta-phonetic-segmenter-a-forced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also reflect on the task and training process for acoustic modeling in forced alignment, highlighting how the output targets for these models do not match phoneticians' conception of similarity between phones and that reconciliation of this tension may require rethinking the task and output targets or how speech itself should be segmented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mason-alberta-phonetic-segmenter-a-forced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Temporal and Causal Reasoners for Video Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-temporal-and-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the LLMs provide effective priors in exploiting $\textit{linguistic shortcuts}$ for temporal and causal reasoning in Video Question Answering (VideoQA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-temporal-and-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Differences in Values Influence Disagreements in Online Discussions?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-differences-in-values-influence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate a hypothesis that differences in personal values are indicative of disagreement in online discussions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-differences-in-values-influence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning From Free-Text Human Feedback -- Collect New Datasets Or Extend Existing Ones?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-free-text-human-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning from free-text human feedback is essential for dialog systems, but annotated data is scarce and usually covers only a small fraction of error types known in conversational AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-free-text-human-feedback</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
