<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 21:05:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explainable Collaborative Filtering with Taste Clusters Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent decades, there have been significant advancements in latent embedding-based CF methods for improved accuracy, such as matrix factorization, neural collaborative filtering, and LightGCN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAC: Fairness-Aware Representation Learning by Suppressing Attribute-Class Associations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flac-fairness-aware-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, this work introduces FLAC, a methodology that minimizes mutual information between the features extracted by the model and a protected attribute, without the use of attribute labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flac-fairness-aware-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Figments and Misalignments: A Framework for Fine-grained Crossmodal Misinformation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figments-and-misalignments-a-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that AMM adds noise to the training and evaluation process while exacerbating the unimodal bias, where text-only or image-only detectors can seemingly outperform their multimodal counterparts on an inherently multimodal task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figments-and-misalignments-a-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Structurally Complex with Additive Parent Causality (SCARY) Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-structurally-complex-with-additive-parent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our SCARY dataset provides a valuable resource for researchers to explore causal discovery under more realistic scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-structurally-complex-with-additive-parent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Is Not the Main Factor Behind the Gap Between SGD and Adam on Transformers, but Sign Descent Might Be</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-is-not-the-main-factor-behind-the-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This suggests that Adam outperform SGD because it uses a more robust gradient estimate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-is-not-the-main-factor-behind-the-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseFusion: Fusing Multi-Modal Sparse Representations for Multi-Sensor 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsefusion-fusing-multi-modal-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, given that objects occupy only a small part of a scene, finding dense candidates and generating dense representations is noisy and inefficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsefusion-fusing-multi-modal-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JaxPruner: A concise library for sparsity research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxpruner-a-concise-library-for-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces JaxPruner, an open-source JAX-based pruning and sparse training library for machine learning research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxpruner-a-concise-library-for-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-discipline on multiple channels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-discipline-on-multiple-channels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparative experimental results on both datasets show that SMC-2 outperforms Label Smoothing Regularizaion and Self-distillation From The Last Mini-batch on all models, and outperforms the state-of-the-art Sharpness-Aware Minimization method on 83% of the models. Compatibility of SMC-2 and data augmentation experimental results show that using both SMC-2 and data augmentation improves the generalization ability of the model between 0. 28% and 1. 80% compared to using only data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-discipline-on-multiple-channels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting People in Their Place: Affordance-Aware Human Insertion into Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-people-in-their-place-affordance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a scene image with a marked region and an image of a person, we insert the person into the scene while respecting the scene affordances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-people-in-their-place-affordance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-Hamiltonian neural networks for learning partial differential equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-hamiltonian-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pseudo-Hamiltonian neural networks (PHNN) were recently introduced for learning dynamical systems that can be modelled by ordinary differential equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-hamiltonian-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing the Boundaries of Tractable Multiperspective Reasoning: A Deduction Calculus for Standpoint EL+</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-boundaries-of-tractable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standpoint EL is a multi-modal extension of the popular description logic EL that allows for the integrated representation of domain knowledge relative to diverse standpoints or perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-boundaries-of-tractable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Big Brother: Attacking Search Engines with Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-big-brother-attacking-search-engines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Search engines are vulnerable to attacks against indexing and searching via text encoding manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-big-brother-attacking-search-engines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishing a planetary transit from false positives: a Transformer-based classification for planetary transit signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-a-planetary-transit-from-false</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models, such as the Transformer architecture, were recently proposed for sequential data with successful results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-a-planetary-transit-from-false</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mimic-IV-ICD: A new benchmark for eXtreme MultiLabel Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-iv-icd-a-new-benchmark-for-extreme-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical notes are assigned ICD codes - sets of codes for diagnoses and procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-iv-icd-a-new-benchmark-for-extreme-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Conformer: Incorporating Convolutions into Vision Transformer Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-conformer-incorporating-convolutions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers are popular neural network models that use layers of self-attention and fully-connected nodes with embedded tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-conformer-incorporating-convolutions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuromorphic Computing with AER using Time-to-Event-Margin Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromorphic-computing-with-aer-using-time-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Address-Event-Representation (AER) is a spike-routing protocol that allows the scaling of neuromorphic and spiking neural network (SNN) architectures to a size that is comparable to that of digital neural network architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromorphic-computing-with-aer-using-time-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatLog: Recording and Analyzing ChatGPT Across Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlog-recording-and-analyzing-chatgpt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there are abundant researches about evaluating ChatGPT on natural language understanding and generation tasks, few studies have investigated how ChatGPT's behavior changes over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlog-recording-and-analyzing-chatgpt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resampling Gradients Vanish in Differentiable Sequential Monte Carlo Samplers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resampling-gradients-vanish-in-differentiable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annealed Importance Sampling (AIS) moves particles along a Markov chain from a tractable initial distribution to an intractable target distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resampling-gradients-vanish-in-differentiable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderately Distributional Exploration for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moderately-distributional-exploration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that MODE can endow models with provable generalization performance on unknown target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moderately-distributional-exploration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight, Pre-trained Transformers for Remote Sensing Timeseries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-pre-trained-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Presto can be used for transfer learning or as a feature extractor for simple models, enabling efficient deployment at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-pre-trained-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Inductive Bias in Transformer for Point Cloud Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inductive-bias-in-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discovering inter-point connection for efficient high-dimensional feature extraction from point coordinate is a key challenge in processing point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inductive-bias-in-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIMS-OS: An automation software to implement a closed loop between artificial intelligence and robotic experiments in materials science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nims-os-an-automation-software-to-implement-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Newly created modules for AI and robotic experiments can be added easily to extend the functionality of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nims-os-an-automation-software-to-implement-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPLUG-Owl: Modularization Empowers Large Language Models with Multimodality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-owl-modularization-empowers-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our code, pre-trained model, instruction-tuned models, and evaluation set are available at https://github. com/X-PLUG/mPLUG-Owl.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-owl-modularization-empowers-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occ3D: A Large-Scale 3D Occupancy Prediction Benchmark for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occ3d-a-large-scale-3d-occupancy-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we introduce a novel task for 3D occupancy prediction, which aims to estimate the detailed occupancy and semantics of objects from multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occ3d-a-large-scale-3d-occupancy-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>string2string: A Modern Python Library for String-to-String Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It includes traditional algorithmic solutions as well as recent advanced neural approaches to tackle various problems in string alignment, distance measurement, lexical and semantic search, and similarity analysis -- along with several helpful visualization tools and metrics to facilitate the interpretation and analysis of these methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modular Approach for Multilingual Timex Detection and Normalization using Deep Learning and Grammar-based methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-approach-for-multilingual-timex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting and normalizing temporal expressions is an essential step for many NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-approach-for-multilingual-timex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Evaluation of POS Taggers: From Wall Street Journal to Fandom Wiki</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-evaluation-of-pos-taggers-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Wall Street Journal section of the Penn Treebank has been the de-facto standard for evaluating POS taggers for a long time, and accuracies over 97\% have been reported.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-evaluation-of-pos-taggers-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataComp: In search of the next generation of multimodal datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datacomp-in-search-of-the-next-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this shortcoming in the machine learning ecosystem, we introduce DataComp, a benchmark where the training code is fixed and researchers innovate by proposing new training sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datacomp-in-search-of-the-next-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN based IoT Device Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnn-based-iot-device-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the use of the Internet of Things is becoming more and more popular, many security vulnerabilities are emerging with the large number of devices being introduced to the market.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnn-based-iot-device-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RegHEC: Hand-Eye Calibration via Simultaneous Multi-view Point Clouds Registration of Arbitrary Object</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reghec-hand-eye-calibration-via-simultaneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RegHEC is a registration-based hand-eye calibration technique with no need for accurate calibration rig but arbitrary available objects, applicable for both eye-in-hand and eye-to-hand cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reghec-hand-eye-calibration-via-simultaneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edit Everything: A Text-Guided Generative System for Images Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edit-everything-a-text-guided-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new generative system called Edit Everything, which can take image and text inputs and produce image outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edit-everything-a-text-guided-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization-Inspired Cross-Attention Transformer for Compressive Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-inspired-cross-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And, PGCA block achieves an enhanced information interaction, which introduces the inertia force into the gradient descent step through a cross attention block.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-inspired-cross-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking Neural Network Decision Feedback Equalization for IM/DD Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-network-decision-feedback-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A spiking neural network (SNN) equalizer with a decision feedback structure is applied to an IM/DD link with various parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-network-decision-feedback-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Object-Centric Generalized Value Functions From Pixels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-centric-generalized-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Reinforcement Learning has shown significant progress in extracting useful representations from high-dimensional inputs albeit using hand-crafted auxiliary tasks and pseudo rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-centric-generalized-value</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Analysis of the FRP Rebar Using Computer Vision Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-analysis-of-the-frp-rebar-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a method to analyze the inner structure of the composite FRP rebar, namely the shift of the real center of gravity with a respect to the geometrical center of rebar and changes of cross-sectional characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-analysis-of-the-frp-rebar-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSTM based IoT Device Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-iot-device-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the use of the Internet of Things is becoming more and more popular, many security vulnerabilities are emerging with the large number of devices being introduced to the market.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-iot-device-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Assembly as a Markov Decision Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-assembly-as-a-markov-decision-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many games feature a progression of levels that doesn't adapt to the player.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/level-assembly-as-a-markov-decision-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViMQ: A Vietnamese Medical Question Dataset for Healthcare Dialogue System Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vimq-a-vietnamese-medical-question-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing medical text datasets usually take the form of ques- tion and answer pairs that support the task of natural language gener- ation, but lacking the composite annotations of the medical terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vimq-a-vietnamese-medical-question-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density Invariant Contrast Maximization for Neuromorphic Earth Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-invariant-contrast-maximization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is to ensure that the contrast is only high around the correct motion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-invariant-contrast-maximization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLT: An R package for Linear Law-based Feature Space Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llt-an-r-package-for-linear-law-based-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The presented R package, called LLT, implements this algorithm in a flexible yet user-friendly way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llt-an-r-package-for-linear-law-based-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity-Level Sentiment Analysis (ELSA): An exploratory task survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-level-sentiment-analysis-elsa-an-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that sentiment in our dataset is expressed not only with an entity mention as target, but also towards targets with a sentiment-relevant relation to a volitional entity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-level-sentiment-analysis-elsa-an-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interweaved Graph and Attention Network for 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interweaved-graph-and-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite substantial progress in 3D human pose estimation from a single-view image, prior works rarely explore global and local correlations, leading to insufficient learning of human skeleton representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interweaved-graph-and-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Attention Model with Occlusion-aware Texture Regression for 3D Hand Reconstruction from a Single RGB Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-attention-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate our probabilistic model's state-of-the-art accuracy in 3D hand and texture reconstruction from a single image in both training schemes, including in the presence of severe occlusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-attention-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're Afraid Language Models Aren't Modeling Ambiguity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-re-afraid-language-models-aren-t-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the task remains extremely challenging, including for the recent GPT-4, whose generated disambiguations are considered correct only 32% of the time in human evaluation, compared to 90% for disambiguations in our dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-re-afraid-language-models-aren-t-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Are State-of-the-Art Evaluators of Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-state-of-the-art-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Token-matching-based metrics, such as BLEU, have demonstrated weak correlations with human practitioners in code generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-state-of-the-art-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SweCTRL-Mini: a data-transparent Transformer-based large language model for controllable text generation in Swedish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swectrl-mini-a-data-transparent-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SweCTRL-Mini, a large Swedish language model that can be used for inference and fine-tuning on a single consumer-grade GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swectrl-mini-a-data-transparent-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeqTrack: Sequence to Sequence Learning for Visual Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqtrack-sequence-to-sequence-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new sequence-to-sequence learning framework for visual tracking, dubbed SeqTrack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqtrack-sequence-to-sequence-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Unsupervised Transfer Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-unsupervised-transfer-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation is a core computer vision competency, with applications spanning a broad range of scientifically and economically valuable domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-unsupervised-transfer-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Segmentation in the Dark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-segmentation-in-the-dark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing instance segmentation techniques are primarily tailored for high-visibility inputs, but their performance significantly deteriorates in extremely low-light environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-segmentation-in-the-dark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaMini-LM: A Diverse Herd of Distilled Models from Large-Scale Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamini-lm-a-diverse-herd-of-distilled-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we carefully develop a large set of 2. 58M instructions based on both existing and newly-generated instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamini-lm-a-diverse-herd-of-distilled-models</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
