<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:13:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Lana: A Language-Capable Navigator for Instruction Following and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lana-a-language-capable-navigator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, visual-language navigation (VLN) -- entailing robot agents to follow navigation instructions -- has shown great advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lana-a-language-capable-navigator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionAD: Denoising Diffusion for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionad-denoising-diffusion-for-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new pipeline, DiffusionAD, to anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusionad-denoising-diffusion-for-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVHeight: A Robust Framework for Vision-based Roadside 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevheight-a-robust-framework-for-vision-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In essence, instead of predicting the pixel-wise depth, we regress the height to the ground to achieve a distance-agnostic formulation to ease the optimization process of camera-only perception methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevheight-a-robust-framework-for-vision-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dually Enhanced Propensity Score Estimation in Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dually-enhanced-propensity-score-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[According to the graph, two complementary propensity scores are estimated from the views of item and user, respectively, based on the same set of user feedback data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dually-enhanced-propensity-score-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Ensembles of Hyper-Rectangles as Base Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-ensembles-of-hyper-rectangles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new extremely simple ensemble-based model with the uniformly generated axis-parallel hyper-rectangles as base models (HRBM) is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-ensembles-of-hyper-rectangles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoseRAC: Pose Saliency Transformer for Repetitive Action Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poserac-pose-saliency-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we introduce a pose-level method, PoseRAC, which is based on this representation and achieves state-of-the-art performance on two new version datasets by using Pose Saliency Annotation to annotate salient poses for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poserac-pose-saliency-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascaded Zoom-in Detector for High Resolution Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-zoom-in-detector-for-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting objects in aerial images is challenging because they are typically composed of crowded small objects distributed non-uniformly over high-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-zoom-in-detector-for-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mirror: A Natural Language Interface for Data Querying, Summarization, and Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirror-a-natural-language-interface-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Mirror, an open-source platform for data exploration and analysis powered by large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mirror-a-natural-language-interface-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitivity-Aware Visual Parameter-Efficient Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-aware-visual-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Parameter-Efficient Tuning (VPET) has become a powerful alternative for full fine-tuning so as to adapt pre-trained vision models to downstream tasks, which only tunes a small number of parameters while freezing the vast majority ones to ease storage burden and optimization difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-aware-visual-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro-video Tagging via Jointly Modeling Social Influence and Tag Relation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micro-video-tagging-via-jointly-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods mostly focus on analyzing video content, neglecting users' social influence and tag relation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micro-video-tagging-via-jointly-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Individualized Effects of Internet-Based Treatment for Genito-Pelvic Pain/Penetration Disorder: Development and Internal Validation of a Multivariable Decision Tree Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-individualized-effects-of-internet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we developed and internally validated a multivariable decision tree model that predicts effects of an internet-based treatment on a multidimensional composite score of GPPPD symptoms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-individualized-effects-of-internet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-less Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-less-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by these limitations, we propose a simple and effective collaborative filtering model (SimRec) that marries the power of knowledge distillation and contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-less-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSeg3D: Multi-modal 3D Semantic Segmentation for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mseg3d-multi-modal-3d-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a multi-modal 3D semantic segmentation model (MSeg3D) with joint intra-modal feature extraction and inter-modal feature fusion to mitigate the modality heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mseg3d-multi-modal-3d-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Teacher for Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-teacher-for-semi-supervised-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study teacher-student learning from the perspective of data initialization and propose a novel algorithm called Active Teacher(Source code are available at: \url{https://github. com/HunterJ-Lin/ActiveTeacher}) for semi-supervised object detection (SSOD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-teacher-for-semi-supervised-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Low-Frequency Neural Fields for Few-Shot View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-low-frequency-neural-fields-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a simple-yet-effective strategy for tuning the frequency to avoid overfitting few-shot inputs: enforcing consistency among the frequency domain of rendered 2D images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-low-frequency-neural-fields-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DualFair: Fair Representation Learning at Both Group and Individual Levels via Contrastive Self-supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualfair-fair-representation-learning-at-both</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic fairness has become an important machine learning problem, especially for mission-critical Web applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualfair-fair-representation-learning-at-both</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Optical Flow from Geometric Matching Consistent Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-optical-flow-from-geometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a rethinking to previous optical flow estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-optical-flow-from-geometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Accurate Template Matching with Differentiable Coarse-to-Fine Correspondence Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-accurate-template-matching-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the challenges, we propose an accurate template matching method based on differentiable coarse-to-fine correspondence refinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-accurate-template-matching-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting 4D CT Perfusion for segmenting infarcted areas in patients with suspected acute ischemic stroke</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-4d-ct-perfusion-for-segmenting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CT Perfusion (CTP) is often used as a primary assessment to determine stroke location, severity, and volume of ischemic lesions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-4d-ct-perfusion-for-segmenting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpiderMesh: Spatial-aware Demand-guided Recursive Meshing for RGB-T Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spidermesh-spatial-aware-demand-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For semantic segmentation in urban scene understanding, RGB cameras alone often fail to capture a clear holistic topology, especially in challenging lighting conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spidermesh-spatial-aware-demand-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepMIM: Deep Supervision for Masked Image Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmim-deep-supervision-for-masked-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep supervision, which involves extra supervisions to the intermediate features of a neural network, was widely used in image classification in the early deep learning era since it significantly reduces the training difficulty and eases the optimization like avoiding gradient vanish over the vanilla training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmim-deep-supervision-for-masked-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiFormer: Vision Transformer with Bi-Level Routing Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-vision-transformer-with-bi-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the core building block of vision transformers, attention is a powerful tool to capture long-range dependency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-vision-transformer-with-bi-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffBEV: Conditional Diffusion Model for Bird's Eye View Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbev-conditional-diffusion-model-for-bird</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models naturally have the ability to denoise noisy samples to the ideal data, which motivates us to utilize the diffusion model to get a better BEV representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbev-conditional-diffusion-model-for-bird</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Distillation from Single to Multi Labels: an Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-from-single-to-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation (KD) has been extensively studied in single-label image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-from-single-to-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining False Positive Examples for Text-Based Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-false-positive-examples-for-text-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-based person re-identification (ReID) aims to identify images of the targeted person from a large-scale person image database according to a given textual description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-false-positive-examples-for-text-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch or Listen: Robust Audio-Visual Speech Recognition with Visual Corruption Modeling and Reliability Scoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-or-listen-robust-audio-visual-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we firstly analyze that the previous AVSR models are not indeed robust to the corruption of multimodal input streams, the audio and the visual inputs, compared to uni-modal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/watch-or-listen-robust-audio-visual-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HYBRIDFORMER: improving SqueezeFormer with hybrid attention and NSR mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridformer-improving-squeezeformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SqueezeFormer has recently shown impressive performance in automatic speech recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridformer-improving-squeezeformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Contour Tracking of Live Cells by Mechanical and Cycle Consistency Losses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-contour-tracking-of-live-cells</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For quantitative evaluation, we labeled sparse tracking points along the contour of live cells from two live cell datasets taken with phase contrast and confocal fluorescence microscopes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-contour-tracking-of-live-cells</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoordFill: Efficient High-Resolution Image Inpainting via Parameterized Coordinate Querying</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coordfill-efficient-high-resolution-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the proposed structure, we only encode the high-resolution image in a relatively low resolution for larger reception field capturing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coordfill-efficient-high-resolution-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sr-init: An interpretable layer pruning method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sr-init-an-interpretable-layer-pruning-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our SR-init method is inspired by the discovery that the accuracy drop due to stochastic re-initialization of layer parameters differs in various layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sr-init-an-interpretable-layer-pruning-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parametric Surface Constrained Upsampler Network for Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-surface-constrained-upsampler</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing a point cloud upsampler, which aims to generate a clean and dense point cloud given a sparse point representation, is a fundamental and challenging problem in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-surface-constrained-upsampler</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quaternion Orthogonal Transformer for Facial Expression Recognition in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quaternion-orthogonal-transformer-for-facial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, to reduce redundancy among features extracted from pre-trained ResNet-50, we use the orthogonal loss to decompose and compact these features into three sets of orthogonal sub-features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quaternion-orthogonal-transformer-for-facial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperspectral Image Segmentation: A Preliminary Study on the Oral and Dental Spectral Image Database (ODSI-DB)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-image-segmentation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual discrimination of clinical tissue types remains challenging, with traditional RGB imaging providing limited contrast for such tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-image-segmentation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBSCAN of Multi-Slice Clustering for three-order Tensor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-of-multi-slice-clustering-for-three</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several methods for triclustering three-dimensional data require the cluster size or the number of clusters in each dimension to be specified.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbscan-of-multi-slice-clustering-for-three</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Ensemble Search Framework for Semantic Segmentation Using Medical Imaging Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-ensemble-search-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable classification and detection of certain medical conditions, in images, with state-of-the-art semantic segmentation networks, require vast amounts of pixel-wise annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-ensemble-search-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Self-Supervised Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-self-supervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This does not generalize across different datasets and downstream recommendation tasks, which is difficult to be adaptive for data augmentation and robust to noise perturbation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-self-supervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversity-Aware Meta Visual Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-aware-meta-visual-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Diversity-Aware Meta Visual Prompting~(DAM-VP), an efficient and effective prompting method for transferring pre-trained models to downstream tasks with frozen backbone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-aware-meta-visual-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2V4Real: A Real-world Large-scale Dataset for Vehicle-to-Vehicle Cooperative Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2v4real-a-real-world-large-scale-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the development of cooperative perception, we present V2V4Real, the first large-scale real-world multi-modal dataset for V2V perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2v4real-a-real-world-large-scale-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A CNN Based Framework for Unistroke Numeral Recognition in Air-Writing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cnn-based-framework-for-unistroke-numeral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Air-writing refers to virtually writing linguistic characters through hand gestures in three-dimensional space with six degrees of freedom.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cnn-based-framework-for-unistroke-numeral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing Implicit Assumptions in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-implicit-assumptions-in-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our Text-to-Image Model Editing method, TIME for short, receives a pair of inputs: a "source" under-specified prompt for which the model makes an implicit assumption (e. g., "a pack of roses"), and a "destination" prompt that describes the same setting, but with a specified desired attribute (e. g., "a pack of blue roses").]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-implicit-assumptions-in-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alias-Free Convnets: Fractional Shift Invariance via Polynomial Activations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alias-free-convnets-fractional-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although CNNs are believed to be invariant to translations, recent works have shown this is not the case, due to aliasing effects that stem from downsampling layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alias-free-convnets-fractional-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrated Teacher for Sparsely Annotated Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-teacher-for-sparsely-annotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works on sparsely annotated object detection alleviate this problem by generating pseudo labels for the missing annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrated-teacher-for-sparsely-annotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdPE: Adversarial Positional Embeddings for Pretraining Vision Transformers via MAE+</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adpe-adversarial-positional-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A criterion in unsupervised pretraining is the pretext task needs to be sufficiently hard to prevent the transformer encoder from learning trivial low-level features not generalizable well to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adpe-adversarial-positional-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Video Deflickering by Neural Filtering with a Flawed Atlas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-video-deflickering-by-neural-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior work usually requires specific guidance such as the flickering frequency, manual annotations, or extra consistent videos to remove the flicker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-video-deflickering-by-neural-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimFLE: Simple Facial Landmark Encoding for Self-Supervised Facial Expression Recognition in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simfle-simple-facial-landmark-encoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the key issues in facial expression recognition in the wild (FER-W) is that curating large-scale labeled facial images is challenging due to the inherent complexity and ambiguity of facial images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simfle-simple-facial-landmark-encoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynaMask: Dynamic Mask Selection for Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamask-dynamic-mask-selection-for-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The representative instance segmentation methods mostly segment different object instances with a mask of the fixed resolution, e. g., 28*28 grid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamask-dynamic-mask-selection-for-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Framework for Open-Vocabulary Segmentation and Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-framework-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present \ourmodel{}, a simple Open-vocabulary Segmentation and Detection framework that jointly learns from different segmentation and detection datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-framework-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIM: Semantic-aware Instance Mask Generation for Box-Supervised Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-semantic-aware-instance-mask-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised instance segmentation using only bounding box annotations has recently attracted much research attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-semantic-aware-instance-mask-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Label based Semantic Segmentation Framework using Object Perimeters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-label-based-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our new PerimeterFit module will be applied to pre-refine the CAM predictions before using the pixel-similarity-based network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-label-based-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of ChatGPT as a Question Answering System for Answering Complex Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-as-a-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As ChatGPT covers resources such as Wikipedia and supports natural language question answering, it has garnered attention as a potential replacement for traditional knowledge based question answering (KBQA) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-as-a-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
