<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 21:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MMS-LLaMA: Efficient LLM-based Audio-Visual Speech Recognition with Minimal Multimodal Speech Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mms-llama-efficient-llm-based-audio-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-Visual Speech Recognition (AVSR) achieves robust speech recognition in noisy environments by combining auditory and visual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mms-llama-efficient-llm-based-audio-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TxAgent: An AI Agent for Therapeutic Reasoning Across a Universe of Tools</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txagent-an-ai-agent-for-therapeutic-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It selects tools based on task objectives and executes structured function calls to solve therapeutic tasks that require clinical reasoning and cross-source validation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/txagent-an-ai-agent-for-therapeutic-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMPerf: GPU Performance Modeling meets Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmperf-gpu-performance-modeling-meets-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On a set of publicly available OpenCL programs, our model achieves a mean absolute percentage error of $46. 1\%$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmperf-gpu-performance-modeling-meets-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-Based Tree-Sliced Wasserstein Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-tree-sliced-wasserstein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, projecting measures onto low-dimensional spaces can lead to a loss of topological information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-tree-sliced-wasserstein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning Outperforms Supervised Fine-Tuning: A Case Study on Audio Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-outperforms-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, reinforcement learning (RL) has been shown to greatly enhance the reasoning capabilities of large language models (LLMs), and RL-based approaches have been progressively applied to visual multimodal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-outperforms-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Modelling for Mathematical Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modelling-for-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new implementation of the LLM-driven genetic algorithm {\it funsearch}, whose aim is to generate examples of interest to mathematicians and which has already had some success in problems in extremal combinatorics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modelling-for-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Facial Privacy Protection via Weakening Diffusion Purification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-facial-privacy-protection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of social media has led to the widespread sharing of individual portrait images, which pose serious privacy risks due to the capabilities of automatic face recognition (AFR) systems for mass surveillance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-facial-privacy-protection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveLMM-o1: A Step-by-Step Reasoning Dataset and Large Multimodal Model for Driving Scenario Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivelmm-o1-a-step-by-step-reasoning-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model achieves a +7. 49% gain in final answer accuracy, along with a 3. 62% improvement in reasoning score over the previous best open-source model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivelmm-o1-a-step-by-step-reasoning-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flows on convex polytopes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flows-on-convex-polytopes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a framework for modeling complex, high-dimensional distributions on convex polytopes by leveraging recent advances in discrete and continuous normalizing flows on Riemannian manifolds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flows-on-convex-polytopes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Quality Assessment: From Human to Machine Preference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-quality-assessment-from-human-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the huge gap between human and machine visual systems, this paper proposes the topic: Image Quality Assessment for Machine Vision for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-quality-assessment-from-human-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hierarchical Semantic Distillation Framework for Open-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-semantic-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a hierarchical semantic distillation framework named HD-OVD to construct a comprehensive distillation process, which exploits generalizable knowledge from the CLIP model in three aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-semantic-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Generalization Power in LiDAR Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-generalization-power-in-lidar-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world environments, a LiDAR point cloud registration method with robust generalization capabilities (across varying distances and datasets) is crucial for ensuring safety in autonomous driving and other LiDAR-based applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-generalization-power-in-lidar-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Student Splatting and Scooping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-student-splatting-and-scooping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) provides a new framework for novel view synthesis, and has spiked a new wave of research in neural rendering and related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-student-splatting-and-scooping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoStoDet-DDPM: Collaborative Training of Stochastic and Deterministic Models Improves Surgical Workflow Anticipation and Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costodet-ddpm-collaborative-training-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, the DDPM branch is discarded during inference, enabling real-time predictions without sacrificing accuracy. Experiments on the Cholec80 dataset show that for the anticipation task, our method achieves a 16% reduction in eMAE compared to state-of-the-art approaches, and for phase recognition, it improves the Jaccard score by 1. 0%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costodet-ddpm-collaborative-training-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEdit : Rethinking the Spatial and Temporal Redundancy for Efficient Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eedit-rethinking-the-spatial-and-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inversion-based image editing is rapidly gaining momentum while suffering from significant computation overhead, hindering its application in real-time interactive scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eedit-rethinking-the-spatial-and-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoCo-Sim: Enhancing Roadside Collaborative Perception through Foreground Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roco-sim-enhancing-roadside-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To significantly enhance roadside collaborative perception and address critical data issues, we present the first simulation framework RoCo-Sim for road-side collaborative perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roco-sim-enhancing-roadside-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniSTVG: Toward Spatio-Temporal Omni-Object Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnistvg-toward-spatio-temporal-omni-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each sequence in BOSTVG, paired with a free-form textual query, encompasses a varying number of targets ranging from 1 to 10.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnistvg-toward-spatio-temporal-omni-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenCarve: Information-Preserving Visual Token Compression in Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokencarve-information-preserving-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This insight introduces a novel information-preserving perspective, making it possible to maintain performance even under extreme token compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokencarve-information-preserving-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCCUQ: Exploring Efficient Uncertainty Quantification for 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occuq-exploring-efficient-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach consistently demonstrates reliable uncertainty measures, indicating its potential for enhancing the robustness of autonomous driving systems in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occuq-exploring-efficient-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Bayesian deep learning through input-skip Latent Binary Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-bayesian-deep-learning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modeling natural phenomena with artificial neural networks (ANNs) often provides highly accurate predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-bayesian-deep-learning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdvPaint: Protecting Images from Inpainting Manipulation via Adversarial Attention Disruption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advpaint-protecting-images-from-inpainting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The outstanding capability of diffusion models in generating high-quality images poses significant threats when misused by adversaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advpaint-protecting-images-from-inpainting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GS-SDF: LiDAR-Augmented Gaussian Splatting and Neural SDF for Geometrically Consistent Rendering and Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gs-sdf-lidar-augmented-gaussian-splatting-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accurate LiDAR point clouds enable a trained neural signed distance field to offer a manifold geometry field, This motivates us to offer an SDF-based Gaussian initialization for physically grounded primitive placement and a comprehensive geometric regularization for geometrically consistent rendering and reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gs-sdf-lidar-augmented-gaussian-splatting-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take Off the Training Wheels Progressive In-Context Learning for Effective Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-off-the-training-wheels-progressive-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the transformer embeds the task function learned from demonstrations into the separator token representation, which plays an important role in the generation of prior response tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-off-the-training-wheels-progressive-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSTA$\ast$: Cost-Sensitive Toolpath Agent for Multi-turn Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costa-ast-cost-sensitive-toolpath-agent-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we combine the strengths of both LLMs and graph search to find cost-efficient tool paths?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costa-ast-cost-sensitive-toolpath-agent-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light-R1: Curriculum SFT, DPO and RL for Long COT from Scratch and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-r1-curriculum-sft-dpo-and-rl-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Light-R1 series of work validates training long-COT models from scratch, showcases the art in SFT data and releases SOTA models from RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-r1-curriculum-sft-dpo-and-rl-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-Agnostic Knowledge Guided Correction for Improved Neural Surrogate Rollout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-knowledge-guided-correction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the evolution of these systems is governed by partial differential equations (PDEs), there are a number of computational simulations which resolve these systems with high accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-knowledge-guided-correction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R1-Onevision: Advancing Generalized Multimodal Reasoning through Cross-Modal Formalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r1-onevision-advancing-generalized-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing visual-language models often struggle to effectively analyze and reason visual content, resulting in suboptimal performance on complex reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r1-onevision-advancing-generalized-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GroundingSuite: Measuring Complex Multi-Granular Pixel Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groundingsuite-measuring-complex-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pixel grounding, encompassing tasks such as Referring Expression Segmentation (RES), has garnered considerable attention due to its immense potential for bridging the gap between vision and language modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groundingsuite-measuring-complex-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeighborRetr: Balancing Hub Centrality in Cross-Modal Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighborretr-balancing-hub-centrality-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal retrieval aims to bridge the semantic gap between different modalities, such as visual and textual data, enabling accurate retrieval across them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighborretr-balancing-hub-centrality-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Once bitten, twice shy: A modeling framework for incorporating heterogeneous mosquito biting into transmission models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/once-bitten-twice-shy-a-modeling-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drivers of multiple biting, like host defensive behaviors or climate factors, also affect the mosquito gonotrophic cycle duration, a quantity used to estimate the biting rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/once-bitten-twice-shy-a-modeling-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OR-LLM-Agent: Automating Modeling and Solving of Operations Research Optimization Problem with Reasoning Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/or-llm-agent-automating-modeling-and-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the lack of dedicated benchmark datasets for evaluating the automated solving of OR problems, we construct a benchmark dataset comprising 83 real-world OR problems described in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/or-llm-agent-automating-modeling-and-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Unbalance in High-frequency Trading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-unbalance-in-high-frequency-trading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In financial trading, return prediction is one of the foundation for a successful trading system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-unbalance-in-high-frequency-trading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-assisted Early Detection of Pancreatic Ductal Adenocarcinoma on Contrast-enhanced CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-assisted-early-detection-of-pancreatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the lack of early and disease-specific symptoms, most patients with PDAC are diagnosed at an advanced disease stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-assisted-early-detection-of-pancreatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing Nonlinear Dynamics via Smooth Prototype Equivalences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-nonlinear-dynamics-via-smooth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our approach enables estimation of the invariant sets of the observed dynamics through the learned mapping from prototype space to data space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-nonlinear-dynamics-via-smooth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing LLMs for Multilingual Discourse Generalization Through a Unified Label Set</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-llms-for-multilingual-discourse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discourse understanding is essential for many NLP tasks, yet most existing work remains constrained by framework-dependent discourse representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-llms-for-multilingual-discourse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R.U.Psycho? Robust Unified Psychometric Testing of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-u-psycho-robust-unified-psychometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present R. U. Psycho, a framework for designing and running robust and reproducible psychometric experiments on generative language models that requires limited coding expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-u-psycho-robust-unified-psychometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Density Principle for MLLM Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-density-principle-for-mllm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a critical principle of Information Density, which examines how much insight a benchmark can provide for the development of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-density-principle-for-mllm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS3C: An Ensemble-Based Two-Step Framework for Classification of Pep Smear Cell Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps3c-an-ensemble-based-two-step-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project aims to promote the development of automated tools for pep smear images classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps3c-an-ensemble-based-two-step-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Self-Supervised Adversarial Training for Robust Vision Models in Histopathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-self-supervised-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial attacks pose significant challenges for vision models in critical fields like healthcare, where reliability is essential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-self-supervised-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StepMathAgent: A Step-Wise Agent for Evaluating Mathematical Processes through Tree-of-Error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stepmathagent-a-step-wise-agent-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating mathematical capabilities is critical for assessing the overall performance of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stepmathagent-a-step-wise-agent-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low Complexity Point Tracking of the Myocardium in 2D Echocardiography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-complexity-point-tracking-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The limits of agreement were wider for both CoTracker2 and EchoTracker, worse than the interobserver variability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-complexity-point-tracking-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGNet: A Neural Network Framework Induced by Discontinuous Galerkin Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgnet-a-neural-network-framework-induced-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general framework for the Discontinuous Galerkin-induced Neural Network (DGNet) inspired by the Interior Penalty Discontinuous Galerkin Method (IPDGM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgnet-a-neural-network-framework-induced-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoT: Unleashing Reasoning Capability of Multimodal Large Language Model for Visual Generation and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/got-unleashing-reasoning-capability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Generation Chain-of-Thought (GoT), a novel paradigm that enables generation and editing through an explicit language reasoning process before outputting images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/got-unleashing-reasoning-capability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVTR: End-to-End Open-Vocabulary Multiple Object Tracking with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovtr-end-to-end-open-vocabulary-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary multiple object tracking aims to generalize trackers to unseen categories during training, enabling their application across a variety of real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovtr-end-to-end-open-vocabulary-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTA: Dual Temporal-channel-wise Attention for Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dta-dual-temporal-channel-wise-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first attempt to concentrate on both the correlation and dependency of temporal-channel using both identical and non-identical attention operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dta-dual-temporal-channel-wise-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyGDA: A Python Library for Graph Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygda-a-python-library-for-graph-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the first comprehensive library in this area, PyGDA covers more than 20 widely used graph domain adaptation methods together with different types of graph datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygda-a-python-library-for-graph-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-objective Good Arm Identification with Bandit Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-good-arm-identification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an algorithm with a sample complexity bound.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-good-arm-identification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whisper Speaker Identification: Leveraging Pre-Trained Multilingual Transformers for Robust Speaker Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whisper-speaker-identification-leveraging-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speaker identification in multilingual settings presents unique challenges, particularly when conventional models are predominantly trained on English data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whisper-speaker-identification-leveraging-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoMA: Scaling up Mamba-based Foundation Models for Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roma-scaling-up-mamba-based-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in self-supervised learning for Vision Transformers (ViTs) have fueled breakthroughs in remote sensing (RS) foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roma-scaling-up-mamba-based-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference-Free 3D Reconstruction of Brain Dissection Photographs with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-free-3d-reconstruction-of-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These photographs bypass the need for exvivo MRI, which is not widely accessible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-free-3d-reconstruction-of-brain</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
