<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:08:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ViT-CoMer: Vision Transformer with Convolutional Multi-scale Feature Interaction for Dense Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vit-comer-vision-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the stateof-the-art, ViT-CoMer has the following advantages: (1) We inject spatial pyramid multi-receptive field convolutional features into the ViT architecture, which effectively alleviates the problems of limited local information interaction and single-feature representation in ViT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vit-comer-vision-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Ranking-based Tests of Independence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-ranking-based-tests-of-independence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we develop a novel nonparametric framework to test the independence of two random variables $\mathbf{X}$ and $\mathbf{Y}$ with unknown respective marginals $H(dx)$ and $G(dy)$ and joint distribution $F(dx dy)$, based on {\it Receiver Operating Characteristic} (ROC) analysis and bipartite ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-ranking-based-tests-of-independence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GuideGen: A Text-guided Framework for Joint CT Volume and Anatomical structure Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidegen-a-text-guided-framework-for-joint-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, our Conditional Image Generator autoregressively generates CT slices conditioned on a corresponding mask slice to incorporate both style information and anatomical guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidegen-a-text-guided-framework-for-joint-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Continual Learning For Interactive Instruction Following Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-for-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To take a step towards a more realistic embodied agent learning scenario, we propose two continual learning setups for embodied agents; learning new behaviors (Behavior Incremental Learning, Behavior-IL) and new environments (Environment Incremental Learning, Environment-IL) For the tasks, previous 'data prior' based continual learning methods maintain logits for the past tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-for-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pyvene: A Library for Understanding and Improving PyTorch Models via Interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyvene-a-library-for-understanding-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interventions on model-internal states are fundamental operations in many areas of AI, including model editing, steering, robustness, and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyvene-a-library-for-understanding-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairRR: Pre-Processing for Group Fairness through Randomized Response</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairrr-pre-processing-for-group-fairness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing usage of machine learning models in consequential decision-making processes has spurred research into the fairness of these systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairrr-pre-processing-for-group-fairness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual All-in-One Adverse Weather Removal with Knowledge Replay on a Unified Network Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-all-in-one-adverse-weather-removal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It considers the characteristics of the image restoration task with multiple degenerations in continual learning, and the knowledge for different degenerations can be shared and accumulated in the unified network structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-all-in-one-adverse-weather-removal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D4D: An RGBD diffusion model to boost monocular depth estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d4d-an-rgbd-diffusion-model-to-boost</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ground-truth RGBD data are fundamental for a wide range of computer vision applications; however, those labeled samples are difficult to collect and time-consuming to produce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d4d-an-rgbd-diffusion-model-to-boost</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSM Meets Video Diffusion Models: Efficient Video Generation with Structured State Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssm-meets-video-diffusion-models-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the experiments, we first evaluate our SSM-based model with UCF101, a standard benchmark of video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssm-meets-video-diffusion-models-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couler: Unified Machine Learning Workflow Optimization in Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/couler-unified-machine-learning-workflow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This variety poses a challenge for end-users in terms of mastering different engine APIs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/couler-unified-machine-learning-workflow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunting Attributes: Context Prototype-Aware Learning for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunting-attributes-context-prototype-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by prototype learning theory, we propose leveraging prototype awareness to capture diverse and fine-grained feature attributes of instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunting-attributes-context-prototype-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoAI: Mixture of All Intelligence for Large Language and Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moai-mixture-of-all-intelligence-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we present a new LLVM, Mixture of All Intelligence (MoAI), which leverages auxiliary visual information obtained from the outputs of external segmentation, detection, SGG, and OCR models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moai-mixture-of-all-intelligence-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSBuilding: Towards General Remote Sensing Image Building Extraction and Change Detection with Foundation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsbuilding-towards-general-remote-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RSBuilding is designed to enhance cross-scene generalization and task universality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsbuilding-towards-general-remote-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Policy from Offline Task Representation Learning via Adversarial Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-policy-from-offline-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the objective of adversarial data augmentation is not merely to generate data analogous to offline data distribution; instead, it aims to create adversarial examples designed to confound learned task representations and lead to incorrect task identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-policy-from-offline-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Competition into Collaboration: The Revolutionary Role of Multi-Agent Systems and Language Models in Modern Organizations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-competition-into-collaboration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article explores the dynamic influence of computational entities based on multi-agent systems theory (SMA) combined with large language models (LLM), which are characterized by their ability to simulate complex human interactions, as a possibility to revolutionize human user interaction from the use of specialized artificial agents to support everything from operational organizational processes to strategic decision making based on applied knowledge and human orchestration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-competition-into-collaboration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemCity: Semantic Scene Generation with Triplane Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semcity-semantic-scene-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we concentrate on generating a real-outdoor scene through learning a diffusion model on a real-world outdoor dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semcity-semantic-scene-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVD-LLM: Truncation-aware Singular Value Decomposition for Large Language Model Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-llm-truncation-aware-singular-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, state-of-the-art SVD-based LLM compression methods have two key limitations: truncating smaller singular values may lead to higher compression loss, and the lack of update on the remaining model parameters after SVD truncation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svd-llm-truncation-aware-singular-value</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NavCoT: Boosting LLM-Based Vision-and-Language Navigation via Learning Disentangled Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navcot-boosting-llm-based-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-and-Language Navigation (VLN), as a crucial research problem of Embodied AI, requires an embodied agent to navigate through complex 3D environments following natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navcot-boosting-llm-based-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Text: Frozen Large Language Models in Visual Signal Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-text-frozen-large-language-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we present the Vision-to-Language Tokenizer, abbreviated as V2T Tokenizer, which transforms an image into a ``foreign language'' with the combined aid of an encoder-decoder, the LLM vocabulary, and a CLIP model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-text-frozen-large-language-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumen: Unleashing Versatile Vision-Centric Capabilities of Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumen-unleashing-versatile-vision-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This adaptation leads to convenient development of such LMMs with minimal modifications, however, it overlooks the intrinsic characteristics of diverse visual tasks and hinders the learning of perception capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumen-unleashing-versatile-vision-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Network Potentials for Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-network-potentials-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic scene completion (SSC) aims to predict complete 3D voxel occupancy and semantics from a single-view RGB-D image, and recent SSC methods commonly adopt multi-modal inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-network-potentials-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMURF: Continuous Dynamics for Motion-Deblurring Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smurf-continuous-dynamics-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural radiance fields (NeRF) has attracted considerable attention for their exceptional ability in synthesizing novel views with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smurf-continuous-dynamics-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterization of Large Language Model Development in the Datacenter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterization-of-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have presented impressive performance across several transformative tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterization-of-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustifying and Boosting Training-Free Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustifying-and-boosting-training-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, the estimation ability of these metrics typically varies across different tasks, making it challenging to achieve robust and consistently good search performance on diverse tasks with only a single training-free metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustifying-and-boosting-training-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Selection: Adaptively Incorporating Public Information for Private Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-selection-adaptively-incorporating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technique allows for public data to be included in a graphical-model-based mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-selection-adaptively-incorporating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning Large Language Models with Sequential Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Targeting the scarcity of sequential instructions in present-day data, we propose sequential instruction tuning, a simple yet effective strategy to automatically augment instruction tuning data and equip LLMs with the ability to execute multiple sequential instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harder Tasks Need More Experts: Dynamic Routing in MoE Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harder-tasks-need-more-experts-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel dynamic expert selection framework for Mixture of Experts (MoE) models, aiming to enhance computational efficiency and model performance by adjusting the number of activated experts based on input difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harder-tasks-need-more-experts-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WorkArena: How Capable Are Web Agents at Solving Common Knowledge Work Tasks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/workarena-how-capable-are-web-agents-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the use of large language model-based agents for interacting with software via web browsers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/workarena-how-capable-are-web-agents-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Different Language Models and Generative Vision Models for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-different-language-models-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore this objective and propose LaVi-Bridge, a pipeline that enables the integration of diverse pre-trained language models and generative vision models for text-to-image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-different-language-models-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Window-based Mamba UNet for Medical Image Segmentation: Beyond Convolution and Self-attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-window-based-mamba-unet-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a Large Window-based Mamba U}-shape Network, or LMa-UNet, for 2D and 3D medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-window-based-mamba-unet-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Synthetic-to-Real Transfer for Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-synthetic-to-real-transfer-for-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With advancements in domain generalized stereo matching networks, models pre-trained on synthetic data demonstrate strong robustness to unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-synthetic-to-real-transfer-for-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Pre-trained LLMs for Generalised Time Series Forecasting via Cross-modal Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-pre-trained-llms-for-generalised-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the surge of the Large Language Models (LLMs), several works have attempted to introduce LLMs into time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-pre-trained-llms-for-generalised-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Decoupling for Motion Magnification via Multi-Level Isomorphic Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-decoupling-for-motion-magnification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we present FD4MM, a new paradigm of Frequency Decoupling for Motion Magnification with a Multi-level Isomorphic Architecture to capture multi-level high-frequency details and a stable low-frequency structure (motion field) in video space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-decoupling-for-motion-magnification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked AutoDecoder is Effective Multi-Task Vision Generalist</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autodecoder-is-effective-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the success of general-purpose models in NLP, recent studies attempt to unify different vision tasks in the same sequence format and employ autoregressive Transformers for sequence prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autodecoder-is-effective-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-Interpolators: Rapid Norm Growth and the Trade-Off between Interpolation and Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-interpolators-rapid-norm-growth-and-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under a random matrix theoretic assumption on the data distribution and an eigendecay assumption on the data covariance matrix $\boldsymbol{\Sigma}$, we demonstrate that any near-interpolator exhibits rapid norm growth: for $\tau$ fixed, $\boldsymbol{\beta}$ has squared $\ell_2$-norm $\mathbb{E}[\|{\boldsymbol{\beta}}\|_{2}^{2}] = \Omega(n^{\alpha})$ where $n$ is the number of samples and $\alpha >1$ is the exponent of the eigendecay, i. e., $\lambda_i(\boldsymbol{\Sigma}) \sim i^{-\alpha}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-interpolators-rapid-norm-growth-and-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triples-to-isiXhosa (T2X): Addressing the Challenges of Low-Resource Agglutinative Data-to-Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triples-to-isixhosa-t2x-addressing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we tackle data-to-text for isiXhosa, which is low-resource and agglutinative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triples-to-isixhosa-t2x-addressing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforced Sequential Decision-Making for Sepsis Treatment: The POSNEGDM Framework with Mortality Classifier and Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-sequential-decision-making-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sepsis, a life-threatening condition triggered by the body's exaggerated response to infection, demands urgent intervention to prevent severe complications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-sequential-decision-making-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LookupFFN: Making Transformers Compute-lite for CPU inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lookupffn-making-transformers-compute-lite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While GPU clusters are the de facto choice for training large deep neural network (DNN) models today, several reasons including ease of workflow, security and cost have led to efforts investigating whether CPUs may be viable for inference in routine use in many sectors of the industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lookupffn-making-transformers-compute-lite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 mJ per Class On-Device Online Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/12-mj-per-class-on-device-online-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Online Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning (O-FSCIL), based on a lightweight model consisting of a pretrained and metalearned feature extractor and an expandable explicit memory storing the class prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/12-mj-per-class-on-device-online-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragAnything: Motion Control for Anything using Entity Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draganything-motion-control-for-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce DragAnything, which utilizes a entity representation to achieve motion control for any object in controllable video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draganything-motion-control-for-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Memorization: The Challenge of Random Memory Access in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-memorization-the-challenge-of-random</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through carefully-designed synthetic tasks, covering the scenarios of full recitation, selective recitation and grounded question answering, we reveal that LMs manage to sequentially access their memory while encountering challenges in randomly accessing memorized content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-memorization-the-challenge-of-random</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Diffusion Model for Image Restoration by Residual Shifting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-diffusion-model-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While diffusion-based image restoration (IR) methods have achieved remarkable success, they are still limited by the low inference speed attributed to the necessity of executing hundreds or even thousands of sampling steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-diffusion-model-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-source-free-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this unified SFDA problem, we propose a novel approach called Latent Causal Factors Discovery (LCFD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-source-free-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableToolBench: Towards Stable Large-Scale Benchmarking on Tool Learning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabletoolbench-towards-stable-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The virtual API server contains a caching system and API simulators which are complementary to alleviate the change in API status.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabletoolbench-towards-stable-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensembling Prioritized Hybrid Policies for Multi-agent Pathfinding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-prioritized-hybrid-policies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first propose a selective communication block to gather richer information for better agent coordination within multi-agent environments and train the model with a Q-learning-based algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-prioritized-hybrid-policies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equipping Computational Pathology Systems with Artifact Processing Pipelines: A Showcase for Computation and Performance Trade-offs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equipping-computational-pathology-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed DL pipelines using two MoEs and two multiclass models of state-of-the-art deep convolutional neural networks (DCNNs) and vision transformers (ViTs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equipping-computational-pathology-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CuVLER: Enhanced Unsupervised Object Discoveries through Exhaustive Self-Supervised Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvler-enhanced-unsupervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce VoteCut, an innovative method for unsupervised object discovery that leverages feature representations from multiple self-supervised models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuvler-enhanced-unsupervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning diagonal scale matrices for HMC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-diagonal-scale-matrices-for-hmc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Three approaches for adaptively tuning diagonal scale matrices for HMC are discussed and compared.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-diagonal-scale-matrices-for-hmc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chronos: Learning the Language of Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chronos-learning-the-language-of-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Chronos, a simple yet effective framework for pretrained probabilistic time series models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chronos-learning-the-language-of-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAMMOTH: Massively Multilingual Modular Open Translation @ Helsinki</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mammoth-massively-multilingual-modular-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NLP in the age of monolithic large language models is approaching its limits in terms of size and information that can be handled.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mammoth-massively-multilingual-modular-open</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
