<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 09:12:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>InternVid: A Large-scale Video-Text Dataset for Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvid-a-large-scale-video-text-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we utilize a multi-scale approach to generate video-related descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvid-a-large-scale-video-text-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Supervised Deep Learning MRI Reconstruction to Multiple and Unseen Contrasts using Meta-Learning Hypernetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-supervised-deep-learning-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hypernetworks and the reconstruction network in the GBML setting provide discriminative mode-specific features and low-level image features, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-supervised-deep-learning-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Functional Structured Data Generators Rooted in Out-of-Equilibrium Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-functional-structured-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address the challenge of using energy-based models to produce high-quality, label-specific data in complex structured datasets, such as population genetics, RNA or protein sequences data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-functional-structured-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mBLIP: Efficient Bootstrapping of Multilingual Vision-LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mblip-efficient-bootstrapping-of-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we \textit{re-align} an image encoder previously tuned to an English LLM to a new, multilingual LLM -- for this, we leverage multilingual data from a mix of vision-and-language tasks, which we obtain by machine-translating high-quality English data to 95 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mblip-efficient-bootstrapping-of-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliGraphs: Datasets for Benchmarking Knowledge Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligraphs-datasets-for-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, Knowledge Graphs are not just sets of links but also have semantics underlying their structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligraphs-datasets-for-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Denoising and the Generative Accumulation of Photons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-denoising-and-the-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This new perspective allows us to make three contributions: We present a new strategy for self-supervised denoising, We present a new method for sampling from the posterior of possible solutions by iteratively sampling and adding small numbers of photons to the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-denoising-and-the-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animate-A-Story: Storytelling with Retrieval-Augmented Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animate-a-story-storytelling-with-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first module, we leverage an off-the-shelf video retrieval system and extract video depths as motion structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animate-a-story-storytelling-with-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-based end-to-end classification of variable-length volumetric data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-end-to-end-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that varying the slice-wise resolution of the input during training results in more informative volume representation as compared to training with fixed number of slices per volume.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-end-to-end-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LimSim: A Long-term Interactive Multi-scenario Traffic Simulator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limsim-a-long-term-interactive-multi-scenario</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the growing popularity of digital twin and autonomous driving in transportation, the demand for simulation systems capable of generating high-fidelity and reliable scenarios is increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limsim-a-long-term-interactive-multi-scenario</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-State-Space Learning: An Identification Approach for Stochastic Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-state-space-learning-an-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Available methods for identification of stochastic dynamical systems from input-output data generally impose restricting structural assumptions on either the noise structure in the data-generating system or the possible state probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-state-space-learning-an-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaterScenes: A Multi-Task 4D Radar-Camera Fusion Dataset and Benchmark for Autonomous Driving on Water Surfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterscenes-a-multi-task-4d-radar-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents WaterScenes, the first multi-task 4D radar-camera fusion dataset for autonomous driving on water surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/waterscenes-a-multi-task-4d-radar-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAN is superior to GraphRNN: node orderings, kernel- and graph embeddings-based metrics for graph generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gran-is-superior-to-graphrnn-node-orderings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use these metrics to compare GraphRNN and GRAN, two well-known generative models for graphs, and unveil the influence of node orderings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gran-is-superior-to-graphrnn-node-orderings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Going Beyond Local: Global Graph-Enhanced Personalized News Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-local-global-graph-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precisely recommending candidate news articles to users has always been a core challenge for personalized news recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/going-beyond-local-global-graph-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prescriptive Process Monitoring Under Resource Constraints: A Reinforcement Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prescriptive-process-monitoring-under-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper argues that, in the presence of resource constraints, a key dilemma in the field of prescriptive process monitoring is to trigger interventions based not only on predictions of their necessity, timeliness, or effect but also on the uncertainty of these predictions and the level of resource utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prescriptive-process-monitoring-under-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-FocalNets: Spatio-Temporal Focal Modulation for Video Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-focalnets-spatio-temporal-focal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video transformer designs are based on self-attention that can model global context at a high computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-focalnets-spatio-temporal-focal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DecompEval: Evaluating Generated Texts as Unsupervised Decomposed Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decompeval-evaluating-generated-texts-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing evaluation metrics for natural language generation (NLG) tasks face the challenges on generalization ability and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decompeval-evaluating-generated-texts-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-regulating Prompts: Foundational Model Adaptation without Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-regulating-prompts-foundational-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first regularization framework for prompt learning that avoids overfitting by jointly attending to pre-trained model features, the training trajectory during prompting, and the textual diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-regulating-prompts-foundational-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Vision-Language Foundation Models for Fine-Grained Downstream Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-vision-language-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language foundation models such as CLIP have shown impressive zero-shot performance on many tasks and datasets, especially thanks to their free-text inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-vision-language-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negated Complementary Commonsense using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negated-complementary-commonsense-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Larger language models, such as GPT-3, have shown to be excellent in many tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negated-complementary-commonsense-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regression-Oriented Knowledge Distillation for Lightweight Ship Orientation Angle Prediction with Optical Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regression-oriented-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Four tiny SOAP models are also created by replacing the convolutional blocks in Mobile-SOAP with four small-scale networks, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regression-oriented-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frameless Graph Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frameless-graph-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation (KD) has shown great potential for transferring knowledge from a complex teacher model to a simple student model in which the heavy learning task can be accomplished efficiently and without losing too much prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frameless-graph-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aeolus Ocean -- A simulation environment for the autonomous COLREG-compliant navigation of Unmanned Surface Vehicles using Deep Reinforcement Learning and Maritime Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeolus-ocean-a-simulation-environment-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[USV control systems must, safely and reliably, be able to adhere to the international regulations for preventing collisions at sea (COLREGs) in encounters with other vessels as they navigate to a given waypoint while being affected by realistic weather conditions, either during the day or at night.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeolus-ocean-a-simulation-environment-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSV: An Alignment Validation Loss for Self-supervised Outlier Model Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsv-an-alignment-validation-loss-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DSV captures the alignment between an augmentation function and the anomaly-generating mechanism with surrogate losses, which approximate the discordance and separability of test data, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsv-an-alignment-validation-loss-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PID-Inspired Inductive Biases for Deep Reinforcement Learning in Partially Observable Control Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-inspired-inductive-biases-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When this is the case, the policy needs to leverage the history of observations to infer the current state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-inspired-inductive-biases-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeFormer: a Semi-Supervised Transformer-based Framework for Tree Counting from a Single High Resolution Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-a-semi-supervised-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic tree density estimation and counting using single aerial and satellite images is a challenging task in photogrammetry and remote sensing, yet has an important role in forest management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-a-semi-supervised-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Embeddings from Large-Scale Acoustic Bird Classifiers Enable Few-Shot Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-embeddings-from-large-scale-acoustic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of deep learning models, classification of important signals from these datasets has markedly improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-embeddings-from-large-scale-acoustic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSE: a drone swarm search environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsse-a-drone-swarm-search-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Drone Swarm Search project is an environment, based on PettingZoo, that is to be used in conjunction with multi-agent (or single-agent) reinforcement learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsse-a-drone-swarm-search-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation-Aware Mutual Learning for Semi-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-mutual-learning-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is based on a mutual learning strategy that incorporates two modules: the Cross-sample Mutual Attention Module (CMA) and the Omni-Correlation Consistency Module (OCC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-mutual-learning-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning for Conversion Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-conversion-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tailor the contrastive learning task to the CVR prediction problem, we propose embedding masking (EM), rather than feature masking, to create two views of augmented samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-conversion-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMBench: Is Your Multi-modal Model an All-around Player?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmbench-is-your-multi-modal-model-an-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to these challenges, we propose MMBench, a novel multi-modality benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmbench-is-your-multi-modal-model-an-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDNAS: Discretized Differentiable Neural Architecture Search for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddnas-discretized-differentiable-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Architecture Search (NAS) has shown promising capability in learning text representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddnas-discretized-differentiable-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessment of the suitability of degradation models for the planning of CCTV inspections of sewer pipes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessment-of-the-suitability-of-degradation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a methodology to assess their suitability to plan inspections considering three dimensions: accuracy metrics, ability to produce long-term degradation curves and explainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessment-of-the-suitability-of-degradation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operational Support Estimator Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/operational-support-estimator-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel approach called Operational Support Estimator Networks (OSENs) for the support estimation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/operational-support-estimator-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently-Verifiable Strong Uniquely Solvable Puzzles and Matrix Multiplication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-verifiable-strong-uniquely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We advance the Cohn-Umans framework for developing fast matrix multiplication algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-verifiable-strong-uniquely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeSeed: Frequency-band-aware and Self-guided Network for Sparse-view CT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseed-frequency-band-aware-and-self-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first propose a frequency-band-aware artifact modeling network (FreeNet), which learns artifact-related frequency-band attention in Fourier domain for better modeling the globally distributed streak artifact on the sparse-view CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseed-frequency-band-aware-and-self-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoK: Comparing Different Membership Inference Attacks with a Comprehensive Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-comparing-different-membership-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have identified three principles for the proposed "comparing different MI attacks" methodology, and we have designed and implemented the MIBench benchmark with 84 evaluation scenarios for each dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-comparing-different-membership-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Faster Gradient Descent via Long Steps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-faster-gradient-descent-via-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work establishes provably faster convergence rates for gradient descent via a computer-assisted analysis technique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-faster-gradient-descent-via-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing Spatiotemporal Data with C-VAEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-spatiotemporal-data-with-c</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing region interpolation methods often fail to generate smooth and realistic representations of a region's evolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-spatiotemporal-data-with-c</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Batch Optimization of Contrastive Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-batch-optimization-of-contrastive-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning has gained significant attention as a method for self-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-batch-optimization-of-contrastive-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifiability Guarantees for Causal Disentanglement from Soft Interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiability-guarantees-for-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal disentanglement aims to uncover a representation of data using latent variables that are interrelated through a causal model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifiability-guarantees-for-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-based estimation of whole-body kinematics from multi-view images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-estimation-of-whole-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is necessary to analyze the whole-body kinematics (including joint locations and joint angles) to assess risks of fatal and musculoskeletal injuries in occupational tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-estimation-of-whole-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhythm Modeling for Voice Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythm-modeling-for-voice-conversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice conversion aims to transform source speech into a different target voice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythm-modeling-for-voice-conversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single-Class Target-Specific Attack against Interpretable Deep Learning Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-class-target-specific-attack-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The universal perturbation is stochastically and iteratively optimized by minimizing the adversarial loss that is designed to consider both the classifier and interpreter costs in targeted and non-targeted categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-class-target-specific-attack-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locally Adaptive Federated Learning via Stochastic Polyak Stepsizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-federated-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that FedSPS converges linearly in strongly convex and sublinearly in convex settings when the interpolation condition (overparametrization) is satisfied, and converges to a neighborhood of the solution in the general case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-federated-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLA-GCN: Global-local Adaptive Graph Convolutional Network for 3D Human</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gla-gcn-global-local-adaptive-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, we concentrate on improving the 3D human pose lifting via ground truth data for the future improvement of more quality estimated pose data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gla-gcn-global-local-adaptive-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashaar: Automatic Analysis and Generation of Arabic Poetry Using Deep Learning Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ashaar-automatic-analysis-and-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Poetry holds immense significance within the cultural and traditional fabric of any nation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ashaar-automatic-analysis-and-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auxiliary-Tasks Learning for Physics-Informed Neural Network-Based Partial Differential Equations Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-learning-for-physics-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these issues, we proposed auxiliary-task learning-based physics-informed neural networks (ATL-PINNs), which provide four different auxiliary-task learning modes and investigate their performance compared with original PINNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-learning-for-physics-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluggable Neural Machine Translation Models via Memory-augmented Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-neural-machine-translation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although neural machine translation (NMT) models perform well in the general domain, it remains rather challenging to control their generation behavior to satisfy the requirement of different users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-neural-machine-translation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rectifying Noisy Labels with Sequential Prior: Multi-Scale Temporal Feature Affinity Learning for Robust Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-noisy-labels-with-sequential-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, Temporal Feature Affinity Learning (TFAL) is devised to indicate possible noisy labels by evaluating the affinity between pixels in two adjacent frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-noisy-labels-with-sequential-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>balance -- a Python package for balancing biased data samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-a-python-package-for-balancing-biased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The balance workflow includes three steps: understanding the initial bias in the data relative to a target we would like to infer, adjusting the data to correct for the bias by producing weights for each unit in the sample based on propensity scores, and evaluating the final biases and the variance inflation after applying the fitted weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-a-python-package-for-balancing-biased</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
