<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 09:15:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Practitioner's Guide to Continual Multimodal Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practitioner-s-guide-to-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we complement current perspectives on continual pretraining through a research test bed as well as provide comprehensive guidance for effective continual model updates in such scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practitioner-s-guide-to-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Causality Manipulation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-causality-manipulation-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown various ability on natural language processing, including problems about causality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-causality-manipulation-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Speech Representations Still Struggle with African American Vernacular English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-speech-representations-still</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underperformance of ASR systems for speakers of African American Vernacular English (AAVE) and other marginalized language varieties is a well-documented phenomenon, and one that reinforces the stigmatization of these varieties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-speech-representations-still</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelEx: Self-Expertise in Fine-Grained Generalized Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selex-self-expertise-in-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address Generalized Category Discovery, aiming to simultaneously uncover novel categories and accurately classify known ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selex-self-expertise-in-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURE4Rec: A Benchmark for Recommendation Unlearning with Deeper Influence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cure4rec-a-benchmark-for-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we consider the deeper influence of unlearning on recommendation fairness and robustness towards data with varying impact levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cure4rec-a-benchmark-for-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAST-LIVO2: Fast, Direct LiDAR-Inertial-Visual Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-livo2-fast-direct-lidar-inertial-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fusion of both visual and LiDAR measurements is based on a single unified voxel map where the LiDAR module constructs the geometric structure for registering new LiDAR scans and the visual module attaches image patches to the LiDAR points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-livo2-fast-direct-lidar-inertial-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score-based change point detection via tracking the best of infinitely many experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-change-point-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We suggest a novel algorithm for online change point detection based on sequential score function estimation and tracking the best expert approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-change-point-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topological filtering of a signal over a network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-filtering-of-a-signal-over-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work bridges topological data analysis and signal processing, presenting a new application of persistent homology as a topological data processing tool.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-filtering-of-a-signal-over-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynaSurfGS: Dynamic Surface Reconstruction with Planar-based Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynasurfgs-dynamic-surface-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that DynaSurfGS surpasses state-of-the-art methods in both high-fidelity surface reconstruction and photorealistic rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynasurfgs-dynamic-surface-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical Proportion Label Perturbation for Learning from Label Proportions in Large Bags</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-proportion-label-perturbation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our method, smaller bags (mini-bags) are generated by sampling instances from large-sized bags (original bags), and these mini-bags are used in place of the original bags.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-proportion-label-perturbation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affine steerers for structured keypoint description</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affine-steerers-for-structured-keypoint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a way to train deep learning based keypoint descriptors that makes them approximately equivariant for locally affine transformations of the image plane.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affine-steerers-for-structured-keypoint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Computational Complexity for Continuous Wavelet Transform in Acoustic Recognition Using Hop Size</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the continuous wavelet transform (CWT) has been employed as a spectral feature extractor for acoustic recognition tasks in conjunction with machine learning and deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social perception of faces in a vision-language model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-perception-of-faces-in-a-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we compare the similarity in CLIP embeddings between different textual prompts and a set of face images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-perception-of-faces-in-a-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Center-Direction Regression for Object Counting and Localization with Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-center-direction-regression-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, learning based on point annotations poses challenges due to the high imbalance between the sets of annotated and unannotated pixels, which is often treated with Gaussian smoothing of point annotations and focal loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-center-direction-regression-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Brief Analysis of the Iterative Next Boundary Detection Network for Tree Rings Delineation in Images of Pinus taeda</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-brief-analysis-of-the-iterative-next</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents the INBD network proposed by Gillert et al. in CVPR-2023 and studies its application for delineating tree rings in RGB images of Pinus taeda cross sections captured by a smartphone (UruDendro dataset), which are images with different characteristics from the ones used to train the method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-brief-analysis-of-the-iterative-next</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Conjugate Label Information for Multi-Instance Partial-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-conjugate-label-information-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we extract the label information embedded in both candidate and non-candidate label sets, incorporating the intrinsic properties of the label space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-conjugate-label-information-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nemesis: Normalizing the Soft-prompt Vectors of Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemesis-normalizing-the-soft-prompt-vectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the prevalence of large-scale pretrained vision-language models (VLMs), such as CLIP, soft-prompt tuning has become a popular method for adapting these models to various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemesis-normalizing-the-soft-prompt-vectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Knowledge Transfer in Learning Using Privileged Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-transfer-in-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research on learning using privileged information (LUPI) aims to transfer the knowledge captured in PI onto a model that can perform inference without PI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-transfer-in-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fact Probability Vector Based Goal Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-probability-vector-based-goal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new approach to goal recognition that involves comparing observed facts with their expected probabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-probability-vector-based-goal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSM-YOLO: A Compact and Effective ROI Detector for Medical Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lsm-yolo-a-compact-and-effective-roi-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, by using LAE to refine feature extraction, the model can obtain more contextual information and high-resolution details from multiscale feature maps, thereby extracting detailed features of ROI in medical images while reducing the influence of noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lsm-yolo-a-compact-and-effective-roi-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of Neural Ordinary Differential Equations for ITER Burning Plasma Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-neural-ordinary-differential-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying this model to ITER's inductive and non-inductive operational scenarios, our results demonstrate that radiation and transport processes effectively remove excess heat from the core plasma, preventing thermal runaway instability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-neural-ordinary-differential-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question answering system of bridge design specification based on large language model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-answering-system-of-bridge-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that full fine-tuning of the Bert pretrained model achieves 100% accuracy in the training-dataset, validation-dataset and test-dataset, and the system can extract the answers from the bridge design specification given by the user to answer various questions of the user; While parameter-efficient fine-tuning of the Bert pretrained model and self-built language model from scratch perform well in the training-dataset, their generalization ability in the test-dataset needs to be improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-answering-system-of-bridge-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Models for Music: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-for-music-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, foundation models (FMs) such as large language models (LLMs) and latent diffusion models (LDMs) have profoundly impacted diverse sectors, including music.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-models-for-music-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Tree-Structured Composition of Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-tree-structured-composition-of-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing augmentation methods such as RandAugment randomly sample from a list of pre-selected transformations, while methods such as AutoAugment apply advanced search to optimize over an augmentation set of size $k^d$, which is the number of transformation sequences of length $d$, given a list of $k$ transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-tree-structured-composition-of-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-CCAM: Enhancing Video-Language Understanding with Causal Cross-Attention Masks for Short and Long Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-ccam-enhancing-video-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we apply cross-attention layers in the intermediate projector between the visual encoder and the large language model (LLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-ccam-enhancing-video-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>May the Forgetting Be with You: Alternate Replay for Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/may-the-forgetting-be-with-you-alternate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forgetting presents a significant challenge during incremental training, making it particularly demanding for contemporary AI systems to assimilate new knowledge in streaming data environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/may-the-forgetting-be-with-you-alternate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLR-Copilot: Autonomous Machine Learning Research based on Large Language Models Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlr-copilot-autonomous-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning research, crucial for technological advancements and innovation, often faces significant challenges due to its inherent complexity, slow pace of experimentation, and the necessity for specialized expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlr-copilot-autonomous-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I2EBench: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Instruction-based Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i2ebench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We will open-source I2EBench, including all instructions, input images, human annotations, edited images from all evaluated methods, and a simple script for evaluating the results from new IIE models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i2ebench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWE-bench-java: A GitHub Issue Resolving Benchmark for Java</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-bench-java-a-github-issue-resolving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GitHub issue resolving is a critical task in software engineering, recently gaining significant attention in both industry and academia.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-bench-java-a-github-issue-resolving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Knowledge Gaps in Radiology Report Generation Models through Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-knowledge-gaps-in-radiology-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in artificial intelligence have significantly improved the automatic generation of radiology reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-knowledge-gaps-in-radiology-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Machine Learning in Insurance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-machine-learning-in-insurance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Machine Learning (AutoML) aims to automatically complete the full life-cycle of ML tasks and provides state-of-the-art ML models without human intervention or supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-machine-learning-in-insurance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Path Adversarial Lifting for Domain Shift Correction in Online Test-time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-path-adversarial-lifting-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce an extra token, referred to as \textit{domain shift token}, at each layer of the transformer network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-path-adversarial-lifting-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHEVA: A Privacy-preserving Human-centric Video Anomaly Detection Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pheva-a-privacy-preserving-human-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study benchmarks state-of-the-art methods on PHEVA using a comprehensive set of metrics, including the 10% Error Rate (10ER), a metric used for anomaly detection for the first time providing insights relevant to real-world deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pheva-a-privacy-preserving-human-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-Mix: Optimizing Data Mixtures for Large Scale Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-mix-optimizing-data-mixtures-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasingly large imitation learning datasets are being collected with the goal of training foundation models for robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-mix-optimizing-data-mixtures-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center Direction Network for Grasping Point Localization on Cloths</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-direction-network-for-grasping-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work bridges a crucial gap, offering a robust solution and benchmark for cloth grasping in computer vision and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-direction-network-for-grasping-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentMove: Predicting Human Mobility Anywhere Using Large Language Model based Agentic Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentmove-predicting-human-mobility-anywhere</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In AgentMove, we first decompose the mobility prediction task into three sub-tasks and then design corresponding modules to complete these subtasks, including spatial-temporal memory for individual mobility pattern mining, world knowledge generator for modeling the effects of urban structure and collective knowledge extractor for capturing the shared patterns among population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentmove-predicting-human-mobility-anywhere</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localization of Synthetic Manipulations in Western Blot Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localization-of-synthetic-manipulations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This problem is not only confined to multimedia data, but also extends to biological images included in scientific publications, like images depicting Western blots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localization-of-synthetic-manipulations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenNav: Efficient Open Vocabulary 3D Object Detection for Smart Wheelchair Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opennav-efficient-open-vocabulary-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenNav improves state-of-the-art significantly on the Replica dataset at mAP25 (+9pts) and mAP50 (+5pts) with marginal improvement at mAP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opennav-efficient-open-vocabulary-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LowCLIP: Adapting the CLIP Model Architecture for Low-Resource Languages in Multimodal Image Retrieval Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowclip-adapting-the-clip-model-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address challenges in vision-language retrieval for low-resource languages, we integrated the CLIP model architecture and employed several techniques to balance computational efficiency with performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowclip-adapting-the-clip-model-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Completeness: A Generalizable Action Proposal Generator for Zero-Shot Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-completeness-a-generalizable-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, in this work, we propose a novel model named Generalizable Action Proposal generator (GAP), which can interface seamlessly with CLIP and generate action proposals in a holistic way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-completeness-a-generalizable-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSVM-UNet: Multi-Scale Vision Mamba UNet for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msvm-unet-multi-scale-vision-mamba-unet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State Space Models (SSMs), especially Mamba, have shown great promise in medical image segmentation due to their ability to model long-range dependencies with linear computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msvm-unet-multi-scale-vision-mamba-unet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConVis: Contrastive Decoding with Hallucination Visualization for Mitigating Hallucinations in Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convis-contrastive-decoding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hallucinations in Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) where generated responses fail to accurately reflect the given image pose a significant challenge to their reliability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convis-contrastive-decoding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOCE: Finding the Sweet Spot for Execution-Based Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doce-finding-the-sweet-spot-for-execution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, a diverse set of decoding and reranking procedures have been shown effective for LLM-based code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doce-finding-the-sweet-spot-for-execution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CV-MOS: A Cross-View Model for Motion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-mos-a-cross-view-model-for-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When performing the motion object segmentation (MOS) task, effectively leveraging motion information from objects becomes a primary challenge in improving the recognition of moving objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cv-mos-a-cross-view-model-for-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MobileQuant: Mobile-friendly Quantization for On-device Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilequant-mobile-friendly-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first investigate the limitations of existing quantization methods for on-device deployment, with a special focus on activation quantization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilequant-mobile-friendly-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of the Machine Translation Meta-Evaluation: Sentinel Metrics Fall In!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardians-of-the-machine-translation-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Annually, at the Conference of Machine Translation (WMT), the Metrics Shared Task organizers conduct the meta-evaluation of Machine Translation (MT) metrics, ranking them according to their correlation with human judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardians-of-the-machine-translation-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FMI-TAL: Few-shot Multiple Instances Temporal Action Localization by Probability Distribution Learning and Interval Cluster Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fmi-tal-few-shot-multiple-instances-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The present few-shot temporal action localization model can't handle the situation where videos contain multiple action instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fmi-tal-few-shot-multiple-instances-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaneTCA: Enhancing Video Lane Detection with Temporal Context Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanetca-enhancing-video-lane-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose LaneTCA to bridge the individual video frames and explore how to effectively aggregate the temporal context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanetca-enhancing-video-lane-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Analysis for Education: Methods, Applications, and Future Directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-analysis-for-education-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The contributions of this paper include a detailed taxonomy of educational data, a synthesis of time series techniques with specific educational applications, and a forward-looking perspective on emerging trends and future research opportunities in educational analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-analysis-for-education-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Adaptive Deep Networks for Image Classification via Uncertainty-aware Decision Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-adaptive-deep-networks-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this observation, we introduce the Collaborative Decision Making (CDM) module, which fuses the multiple classifier heads to enhance the inference performance of adaptive deep networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-adaptive-deep-networks-for-image</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
