<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 09:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Reward Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-reward-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-markovian Reinforcement Learning (RL) tasks are very hard to solve, because agents must consider the entire history of state-action pairs to act rationally in the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-reward-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Unsupervised Learning Framework Combined with Heuristics for the Maximum Minimal Cut Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-unsupervised-learning-framework-combined</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unsupervised solver is inspired by a relaxation-plus-rounding approach, the relaxed solution is parameterized by graph neural networks, and the cost and penalty of MMCP are explicitly written out, which can train the model end-to-end.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-unsupervised-learning-framework-combined</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-RAF: A Simulation-Based Robustness Assessment Framework for Responsible Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-raf-a-simulation-based-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, varying perceptions of robustness among AI developers create misaligned evaluation metrics, complicating the assessment and certification of safety-critical and complex AI systems such as autonomous driving (AD) agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-raf-a-simulation-based-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>String Diagram of Optimal Transports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string-diagram-of-optimal-transports</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a hierarchical framework of optimal transports (OTs), namely string diagrams of OTs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string-diagram-of-optimal-transports</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyRec: Simple yet Effective Language Models for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-simple-yet-effective-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks have become a powerful technique for learning representations from user-item interaction data in collaborative filtering (CF) for recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-simple-yet-effective-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentSimulator: An Agent-based Approach for Data-driven Business Process Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentsimulator-an-agent-based-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Business process simulation (BPS) is a versatile technique for estimating process performance across various scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentsimulator-an-agent-based-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepDFA: Automata Learning through Neural Probabilistic Relaxations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepdfa-automata-learning-through-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce DeepDFA, a novel approach to identifying Deterministic Finite Automata (DFAs) from traces, harnessing a differentiable yet discrete model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepdfa-automata-learning-through-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadioDiff: An Effective Generative Diffusion Model for Sampling-Free Dynamic Radio Map Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiodiff-an-effective-generative-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, to enhance RM construction performance, in this paper, the sampling-free RM construction is modeled as a conditional generative problem, where a denoised diffusion-based method, named RadioDiff, is proposed to achieve high-quality RM construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiodiff-an-effective-generative-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HistoGym: A Reinforcement Learning Environment for Histopathological Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histogym-a-reinforcement-learning-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In pathological research, education, and clinical practice, the decision-making process based on pathological images is critically important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histogym-a-reinforcement-learning-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAMER: Tree-Aware Transformer for Handwritten Mathematical Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tamer-tree-aware-transformer-for-handwritten</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TAMER combines the advantages of both sequence decoding and tree decoding models by jointly optimizing sequence prediction and tree structure prediction tasks, which enhances the model's understanding and generalization of complex mathematical expression structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tamer-tree-aware-transformer-for-handwritten</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy Coding of Unordered Data Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-coding-of-unordered-data-structures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present shuffle coding, a general method for optimal compression of sequences of unordered objects using bits-back coding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-coding-of-unordered-data-structures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-Friendly Concept Protection via Selective Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-friendly-concept-protection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Qualitative and quantitative experiments validate that VCPro achieves a better trade-off between the visibility of perturbations and protection effectiveness, effectively prioritizing the protection of target concepts in images with less perceptible perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-friendly-concept-protection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextCAVs: Debugging vision models using text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textcavs-debugging-vision-models-using-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept-based interpretability methods are a popular form of explanation for deep learning models which provide explanations in the form of high-level human interpretable concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textcavs-debugging-vision-models-using-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Benchmarks of Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-benchmarks-of-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) are gaining increasing popularity in both academia and industry due to their remarkable performance in various applications such as visual question answering, visual perception, understanding, and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-benchmarks-of-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Dataset Distillation Based on Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-dataset-distillation-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we proposed a novel generative dataset distillation method based on Stable Diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-dataset-distillation-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroSSIM: Improved Structural Similarity for Comparing Microscopy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microssim-improved-structural-similarity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For such tasks, the best evaluation would be when both low-SNR noisy images and corresponding high-SNR clean images are obtained directly from a microscope.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microssim-improved-structural-similarity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Image-to-Image Diffusion Classifier for Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-image-to-image-diffusion-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this issue, we redesign the diffusion framework from generating high-quality images to predicting distinguishable image labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-image-to-image-diffusion-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning A Low-Level Vision Generalist via Visual Task Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-low-level-vision-generalist-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, these methods are sensitive to prompt image content and often struggle with low-frequency information processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-low-level-vision-generalist-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning LLMs for Autonomous Spacecraft Control: A Case Study Using Kerbal Space Program</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-llms-for-autonomous-spacecraft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the use of fine-tuned Large Language Models (LLMs) for autonomous spacecraft control, using the Kerbal Space Program Differential Games suite (KSPDG) as a testing environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-llms-for-autonomous-spacecraft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference-free Axial Super-resolution of 3D Microscopy Images using Implicit Neural Representation with a 2D Diffusion Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-free-axial-super-resolution-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a reconstruction framework based on implicit neural representation (INR), which allows 3D coherency even when optimized by independent axial slices in a batch-wise manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-free-axial-super-resolution-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupling Feature Representations of Ego and Other Modalities for Incomplete Multi-modal Brain Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-feature-representations-of-ego-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal brain tumor segmentation typically involves four magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) modalities, while incomplete modalities significantly degrade performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-feature-representations-of-ego-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Learning Approach for Intracranial Hemorrhage Prognosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-approach-for-intracranial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prognosis after intracranial hemorrhage (ICH) is influenced by a complex interplay between imaging and tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-approach-for-intracranial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GS-ID: Illumination Decomposition on Gaussian Splatting via Diffusion Prior and Parametric Light Source Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gs-id-illumination-decomposition-on-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GS-ID, a novel framework for illumination decomposition on Gaussian Splatting, achieving photorealistic novel view synthesis and intuitive light editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gs-id-illumination-decomposition-on-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Med-PMC: Medical Personalized Multi-modal Consultation with a Proactive Ask-First-Observe-Next Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-pmc-medical-personalized-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of the Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) in medical clinical scenarios remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-pmc-medical-personalized-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SYMPOL: Symbolic Tree-Based On-Policy Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sympol-symbolic-tree-based-on-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SYMPOL, a novel method for SYMbolic tree-based on-POLicy RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sympol-symbolic-tree-based-on-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Giant Impact Simulations with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-giant-impact-simulations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By combining with a model for predicting long-term stability, we create an efficient ML-based giant impact emulator, which can predict the outcomes of giant impact simulations with a speedup of up to four orders of magnitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-giant-impact-simulations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Driven Interactive Shadow Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-interactive-shadow-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this dataset, we propose a Referring Shadow-Track Memory Network (RSM-Net) for addressing the RVSD task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-driven-interactive-shadow-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM2-UNet: Segment Anything 2 Makes Strong Encoder for Natural and Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2-unet-segment-anything-2-makes-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image segmentation plays an important role in vision understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2-unet-segment-anything-2-makes-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus on Focus: Focus-oriented Representation Learning and Multi-view Cross-modal Alignment for Glioma Grading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-on-focus-focus-oriented-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, our FoF achieves superior performance using only histopathology slides compared to existing multimodal methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-on-focus-focus-oriented-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VF-NeRF: Learning Neural Vector Fields for Indoor Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vf-nerf-learning-neural-vector-fields-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we develop a novel density-VF relationship and a training scheme that allows us to learn VF via volume rendering By doing this, VF-NeRF can model large planar surfaces and sharp corners accurately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vf-nerf-learning-neural-vector-fields-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuseChat: Knowledge Fusion of Chat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusechat-knowledge-fusion-of-chat-models-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new framework for the knowledge fusion of chat LLMs through two main stages, resulting in FuseChat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusechat-knowledge-fusion-of-chat-models-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning Large Language Models with Human-inspired Learning Strategies in Medical Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-with-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training Large Language Models (LLMs) incurs substantial data-related costs, motivating the development of data-efficient training methods through optimised data ordering and selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-large-language-models-with-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Medical Anomaly Detection in Brain MRI: An Image Quality Assessment Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-medical-anomaly-detection-in-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstruction-based methods, particularly those leveraging autoencoders, have been widely adopted to perform anomaly detection in brain MRI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-medical-anomaly-detection-in-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MobileMEF: Fast and Efficient Method for Multi-Exposure Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilemef-fast-and-efficient-method-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in camera design and imaging technology have enabled the capture of high-quality images using smartphones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilemef-fast-and-efficient-method-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IIU: Independent Inference Units for Knowledge-based Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iiu-independent-inference-units-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Independent Inference Units (IIU) for fine-grained multi-modal reasoning to decompose intra-modal information by the functionally independent units.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iiu-independent-inference-units-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InVAErt networks for amortized inference and identifiability analysis of lumped parameter hemodynamic models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invaert-networks-for-amortized-inference-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimation of cardiovascular model parameters from electronic health records (EHR) poses a significant challenge primarily due to lack of identifiability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invaert-networks-for-amortized-inference-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normalized AOPC: Fixing Misleading Faithfulness Metrics for Feature Attribution Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalized-aopc-fixing-misleading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural network predictions are notoriously difficult to interpret.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalized-aopc-fixing-misleading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Part Discovery via Dual Representation Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-part-discovery-via-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object parts serve as crucial intermediate representations in various downstream tasks, but part-level representation learning still has not received as much attention as other vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-part-discovery-via-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximally Permissive Reward Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximally-permissive-reward-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that learning using such "maximally permissive" reward machines results in higher rewards than learning using RMs based on a single plan.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximally-permissive-reward-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptation of uncertainty-penalized Bayesian information criterion for parametric partial differential equation discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-uncertainty-penalized-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-driven discovery of partial differential equations (PDEs) has emerged as a promising approach for deriving governing physics when domain knowledge about observed data is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-uncertainty-penalized-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAIR: Hypernetworks-based All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hair-hypernetworks-based-all-in-one-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be more specific, the Classifier is a simple image classification network which is used to generate a Global Information Vector (GIV) that contains the degradation information of the input image; And the HSNs can be seen as a simple Fully-connected Neural Network that receive the GIV and output parameters for the corresponding modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hair-hypernetworks-based-all-in-one-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAG-SQL: Multi-Agent Generative Approach with Soft Schema Linking and Iterative Sub-SQL Refinement for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mag-sql-multi-agent-generative-approach-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose MAG-SQL, a multi-agent generative approach with soft schema linking and iterative Sub-SQL refinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mag-sql-multi-agent-generative-approach-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snuffy: Efficient Whole Slide Image Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snuffy-efficient-whole-slide-image-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our sparsity pattern is tailored for pathology and is theoretically proven to be a universal approximator with the tightest probabilistic sharp bound on the number of layers for sparse transformers, to date.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snuffy-efficient-whole-slide-image-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-Prover-V1.5: Harnessing Proof Assistant Feedback for Reinforcement Learning and Monte-Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-prover-v1-5-harnessing-proof</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce DeepSeek-Prover-V1. 5, an open-source language model designed for theorem proving in Lean 4, which enhances DeepSeek-Prover-V1 by optimizing both training and inference processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-prover-v1-5-harnessing-proof</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashGS: Efficient 3D Gaussian Splatting for Large-scale and High-resolution Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashgs-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces FlashGS, an open-source CUDA Python library, designed to facilitate the efficient differentiable rasterization of 3D Gaussian Splatting through algorithmic and kernel-level optimizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashgs-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Fairness Analytics: Quantifying Fairness in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-fairness-analytics-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) is a privacy-enhancing technology for distributed ML.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-fairness-analytics-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision Model Compression Techniques for Embedded Systems: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-vision-model-compression-techniques</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks have consistently represented the state of the art in most computer vision problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-vision-model-compression-techniques</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Category-Prompt Refined Feature Learning for Long-Tailed Multi-Label Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-prompt-refined-feature-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world data consistently exhibits a long-tailed distribution, often spanning multiple categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-prompt-refined-feature-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penny-Wise and Pound-Foolish in Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penny-wise-and-pound-foolish-in-deepfake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper critiques the overly specialized approach of fine-tuning pre-trained models solely with a penny-wise objective on a single deepfake dataset, while disregarding the pound-wise balance for generalization and knowledge retention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penny-wise-and-pound-foolish-in-deepfake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Path Tracing and Statistical Event Detection for Event Camera Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-path-tracing-and-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel event camera simulation system fully based on physically based Monte Carlo path tracing with adaptive path sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-path-tracing-and-statistical</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
