<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 09:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>One Model for All Domains: Collaborative Domain-Prefix Tuning for Cross-Domain NER</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-model-for-all-domains-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous typical solutions mainly obtain a NER model by pre-trained language models (PLMs) with data from a rich-resource domain and adapt it to the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-model-for-all-domains-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HealthEdge: A Machine Learning-Based Smart Healthcare Framework for Prediction of Type 2 Diabetes in an Integrated IoT, Edge, and Cloud Computing System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthedge-a-machine-learning-based-smart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diabetes Mellitus has no permanent cure to date and is one of the leading causes of death globally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthedge-a-machine-learning-based-smart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing Language Model-based Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-language-model-based-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build four new datasets: E-FB15k237, A-FB15k237, E-WN18RR, and A-WN18RR, and evaluate several knowledge editing baselines demonstrating the limited ability of previous models to handle the proposed challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-language-model-based-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Approximate Method for Online Convolutional Dictionary Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-approximate-method-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing convolutional dictionary learning (CDL) algorithms are based on batch learning, where the dictionary filters and the convolutional sparse representations are optimized in an alternating manner using a training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-approximate-method-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Tenant Optimization For Few-Shot Task-Oriented FAQ Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-tenant-optimization-for-few-shot-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Business-specific Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) retrieval in task-oriented dialog systems poses unique challenges vis-\`a-vis community based FAQs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-tenant-optimization-for-few-shot-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Control of Partial Differential Equations Using Convolutional Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-control-of-partial-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a convolutional framework which significantly reduces the complexity and thus, the computational effort for distributed reinforcement learning control of dynamical systems governed by partial differential equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-control-of-partial-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLPGradientFlow: going with the flow of multilayer perceptrons (and finding minima fast and accurately)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlpgradientflow-going-with-the-flow-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLPGradientFlow is a software package to solve numerically the gradient flow differential equation $\dot \theta = -\nabla \mathcal L(\theta; \mathcal D)$, where $\theta$ are the parameters of a multi-layer perceptron, $\mathcal D$ is some data set, and $\nabla \mathcal L$ is the gradient of a loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlpgradientflow-going-with-the-flow-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Consistent Deep Rigid MRI Motion Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-consistent-deep-rigid-mri-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion artifacts are a pervasive problem in MRI, leading to misdiagnosis or mischaracterization in population-level imaging studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-consistent-deep-rigid-mri-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViDeBERTa: A powerful pre-trained language model for Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videberta-a-powerful-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ViDeBERTa, a new pre-trained monolingual language model for Vietnamese, with three versions - ViDeBERTa_xsmall, ViDeBERTa_base, and ViDeBERTa_large, which are pre-trained on a large-scale corpus of high-quality and diverse Vietnamese texts using DeBERTa architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videberta-a-powerful-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact and rapid linear clustering of networks with dynamic programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-and-rapid-linear-clustering-of-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of clustering networks whose nodes have imputed or physical positions in a single dimension, such as prestige hierarchies or the similarity dimension of hyperbolic embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-and-rapid-linear-clustering-of-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated multilingual detection of Pro-Kremlin propaganda in newspapers and Telegram posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-multilingual-detection-of-pro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The full-scale conflict between the Russian Federation and Ukraine generated an unprecedented amount of news articles and social media data reflecting opposing ideologies and narratives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-multilingual-detection-of-pro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEJA VU: Continual Model Generalization For Unseen Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-continual-model-generalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations of DA and DG in handling the Unfamiliar Period during continual domain shift, we propose RaTP, a framework that focuses on improving models' target domain generalization (TDG) capability, while also achieving effective target domain adaptation (TDA) capability right after training on certain domains and forgetting alleviation (FA) capability on past domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-continual-model-generalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Selection: Key to Enhance Node Classification with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-key-to-enhance-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs help to define the relationships between entities in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-key-to-enhance-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a Waffle Iron for Automotive Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-waffle-iron-for-automotive-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation of point clouds in autonomous driving datasets requires techniques that can process large numbers of points over large field of views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-waffle-iron-for-automotive-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model soups to increase inference without increasing compute time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-soups-to-increase-inference-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we compare Model Soups performances on three different models (ResNet, ViT and EfficientNet) using three Soup Recipes (Greedy Soup Sorted, Greedy Soup Random and Uniform soup) from arXiv:2203. 05482, and reproduce the results of the authors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-soups-to-increase-inference-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audience-Centric Natural Language Generation via Style Infusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audience-centric-natural-language-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing approaches demonstrate textual style transfer with large volumes of parallel or non-parallel data, we argue that grounding style on audience-independent external factors is innately limiting for two reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audience-centric-natural-language-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GePA*SE: Generalized Edge-Based Parallel A* for Slow Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gepa-se-generalized-edge-based-parallel-a-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in a number of robotics domains, the action space is heterogenous in the computational effort required to evaluate the cost of an action and its outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gepa-se-generalized-edge-based-parallel-a-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LDMIC: Learning-based Distributed Multi-view Image Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ldmic-learning-based-distributed-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-view image compression plays a critical role in 3D-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ldmic-learning-based-distributed-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Reinforcement Learning for Dexterous Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-reinforcement-learning-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A potential way to address these limitations is to add constraints during learning that restrict and guide the robot's behavior during training as well as roll outs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-reinforcement-learning-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Interactive Lung Lesion Segmentation: A Framework for Annotating PET/CT Images based on Physiological and Anatomical Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interactive-lung-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep learning enabled the accurate segmentation of various diseases in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interactive-lung-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Super-Resolution using Efficient Striped Window Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-using-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further exploit the potential of the transformer, we propose a novel flexible window training strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-using-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting the 2016-2017 Central Apennines Earthquake Sequence with a Neural Point Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-the-2016-2017-central-apennines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate whether these flexible point process models can be applied to short-term seismicity forecasting by extending an existing temporal neural model to the magnitude domain and we show how this model can forecast earthquakes above a target magnitude threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-the-2016-2017-central-apennines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViHOS: Hate Speech Spans Detection for Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vihos-hate-speech-spans-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise in hateful and offensive language directed at other users is one of the adverse side effects of the increased use of social networking platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vihos-hate-speech-spans-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RD-NAS: Enhancing One-shot Supernet Ranking Ability via Ranking Distillation from Zero-cost Proxies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rd-nas-enhancing-one-shot-supernet-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Ranking Distillation one-shot NAS (RD-NAS) to enhance ranking consistency, which utilizes zero-cost proxies as the cheap teacher and adopts the margin ranking loss to distill the ranking knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rd-nas-enhancing-one-shot-supernet-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same or Different? Diff-Vectors for Authorship Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/same-or-different-diff-vectors-for-authorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the effects on authorship identification tasks of a fundamental shift in how to conceive the vectorial representations of documents that are given as input to a supervised learner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/same-or-different-diff-vectors-for-authorship</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation Alone Can Improve Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-alone-can-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation, which is effective at preventing overfitting in standard training, has been observed by many previous works to be ineffective in mitigating overfitting in adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-alone-can-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Semantic Scholar Open Data Platform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-semantic-scholar-open-data-platform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The volume of scientific output is creating an urgent need for automated tools to help scientists keep up with developments in their field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-semantic-scholar-open-data-platform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Neural Architecture Search for Temporal Convolutional Networks at the Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-neural-architecture-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Architecture Search (NAS) is quickly becoming the go-to approach to optimize the structure of Deep Learning (DL) models for complex tasks such as Image Classification or Object Detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-neural-architecture-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Learning Enables Population-Scale Analysis of Leaf Traits in Populus trichocarpa</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-learning-enables-population-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, the current work is designed to provide the plant phenotyping community with (i) methods for fast and accurate image-based feature extraction that require minimal training data, and (ii) a new population-scale data set, including 68 different leaf phenotypes, for domain scientists and machine learning researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-learning-enables-population-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-based method for segmenting epithelial layer of tubules in histopathological images of testicular tissue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-method-for-segmenting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pretrained ResNet-34 in the encoder and attention block suggested in the decoder result in better segmentation and generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-method-for-segmenting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Adaptive Unfolding Network for Hyperspectral Image Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-adaptive-unfolding-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a simple, efficient, and scalable unfolding network, SAUNet, to simplify the network design with an adaptive alternate optimization framework for hyperspectral image (HSI) reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-adaptive-unfolding-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opportunities and Challenges in Neural Dialog Tutoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opportunities-and-challenges-in-neural-dialog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing dialog tutors has been challenging as it involves modeling the diverse and complex pedagogical strategies employed by human tutors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opportunities-and-challenges-in-neural-dialog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesostructures: Beyond Spectrogram Loss in Differentiable Time-Frequency Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesostructures-beyond-spectrogram-loss-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer musicians refer to mesostructures as the intermediate levels of articulation between the microstructure of waveshapes and the macrostructure of musical forms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesostructures-beyond-spectrogram-loss-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planar Object Tracking via Weighted Optical Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planar-object-tracking-via-weighted-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose WOFT -- a novel method for planar object tracking that estimates a full 8 degrees-of-freedom pose, i. e. the homography w. r. t.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planar-object-tracking-via-weighted-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K-Planes: Explicit Radiance Fields in Space, Time, and Appearance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-planes-explicit-radiance-fields-in-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce k-planes, a white-box model for radiance fields in arbitrary dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-planes-explicit-radiance-fields-in-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEASEL 2.0 -- A Random Dilated Dictionary Transform for Fast, Accurate and Memory Constrained Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weasel-2-0-a-random-dilated-dictionary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series classification (TSC) is the task of assigning a time series to one of a set of predefined classes, usually based on a model learned from examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weasel-2-0-a-random-dilated-dictionary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Patcher: One Mistake worth One Neuron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-patcher-one-mistake-worth-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms previous fine-tuning and HyperNetwork-based methods and achieves state-of-the-art performance for Sequential Model Editing (SME).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-patcher-one-mistake-worth-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Distillation for Semi-Supervised Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-distillation-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a model well-trained with a large-scale base dataset, Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning (FSCIL) aims at incrementally learning novel classes from a few labeled samples by avoiding overfitting, without catastrophically forgetting all encountered classes previously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-distillation-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Agnostic Sample Reweighting for Out-of-Distribution Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-sample-reweighting-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The overfitting issue is addressed by considering a bilevel formulation to search for the sample reweighting, in which the generalization complexity depends on the search space of sample weights instead of the model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-sample-reweighting-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexi: Self-Supervised Learning of the UI Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexi-self-supervised-learning-of-the-ui</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along with text, these resources include visual content such as UI screenshots and images of application icons referenced in the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexi-self-supervised-learning-of-the-ui</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoder-based Joint Communication and Sensing of Multiple Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-joint-communication-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foremost, we develop a suitable encoding scheme for the training of the AE and for targeting a fixed false alarm rate of the target detection during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-joint-communication-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleGAN-T: Unlocking the Power of GANs for Fast Large-Scale Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylegan-t-unlocking-the-power-of-gans-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image synthesis has recently seen significant progress thanks to large pretrained language models, large-scale training data, and the introduction of scalable model families such as diffusion and autoregressive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylegan-t-unlocking-the-power-of-gans-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensemaking About Contraceptive Methods Across Online Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensemaking-about-contraceptive-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selecting a birth control method is a complex healthcare decision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensemaking-about-contraceptive-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Active 3D Object Detection from a Generalization Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-active-3d-object-detection-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the high annotation cost in LiDAR-based 3D object detection, active learning is a promising solution that learns to select only a small portion of unlabeled data to annotate, without compromising model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-active-3d-object-detection-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StockEmotions: Discover Investor Emotions for Financial Sentiment Analysis and Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stockemotions-discover-investor-emotions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been growing interest in applying NLP techniques in the financial domain, however, resources are extremely limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stockemotions-discover-investor-emotions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction-Powered Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-powered-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce prediction-powered inference $\unicode{x2013}$ a framework for performing valid statistical inference when an experimental data set is supplemented with predictions from a machine-learning system such as AlphaFold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-powered-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ddml: Double/debiased machine learning in Stata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddml-double-debiased-machine-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the package ddml for Double/Debiased Machine Learning (DDML) in Stata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddml-double-debiased-machine-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Processes analogous to ecological interactions and dispersal shape the dynamics of economic activities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/processes-analogous-to-ecological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find strong support for the models capturing positive interactions between economic activities and spatial dispersal of the activities across countries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/processes-analogous-to-ecological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimising Event-Driven Spiking Neural Network with Regularisation and Cutoff</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-event-driven-spiking-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two novel optimisation techniques are presented to achieve AOI-SNNs: a regularisation and a cutoff.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-event-driven-spiking-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Expressive Power of Geometric Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-geometric-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The expressive power of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) has been studied extensively through the Weisfeiler-Leman (WL) graph isomorphism test.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-geometric-graph</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
