<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 09:14:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>THOUGHTSCULPT: Reasoning with Intermediate Revision and Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thoughtsculpt-reasoning-with-intermediate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present THOUGHTSCULPT, a general reasoning and search method for tasks with outputs that can be decomposed into components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thoughtsculpt-reasoning-with-intermediate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Domain Generation Algorithm Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-domain-generation-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we conduct a comprehensive study on the robustness of domain generation algorithm (DGA) classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-domain-generation-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Barlow Twins to Triplet Training: Differentiating Dementia with Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-barlow-twins-to-triplet-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose Triplet Training for differential diagnosis with limited target data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-barlow-twins-to-triplet-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPNet: Dynamic Trajectory Forecasting with Historical Prediction Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpnet-dynamic-trajectory-forecasting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed Historical Prediction Attention together with the Agent Attention and Mode Attention is further formulated as the Triple Factorized Attention module, serving as the core design of HPNet. Experiments on the Argoverse and INTERACTION datasets show that HPNet achieves state-of-the-art performance, and generates accurate and stable future trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpnet-dynamic-trajectory-forecasting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Robust Point Cloud Registration via Heuristics-guided Parameter Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-point-cloud-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our strategy largely reduces the search space and can guarantee accuracy with only a few inlier samples, therefore enjoying an excellent trade-off between efficiency and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-robust-point-cloud-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LRR: Language-Driven Resamplable Continuous Representation against Adversarial Tracking Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrr-language-driven-resamplable-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve high accuracy on both clean and adversarial data, we propose building a spatial-temporal continuous representation using the semantic text guidance of the object of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrr-language-driven-resamplable-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effect of (Near) Duplicate Subwords in Language Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effect-of-near-duplicate-subwords-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the impact of near duplicate subwords on LM training efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effect-of-near-duplicate-subwords-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColorMNet: A Memory-based Deep Spatial-Temporal Feature Propagation Network for Video Colorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colormnet-a-memory-based-deep-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explore this property for better spatial and temporal feature utilization, we develop a local attention module to aggregate the features from adjacent frames in a spatial-temporal neighborhood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colormnet-a-memory-based-deep-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural networks can be FLOP-efficient integrators of 1D oscillatory integrands</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-can-be-flop-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train a feed-forward neural network to compute integrals of highly oscillatory 1D functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-can-be-flop-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM-XComposer2-4KHD: A Pioneering Large Vision-Language Model Handling Resolutions from 336 Pixels to 4K HD</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-4khd-a-pioneering-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Large Vision-Language Model (LVLM) field has seen significant advancements, yet its progression has been hindered by challenges in comprehending fine-grained visual content due to limited resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-4khd-a-pioneering-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniCPM: Unveiling the Potential of Small Language Models with Scalable Training Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicpm-unveiling-the-potential-of-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For data scaling, we introduce a Warmup-Stable-Decay (WSD) learning rate scheduler (LRS), conducive to continuous training and domain adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicpm-unveiling-the-potential-of-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qiskit-Torch-Module: Fast Prototyping of Quantum Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qiskit-torch-module-fast-prototyping-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum computer simulation software is an integral tool for the research efforts in the quantum computing community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qiskit-torch-module-fast-prototyping-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Not) Understanding Latin Poetic Style with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-understanding-latin-poetic-style-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article summarizes some mostly unsuccessful attempts to understand authorial style by examining the attention of various neural networks (LSTMs and CNNs) trained on a corpus of classical Latin verse that has been encoded to include sonic and metrical features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-understanding-latin-poetic-style-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pfl-research: simulation framework for accelerating research in Private Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfl-research-simulation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is an emerging machine learning (ML) training paradigm where clients own their data and collaborate to train a global model, without revealing any data to the server and other participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfl-research-simulation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concise Plane Arrangements for Low-Poly Surface and Volume Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concise-plane-arrangements-for-low-poly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce two key novelties that enable the construction of plane arrangements for complex objects and entire scenes: an ordering scheme for the plane insertion and the direct use of input points during arrangement construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concise-plane-arrangements-for-low-poly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scRDiT: Generating single-cell RNA-seq data by diffusion transformers and accelerating sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrdit-generating-single-cell-rna-seq-data-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method is a neural network constructed based on Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models (DDPMs) and Diffusion Transformers (DiTs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrdit-generating-single-cell-rna-seq-data-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Embed-KD: Computationally Efficient Knowledge Distillation Using Embeddings as Teachers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-embed-kd-computationally-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP) has been shown to improve zero-shot generalization capabilities of language and vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-embed-kd-computationally-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniFusion Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnifusion-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an \textit{OmniFusion} model based on a pretrained LLM and adapters for visual modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnifusion-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter-Free Medical Image Synthesis for Sharing Data and Improving Site-Specific Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-free-medical-image-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharing synthetic medical images is a promising alternative to sharing real images that can improve patient privacy and data security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-free-medical-image-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActNetFormer: Transformer-ResNet Hybrid Method for Semi-Supervised Action Recognition in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actnetformer-transformer-resnet-hybrid-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework leverages both labeled and unlabelled data to robustly learn action representations in videos, combining pseudo-labeling with contrastive learning for effective learning from both types of samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actnetformer-transformer-resnet-hybrid-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-enhanced Retrieval in Real-time Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-enhanced-retrieval-in-real-time-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to strengthen the focus on critical event information in events, we include a decoder module after the document encoder, introduce a generative event triplet extraction scheme based on prompt-tuning, and correlate the events with query encoder optimization through comparative learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-enhanced-retrieval-in-real-time-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Visual Generalized Zero-Shot Learning using Pre-Trained Large Multi-Modal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-generalized-zero-shot-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing benchmarks predate the popularization of large multi-modal models, such as CLIP and CLAP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-generalized-zero-shot-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GO4Align: Group Optimization for Multi-Task Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go4align-group-optimization-for-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes \textit{GO4Align}, a multi-task optimization approach that tackles task imbalance by explicitly aligning the optimization across tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go4align-group-optimization-for-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeEval: A Modular Framework for Trustworthy and Efficient Evaluation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeeval-a-modular-framework-for-trustworthy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of large language model (LLM) evaluation methodologies and datasets has led to a profound challenge: integrating state-of-the-art evaluation techniques cost-effectively while ensuring reliability, reproducibility, and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeeval-a-modular-framework-for-trustworthy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nEMO: Dataset of Emotional Speech in Polish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-dataset-of-emotional-speech-in-polish</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech emotion recognition has become increasingly important in recent years due to its potential applications in healthcare, customer service, and personalization of dialogue systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemo-dataset-of-emotional-speech-in-polish</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ada-LEval: Evaluating long-context LLMs with length-adaptable benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-leval-evaluating-long-context-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the large language model (LLM) community has shown increasing interest in enhancing LLMs' capability to handle extremely long documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-leval-evaluating-long-context-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLEX: FLEXible Federated Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flex-flexible-federated-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of Artificial Intelligence (AI), the need for privacy and security in data processing has become paramount.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flex-flexible-federated-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Potential of Large Foundation Models for Open-Vocabulary HOI Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-large-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, these detectors primarily rely on category names and overlook the rich contextual information that language can provide, which is essential for capturing open vocabulary concepts that are typically rare and not well-represented by category names alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-large-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scCDCG: Efficient Deep Structural Clustering for single-cell RNA-seq via Deep Cut-informed Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sccdcg-efficient-deep-structural-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing these limitations, we introduce scCDCG (single-cell RNA-seq Clustering via Deep Cut-informed Graph), a novel framework designed for efficient and accurate clustering of scRNA-seq data that simultaneously utilizes intercellular high-order structural information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sccdcg-efficient-deep-structural-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Multi-modal Diagnostic Framework with Reconstruction Pre-training and Heterogeneity-combat Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-multi-modal-diagnostic-framework-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to enhance the representation abilities of vision and language encoders, we propose the Multi-level Reconstruction Pre-training (MR-Pretrain) strategy, including a feature-level and data-level reconstruction, which guides models to capture the semantic information from masked inputs of different modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-multi-modal-diagnostic-framework-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synaptogen: A cross-domain generative device model for large-scale neuromorphic circuit design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synaptogen-a-cross-domain-generative-device</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a fast generative modeling approach for resistive memories that reproduces the complex statistical properties of real-world devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synaptogen-a-cross-domain-generative-device</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGTNet: A Process Graph Transformer Network for Remaining Time Prediction of Business Process Instances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgtnet-a-process-graph-transformer-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PGTNet, an approach that transforms event logs into graph datasets and leverages graph-oriented data for training Process Graph Transformer Networks to predict the remaining time of business process instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgtnet-a-process-graph-transformer-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elephants Never Forget: Memorization and Learning of Tabular Data in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elephants-never-forget-memorization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then compare the few-shot learning performance of LLMs on datasets that were seen during training to the performance on datasets released after training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elephants-never-forget-memorization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentQuest: A Modular Benchmark Framework to Measure Progress and Improve LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentquest-a-modular-benchmark-framework-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advances made by Large Language Models (LLMs) have led to the pursuit of LLM agents that can solve intricate, multi-step reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentquest-a-modular-benchmark-framework-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little Strokes Fell Great Oaks: Boosting the Hierarchical Features for Multi-exposure Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/little-strokes-fell-great-oaks-boosting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, deep learning networks have made remarkable strides in the domain of multi-exposure image fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/little-strokes-fell-great-oaks-boosting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolving Collective Behavior in Self-Organizing Particle Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-collective-behavior-in-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present EvoSOPS, an evolutionary framework that searches landscapes of stochastic distributed algorithms for those that achieve a mathematically specified target behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolving-collective-behavior-in-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoryImager: A Unified and Efficient Framework for Coherent Story Visualization and Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyimager-a-unified-and-efficient-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3) The story visualization and continuation models are trained and inferred independently, which is not user-friendly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyimager-a-unified-and-efficient-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rolling Shutter Correction with Intermediate Distortion Flow Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rolling-shutter-correction-with-intermediate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, a multi-distortion flow prediction strategy is integrated to mitigate the issue of inaccurate flow estimation further.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rolling-shutter-correction-with-intermediate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Evaluation and Refinement of Digital Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-evaluation-and-refinement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that domain-general automatic evaluators can significantly improve the performance of agents for web navigation and device control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-evaluation-and-refinement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VI-OOD: A Unified Representation Learning Framework for Textual Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vi-ood-a-unified-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection plays a crucial role in ensuring the safety and reliability of deep neural networks in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vi-ood-a-unified-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A comparative analysis of deep learning models for lung segmentation on X-ray images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust and highly accurate lung segmentation in X-rays is crucial in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hash3D: Training-free Acceleration for 3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hash3d-training-free-acceleration-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evolution of 3D generative modeling has been notably propelled by the adoption of 2D diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hash3d-training-free-acceleration-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartControl: Enhancing ControlNet for Handling Rough Visual Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartcontrol-enhancing-controlnet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key idea of our SmartControl is to relax the visual condition on the areas that are conflicted with text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartcontrol-enhancing-controlnet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Dynamic and Hierarchical Relationship Modeling for Facial Action Units Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-dynamic-and-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human facial action units (AUs) are mutually related in a hierarchical manner, as not only they are associated with each other in both spatial and temporal domains but also AUs located in the same/close facial regions show stronger relationships than those of different facial regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-dynamic-and-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On adversarial training and the 1 Nearest Neighbor classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-adversarial-training-and-the-1-nearest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to fool deep learning classifiers with tiny perturbations of the input has lead to the development of adversarial training in which the loss with respect to adversarial examples is minimized in addition to the training examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-adversarial-training-and-the-1-nearest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Pancakes: Geometrically-Regularized 3D Gaussian Splatting for Realistic Endoscopic Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-pancakes-geometrically-regularized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within colorectal cancer diagnostics, conventional colonoscopy techniques face critical limitations, including a limited field of view and a lack of depth information, which can impede the detection of precancerous lesions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-pancakes-geometrically-regularized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM2Vec: Large Language Models Are Secretly Powerful Text Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm2vec-large-language-models-are-secretly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We outperform encoder-only models by a large margin on word-level tasks and reach a new unsupervised state-of-the-art performance on the Massive Text Embeddings Benchmark (MTEB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm2vec-large-language-models-are-secretly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamView: Injecting View-specific Text Guidance into Text-to-3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamview-injecting-view-specific-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-3D generation, which synthesizes 3D assets according to an overall text description, has significantly progressed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamview-injecting-view-specific-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Quantization and Mapping Synergy in Hardware-Aware Deep Neural Network Accelerators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-quantization-and-mapping-synergy-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Energy efficiency and memory footprint of a convolutional neural network (CNN) implemented on a CNN inference accelerator depend on many factors, including a weight quantization strategy (i. e., data types and bit-widths) and mapping (i. e., placement and scheduling of DNN elementary operations on hardware units of the accelerator).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-quantization-and-mapping-synergy-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree Search-Based Policy Optimization under Stochastic Execution Delay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-search-based-policy-optimization-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that given observed delay values, it is sufficient to perform a policy search in the class of Markov policies in order to reach optimal performance, thus extending the deterministic fixed delay case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-search-based-policy-optimization-under</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
