<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 21:08:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Bi-directional Quantum Search Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bi-directional-quantum-search-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grover's search algorithms, including various partial Grover searches, experience scaling problems as the number of iterations rises with increased qubits, making implementation more computationally expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bi-directional-quantum-search-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynthEval: A Framework for Detailed Utility and Privacy Evaluation of Tabular Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntheval-a-framework-for-detailed-utility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the growing demand for synthetic data to address contemporary issues in machine learning, such as data scarcity, data fairness, and data privacy, having robust tools for assessing the utility and potential privacy risks of such data becomes crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntheval-a-framework-for-detailed-utility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Deep Survival Machines: Survival Regression with Censored Outcomes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-deep-survival-machines-survival</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, We present a novel method to predict the survival time by better clustering the survival data and combine primitive distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-deep-survival-machines-survival</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Out-of-Distribution Detection in LiDAR-based 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-out-of-distribution-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR-based 3D object detection has become an essential part of automated driving due to its ability to localize and classify objects precisely in 3D.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-out-of-distribution-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dynamic Kernel Prior Model for Unsupervised Blind Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-kernel-prior-model-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an unsupervised kernel estimation model, named dynamic kernel prior (DKP), to realize an unsupervised and pre-training-free learning-based algorithm for solving the BSR problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-kernel-prior-model-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks for Vulnerability Detection: A Counterfactual Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-vulnerability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that these factual reasoning-based explanations cannot answer critical what-if questions: What would happen to the GNN's decision if we were to alter the code graph into alternative structures?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-vulnerability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drawing the Line: Deep Segmentation for Extracting Art from Ancient Etruscan Mirrors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drawing-the-line-deep-segmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Etruscan mirrors constitute a significant category within Etruscan art and, therefore, undergo systematic examinations to obtain insights into ancient times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drawing-the-line-deep-segmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raformer: Redundancy-Aware Transformer for Video Wire Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raformer-redundancy-aware-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Wire Inpainting (VWI) is a prominent application in video inpainting, aimed at flawlessly removing wires in films or TV series, offering significant time and labor savings compared to manual frame-by-frame removal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raformer-redundancy-aware-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImplicitAVE: An Open-Source Dataset and Multimodal LLMs Benchmark for Implicit Attribute Value Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicitave-an-open-source-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we present ImplicitAVE, the first, publicly available multimodal dataset for implicit attribute value extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicitave-an-open-source-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FR-NAS: Forward-and-Reverse Graph Predictor for Efficient Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fr-nas-forward-and-reverse-graph-predictor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we incorporate a customized training loss within the GNN predictor to ensure efficient utilization of both types of representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fr-nas-forward-and-reverse-graph-predictor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CutDiffusion: A Simple, Fast, Cheap, and Strong Diffusion Extrapolation Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cutdiffusion-a-simple-fast-cheap-and-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transforming large pre-trained low-resolution diffusion models to cater to higher-resolution demands, i. e., diffusion extrapolation, significantly improves diffusion adaptability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cutdiffusion-a-simple-fast-cheap-and-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IryoNLP at MEDIQA-CORR 2024: Tackling the Medical Error Detection &amp; Correction Task On the Shoulders of Medical Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iryonlp-at-mediqa-corr-2024-tackling-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In natural language processing applied to the clinical domain, utilizing large language models has emerged as a promising avenue for error detection and correction on clinical notes, a knowledge-intensive task for which annotated data is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iryonlp-at-mediqa-corr-2024-tackling-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Universal Dense Blocking for Entity Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-universal-dense-blocking-for-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blocking is a critical step in entity resolution, and the emergence of neural network-based representation models has led to the development of dense blocking as a promising approach for exploring deep semantics in blocking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-universal-dense-blocking-for-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Neural Networks for Continual Learning: An Architectural Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-neural-networks-for-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper seeks to bridge this gap between network architecture design and CL, and to present a holistic study on the impact of network architectures on CL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-neural-networks-for-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Diffusion Probabilistic Models for Character Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-probabilistic-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel character control framework that effectively utilizes motion diffusion probabilistic models to generate high-quality and diverse character animations, responding in real-time to a variety of dynamic user-supplied control signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-probabilistic-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elucidating the theoretical underpinnings of surrogate gradient learning in spiking neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elucidating-the-theoretical-underpinnings-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the latter provides the missing theoretical basis for surrogate gradients in stochastic spiking neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elucidating-the-theoretical-underpinnings-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-3D: Explicit 3D Structure Modeling for Point Cloud Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-3d-explicit-3d-structure-modeling-for-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we contend that such implicit high-dimensional structure modeling approch inadequately represents the local geometric structure of point clouds due to the absence of explicit structural information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-3d-explicit-3d-structure-modeling-for-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Matching to Generation: A Survey on Generative Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-matching-to-generation-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We will summarize the advancements in GR regarding model training, document identifier, incremental learning, downstream tasks adaptation, multi-modal GR and generative recommendation, as well as progress in reliable response generation in aspects of internal knowledge memorization, external knowledge augmentation, generating response with citations and personal information assistant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-matching-to-generation-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate-on-Graph: Treat LLM as both Agent and KG in Incomplete Knowledge Graph Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-on-graph-treat-llm-as-both-agent-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To simulate real-world scenarios and evaluate the ability of LLMs to integrate internal and external knowledge, in this paper, we propose leveraging LLMs for QA under Incomplete Knowledge Graph (IKGQA), where the given KG doesn't include all the factual triples involved in each question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-on-graph-treat-llm-as-both-agent-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Predictive Systems Under Covariate Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-predictive-systems-under-covariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal Predictive Systems (CPS) offer a versatile framework for constructing predictive distributions, allowing for calibrated inference and informative decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-predictive-systems-under-covariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leverage Variational Graph Representation For Model Poisoning on Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leverage-variational-graph-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper puts forth a new training data-untethered model poisoning (MP) attack on federated learning (FL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leverage-variational-graph-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Task-Oriented Dialogues with State Transition Graphs and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-task-oriented-dialogues-with-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, using graph-guided response simulations leads to significant improvements in intent classification, slot filling and response relevance compared to naive single-prompt simulated conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-task-oriented-dialogues-with-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Hyperbolic Metric Learning through Hard Negative Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-hyperbolic-metric-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been a growing trend of incorporating hyperbolic geometry methods into computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-hyperbolic-metric-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traditional to Transformers: A Survey on Current Trends and Future Prospects for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traditional-to-transformers-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperspectral image classification is a challenging task due to the high dimensionality and complex nature of hyperspectral data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traditional-to-transformers-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Unsupervised Salient Object Detection via Knowledge Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-unsupervised-salient-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose a Progressive Curriculum Learning-based Saliency Distilling (PCL-SD) mechanism to extract saliency cues from a pre-trained deep network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-unsupervised-salient-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pillars of Grammatical Error Correction: Comprehensive Inspection Of Contemporary Approaches In The Era of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pillars-of-grammatical-error-correction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we carry out experimental research on Grammatical Error Correction, delving into the nuances of single-model systems, comparing the efficiency of ensembling and ranking methods, and exploring the application of large language models to GEC as single-model systems, as parts of ensembles, and as ranking methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pillars-of-grammatical-error-correction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAGE: Circumplex Affect Guided Expression Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cage-circumplex-affect-guided-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a small-scaled MaxViT-based model architecture, we evaluate the impact of discrete expression category labels in training with the continuous valence and arousal labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cage-circumplex-affect-guided-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XFT: Unlocking the Power of Code Instruction Tuning by Simply Merging Upcycled Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xft-unlocking-the-power-of-code-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce XFT, a simple yet powerful training scheme, by simply merging upcycled Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) to unleash the performance limit of instruction-tuned code Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xft-unlocking-the-power-of-code-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple, Efficient and Scalable Structure-aware Adapter Boosts Protein Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-efficient-and-scalable-structure-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning Pre-trained protein language models (PLMs) has emerged as a prominent strategy for enhancing downstream prediction tasks, often outperforming traditional supervised learning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-efficient-and-scalable-structure-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniMERNet: A Universal Network for Real-World Mathematical Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimernet-a-universal-network-for-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the UniMER dataset to provide the first study on Mathematical Expression Recognition (MER) towards complex real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimernet-a-universal-network-for-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Importance of Disjoint Sampling in Conventional and Transformer Models for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/importance-of-disjoint-sampling-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an innovative disjoint sampling approach for training SOTA models on Hyperspectral image classification (HSIC) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/importance-of-disjoint-sampling-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ID-Animator: Zero-Shot Identity-Preserving Human Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/id-animator-zero-shot-identity-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this pipeline, a random face reference training method is further devised to precisely capture the ID-relevant embeddings from reference images, thus improving the fidelity and generalization capacity of our model for ID-specific video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/id-animator-zero-shot-identity-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CultureBank: An Online Community-Driven Knowledge Base Towards Culturally Aware Language Technologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/culturebank-an-online-community-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance language models' cultural awareness, we design a generalizable pipeline to construct cultural knowledge bases from different online communities on a massive scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/culturebank-an-online-community-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep neural networks for choice analysis: Enhancing behavioral regularity with gradient regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-networks-for-choice-analysis-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the proposed framework is applicable to other NN-based choice models such as TasteNets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-networks-for-choice-analysis-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulating Recommender Systems: A Survey of Poisoning Attacks and Countermeasures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-recommender-systems-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey aims to fill this gap by primarily focusing on poisoning attacks and their countermeasures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-recommender-systems-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Session SLAM with Differentiable Wide-Baseline Pose Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-session-slam-with-differentiable-wide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The backbone is trained end-to-end using a novel differentiable solver for wide-baseline two-view pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-session-slam-with-differentiable-wide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killkan: The Automatic Speech Recognition Dataset for Kichwa with Morphosyntactic Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/killkan-the-automatic-speech-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset, the ASR model, and the code used to develop them will be publicly available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/killkan-the-automatic-speech-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Systematic Evaluation of Logical Reasoning Ability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-systematic-evaluation-of-logical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work investigating this reasoning ability of LLMs has focused only on a couple of inference rules (such as modus ponens and modus tollens) of propositional and first-order logic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-systematic-evaluation-of-logical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metric-guided Image Reconstruction Bounds via Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-guided-image-reconstruction-bounds-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply our method to sparse-view CT for downstream radiotherapy planning and show 1) that metric-guided bounds have valid coverage for downstream metrics while conventional pixel-wise bounds do not and 2) anatomical differences of upper/lower bounds between metric-guided and pixel-wise methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-guided-image-reconstruction-bounds-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyramid Hierarchical Transformer for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-hierarchical-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The traditional Transformer model encounters challenges with variable-length input sequences, particularly in Hyperspectral Image Classification (HSIC), leading to efficiency and scalability concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-hierarchical-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASPR: Automated Evaluation Metric for Contrastive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caspr-automated-evaluation-metric-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summarizing comparative opinions about entities (e. g., hotels, phones) from a set of source reviews, often referred to as contrastive summarization, can considerably aid users in decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caspr-automated-evaluation-metric-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoProNN: Concept-based Prototypical Nearest Neighbors for Explaining Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copronn-concept-based-prototypical-nearest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A promising approach towards designing useful task specific explanations with domain experts is based on compositionality of semantic concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copronn-concept-based-prototypical-nearest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularized Gauss-Newton for Optimizing Overparameterized Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-gauss-newton-for-optimizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work studies a GGN method for optimizing a two-layer neural network with explicit regularization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularized-gauss-newton-for-optimizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Deep Learning to Identify Initial Error Sensitivity of ENSO Forecasts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-deep-learning-to-identify-initial-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a hybrid method that integrates deep learning with model-analog forecasting, a straightforward yet effective approach that generates forecasts from similar initial climate states in a repository of model simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-deep-learning-to-identify-initial-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Causal Preference Learning for Out-of-Distribution Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-causal-preference-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems use users' historical interactions to learn their preferences and deliver personalized recommendations from a vast array of candidate items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-causal-preference-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring and Unleashing the Power of Large Language Models in Automated Code Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-and-unleashing-the-power-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, UniTrans first craft a series of test cases for target programs with the assistance of source programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-and-unleashing-the-power-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Temporal Spectrogram Autoencoder (CTSAE): Unsupervised Dimensionality Reduction for Clustering Gravitational Wave Glitches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-temporal-spectrogram-autoencoder-ctsae</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to this challenge, we introduce the Cross-Temporal Spectrogram Autoencoder (CTSAE), a pioneering unsupervised method for the dimensionality reduction and clustering of gravitational wave glitches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-temporal-spectrogram-autoencoder-ctsae</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Architecture Search with Self-Training for Land Cover Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we proposed a simple yet effective framework to search for lightweight neural networks automatically for land cover mapping tasks under domain shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning the path with Reinforcement Learning: Optimal Robot Motion Planning in RoboCup Small Size League Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-the-path-with-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work investigates the potential of Reinforcement Learning (RL) to tackle robot motion planning challenges in the dynamic RoboCup Small Size League (SSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planning-the-path-with-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of the Noisy Channel: Unsupervised End-to-End Task-Oriented Dialogue with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-the-noisy-channel-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training task-oriented dialogue systems typically requires turn-level annotations for interacting with their APIs: e. g. a dialogue state and the system actions taken at each step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-the-noisy-channel-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
