<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:06:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Unifying Medical Vision-and-Language Pre-training via Soft Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-medical-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical vision-and-language pre-training (Med-VLP) has shown promising improvements on many downstream medical tasks owing to its applicability to extracting generic representations from medical images and texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-medical-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$h$-analysis and data-parallel physics-informed neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-analysis-and-data-parallel-physics-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the data-parallel acceleration of physics-informed machine learning (PIML) schemes, with a focus on physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) for multiple graphics processing units (GPUs) architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-analysis-and-data-parallel-physics-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Cross-modal Fusion based Refinement for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-cross-modal-fusion-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed FF-Block integrates an attention block and several convolution layers to effectively fuse the fine-grained word-context features into the corresponding visual features, in which the text information is fully used to refine the initial image with more details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-cross-modal-fusion-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Response Generation for Chinese Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-response-generation-for-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we construct a new dataset called Penguin to promote the research of MRC, providing a training and test bed for natural response generation to real scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-response-generation-for-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entry Separation using a Mixed Visual and Textual Language Model: Application to 19th century French Trade Directories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entry-separation-using-a-mixed-visual-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When extracting structured data from repetitively organized documents, such as dictionaries, directories, or even newspapers, a key challenge is to correctly segment what constitutes the basic text regions for the target database.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entry-separation-using-a-mixed-visual-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating Knowledge Graphs for Geographic Data on the Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-knowledge-graphs-for-geographic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Geographic data plays an essential role in various Web, Semantic Web and machine learning applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-knowledge-graphs-for-geographic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binary Embedding-based Retrieval at Tencent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binary-embedding-based-retrieval-at-tencent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the challenge, we propose a binary embedding-based retrieval (BEBR) engine equipped with a recurrent binarization algorithm that enables customized bits per dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binary-embedding-based-retrieval-at-tencent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep comparisons of Neural Networks from the EEGNet family</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-comparisons-of-neural-networks-from-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we compared 5 well-known neural networks (Shallow ConvNet, Deep ConvNet, EEGNet, EEGNet Fusion, MI-EEGNet) using open-access databases with many subjects next to the BCI Competition 4 2a dataset to acquire statistically significant results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-comparisons-of-neural-networks-from-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Insights for the Stability-Plasticity Dilemma in Online Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-insights-for-the-stability-plasticity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim of continual learning is to learn new tasks continuously (i. e., plasticity) without forgetting previously learned knowledge from old tasks (i. e., stability).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-insights-for-the-stability-plasticity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Human Pose Lifting with Grid Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-human-pose-lifting-with-grid-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing lifting networks for regressing 3D human poses from 2D single-view poses are typically constructed with linear layers based on graph-structured representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-human-pose-lifting-with-grid-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piecewise Deterministic Markov Processes for Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piecewise-deterministic-markov-processes-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference on modern Bayesian Neural Networks (BNNs) often relies on a variational inference treatment, imposing violated assumptions of independence and the form of the posterior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piecewise-deterministic-markov-processes-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Diffusion Models: Mitigating Sampling Drift by Learning to be Consistent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-diffusion-models-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imperfect score-matching leads to a shift between the training and the sampling distribution of diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-diffusion-models-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>jazznet: A Dataset of Fundamental Piano Patterns for Music Audio Machine Learning Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jazznet-a-dataset-of-fundamental-piano</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the jazznet Dataset, a dataset of fundamental jazz piano music patterns for developing machine learning (ML) algorithms in music information retrieval (MIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jazznet-a-dataset-of-fundamental-piano</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Like a Good Nearest Neighbor: Practical Content Moderation with Sentence Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/like-a-good-nearest-neighbor-practical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern text classification systems have impressive capabilities but are infeasible to deploy and use reliably due to their dependence on prompting and billion-parameter language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/like-a-good-nearest-neighbor-practical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Doctor for Diagnosing and Treating Segmentation Error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-doctor-for-diagnosing-and-treating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable progress in semantic segmentation tasks with the advancement of deep neural networks, existing U-shaped hierarchical typical segmentation networks still suffer from local misclassification of categories and inaccurate target boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-doctor-for-diagnosing-and-treating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Polypharmacy and Predicting Drug-Drug Interactions using Deep Generative Models on Multimodal Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-polypharmacy-and-predicting-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Latent representations of drugs and their targets produced by contemporary graph autoencoder models have proved useful in predicting many types of node-pair interactions on large networks, including drug-drug, drug-target, and target-target interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-polypharmacy-and-predicting-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Label Proportion with Online Pseudo-Label Decision by Regret Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-label-proportion-with-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel and efficient method for Learning from Label Proportions (LLP), whose goal is to train a classifier only by using the class label proportions of instance sets, called bags.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-label-proportion-with-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swapped goal-conditioned offline reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swapped-goal-conditioned-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline goal-conditioned reinforcement learning (GCRL) can be challenging due to overfitting to the given dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swapped-goal-conditioned-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiDi: Mixed Graph and 3D Denoising Diffusion for Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/midi-mixed-graph-and-3d-denoising-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces MiDi, a diffusion model for jointly generating molecular graphs and corresponding 3D conformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/midi-mixed-graph-and-3d-denoising-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CK-Transformer: Commonsense Knowledge Enhanced Transformers for Referring Expression Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ck-transformer-commonsense-knowledge-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of multimodal referring expression comprehension (REC), aiming at localizing an image region described by a natural language expression, has recently received increasing attention within the research comminity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ck-transformer-commonsense-knowledge-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Discrepancy Optimization for Reliable Image Anomaly Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-discrepancy-optimization-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CDO introduces a margin optimization module and an overlap optimization module to optimize the two key factors determining the localization performance, i. e., the margin and the overlap between the discrepancy distributions (DDs) of normal and abnormal samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-discrepancy-optimization-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Data Types More Problems: A Temporal Analysis of Complexity, Stability, and Sensitivity in Privacy Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-data-types-more-problems-a-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we examine a large textual dataset of privacy policies from 1997-2019 in order to investigate the data collection activities of data brokers and data processors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-data-types-more-problems-a-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient subtyping of ovarian cancer histopathology whole slide images using active sampling in multiple instance learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-subtyping-of-ovarian-cancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly-supervised classification of histopathology slides is a computationally intensive task, with a typical whole slide image (WSI) containing billions of pixels to process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-subtyping-of-ovarian-cancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Topological Features for Phylogenetic Inference via Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-topological-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Structural information of phylogenetic tree topologies plays an important role in phylogenetic inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-topological-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Training of Mean Variance Estimation Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-training-of-mean-variance-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This recommendation is often not used in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-training-of-mean-variance-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unique Identification of 50,000+ Virtual Reality Users from Head &amp; Hand Motion Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unique-identification-of-50000-virtual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent explosive growth of interest and investment in virtual reality (VR) and the so-called "metaverse," public attention has rightly shifted toward the unique security and privacy threats that these platforms may pose.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unique-identification-of-50000-virtual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DREEAM: Guiding Attention with Evidence for Improving Document-Level Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreeam-guiding-attention-with-evidence-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we propose DREEAM, a memory-efficient approach that adopts evidence information as the supervisory signal, thereby guiding the attention modules of the DocRE system to assign high weights to evidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreeam-guiding-attention-with-evidence-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metropolitan Segment Traffic Speeds from Massive Floating Car Data in 10 Cities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metropolitan-segment-traffic-speeds-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic analysis is crucial for urban operations and planning, while the availability of dense urban traffic data beyond loop detectors is still scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metropolitan-segment-traffic-speeds-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2I-Adapter: Learning Adapters to Dig out More Controllable Ability for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2i-adapter-learning-adapters-to-dig-out-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The incredible generative ability of large-scale text-to-image (T2I) models has demonstrated strong power of learning complex structures and meaningful semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2i-adapter-learning-adapters-to-dig-out-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Noise Suppression in Random SVPWM to Shape the Voltage and Current Spectrum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-noise-suppression-in-random-svpwm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed methods provide a reference to eliminate the electromagnetic noise at the modal frequencies in motors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-noise-suppression-in-random-svpwm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Album: Multi-domain Meta-Dataset for Few-Shot Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-album-multi-domain-meta-dataset-for-few-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Meta-Album, an image classification meta-dataset designed to facilitate few-shot learning, transfer learning, meta-learning, among other tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-album-multi-domain-meta-dataset-for-few-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Rejection for Abstractive Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-rejection-for-abstractive-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art abstractive summarization systems frequently hallucinate content that is not supported by the source document, mainly due to noise in the training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-rejection-for-abstractive-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theory and Implementation of Complex-Valued Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theory-and-implementation-of-complex-valued</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work explains in detail the theory behind Complex-Valued Neural Network (CVNN), including Wirtinger calculus, complex backpropagation, and basic modules such as complex layers, complex activation functions, or complex weight initialization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theory-and-implementation-of-complex-valued</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assisting Human Decisions in Document Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assisting-human-decisions-in-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many practical applications, ranging from paper-reviewer assignment in peer review to job-applicant matching for hiring, require human decision makers to identify relevant matches by combining their expertise with predictions from machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assisting-human-decisions-in-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-augmented Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The encoder in our model jointly processes the image and retrieved captions using a pretrained V&L BERT, while the decoder attends to the multimodal encoder representations, benefiting from the extra textual evidence from the retrieved captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fossil Image Identification using Deep Learning Ensembles of Data Augmented Multiviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fossil-image-identification-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, OGS obtains the superior or comparable performance compared to the method under well-known bagging framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fossil-image-identification-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-augmented Graph Machine Learning for Drug Discovery: A Survey from Precision to Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-augmented-graph-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As of late, Graph Machine Learning (GML) has gained considerable attention for its exceptional ability to model graph-structured biomedical data and investigate their properties and functional relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-augmented-graph-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPLoss: A Temporal Acoustic Parameter Loss for Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taploss-a-temporal-acoustic-parameter-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an objective for perceptual quality based on temporal acoustic parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taploss-a-temporal-acoustic-parameter-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singular Value Representation: A New Graph Perspective On Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singular-value-representation-a-new-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Singular Value Representation (SVR), a new method to represent the internal state of neural networks using SVD factorization of the weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singular-value-representation-a-new-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiency 360: Efficient Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-360-efficient-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers are widely used for solving tasks in natural language processing, computer vision, speech, and music domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-360-efficient-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SyreaNet: A Physically Guided Underwater Image Enhancement Framework Integrating Synthetic and Real Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syreanet-a-physically-guided-underwater-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although learning-based UIE methods have made remarkable achievements in recent years, it's still challenging for them to consistently deal with various underwater conditions, which could be caused by: 1) the use of the simplified atmospheric image formation model in UIE may result in severe errors; 2) the network trained solely with synthetic images might have difficulty in generalizing well to real underwater images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syreanet-a-physically-guided-underwater-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Causal Discovery for Estimating Causal Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-causal-discovery-for-estimating-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even when the causal graph underlying our data is unknown, we can use observational data to narrow down the possible values that an average treatment effect (ATE) can take by (1) identifying the graph up to a Markov equivalence class; and (2) estimating that ATE for each graph in the class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-causal-discovery-for-estimating-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE-MAN -- Homomorphically Encrypted MAchine learning with oNnx models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/he-man-homomorphically-encrypted-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fully homomorphic encryption (FHE) is a promising technique to enable individuals using ML services without giving up privacy and protecting the ML model of service providers at the same time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/he-man-homomorphically-encrypted-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URCDC-Depth: Uncertainty Rectified Cross-Distillation with CutFlip for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urcdc-depth-uncertainty-rectified-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we use the depth estimates from the Transformer branch and the CNN branch as pseudo labels to teach each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/urcdc-depth-uncertainty-rectified-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Remote Sensing Image Super-Resolution based on Context Interaction in Implicit Function Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-remote-sensing-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its fruitful applications in remote sensing, image super-resolution is troublesome to train and deploy as it handles different resolution magnifications with separate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-remote-sensing-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural PDE Solver with Temporal Stencil Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-pde-solver-with-temporal-stencil</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical simulation of non-linear partial differential equations plays a crucial role in modeling physical science and engineering phenomena, such as weather, climate, and aerodynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-pde-solver-with-temporal-stencil</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIFUSCO: Graph-based Diffusion Solvers for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difusco-graph-based-diffusion-solvers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the MIS problem, DIFUSCO outperforms the previous state-of-the-art neural solver on the challenging SATLIB benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difusco-graph-based-diffusion-solvers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Spoken Language Identification with Map-Mix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-spoken-language-identification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pre-trained multi-lingual XLSR model generalizes well for language identification after fine-tuning on unseen languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-spoken-language-identification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counting Carbon: A Survey of Factors Influencing the Emissions of Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counting-carbon-a-survey-of-factors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) requires using energy to carry out computations during the model training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counting-carbon-a-survey-of-factors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Non-Local Spatial-Angular Correlation for Light Field Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-local-spatial-angular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploiting spatial-angular correlation is crucial to light field (LF) image super-resolution (SR), but is highly challenging due to its non-local property caused by the disparities among LF images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-non-local-spatial-angular</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
