<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 21:08:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multiwinner Temporal Voting with Aversion to Change</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiwinner-temporal-voting-with-aversion-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study two-stage committee elections where voters have dynamic preferences over candidates; at each stage, a committee is chosen under a given voting rule.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiwinner-temporal-voting-with-aversion-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Multimodal Deformable Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first utilize a CNN encoder to extract deep visual features from cross-modal image pairs, then we use the first adapter to adjust these tokens, and use LoRA in pre-trained LLMs to fine-tune their weights, both aimed at eliminating the domain gap between the pre-trained LLMs and the MDIR task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Current Deepfake Audio Detection Model Effectively Detect ALM-based Deepfake Audio?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-current-deepfake-audio-detection-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, Audio Language Models (ALMs) are rapidly advancing due to the developments in large language models and audio neural codecs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-current-deepfake-audio-detection-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenScan: A Benchmark for Generalized Open-Vocabulary 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openscan-a-benchmark-for-generalized-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a more challenging task called Generalized Open-Vocabulary 3D Scene Understanding (GOV-3D) to explore the open vocabulary problem beyond object classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openscan-a-benchmark-for-generalized-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ETGuard: Malicious Encrypted Traffic Detection in Blockchain-based Power Grid Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etguard-malicious-encrypted-traffic-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The escalating prevalence of encryption protocols has led to a concomitant surge in the number of malicious attacks that hide in encrypted traffic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/etguard-malicious-encrypted-traffic-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Modeling on Tabular Data: A Survey of Foundations, Techniques and Evolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-modeling-on-tabular-data-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper fills this gap by providing a systematic review of the development of language modeling for tabular data, encompassing: (1) a categorization of different tabular data structures and data types; (2) a review of key datasets used in model training and tasks used for evaluation; (3) a summary of modeling techniques including widely-adopted data processing methods, popular architectures, and training objectives; (4) the evolution from adapting traditional Pre-training/Pre-trained language models to the utilization of large language models; (5) an identification of persistent challenges and potential future research directions in language modeling for tabular data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-modeling-on-tabular-data-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wave-Mask/Mix: Exploring Wavelet-Based Augmentations for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wave-mask-mix-exploring-wavelet-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces two augmentation approaches using the discrete wavelet transform (DWT) to adjust frequency elements while preserving temporal dependencies in time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wave-mask-mix-exploring-wavelet-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hokoff: Real Game Dataset from Honor of Kings and its Offline Reinforcement Learning Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hokoff-real-game-dataset-from-honor-of-kings-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advancement of Offline Reinforcement Learning (RL) and Offline Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) critically depends on the availability of high-quality, pre-collected offline datasets that represent real-world complexities and practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hokoff-real-game-dataset-from-honor-of-kings-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiRED: Attention-Guided Token Dropping for Efficient Inference of High-Resolution Vision-Language Models in Resource-Constrained Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hired-attention-guided-token-dropping-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, using the attention in the final layer, we select the most important visual tokens from each partition within the allocated budget, dropping the rest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hired-attention-guided-token-dropping-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Norm Amplification for Out-of-Distribution Detection in Long-Tail Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-norm-amplification-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main idea is to use the norm of the representation as a new dimension for OOD detection, and to develop a training method that generates a noticeable discrepancy in the representation norm between ID and OOD data, while not perturbing the feature learning for ID classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-norm-amplification-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAME: Learning to Navigate with Multimodal LLM in Urban Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flame-learning-to-navigate-with-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated potential in Vision-and-Language Navigation (VLN) tasks, yet current applications face challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flame-learning-to-navigate-with-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>deepmriprep: Voxel-based Morphometry (VBM) Preprocessing via Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmriprep-voxel-based-morphometry-vbm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voxel-based Morphometry (VBM) has emerged as a powerful approach in neuroimaging research, utilized in over 7, 000 studies since the year 2000.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmriprep-voxel-based-morphometry-vbm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViLReF: A Chinese Vision-Language Retinal Foundation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilref-a-chinese-vision-language-retinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate the powerful zero-shot and transfer learning capabilities of ViLReF, verifying the effectiveness of our pre-training strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilref-a-chinese-vision-language-retinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subspace Prototype Guidance for Mitigating Class Imbalance in Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-prototype-guidance-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the point cloud is initially separated into independent point sets by category to provide initial conditions for the generation of feature subspaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-prototype-guidance-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hologram Reasoning for Solving Algebra Problems with Geometry Diagrams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hologram-reasoning-for-solving-algebra</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reach this goal, it first defines a hologram, being a kind of graph, and proposes a hologram generator to convert a given APGD into a hologram, which represents the entire information of APGD and the relations for solving the problem can be acquired from it by a uniform way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hologram-reasoning-for-solving-algebra</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SZTU-CMU at MER2024: Improving Emotion-LLaMA with Conv-Attention for Multimodal Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sztu-cmu-at-mer2024-improving-emotion-llama</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our winning approach for the MER-NOISE and MER-OV tracks of the MER2024 Challenge on multimodal emotion recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sztu-cmu-at-mer2024-improving-emotion-llama</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ferret: Faster and Effective Automated Red Teaming with Reward-Based Scoring Technique</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-faster-and-effective-automated-red</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we propose Ferret, a novel approach that builds upon Rainbow Teaming by generating multiple adversarial prompt mutations per iteration and using a scoring function to rank and select the most effective adversarial prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferret-faster-and-effective-automated-red</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-facial-expression-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To preserve the generalization ability of CLIP and the high precision of the FER model, we design a novel approach that learns sigmoid masks based on the fixed CLIP face features to extract expression features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-facial-expression-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRformer: Pyramidal Recurrent Transformer for Multivariate Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prformer-pyramidal-recurrent-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The self-attention mechanism in Transformer architecture, invariant to sequence order, necessitates positional embeddings to encode temporal order in time series prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prformer-pyramidal-recurrent-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Goal-Conditioned RL Algorithms and Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-goal-conditioned-rl-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervision has the potential to transform reinforcement learning (RL), paralleling the breakthroughs it has enabled in other areas of machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-goal-conditioned-rl-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting People in LLMs' Shoes: Generating Better Answers via Question Rewriter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-people-in-llms-shoes-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By enhancing the intelligibility of human questions for black-box LLMs, our question rewriter improves the quality of generated answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-people-in-llms-shoes-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Neural Networks Learn to Store and Generate Sequences using Non-Linear Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-neural-networks-learn-to-store-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a counterexample to this strong LRH: when trained to repeat an input token sequence, gated recurrent neural networks (RNNs) learn to represent the token at each position with a particular order of magnitude, rather than a direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-neural-networks-learn-to-store-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Assignment Invariant Neural Networks for Learning Logic Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-assignment-invariant-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning from interpretation transition (LFIT) is a framework for learning rules from observed state transitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-assignment-invariant-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Novelty Detection Through Adaptive Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-novelty-detection-through-adaptive-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More precisely, for novelty detection, distribution shifts may occur in the training set or the test set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-novelty-detection-through-adaptive-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Guided Image-Adaptive Neural Implicit Lookup Tables for Interpretable Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-guided-image-adaptive-neural-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve into the concept of interpretable image enhancement, a technique that enhances image quality by adjusting filter parameters with easily understandable names such as "Exposure" and "Contrast".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-guided-image-adaptive-neural-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnyGraph: Graph Foundation Model in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anygraph-graph-foundation-model-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we have validated the model's fast adaptation ability and scaling law emergence, showcasing its versatility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anygraph-graph-foundation-model-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerturBench: Benchmarking Machine Learning Models for Cellular Perturbation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbench-benchmarking-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a comprehensive framework for predicting the effects of perturbations in single cells, designed to standardize benchmarking in this rapidly evolving field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbench-benchmarking-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EdgeNAT: Transformer for Efficient Edge Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgenat-transformer-for-efficient-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the one hand, EdgeNAT captures global contextual information and detailed local cues with DiNAT, on the other hand, it enhances feature representation with a novel SCAF-MLA decoder by utilizing both inter-spatial and inter-channel relationships of feature maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgenat-transformer-for-efficient-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SysBench: Can Large Language Models Follow System Messages?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sysbench-can-large-language-models-follow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to enable effective evaluation, SysBench constructs multi-turn user conversations covering various interaction relationships, based on six common types of constraints from system messages in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sysbench-can-large-language-models-follow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Calorimeter for Anti-neutron Reconstruction: A Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-calorimeter-for-anti-neutron</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce Vision Calorimeter (ViC), a baseline method for anti-neutron reconstruction that leverages deep learning detectors to analyze the implicit relationships between EMC responses and incident $\bar{n}$ characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-calorimeter-for-anti-neutron</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atmospheric Transport Modeling of CO$_2$ with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atmospheric-transport-modeling-of-co-2-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately describing the distribution of CO$_2$ in the atmosphere with atmospheric tracer transport models is essential for greenhouse gas monitoring and verification support systems to aid implementation of international climate agreements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atmospheric-transport-modeling-of-co-2-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REInstruct: Building Instruction Data from Unlabeled Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinstruct-building-instruction-data-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Manually annotating instruction data for large language models is difficult, costly, and hard to scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinstruct-building-instruction-data-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAAD: Dynamic Analysis and Adaptive Discriminator for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daad-dynamic-analysis-and-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In current web environment, fake news spreads rapidly across online social networks, posing serious threats to society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daad-dynamic-analysis-and-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While GitHub Copilot Excels at Coding, Does It Ensure Responsible Output?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/while-github-copilot-excels-at-coding-does-it</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of large language models (LLMs) has significantly advanced code completion capabilities, giving rise to a new generation of LLM-based Code Completion Tools (LCCTs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/while-github-copilot-excels-at-coding-does-it</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Framework for AI-driven Molecular Design of Multi-target Drugs: Brain Diseases as a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-framework-for-ai-driven-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, this work will assess the performance of four deep generative models and evolutionary algorithms over our benchmark suite.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-framework-for-ai-driven-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A toolbox for calculating objective image properties in aesthetics research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-toolbox-for-calculating-objective-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the Toolbox, we integrated the original scripts of four different research groups and translated them into Python 3.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-toolbox-for-calculating-objective-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UIE-UnFold: Deep Unfolding Network with Color Priors and Vision Transformer for Underwater Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uie-unfold-deep-unfolding-network-with-color</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By explicitly incorporating color priors and modeling the physical characteristics of underwater image formation, the proposed DUN model achieves more accurate and reliable enhancement results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uie-unfold-deep-unfolding-network-with-color</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeJudge-Eval: Can Large Language Models be Good Judges in Code Understanding?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codejudge-eval-can-large-language-models-be</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have showcased impressive code generation capabilities, primarily evaluated through language-to-code benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codejudge-eval-can-large-language-models-be</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPL: Lifting 3D Human Pose from Multi-view 2D Poses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpl-lifting-3d-human-pose-from-multi-view-2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating 3D human poses from 2D images is challenging due to occlusions and projective acquisition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpl-lifting-3d-human-pose-from-multi-view-2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Sharing and Transfer via Centralized Reward Agent for Multi-Task Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-sharing-and-transfer-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reward shaping is effective in addressing the sparse-reward challenge in reinforcement learning by providing immediate feedback through auxiliary informative rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-sharing-and-transfer-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second-Order Forward-Mode Automatic Differentiation for Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/second-order-forward-mode-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a second-order hyperplane search, a novel optimization step that generalizes a second-order line search from a line to a $k$-dimensional hyperplane.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/second-order-forward-mode-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning on Augmented Gene Expression Profiles for Enhanced Lung Cancer Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-on-augmented-gene-expression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply this framework to well-established deep learning methodologies and employ four distinct datasets for the meta-learning tasks, where one as the target dataset and the rest as source datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-on-augmented-gene-expression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-UNet:Enhancing Zero-Shot Segmentation of SAM for Universal Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-unet-enhancing-zero-shot-segmentation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train SAM-UNet on SA-Med2D-16M, the largest 2-dimensional medical image segmentation dataset to date, yielding a universal pretrained model for medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-unet-enhancing-zero-shot-segmentation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMILE: Zero-Shot Sparse Mixture of Low-Rank Experts Construction From Pre-Trained Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smile-zero-shot-sparse-mixture-of-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep model training on extensive datasets is increasingly becoming cost-prohibitive, prompting the widespread adoption of deep model fusion techniques to leverage knowledge from pre-existing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smile-zero-shot-sparse-mixture-of-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDNetGen: Empowering Complex Network Resilience Prediction with Generative Augmentation of Topology and Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdnetgen-empowering-complex-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the resilience of complex networks, which represents the ability to retain fundamental functionality amidst external perturbations or internal failures, plays a critical role in understanding and improving real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdnetgen-empowering-complex-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuFlow v2: High-Efficiency Optical Flow Estimation on Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuflow-v2-high-efficiency-optical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a highly efficient optical flow method that balances high accuracy with reduced computational demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuflow-v2-high-efficiency-optical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Grid Convolution for Multi-Scale Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-grid-convolution-for-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a single encoder to extract features and introduce a novel upsampler, Implicit Grid Convolution~(IGConv), which integrates SPConv at all scales within a single module to predict multiple scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-grid-convolution-for-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning for Autonomous Driving: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-for-22</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) is a potent tool for sequential decision-making and has achieved performance surpassing human capabilities across many challenging real-world tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-for-22</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpoMamba: Exploiting Frequency SSM Blocks for Efficient and Effective Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expomamba-exploiting-frequency-ssm-blocks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-light image enhancement remains a challenging task in computer vision, with existing state-of-the-art models often limited by hardware constraints and computational inefficiencies, particularly in handling high-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expomamba-exploiting-frequency-ssm-blocks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-MacroFin: Informed Equilibrium Neural Network for Continuous Time Economic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-macrofin-informed-equilibrium-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Deep-MacroFin, a comprehensive framework designed to solve partial differential equations, with a particular focus on models in continuous time economics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-macrofin-informed-equilibrium-neural</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
