<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 09:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ViTag: Online WiFi Fine Time Measurements Aided Vision-Motion Identity Association in Multi-person Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitag-online-wifi-fine-time-measurements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ViTag associates a sequence of vision tracker generated bounding boxes with Inertial Measurement Unit (IMU) data and Wi-Fi Fine Time Measurements (FTM) from smartphones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitag-online-wifi-fine-time-measurements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View-Disentangled Transformer for Brain Lesion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-disentangled-transformer-for-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have been widely adopted in brain lesion detection and segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-disentangled-transformer-for-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoV-TI-Net: Transferred Initialization with Modified End Layer for COVID-19 Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cov-ti-net-transferred-initialization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research, the PyTorch pre-trained models (VGG19\_bn and WideResNet -101) are applied in the MNIST dataset for the first time as initialization and with modified fully connected layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cov-ti-net-transferred-initialization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modal Learning for Image-Guided Point Cloud Shape Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-learning-for-image-guided-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we explore the recent topic of point cloud completion, guided by an auxiliary image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-learning-for-image-guided-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Graph Message Passing Networks for Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-graph-message-passing-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A fully-connected graph, such as the self-attention operation in Transformers, is beneficial for such modelling, however, its computational overhead is prohibitive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-graph-message-passing-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Light: Zero-Shot Text-Driven HDR Panorama Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2light-zero-shot-text-driven-hdr-panorama</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve super-resolution inverse tone mapping, we derive a continuous representation of 360-degree imaging from the LDR panorama as a set of structured latent codes anchored to the sphere.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2light-zero-shot-text-driven-hdr-panorama</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Replay-Based Continual Semantic Segmentation with Smart Data Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-replay-based-continual-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning for Semantic Segmentation (CSS) is a rapidly emerging field, in which the capabilities of the segmentation model are incrementally improved by learning new classes or new domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-replay-based-continual-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extremely Simple Activation Shaping for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extremely-simple-activation-shaping-for-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The separation between training and deployment of machine learning models implies that not all scenarios encountered in deployment can be anticipated during training, and therefore relying solely on advancements in training has its limits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extremely-simple-activation-shaping-for-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Edge Enhancement and Suppression Learning for 3D Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-edge-enhancement-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we experimentally observe and verify the edge enhancement and suppression behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-edge-enhancement-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Image Pyramid Structure for High Resolution Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-image-pyramid-structure-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Salient object detection (SOD) has been in the spotlight recently, yet has been studied less for high-resolution (HR) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-image-pyramid-structure-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Early Exit in DNNs with Multiple Exits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-early-exit-in-dnns-with-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence one is faced with the problem of selecting the optimal exit in an unsupervised setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-early-exit-in-dnns-with-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Joint Imitation-Reinforcement Learning Framework for Reduced Baseline Regret</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-joint-imitation-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The learning process in JIRL assumes the availability of a baseline policy and is designed with two objectives in mind \textbf{(a)} leveraging the baseline's online demonstrations to minimize the regret w. r. t the baseline policy during training, and \textbf{(b)} eventually surpassing the baseline performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-joint-imitation-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Outlier Exposure Approach to Improve Visual Anomaly Detection Performance for Mobile Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-outlier-exposure-approach-to-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of building visual anomaly detection systems for mobile robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-outlier-exposure-approach-to-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review of data types and model dimensionality for cardiac DTI SMS-related artefact removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/review-of-data-types-and-model-dimensionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As diffusion tensor imaging (DTI) gains popularity in cardiac imaging due to its unique ability to non-invasively assess the cardiac microstructure, deep learning-based Artificial Intelligence is becoming a crucial tool in mitigating some of its drawbacks, such as the long scan times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/review-of-data-types-and-model-dimensionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Centric AI Paradigm Based on Application-Driven Fine-grained Dataset Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-centric-ai-paradigm-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has a wide range of applications in industrial scenario, but reducing false alarm (FA) remains a major difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-centric-ai-paradigm-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target-Guided Open-Domain Conversation Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-guided-open-domain-conversation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior studies addressing target-oriented conversational tasks lack a crucial notion that has been intensively studied in the context of goal-oriented artificial intelligence agents, namely, planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-guided-open-domain-conversation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Linguistic Supervision for Contrastive Learning of Sentence Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-linguistic-supervision-for-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This indicates that Transformer models are able to generalize better by doing a similar task (i. e., clustering) with unpaired examples from different modalities in a multi-task fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-linguistic-supervision-for-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting respiratory motion artefacts for cardiovascular MRIs to ensure high-quality segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-respiratory-motion-artefacts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In cardiovascular magnetic resonance imaging (CMR), respiratory motion represents a major challenge in terms of acquisition quality and therefore subsequent analysis and final diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-respiratory-motion-artefacts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Label Sequence Generation for Prompting Sequence-to-sequence Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-label-sequence-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompting, which casts downstream applications as language modeling tasks, has shown to be sample efficient compared to standard fine-tuning with pre-trained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-label-sequence-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Benchmarking Clustering Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-benchmarking-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of clustering algorithms can be performed by running them on a variety of benchmark problems, and comparing their outputs to the reference, ground-truth groupings provided by experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-benchmarking-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can we do that simpler? Simple, Efficient, High-Quality Evaluation Metrics for NLG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-do-that-simpler-simple-efficient-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore efficient evaluation metrics for Natural Language Generation (NLG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-do-that-simpler-simple-efficient-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Vicious Attacks on Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-vicious-attacks-on-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on a specific, white-box attack to GNN-based link prediction models, where a malicious node aims to appear in the list of recommended nodes for a given target victim.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-vicious-attacks-on-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature embedding in click-through rate prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-embedding-in-click-through-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The embedding modules act as a way to improve baseline model feature embeddings and are trained alongside the rest of the model parameters in an end-to-end manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-embedding-in-click-through-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Gender Wage Gap: Adversarial Fairness in Job Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gender-wage-gap-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude that adversarial debiasing of word representations can increase real-world fairness of systems and thus may be part of the solution for creating fairness-aware recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-gender-wage-gap-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first neural machine translation system for the Erzya language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-neural-machine-translation-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first neural machine translation system for translation between the endangered Erzya language and Russian and the dataset collected by us to train and evaluate it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-neural-machine-translation-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the SV-Ident 2022 Shared Task on Survey Variable Identification in Social Science Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-the-sv-ident-2022-shared-task-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide an overview of the SV-Ident shared task as part of the 3rd Workshop on Scholarly Document Processing (SDP) at COLING 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-the-sv-ident-2022-shared-task-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fusion of Multi-object Densities Using Transfomer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fusion-of-multi-object-densities-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the performance of the transformer-based fusion method with a well-performing model-based Bayesian fusion method in several simulated scenarios with different parameter settings using synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fusion-of-multi-object-densities-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimberTrek: Exploring and Curating Sparse Decision Trees with Interactive Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timbertrek-exploring-and-curating-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given thousands of equally accurate machine learning (ML) models, how can users choose among them?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timbertrek-exploring-and-curating-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time Online Video Detection with Temporal Smoothing Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-online-video-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Streaming video recognition reasons about objects and their actions in every frame of a video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-online-video-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Optimization for Cardinality-constrained Minimum Sum-of-Squares Clustering via Semidefinite Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-optimization-for-cardinality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the upper bound, instead, we present a local search procedure that exploits the solution of the SDP relaxation solved at each node.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-optimization-for-cardinality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequence-to-Set Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-to-set-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present GRU2Set, which is an instance of our sequence-to-set method and employs the famous GRU model as the sequence generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-to-set-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computing Anti-Derivatives using Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computing-anti-derivatives-using-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have used this algorithm to obtain the anti-derivatives of several functions, including non-elementary and oscillatory integrals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computing-anti-derivatives-using-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visible-Infrared Person Re-Identification Using Privileged Intermediate Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visible-infrared-person-re-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[% This paper introduces a novel approach for a creating intermediate virtual domain that acts as bridges between the two main domains (i. e., RGB and IR modalities) during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visible-infrared-person-re-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust leave-one-out cross-validation for high-dimensional Bayesian models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-leave-one-out-cross-validation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method retains the simplicity and computational convenience of classical approaches, while guaranteeing finite variance of the resulting estimators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-leave-one-out-cross-validation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Biased Artist: Exploiting Cultural Biases via Homoglyphs in Text-Guided Image Generation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-biased-artist-exploiting-cultural-biases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results further indicate that text encoders trained on multilingual data provide a way to mitigate the effects of homoglyph replacements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-biased-artist-exploiting-cultural-biases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-PL: Domain Adaptive Depth Estimation with 3D-aware Pseudo-Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pl-domain-adaptive-depth-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a domain adaptation framework via generating reliable pseudo ground truths of depth from real data to provide direct supervisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pl-domain-adaptive-depth-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Knowledge Graph Evaluation Under the Open-World Assumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-graph-evaluation-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, evaluation of knowledge graph completion (KGC) models often ignores the incompleteness -- facts in the test set are ranked against all unknown triplets which may contain a large number of missing facts not included in the KG yet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-knowledge-graph-evaluation-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Language Semantic and Structure Embedding for Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-language-semantic-and-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike previous approaches that rely on either the structures or semantics of the knowledge graphs, we propose to jointly embed the semantics in the natural language description of the knowledge triplets with their structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-language-semantic-and-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Face Inpainting Through Residual Attention UNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-face-inpainting-through-residual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Realistic image restoration with high texture areas such as removing face masks is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-face-inpainting-through-residual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding reinforcement learned crowds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-reinforcement-learned-crowds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each of these choices has a significant, and potentially nontrivial impact on the results, and so researchers should be mindful about choosing and reporting them in their work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-reinforcement-learned-crowds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batch Layer Normalization, A new normalization layer for CNNs and RNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-layer-normalization-a-new-normalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a combined version of batch and layer normalization, BLN adaptively puts appropriate weight on mini-batch and feature normalization based on the inverse size of mini-batches to normalize the input to a layer during the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-layer-normalization-a-new-normalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Geometric Space Embedding Model for Two-View Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-geometric-space-embedding-model-for-two</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For works that seek to put both views of the KG together, the instance and ontology views are assumed to belong to the same geometric space, such as all nodes embedded in the same Euclidean space or non-Euclidean product space, an assumption no longer reasonable for two-view KGs where different portions of the graph exhibit different structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-geometric-space-embedding-model-for-two</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic incident duration prediction via a deep learning framework for text description encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-incident-duration-prediction-via-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the traffic incident duration is a hard problem to solve due to the stochastic nature of incident occurrence in space and time, a lack of information at the beginning of a reported traffic disruption, and lack of advanced methods in transport engineering to derive insights from past accidents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-incident-duration-prediction-via-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Adapt Pre-trained Vision-and-Language Models to a Text-only Input?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-adapt-pre-trained-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To find the best approach, we investigate and compare seven possible methods for adapting three different pre-trained VL models to text-only input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-adapt-pre-trained-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewarding Episodic Visitation Discrepancy for Exploration in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewarding-episodic-visitation-discrepancy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploration is critical for deep reinforcement learning in complex environments with high-dimensional observations and sparse rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewarding-episodic-visitation-discrepancy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Spurious Correlations in Popular Event-Based Rumor Detection Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-spurious-correlations-in-popular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As social media becomes a hotbed for the spread of misinformation, the crucial task of rumor detection has witnessed promising advances fostered by open-source benchmark datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-spurious-correlations-in-popular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGC-Net: A Lightweight Gyroscope Calibration Network for Efficient Attitude Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgc-net-a-lightweight-gyroscope-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a lightweight, efficient calibration neural network model for denoising low-cost microelectromechanical system (MEMS) gyroscope and estimating the attitude of a robot in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgc-net-a-lightweight-gyroscope-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Task Vision Transformer for Semi-Supervised Driver Distraction Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-vision-transformer-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driver distraction detection is an important computer vision problem that can play a crucial role in enhancing traffic safety and reducing traffic accidents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-vision-transformer-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOCRATES: A Stereo Camera Trap for Monitoring of Biodiversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socrates-a-stereo-camera-trap-for-monitoring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach employs stereo vision to infer 3D information of natural habitats and is designated as StereO CameRA Trap for monitoring of biodivErSity (SOCRATES).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socrates-a-stereo-camera-trap-for-monitoring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D&amp;D: Learning Human Dynamics from Dynamic Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-d-learning-human-dynamics-from-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present D&D (Learning Human Dynamics from Dynamic Camera), which leverages the laws of physics to reconstruct 3D human motion from the in-the-wild videos with a moving camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-d-learning-human-dynamics-from-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
