<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 21:09:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Multi-Modality Guidance for Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-multi-modality-guidance-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image inpainting is an ill-posed problem to recover missing or damaged image content based on incomplete images with masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-multi-modality-guidance-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Construct 3D Building Wireframes from 3D Line Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-construct-3d-building-wireframes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Line clouds, though under-investigated in the previous work, potentially encode more compact structural information of buildings than point clouds extracted from multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-construct-3d-building-wireframes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Clustering with an EM algorithm for Mixtures of Linear Gaussian State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-clustering-with-an-em-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a novel model-based time series clustering method with mixtures of linear Gaussian state space models, which have high flexibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-clustering-with-an-em-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refine and Represent: Region-to-Object Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refine-and-represent-region-to-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works in self-supervised learning have demonstrated strong performance on scene-level dense prediction tasks by pretraining with object-centric or region-based correspondence objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refine-and-represent-region-to-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Multimodal Emotion Recognition using Hybrid Fusion of Speech and Image Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-emotion-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new interpretability technique has been developed to identify the important speech & image features leading to the prediction of particular emotion classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-emotion-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Analysis of the Efficacy of Different Sampling Techniques for Imbalanced Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-analysis-of-the-efficacy-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are numerous approaches to dealing with imbalanced data, but the efficacy of such techniques or an experimental comparison among those techniques has not been conducted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-analysis-of-the-efficacy-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton Prototype Contrastive Learning with Multi-Level Graph Relation Modeling for Unsupervised Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-prototype-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we propose a skeleton prototype contrastive learning scheme that clusters feature-correlative instances of unlabeled graph representations and contrasts their inherent similarity with representative skeleton features ("skeleton prototypes") to learn discriminative skeleton representations for person re-ID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-prototype-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Relational Causal Models with Cycles through Relational Acyclification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-relational-causal-models-with-cycles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce \textit{relational acyclification}, an operation specifically designed for relational models that enables reasoning about the identifiability of cyclic relational causal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-relational-causal-models-with-cycles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Truncated Linear Regression with Unknown Noise Variance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-truncated-linear-regression-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide the first computationally and statistically efficient estimators for truncated linear regression when the noise variance is unknown, estimating both the linear model and the variance of the noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-truncated-linear-regression-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Sensitive Knowledge Propagation for Cloth-Changing Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-sensitive-knowledge-propagation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the resolution degradation issue and mine identity-sensitive cues from human faces, we propose to restore the missing facial details using prior facial knowledge, which is then propagated to a smaller network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-sensitive-knowledge-propagation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deep learning approach to predict the number of k-barriers for intrusion detection over a circular region using wireless sensor networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-to-predict-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the crucial applications of WSNs is intrusion detection and surveillance at the border areas and in the defense establishments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-to-predict-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-based approaches for automatic detection of shell nouns and evaluation on WikiText-2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-approaches-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All discovered shell nouns as well as pre-trained models and code are available on GitHub.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-approaches-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAXFit: Trust Region Method for Nonlinear Least-Squares Curve Fitting on the GPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxfit-trust-region-method-for-nonlinear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement a trust region method on the GPU for nonlinear least squares curve fitting problems using a new deep learning Python library called JAX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxfit-trust-region-method-for-nonlinear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of Reinforcement Learning Frameworks for Software Testing Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we empirically investigate the applications of carefully selected RL algorithms on two important software testing tasks: test case prioritization in the context of Continuous Integration (CI) and game testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Contrastive Learning for Affect Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-contrastive-learning-for-affect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Affect modeling is viewed, traditionally, as the process of mapping measurable affect manifestations from multiple modalities of user input to affect labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-contrastive-learning-for-affect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ReprGesture entry to the GENEA Challenge 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reprgesture-entry-to-the-genea-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the ReprGesture entry to the Generation and Evaluation of Non-verbal Behaviour for Embodied Agents (GENEA) challenge 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reprgesture-entry-to-the-genea-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pix4Point: Image Pretrained Transformers for 3D Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix4point-image-pretrained-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of 3D point clouds, the availability of large datasets is a challenge, which exacerbates the issue of training Transformers for 3D tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix4point-image-pretrained-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Dimensionality Reduction and Classification with Convolutional Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-dimensionality-reduction-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It turned out that this methodology can also be greatly beneficial in enforcing explainability of deep learning architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-dimensionality-reduction-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Audio-Language Learning for Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-audio-language-learning-for-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore cross-modal learning in an attempt to bridge audio and language in the music domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-audio-language-learning-for-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polarimetric Inverse Rendering for Transparent Shapes Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polarimetric-inverse-rendering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build a polarization dataset for multi-view transparent shapes reconstruction to verify our method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polarimetric-inverse-rendering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven Predictive Tracking Control based on Koopman Operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-predictive-tracking-control-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We seek to combine the nonlinear modeling capabilities of a wide class of neural networks with the safety guarantees of model predictive control (MPC) in a rigorous and online computationally tractable framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-predictive-tracking-control-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders Enable Efficient Knowledge Distillers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-enable-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, by distilling the knowledge from an MAE pre-trained ViT-L into a ViT-B, our method achieves 84. 0% ImageNet top-1 accuracy, outperforming the baseline of directly distilling a fine-tuned ViT-L by 1. 2%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-enable-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Perception Transformer for Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-perception-transformer-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, their multi-stage designs cannot generate action boundaries and categories straightforwardly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-perception-transformer-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards an Awareness of Time Series Anomaly Detection Models' Adversarial Vulnerability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-awareness-of-time-series-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our understanding, we demonstrate, for the first time, the vulnerabilities of anomaly detection systems against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-awareness-of-time-series-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAN-based generative modelling for dermatological applications -- comparative study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gan-based-generative-modelling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of sufficiently large open medical databases is one of the biggest challenges in AI-powered healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gan-based-generative-modelling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Learning Approach Using Masked Image Modeling for Reconstruction of Undersampled K-spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-using-masked-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model was evaluated through L1 loss, gradient normalization, and structural similarity values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-using-masked-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Nearest Convolution for Real-Time Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-nearest-convolution-for-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed nearest convolution has the same performance as the nearest upsampling but is much faster and more suitable for Android NNAPI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-nearest-convolution-for-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCSF: Deep Convolutional Set Functions for Classification of Asynchronous Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcsf-deep-convolutional-set-functions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of the asynchronous nature, they pose a significant challenge to deep learning architectures, which presume that the time series presented to them are regularly sampled, fully observed, and aligned with respect to time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcsf-deep-convolutional-set-functions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-Net: Query-Informed Few-Shot Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-net-query-informed-few-shot-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has achieved tremendous success in computer vision, while medical image segmentation (MIS) remains a challenge, due to the scarcity of data annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-net-query-informed-few-shot-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Design of Privacy-Aware Cameras: a Study on Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-design-of-privacy-aware-cameras-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the same time, we ensure that useful non-sensitive data can still be extracted from distorted images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-design-of-privacy-aware-cameras-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliding Window Recurrent Network for Efficient Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-window-recurrent-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from single image super-resolution, VSR can utilize frames' temporal information to reconstruct results with more details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliding-window-recurrent-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RZSR: Reference-based Zero-Shot Super-Resolution with Depth Guided Self-Exemplars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rzsr-reference-based-zero-shot-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance ZSSR, we obtain reference image patches with rich textures and high-frequency details which are also extracted only from the input image using cross-scale matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rzsr-reference-based-zero-shot-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bayesian Variational principle for dynamic Self Organizing Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-variational-principle-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose organisation conditions that yield a method for training SOM with adaptative neighborhood radius in a variational Bayesian framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-variational-principle-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking by weakly-supervised learning and graph optimization for whole-embryo C. elegans lineages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-by-weakly-supervised-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work specifically addresses the following challenging properties of C. elegans embryo recordings: (1) Many cell divisions as compared to benchmark recordings of other organisms, and (2) the presence of polar bodies that are easily mistaken as cell nuclei.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-by-weakly-supervised-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Filtering: A Noise-Aware Sample Selection for Label Noise with Confidence Penalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-filtering-a-noise-aware-sample-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sample selection is an effective strategy to mitigate the effect of label noise in robust learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-filtering-a-noise-aware-sample-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A novel approach for Fair Principal Component Analysis based on eigendecomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-approach-for-fair-principal-component</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Principal component analysis (PCA), a ubiquitous dimensionality reduction technique in signal processing, searches for a projection matrix that minimizes the mean squared error between the reduced dataset and the original one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-approach-for-fair-principal-component</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applying Eigencontours to PolarMask-Based Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-eigencontours-to-polarmask-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Eigencontours are the first data-driven contour descriptors based on singular value decomposition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applying-eigencontours-to-polarmask-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrestricted Black-box Adversarial Attack Using GAN with Limited Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrestricted-black-box-adversarial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we demonstrate that our targeted attack method is query-efficient to produce unrestricted adversarial examples for a facial identity recognition model that contains 307 identities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrestricted-black-box-adversarial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Hyperspectral and Multispectral Image Fusion with Inter-image Variability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hyperspectral-and-multispectral-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fusion problem is stated as an optimization problem in the maximum a posteriori framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hyperspectral-and-multispectral-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secondary Protein Structure Prediction Using Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-protein-structure-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we test the impact of varying the length of protein sequence we input into the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secondary-protein-structure-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Token Uniformity in Transformers via Singular Value Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-token-uniformity-in-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to use the distribution of singular values of outputs of each transformer layer to characterise the phenomenon of token uniformity and empirically illustrate that a less skewed singular value distribution can alleviate the `token uniformity' problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-token-uniformity-in-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Replay: Scene Graph as Prompt for Continual Learning on VQA Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-replay-scene-graph-as-prompt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, CL on VQA involves not only the expansion of label sets (new Answer sets).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-replay-scene-graph-as-prompt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEG4Students: An Experimental Design for EEG Data Collection and Machine Learning Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg4students-an-experimental-design-for-eeg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, during the COVID-19 pandemic, data collection and analysis could be more challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg4students-an-experimental-design-for-eeg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining phylogeny and coevolution improves the inference of interaction partners among paralogous proteins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-phylogeny-and-coevolution-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that these two signals can be combined to improve the performance of the inference of interaction partners among paralogs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-phylogeny-and-coevolution-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPTDR: Deep Prompt Tuning for Dense Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dptdr-deep-prompt-tuning-for-dense-passage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe this work facilitates the industry, as it saves enormous efforts and costs of deployment and increases the utility of computing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dptdr-deep-prompt-tuning-for-dense-passage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOPv2: Better, Faster, Stronger for Panoptic Driving Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolopv2-better-faster-stronger-for-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the last decade, multi-tasking learning approaches have achieved promising results in solving panoptic driving perception problems, providing both high-precision and high-efficiency performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolopv2-better-faster-stronger-for-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Human Criteria and Automatic Metrics: A Benchmark of the Evaluation of Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-human-criteria-and-automatic-metrics-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there is no consensus on which human evaluation criteria to use, and no analysis of how well automatic criteria correlate with them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/of-human-criteria-and-automatic-metrics-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeRFception: Perception using Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfception-perception-using-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent progress in implicit 3D representation, i. e., Neural Radiance Fields (NeRFs), has made accurate and photorealistic 3D reconstruction possible in a differentiable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfception-perception-using-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Endoscopic Image Key-Points Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-endoscopic-image-key-points</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature matching and finding correspondences between endoscopic images is a key step in many clinical applications such as patient follow-up and generation of panoramic image from clinical sequences for fast anomalies localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-endoscopic-image-key-points</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Likelihood on the Joint (Data, Condition) Distribution for Solving Ill-Posed Problems with Conditional Flow Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-likelihood-on-the-joint-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The utility of this trick is limited for non-conditional models, but an extension of the approach, applied to maximum likelihood of the joint probability distribution of data and conditioning information, can be used to train sophisticated \textit{conditional} flow models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-likelihood-on-the-joint-data</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
