<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:12:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Can Automatically Engineer Features for Few-Shot Tabular Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-automatically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed FeatLLM framework only uses this simple predictive model with the discovered features at inference time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-automatically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If there's a Trigger Warning, then where's the Trigger? Investigating Trigger Warnings at the Passage Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/if-there-s-a-trigger-warning-then-where-s-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trigger warnings are labels that preface documents with sensitive content if this content could be perceived as harmful by certain groups of readers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/if-there-s-a-trigger-warning-then-where-s-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RanLayNet: A Dataset for Document Layout Detection used for Domain Adaptation and Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranlaynet-a-dataset-for-document-layout</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, domain adaptation approaches have been developed that use a small quantity of labeled data to adjust the model to the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ranlaynet-a-dataset-for-document-layout</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-in-one simulation-based inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-simulation-based-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amortized Bayesian inference trains neural networks to solve stochastic inference problems using model simulations, thereby making it possible to rapidly perform Bayesian inference for any newly observed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-simulation-based-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Techniques for Python Source Code Vulnerability Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-techniques-for-python-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Software vulnerabilities are a fundamental reason for the prevalence of cyber attacks and their identification is a crucial yet challenging problem in cyber security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-techniques-for-python-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-KD: Towards Alignment Invariant Face Image Quality Assessment Using Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-kd-towards-alignment-invariant-face-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we present in this paper a novel knowledge distillation approach, termed AI-KD that can extend on any existing FIQA technique, improving its robustness to alignment variations and, in turn, performance with different alignment procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-kd-towards-alignment-invariant-face-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMCode: Evaluating Multi-Modal Code Large Language Models with Visually Rich Programming Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmcode-evaluating-multi-modal-code-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Programming often involves converting detailed and complex specifications into code, a process during which developers typically utilize visual aids to more effectively convey concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmcode-evaluating-multi-modal-code-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtually Enriched NYU Depth V2 Dataset for Monocular Depth Estimation: Do We Need Artificial Augmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtually-enriched-nyu-depth-v2-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ANYU, a new virtually augmented version of the NYU depth v2 dataset, designed for monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtually-enriched-nyu-depth-v2-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CREST: Cross-modal Resonance through Evidential Deep Learning for Enhanced Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crest-cross-modal-resonance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot learning (ZSL) enables the recognition of novel classes by leveraging semantic knowledge transfer from known to unknown categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crest-cross-modal-resonance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Self-feedback Knowledge Elicitation Approach for Chemical Reaction Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-self-feedback-knowledge-elicitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of chemical reaction predictions (CRPs) plays a pivotal role in advancing drug discovery and material science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-self-feedback-knowledge-elicitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyGO: Discrete Modality Information as Fine-Grained Tokens for Multi-modal Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mygo-discrete-modality-information-as-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome their inherent incompleteness, multi-modal knowledge graph completion (MMKGC) aims to discover unobserved knowledge from given MMKGs, leveraging both structural information from the triples and multi-modal information of the entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mygo-discrete-modality-information-as-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Training Network Compression for 3D Medical Image Segmentation: Reducing Computational Efforts via Tucker Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-network-compression-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of Tucker decomposition to the TS model substantially reduced the model parameters and FLOPs across various compression rates, with limited loss in segmentation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-network-compression-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amplitude-Phase Fusion for Enhanced Electrocardiogram Morphological Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplitude-phase-fusion-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the variability of amplitude and phase patterns in electrocardiogram (ECG) signals due to cardiac activity and individual differences, existing entropy-based studies have not fully utilized these two patterns and lack integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplitude-phase-fusion-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AesExpert: Towards Multi-modality Foundation Model for Image Aesthetics Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesexpert-towards-multi-modality-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above challenge, we first introduce a comprehensively annotated Aesthetic Multi-Modality Instruction Tuning (AesMMIT) dataset, which serves as the footstone for building multi-modality aesthetics foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesexpert-towards-multi-modality-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo-Realistic Image Restoration in the Wild with Controlled Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photo-realistic-image-restoration-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though diffusion models have been successfully applied to various image restoration (IR) tasks, their performance is sensitive to the choice of training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photo-realistic-image-restoration-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FSPEN: AN ULTRA-LIGHTWEIGHT NETWORK FOR REAL TIME SPEECH ENAHNCMENT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fspen-an-ultra-lightweight-network-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning-based speech enhancement methods have shown promising result in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fspen-an-ultra-lightweight-network-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plus Strategies are Exponentially Slower for Planted Optima of Random Height</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plus-strategies-are-exponentially-slower-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the $(1,\lambda)$-EA and the $(1 + \lambda)$-EA on the recently introduced benchmark DisOM, which is the OneMax function with randomly planted local optima.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plus-strategies-are-exponentially-slower-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMPCliff: quantitative definition and benchmarking of activity cliffs in antimicrobial peptides</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ampcliff-quantitative-definition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis reveals that these models are capable of detecting AMP AC events and the pre-trained protein language ESM2 model demonstrates superior performance across the evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ampcliff-quantitative-definition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Hallucination in Abstractive Summarization with Domain-Conditional Mutual Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucination-in-abstractive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hypothesize that the domain (or topic) of the source text triggers the model to generate text that is highly probable in the domain, neglecting the details of the source text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-hallucination-in-abstractive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Clothing: Controllable Garment-Driven Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-clothing-controllable-garment-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Magic Clothing, a latent diffusion model (LDM)-based network architecture for an unexplored garment-driven image synthesis task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-clothing-controllable-garment-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Behavior-Specific Context Improves Zero-Shot Generalization in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-behavior-specific-context-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the challenge of zero-shot generalization (ZSG) in Reinforcement Learning (RL), where agents must adapt to entirely novel environments without additional training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-behavior-specific-context-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Space Model for New-Generation Network Alternative to Transformers: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-space-model-for-new-generation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we give the first comprehensive review of these works and also provide experimental comparisons and analysis to better demonstrate the features and advantages of SSM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-space-model-for-new-generation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Vision and Language Spaces with Assignment Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-vision-and-language-spaces-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces VLAP, a novel approach that bridges pretrained vision models and large language models (LLMs) to make frozen LLMs understand the visual world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-vision-and-language-spaces-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prepacking: A Simple Method for Fast Prefilling and Increased Throughput in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prepacking-a-simple-method-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we highlight the following pitfall of prefilling: for batches containing high-varying prompt lengths, significant computation is wasted by the standard practice of padding sequences to the maximum length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prepacking-a-simple-method-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Library of Variational LSE Solvers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-library-of-variational-lse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linear systems of equations can be found in various mathematical domains, as well as in the field of machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-library-of-variational-lse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSAR: Modeling User Transition Behaviors between Search and Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisar-modeling-user-transition-behaviors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework named UniSAR that effectively models the different types of fine-grained behavior transitions for providing users a Unified Search And Recommendation service.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisar-modeling-user-transition-behaviors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCCT-Net: Two-Stream Network Architecture for Fast and Efficient Engagement Estimation via Behavioral Feature Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcct-net-two-stream-network-architecture-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Engagement analysis finds various applications in healthcare, education, advertisement, services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcct-net-two-stream-network-architecture-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equipping Diffusion Models with Differentiable Spatial Entropy for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equipping-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel method that shifts the focus from a deterministic pixel-by-pixel comparison to a statistical perspective, emphasizing the learning of distributions rather than individual pixel values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equipping-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoofDiffusion: Constructing Roofs from Severely Corrupted Point Data via Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roofdiffusion-constructing-roofs-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate completion and denoising of roof height maps are crucial to reconstructing high-quality 3D buildings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roofdiffusion-constructing-roofs-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qandle: Accelerating State Vector Simulation Using Gate-Matrix Caching and Circuit Splitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qandle-accelerating-state-vector-simulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the computational complexity associated with state-vector simulation for quantum circuits, we propose a combination of advanced techniques to accelerate circuit execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qandle-accelerating-state-vector-simulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OWLOOP: Interfaces for Mapping OWL Axioms into OOP Hierarchies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owloop-interfaces-for-mapping-owl-axioms-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The issues of mapping OWL axioms hierarchies and OOP objects hierarchies are due to OWL-based reasoning algorithms, which might change an OWL hierarchy at runtime; instead, OOP hierarchies are usually defined as static structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owloop-interfaces-for-mapping-owl-axioms-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEGNN: Dual Experts Graph Neural Network Handling Both Edge and Node Feature Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degnn-dual-experts-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging these modified representations, DEGNN subsequently addresses downstream tasks, ensuring robustness against noise present in both edges and node features of real-world graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degnn-dual-experts-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RF-Diffusion: Radio Signal Generation via Time-Frequency Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rf-diffusion-radio-signal-generation-via-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, inspired by the stellar achievements of the diffusion model in CV and NLP, we adapt it to the RF domain and propose RF-Diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rf-diffusion-radio-signal-generation-via-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRS-NeRF: Visual Relocalization with Sparse Neural Radiance Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrs-nerf-visual-relocalization-with-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in spite of high efficiency, APRs and SCRs have limited accuracy especially in large-scale outdoor scenes; HMs are accurate but need to store a large number of 2D descriptors for matching, resulting in poor efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrs-nerf-visual-relocalization-with-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StreakNet-Arch: An Anti-scattering Network-based Architecture for Underwater Carrier LiDAR-Radar Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaknet-arch-an-anti-scattering-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce StreakNet-Arch, a novel signal processing architecture designed for Underwater Carrier LiDAR-Radar (UCLR) imaging systems, to address the limitations in scatter suppression and real-time imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streaknet-arch-an-anti-scattering-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Generative AI Agents for Satellite Networks through a Mixture of Experts Transmission</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-generative-ai-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the superiority of the proposed MoE-ppo approach over other benchmarks is confirmed in solving the formulated problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-generative-ai-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-Driven Exploration: Decoupling and Inter-Task Feedback for Joint Moment Retrieval and Highlight Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-driven-exploration-decoupling-and-inter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video moment retrieval and highlight detection are two highly valuable tasks in video understanding, but until recently they have been jointly studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-driven-exploration-decoupling-and-inter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundational GPT Model for MEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundational-gpt-model-for-meg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the performance of these deep learning models with standard linear autoregressive (AR) modelling on MEG data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundational-gpt-model-for-meg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Bytes to Borsch: Fine-Tuning Gemma and Mistral for the Ukrainian Language Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-bytes-to-borsch-fine-tuning-gemma-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our research not only advances the field of NLP but also highlights the importance of linguistic diversity in AI, which is crucial for cultural preservation, education, and expanding AI's global utility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-bytes-to-borsch-fine-tuning-gemma-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TLDR at SemEval-2024 Task 2: T5-generated clinical-Language summaries for DeBERTa Report Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tldr-at-semeval-2024-task-2-t5-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces novel methodologies for the Natural Language Inference for Clinical Trials (NLI4CT) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tldr-at-semeval-2024-task-2-t5-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Guiding Network: Incorporating Change Prior to Guide Change Detection in Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-guiding-network-incorporating-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of automated artificial intelligence algorithms and remote sensing instruments has benefited change detection (CD) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-guiding-network-incorporating-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANet: A Hierarchical Attention Network for Change Detection With Bitemporal Very-High-Resolution Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hanet-a-hierarchical-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from the developments in deep learning technology, deep-learning-based algorithms employing automatic feature extraction have achieved remarkable performance on the change detection (CD) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hanet-a-hierarchical-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrafficVLM: A Controllable Visual Language Model for Traffic Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trafficvlm-a-controllable-visual-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic video description and analysis have received much attention recently due to the growing demand for efficient and reliable urban surveillance systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trafficvlm-a-controllable-visual-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextHawk: Exploring Efficient Fine-Grained Perception of Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texthawk-exploring-efficient-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments on both general and document-oriented MLLM benchmarks, and show that TextHawk outperforms the state-of-the-art methods, demonstrating its effectiveness and superiority in fine-grained document perception and general abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texthawk-exploring-efficient-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Spatiotemporal Network for Online Eye Tracking with Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-spatiotemporal-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-based data are commonly encountered in edge computing environments where efficiency and low latency are critical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-spatiotemporal-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaSkel: A Model for Human Whole-body X-rays Generation from Human Masking Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskel-a-model-for-human-whole-body-x-rays</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, We proposed a new method to directly generate the 2D human whole-body X-rays from the human masking images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskel-a-model-for-human-whole-body-x-rays</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Misinformation Resilient Search Rankings with Webgraph-based Interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misinformation-resilient-search-rankings-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of unreliable news domains on the internet has had wide-reaching negative impacts on society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misinformation-resilient-search-rankings-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeDoDe v2: Analyzing and Improving the DeDoDe Keypoint Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dedode-v2-analyzing-and-improving-the-dedode</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we find that DeDoDe keypoints tend to cluster together, which we fix by performing non-max suppression on the target distribution of the detector during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dedode-v2-analyzing-and-improving-the-dedode</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Cross-Document Event Coreference Resolution Using Linear Semantic Transfer and Mixed-Modality Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-cross-document-event-coreference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We establish three methods that incorporate images and text for coreference: 1) a standard fused model with finetuning, 2) a novel linear mapping method without finetuning and 3) an ensembling approach based on splitting mention pairs by semantic and discourse-level difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-cross-document-event-coreference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EIVEN: Efficient Implicit Attribute Value Extraction using Multimodal LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiven-efficient-implicit-attribute-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we introduce EIVEN, a data- and parameter-efficient generative framework that pioneers the use of multimodal LLM for implicit attribute value extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiven-efficient-implicit-attribute-value</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
