<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 09:12:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Inspired Facial Sketch Synthesis with Dynamic Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-inspired-facial-sketch-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, different artists may use diverse drawing techniques and create multiple styles of sketches; but the style is globally consistent in a sketch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-inspired-facial-sketch-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseSat-NeRF: Dense Depth Supervised Neural Radiance Fields for Sparse Satellite Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsesat-nerf-dense-depth-supervised-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, NeRF and its variants require many views to produce convincing scene's geometries which in earth observation satellite imaging is rare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsesat-nerf-dense-depth-supervised-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patent image retrieval using transformer-based deep metric learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intellectual property work covers a wide range of areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patent-image-retrieval-using-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Theoretical and Practical Framework for Evaluating Uncertainty Calibration in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-and-practical-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of Deep Neural Networks has resulted in machine learning systems becoming increasingly more present in various real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretical-and-practical-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLdepth: Generalizable Self-Supervised Fine-Structured Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqldepth-generalizable-self-supervised-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each individual slice of the volume signifies the relative distances between points and objects within a latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqldepth-generalizable-self-supervised-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple transformation function estimation for image enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-transformation-function-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we develop a histogram-based multiple transformation function estimation network (HMTF-Net) to estimate multiple transformation functions by exploiting both the spatial and statistical information of the input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-transformation-function-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copiloting the Copilots: Fusing Large Language Models with Completion Engines for Automated Program Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copiloting-the-copilots-fusing-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose Repilot, a framework to further copilot the AI "copilots" (i. e., LLMs) by synthesizing more valid patches during the repair process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copiloting-the-copilots-fusing-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-based NLOS Detection and Uncertainty Prediction of GNSS Observations with Transformer-Enhanced LSTM Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-nlos-detection-and-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a Deep-Learning-based method to detect NLOS receptions and predict GNSS pseudorange errors by analyzing GNSS observations as a spatio-temporal modeling problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-nlos-detection-and-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-Bind &amp; Point-LLM: Aligning Point Cloud with Multi-modality for 3D Understanding, Generation, and Instruction Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-bind-point-llm-aligning-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Point-Bind, a 3D multi-modality model aligning point clouds with 2D image, language, audio, and video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-bind-point-llm-aligning-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Active Learning for Preference Elicitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-active-learning-for-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement the proposed preference elicitation methodology for food recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-active-learning-for-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffuGen: Adaptable Approach for Generating Labeled Image Datasets using Stable Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffugen-adaptable-approach-for-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating high-quality labeled image datasets is crucial for training accurate and robust machine learning models in the field of computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffugen-adaptable-approach-for-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Morphological Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-morphological-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A DMNN architecture, which is represented by a Morphological Computational Graph, is designed as in the classical heuristic design of morphological operators, in which the designer should combine a set of MM operators and Boolean operations based on prior information and theoretical knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-morphological-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Text-based Approach For Link Prediction on Wikipedia Articles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-approach-for-link-prediction-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper present our work in the DSAA 2023 Challenge about Link Prediction for Wikipedia Articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-text-based-approach-for-link-prediction-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JoTR: A Joint Transformer and Reinforcement Learning Framework for Dialog Policy Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jotr-a-joint-transformer-and-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, JoTR employs reinforcement learning with a reward-shaping mechanism to efficiently finetune the word-level dialogue policy, which allows the model to learn from its interactions, improving its performance over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jotr-a-joint-transformer-and-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeMig -- A Bilingual News Collection and Knowledge Graph about Migration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemig-a-bilingual-news-collection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[News recommendation plays a critical role in shaping the public's worldviews through the way in which it filters and disseminates information about different topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nemig-a-bilingual-news-collection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publicly Shareable Clinical Large Language Model Built on Synthetic Clinical Notes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/publicly-shareable-clinical-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of large language models tailored for handling patients' clinical notes is often hindered by the limited accessibility and usability of these notes due to strict privacy regulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/publicly-shareable-clinical-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-fidelity reduced-order surrogate modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-fidelity-reduced-order-surrogate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-fidelity numerical simulations of partial differential equations (PDEs) given a restricted computational budget can significantly limit the number of parameter configurations considered and/or time window evaluated for modeling a given system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-fidelity-reduced-order-surrogate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroSurgeon: A Toolkit for Subnetwork Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosurgeon-a-toolkit-for-subnetwork</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in the field of explainability, much remains unknown about the algorithms that neural networks learn to represent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurosurgeon-a-toolkit-for-subnetwork</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FederatedScope-LLM: A Comprehensive Package for Fine-tuning Large Language Models in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federatedscope-llm-a-comprehensive-package</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When several entities have similar interested tasks, but their data cannot be shared because of privacy concerns regulations, federated learning (FL) is a mainstream solution to leverage the data of different entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federatedscope-llm-a-comprehensive-package</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Locality-based Neural Solver for Optical Motion Capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-locality-based-neural-solver-for-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a training regime based on representation learning and data augmentation, by training the model on data with masking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-locality-based-neural-solver-for-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multi-View Graph Clustering with Local and Global Structure Preservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-view-graph-clustering-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anchor-based multi-view graph clustering (AMVGC) has received abundant attention owing to its high efficiency and the capability to capture complementary structural information across multiple views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-view-graph-clustering-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised CT Metal Artifact Reduction by Plugging Diffusion Priors in Dual Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-ct-metal-artifact-reduction-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised MAR method based on the diffusion model, a generative model with a high capacity to represent data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-ct-metal-artifact-reduction-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything, Everywhere All in One Evaluation: Using Multiverse Analysis to Evaluate the Influence of Model Design Decisions on Algorithmic Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everything-everywhere-all-in-one-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is therefore important to make explicit the decisions made during the design of ADM systems and understand how these decisions affect the fairness of the resulting system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everything-everywhere-all-in-one-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Gradient Regularizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-gradient-regularizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NGR is applicable to various image types and different image processing tasks, functioning in a zero-shot learning fashion, making it a versatile and plug-and-play regularizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-gradient-regularizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointLLM: Empowering Large Language Models to Understand Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointllm-empowering-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The unprecedented advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have created a profound impact on natural language processing but are yet to fully embrace the realm of 3D understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointllm-empowering-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Lens Flare Removal with General Purpose Pipeline and Multiple Light Sources Recovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lens-flare-removal-with-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a solution to improve the performance of lens flare removal by revisiting the ISP and remodeling the principle of automatic exposure in the synthesis pipeline and design a more reliable light sources recovery strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-lens-flare-removal-with-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illumination Distillation Framework for Nighttime Person Re-Identification and A New Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-distillation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The illumination enhancement branch first estimates an enhanced image from the nighttime image using a nonlinear curve mapping method and then extracts the enhanced features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illumination-distillation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-STMN: Dependency-Driven Superpoint-Text Matching Network for End-to-End 3D Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-stmn-dependency-driven-superpoint-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In 3D Referring Expression Segmentation (3D-RES), the earlier approach adopts a two-stage paradigm, extracting segmentation proposals and then matching them with referring expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-stmn-dependency-driven-superpoint-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Optimal Patch Size in Vision Transformers for Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-optimal-patch-size-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although transformers can capture long-range features, their segmentation performance decreases with various tumor sizes due to the model sensitivity to the input patch size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-optimal-patch-size-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YaRN: Efficient Context Window Extension of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yarn-efficient-context-window-extension-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rotary Position Embeddings (RoPE) have been shown to effectively encode positional information in transformer-based language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yarn-efficient-context-window-extension-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScrollNet: Dynamic Weight Importance for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrollnet-dynamic-weight-importance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The importance of weights for each task can be determined either explicitly through learning a task-specific mask during training (e. g., parameter isolation-based approaches) or implicitly by introducing a regularization term (e. g., regularization-based approaches).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scrollnet-dynamic-weight-importance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Energy-Aware Approach to Design Self-Adaptive AI-based Applications on the Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-energy-aware-approach-to-design-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an energy-aware approach for the design and deployment of self-adaptive AI-based applications that can balance application objectives (e. g., accuracy in object detection and frames processing rate) with energy consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-energy-aware-approach-to-design-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RepCodec: A Speech Representation Codec for Speech Tokenization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repcodec-a-speech-representation-codec-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the performance of these discrete speech tokens, we present RepCodec, a novel speech representation codec for semantic speech tokenization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repcodec-a-speech-representation-codec-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Prediction of Antibody Function and Structure Using Bio-Inspired Antibody Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-prediction-of-antibody-function-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, BALMFold outperforms those well-established methods like AlphaFold2, IgFold, ESMFold, and OmegaFold in the antibody benchmark, demonstrating significant potential to advance innovative engineering and streamline therapeutic antibody development by reducing the need for unnecessary trials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-prediction-of-antibody-function-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechTokenizer: Unified Speech Tokenizer for Speech Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechtokenizer-unified-speech-tokenizer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose SpeechTokenizer, a unified speech tokenizer for speech large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechtokenizer-unified-speech-tokenizer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Diagnosis of Chest x-rays Using an Ensemble of Random Discriminative Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-diagnosis-of-chest-x-rays-using-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the scarcity of annotated data in the medical domain, few-shot learning may be useful for medical image analysis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-diagnosis-of-chest-x-rays-using-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sequential Framework for Detection and Classification of Abnormal Teeth in Panoramic X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sequential-framework-for-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, we employed a Faster-RCNN model for detecting and identifying teeth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sequential-framework-for-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-adaptive Message Passing Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-message-passing-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-network node classification (CNNC), which aims to classify nodes in a label-deficient target network by transferring the knowledge from a source network with abundant labels, draws increasing attention recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-message-passing-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Incomplete Multi-View Clustering with Structure Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although several anchor-based IMVC methods have been proposed to process the large-scale incomplete data, they still suffer from the following drawbacks: i) Most existing approaches neglect the inter-view discrepancy and enforce cross-view representation to be consistent, which would corrupt the representation capability of the model; ii) Due to the samples disparity between different views, the learned anchor might be misaligned, which we referred as the Anchor-Unaligned Problem for Incomplete data (AUP-ID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Power of MEME: Adversarial Malware Creation with Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-meme-adversarial-malware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, machine learning models are susceptible to adversarial attacks, requiring the testing of model and product robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-power-of-meme-adversarial-malware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-Varying Quasi-Closed-Phase Analysis for Accurate Formant Tracking in Speech Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-varying-quasi-closed-phase-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Formant tracking experiments with a wide variety of synthetic and natural speech signals show that the proposed TVQCP method performs better than conventional and popular formant tracking tools, such as Wavesurfer and Praat (based on dynamic programming), the KARMA algorithm (based on Kalman filtering), and DeepFormants (based on deep neural networks trained in a supervised manner).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-varying-quasi-closed-phase-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Semantic Segmentation: Consistency over Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-semantic-segmentation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate medical image segmentation is of utmost importance for enabling automated clinical decision procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-semantic-segmentation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CktGNN: Circuit Graph Neural Network for Electronic Design Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cktgnn-circuit-graph-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The electronic design automation of analog circuits has been a longstanding challenge in the integrated circuit field due to the huge design space and complex design trade-offs among circuit specifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cktgnn-circuit-graph-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhonMatchNet: Phoneme-Guided Zero-Shot Keyword Spotting for User-Defined Keywords</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phonmatchnet-phoneme-guided-zero-shot-keyword</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a novel zero-shot user-defined keyword spotting model that utilizes the audio-phoneme relationship of the keyword to improve performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phonmatchnet-phoneme-guided-zero-shot-keyword</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM in the Shell: Generative Honeypots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-in-the-shell-generative-honeypots</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Honeypots are essential tools in cybersecurity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-in-the-shell-generative-honeypots</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGB-T Tracking via Multi-Modal Mutual Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-tracking-via-multi-modal-mutual-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object tracking based on the fusion of visible and thermal im-ages, known as RGB-T tracking, has gained increasing atten-tion from researchers in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgb-t-tracking-via-multi-modal-mutual-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Njobvu-AI: An open-source tool for collaborative image labeling and implementation of computer vision models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/njobvu-ai-an-open-source-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This step is often not compatible with many cloud-based services for marking or labeling image and video data due to limited internet bandwidth in many regions of the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/njobvu-ai-an-open-source-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNFactor: Multi-Task Real Robot Learning with Generalizable Neural Feature Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnfactor-multi-task-real-robot-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To incorporate semantics in 3D, the reconstruction module utilizes a vision-language foundation model ($\textit{e. g.}$, Stable Diffusion) to distill rich semantic information into the deep 3D voxel.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnfactor-multi-task-real-robot-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterDiff: Generating 3D Human-Object Interactions with Physics-Informed Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interdiff-generating-3d-human-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses a novel task of anticipating 3D human-object interactions (HOIs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interdiff-generating-3d-human-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank Collapse Causes Over-Smoothing and Over-Correlation in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-collapse-causes-over-smoothing-and-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study reveals new theoretical insights into over-smoothing and feature over-correlation in deep graph neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-collapse-causes-over-smoothing-and-over</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
