<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:13:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Health Index Estimation Through Integration of General Knowledge with Unsupervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/health-index-estimation-through-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hybrid models combining prior knowledge about degradation with deep learning models have been proposed to overcome this challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/health-index-estimation-through-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenESS: Event-based Semantic Scene Understanding with Open Vocabularies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openess-event-based-semantic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-based semantic segmentation (ESS) is a fundamental yet challenging task for event camera sensing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openess-event-based-semantic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian Attribute Recognition as Label-balanced Multi-label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-attribute-recognition-as-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rooting in the scarcity of most attributes, realistic pedestrian attribute datasets exhibit unduly skewed data distribution, from which two types of model failures are delivered: (1) label imbalance: model predictions lean greatly towards the side of majority labels; (2) semantics imbalance: model is easily overfitted on the under-represented attributes due to their insufficient semantic diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-attribute-recognition-as-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Data-Efficient 3D Scene Understanding for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-data-efficient-3d-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient data utilization is crucial for advancing 3D scene understanding in autonomous driving, where reliance on heavily human-annotated LiDAR point clouds challenges fully supervised methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-data-efficient-3d-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sparse Tensor Generator with Efficient Feature Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sparse-tensor-generator-with-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse tensor operations are gaining attention in emerging applications such as social networks, deep learning, diagnosis, crime, and review analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sparse-tensor-generator-with-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILCodec: High Fidelity and Lightweight Neural Audio Codec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hilcodec-high-fidelity-and-lightweight-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advancement of end-to-end neural audio codecs enables compressing audio at very low bitrates while reconstructing the output audio with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hilcodec-high-fidelity-and-lightweight-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Power of MLLMs for Transferable Text-to-Image Person ReID</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-mllms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose a novel method that uses MLLMs to caption images according to various templates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-mllms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinePOSE: Fine-Grained Prompt-Driven 3D Human Pose Estimation via Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finepose-fine-grained-prompt-driven-3d-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further extend FinePOSE to multi-human pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finepose-fine-grained-prompt-driven-3d-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMatch: Visual-Language Guidance Makes Better Semi-supervised Change Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmatch-visual-language-guidance-makes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we first propose a VLM-based mixed change event generation (CEG) strategy to yield pseudo labels for unlabeled CD data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmatch-visual-language-guidance-makes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Place Recognition Survey: Towards Real-World Autonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-place-recognition-survey-towards-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude with a discussion on PR's future directions, accompanied by a summary of the literature covered and access to our open-source library, available to the robotics community at: https://github. com/MetaSLAM/GPRS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-place-recognition-survey-towards-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVA-X: A Foundation Model for General Chest X-ray Analysis with Self-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-x-a-foundation-model-for-general-chest-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diagnosis and treatment of chest diseases play a crucial role in maintaining human health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-x-a-foundation-model-for-general-chest-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Motion Detection Using Dynamic Mode Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-motion-detection-using-dynamic-mode</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic Mode Decomposition (DMD) is a numerical method that seeks to fit timeseries data to a linear dynamical system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-motion-detection-using-dynamic-mode</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication-Efficient Collaborative Perception via Information Filling with Codebook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-collaborative-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It inherently results in a fundamental trade-off between perception ability and communication cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-collaborative-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecule-Space: Free Lunch in Unified Multimodal Space via Knowledge Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecule-space-free-lunch-in-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unified multi-model representation spaces are the foundation of multimodal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecule-space-free-lunch-in-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDD Challenge 2024: A Singing Voice Deepfake Detection Challenge Evaluation Plan</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdd-challenge-2024-a-singing-voice-deepfake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of AI-generated singing voices, which now closely mimic natural human singing and align seamlessly with musical scores, has led to heightened concerns for artists and the music industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdd-challenge-2024-a-singing-voice-deepfake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Language Models Can Provide Feedback: Evaluating LLMs' Ability to Help Students Using GPT-4-As-A-Judge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-language-models-can-provide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by recent work that has utilised very powerful LLMs, such as GPT-4, to evaluate the outputs produced by less powerful models, we conduct an automated analysis of the quality of the feedback produced by several open source models using a dataset from an introductory programming course.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-language-models-can-provide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Entropy Enigma: Success and Failure of Entropy Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-entropy-enigma-success-and-failure-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After many steps of optimization, EM makes the model embed test images far away from the embeddings of training images, which results in a degradation of accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-entropy-enigma-success-and-failure-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HMANet: Hybrid Multi-Axis Aggregation Network for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmanet-hybrid-multi-axis-aggregation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the super-resolution task in the training phase, a novel pre-training method is designed to enhance the model representation capabilities further and validate the proposed model's effectiveness through many experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hmanet-hybrid-multi-axis-aggregation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Training and Evaluation of Robust Models against $l_0$ Bounded Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-training-and-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we combine sparse-PGD with a black-box attack to comprehensively and more reliably evaluate the models' robustness against $l_0$ bounded adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-training-and-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisionGraph: Leveraging Large Multimodal Models for Graph Theory Problems in Visual Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visiongraph-leveraging-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) have achieved impressive success in visual understanding and reasoning, remarkably improving the performance of mathematical reasoning in a visual context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visiongraph-leveraging-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DALK: Dynamic Co-Augmentation of LLMs and KG to answer Alzheimer's Disease Questions with Scientific Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dalk-dynamic-co-augmentation-of-llms-and-kg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a synergized framework of LLM and KG mutually enhancing each other, we first leverage LLM to construct an evolving AD-specific knowledge graph (KG) sourced from AD-related scientific literature, and then we utilize a coarse-to-fine sampling method with a novel self-aware knowledge retrieval approach to select appropriate knowledge from the KG to augment LLM inference capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dalk-dynamic-co-augmentation-of-llms-and-kg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Bottleneck Transformer for Weakly Supervised Multimodal Violence Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-bottleneck-transformer-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the pursuit of effective multimodal violence detection (MVD), information redundancy, modality imbalance, and modality asynchrony are identified as three key challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-bottleneck-transformer-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How does GPT-2 Predict Acronyms? Extracting and Understanding a Circuit via Mechanistic Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-gpt-2-predict-acronyms-extracting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discover that the prediction is performed by a circuit composed of 8 attention heads (~5% of the total heads) which we classified in three groups according to their role.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-gpt-2-predict-acronyms-extracting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granite Code Models: A Family of Open Foundation Models for Code Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-code-models-a-family-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Increasingly, code LLMs are being integrated into software development environments to improve the productivity of human programmers, and LLM-based agents are beginning to show promise for handling complex tasks autonomously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granite-code-models-a-family-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing the Efficiency and Accuracy of Underlying Asset Reviews in Structured Finance: The Application of Multi-agent Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-efficiency-and-accuracy-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Structured finance, which involves restructuring diverse assets into securities like MBS, ABS, and CDOs, enhances capital market efficiency but presents significant due diligence challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-efficiency-and-accuracy-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocRes: A Generalist Model Toward Unifying Document Image Restoration Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docres-a-generalist-model-toward-unifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This underscores the potential of DocRes across a broader spectrum of document image restoration tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docres-a-generalist-model-toward-unifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Learning with a Language Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-learning-with-a-language-bottleneck</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern AI systems such as self-driving cars and game-playing agents achieve superhuman performance, but often lack human-like features such as generalization, interpretability and human inter-operability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-learning-with-a-language-bottleneck</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acceleration Algorithms in GNNs: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acceleration-algorithms-in-gnns-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the critical challenges, a range of algorithms have been proposed to accelerate training and inference of GNNs, attracting increasing attention from the research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acceleration-algorithms-in-gnns-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba: A Comprehensive Survey and Taxonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-a-comprehensive-survey-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of deep learning, state space models are used to process sequence data, such as time series analysis, natural language processing (NLP) and video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-a-comprehensive-survey-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Feature Vectors from Phonetic Transcriptions in Cross-Linguistic Data Formats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-feature-vectors-from-phonetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When comparing speech sounds across languages, scholars often make use of feature representations of individual sounds in order to determine fine-grained sound similarities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-feature-vectors-from-phonetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CleanGraph: Human-in-the-loop Knowledge Graph Refinement and Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleangraph-human-in-the-loop-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CleanGraph allows users to perform Create, Read, Update, and Delete (CRUD) operations on their graphs, as well as apply models in the form of plugins for graph refinement and completion tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleangraph-human-in-the-loop-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRACTAL: An Ultra-Large-Scale Aerial Lidar Dataset for 3D Semantic Segmentation of Diverse Landscapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fractal-an-ultra-large-scale-aerial-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this data gap, we present the FRench ALS Clouds from TArgeted Landscapes (FRACTAL) dataset: an ultra-large-scale aerial Lidar dataset made of 100, 000 dense point clouds with high-quality labels for 7 semantic classes and spanning 250 km$^2$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fractal-an-ultra-large-scale-aerial-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structured Click Control in Transformer-based Interactive Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-click-control-in-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then the graph nodes will be aggregated to obtain structured interaction features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structured-click-control-in-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMU-Aided Event-based Stereo Visual Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imu-aided-event-based-stereo-visual-odometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we improve our previous direct pipeline \textit{Event-based Stereo Visual Odometry} in terms of accuracy and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imu-aided-event-based-stereo-visual-odometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEDVOC: Vocabulary Adaptation for Fine-tuning Pre-trained Language Models on Medical Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medvoc-vocabulary-adaptation-for-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to existing domain adaptation approaches in summarization, MEDVOC treats vocabulary as an optimizable parameter and optimizes the PLM vocabulary based on fragment score conditioned only on the downstream task's reference summaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medvoc-vocabulary-adaptation-for-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QServe: W4A8KV4 Quantization and System Co-design for Efficient LLM Serving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qserve-w4a8kv4-quantization-and-system-co</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key insight driving QServe is that the efficiency of LLM serving on GPUs is critically influenced by operations on low-throughput CUDA cores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qserve-w4a8kv4-quantization-and-system-co</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Linear Block Error Correction Codes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-linear-block-error-correction-codes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose for the first time a unified encoder-decoder training of binary linear block codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-linear-block-error-correction-codes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LTLDoG: Satisfying Temporally-Extended Symbolic Constraints for Safe Diffusion-based Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltldog-satisfying-temporally-extended</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Operating effectively in complex environments while complying with specified constraints is crucial for the safe and successful deployment of robots that interact with and operate around people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ltldog-satisfying-temporally-extended</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-V2: A Strong, Economical, and Efficient Mixture-of-Experts Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-v2-a-strong-economical-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLA guarantees efficient inference through significantly compressing the Key-Value (KV) cache into a latent vector, while DeepSeekMoE enables training strong models at an economical cost through sparse computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-v2-a-strong-economical-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Sharpness-aware Minimization for Molecular Graph Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sharpness-aware-minimization-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharpness-aware minimization (SAM) has received increasing attention in computer vision since it can effectively eliminate the sharp local minima from the training trajectory and mitigate generalization degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-sharpness-aware-minimization-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting character-level adversarial attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-character-level-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial attacks in Natural Language Processing apply perturbations in the character or token levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-character-level-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Post-Processing for Fair Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-post-processing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a differentially private post-processing algorithm for learning fair regressors satisfying statistical parity, addressing privacy concerns of machine learning models trained on sensitive data, as well as fairness concerns of their potential to propagate historical biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-post-processing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextualization with SPLADE for High Recall Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualization-with-splade-for-high-recall</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High Recall Retrieval (HRR), such as eDiscovery and medical systematic review, is a search problem that optimizes the cost of retrieving most relevant documents in a given collection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualization-with-splade-for-high-recall</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Chemical Space with Latent Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-chemical-space-with-latent-flows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new framework, ChemFlow, to traverse chemical space through navigating the latent space learned by molecule generative models through flows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-chemical-space-with-latent-flows</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Exact Retrieval for Nearest-neighbor Lookup (FERN)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-exact-retrieval-for-nearest-neighbor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately the algorithm deteriorates rapidly to a $O(dN)$ solution at high dimensions (e. g. $k=128$), in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-exact-retrieval-for-nearest-neighbor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACEGEN: Reinforcement learning of generative chemical agents for drug discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acegen-reinforcement-learning-of-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, reinforcement learning (RL) has emerged as a valuable tool in drug design, offering the potential to propose and optimize molecules with desired properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acegen-reinforcement-learning-of-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning To See But Forgetting To Follow: Visual Instruction Tuning Makes LLMs More Prone To Jailbreak Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-see-but-forgetting-to-follow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Augmenting Large Language Models (LLMs) with image-understanding capabilities has resulted in a boom of high-performing Vision-Language models (VLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-see-but-forgetting-to-follow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning of Daily Movement Data Using Text Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-of-daily-movement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-series representation learning is a key area of research for remote healthcare monitoring applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-of-daily-movement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Adversarial Autoencoders for the design of Plasmonic Metasurfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-adversarial-autoencoders-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An example of this is the design of photonic metasurfaces by using their photoluminescent spectrum as the input data to predict their topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-adversarial-autoencoders-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Speech Sentiment Analysis in Chinese Psychological Support Hotlines Based on Large-scale Pre-trained Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-speech-sentiment-analysis-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the high demand for psychological interventions often results in a shortage of professional operators, highlighting the need for an effective speech emotion recognition model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-speech-sentiment-analysis-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
