<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 21:08:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>QUILL: Quotation Generation Enhancement of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quill-quotation-generation-enhancement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the LLMs' quotation generation abilities, we construct a bilingual knowledge base that is broad in scope and rich in dimensions, containing up to 32, 022 quotes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quill-quotation-generation-enhancement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconsidering the Performance of GAE in Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconsidering-the-performance-of-gae-in-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various graph neural networks (GNNs) with advanced training techniques and model designs have been proposed for link prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconsidering-the-performance-of-gae-in-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLORA: Efficient Exemplar Subset Selection for Complex Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explora-efficient-exemplar-subset-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Answering reasoning-based complex questions over text and hybrid sources, including tables, is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explora-efficient-exemplar-subset-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMNCutter: Affinity-Attention-Guided Multi-View Normalized Cutter for Unsupervised Surgical Instrument Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amncutter-affinity-attention-guided-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent unsupervised surgical instrument segmentation (USIS) methods primarily rely on pseudo-labels derived from low-level features such as color and optical flow, but these methods show limited effectiveness and generalizability in complex and unseen endoscopic scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amncutter-affinity-attention-guided-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Defenses Against Gradient Reconstruction Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-defenses-against-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) is designed to prevent data leakage through collaborative model training without centralized data storage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-defenses-against-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the challenge of AI value alignment with multiple individuals that have different reward functions and optimal policies in an underlying Markov decision process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Consistent Gaussian Splatting with Matching Prior for Few-shot Novel View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-consistent-gaussian-splatting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose SCGaussian, a Structure Consistent Gaussian Splatting method using matching priors to learn 3D consistent scene structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-consistent-gaussian-splatting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaVL: Discovering and Mitigating Spurious Correlations in Fine-Tuned Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ravl-discovering-and-mitigating-spurious</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuned vision-language models (VLMs) often capture spurious correlations between image features and textual attributes, resulting in degraded zero-shot performance at test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ravl-discovering-and-mitigating-spurious</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalize or Detect? Towards Robust Semantic Segmentation Under Multiple Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalize-or-detect-towards-robust-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the effectiveness of our method across benchmarks featuring both semantic and domain shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalize-or-detect-towards-robust-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCP-Fusion: A Neural Implicit SLAM with Enhanced Local Constraints and Computable Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcp-fusion-a-neural-implicit-slam-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present LCP-Fusion, a neural implicit SLAM system with enhanced local constraints and computable prior, which takes the sparse voxel octree structure containing feature grids and SDF priors as hybrid scene representation, enabling the scalability and robustness during mapping and tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcp-fusion-a-neural-implicit-slam-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Moral Beliefs across LLMs through a Pluralistic Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-moral-beliefs-across-llms-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, through moral debates, we investigate the firmness of these models to their moral choices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-moral-beliefs-across-llms-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Collaborative Content Moderation Framework for Toxicity Detection based on Conformalized Estimates of Annotation Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-collaborative-content-moderation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Content moderation typically combines the efforts of human moderators and machine learning models. However, these systems often rely on data where significant disagreement occurs during moderation, reflecting the subjective nature of toxicity perception. Rather than dismissing this disagreement as noise, we interpret it as a valuable signal that highlights the inherent ambiguity of the content, an insight missed when only the majority label is considered. In this work, we introduce a novel content moderation framework that emphasizes the importance of capturing annotation disagreement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-collaborative-content-moderation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Fourier Filtering Network with Contrastive Learning for UAV-based Unaligned Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fourier-filtering-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the UAV RGB-T 2400 and three weakly aligned datasets demonstrate that AlignSal achieves both real-time inference speed and better performance and generalizability compared to sixteen state-of-the-art BSOD models across most evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fourier-filtering-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaSociety: An Adaptive Environment with Social Structures for Multi-Agent Decision-Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adasociety-an-adaptive-environment-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As agents progress, the environment adaptively generates new tasks with social structures for agents to undertake.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adasociety-an-adaptive-environment-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi3Hate: Multimodal, Multilingual, and Multicultural Hate Speech Detection with Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi3hate-multimodal-multilingual-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To investigate this, we create the first multimodal and multilingual parallel hate speech dataset, annotated by a multicultural set of annotators, called Multi3Hate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi3hate-multimodal-multilingual-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBIN: Robust and Invisible Watermarks for Diffusion Models with Adversarial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robin-robust-and-invisible-watermarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They empirically inject a watermark that is both invisible and robust and passively achieve concealment by limiting the strength of the watermark, thus reducing the robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robin-robust-and-invisible-watermarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexicalization Is All You Need: Examining the Impact of Lexical Knowledge in a Compositional QALD System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicalization-is-all-you-need-examining-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue in this paper that lexicalization, that is explicit knowledge about the potential interpretations of a word with respect to the given vocabulary, significantly eases the task and increases the performance of QA systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicalization-is-all-you-need-examining-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-labeling with Keyword Refining for Few-Supervised Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-with-keyword-refining-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the former employs the repetition penalized sampling to encourage the model to yield concise pseudo-labeled sentences with less repetition, and selects the most relevant sentences upon a pretrained video-text model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-with-keyword-refining-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEG: Medical Knowledge-Augmented Large Language Models for Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meg-medical-knowledge-augmented-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our method on four popular medical multiple-choice datasets and show that LLMs greatly benefit from the factual grounding provided by knowledge graph embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meg-medical-knowledge-augmented-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number Cookbook: Number Understanding of Language Models and How to Improve It</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/number-cookbook-number-understanding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also finetune practical-scale LLMs on our proposed NUPA tasks and find that 1) naive finetuning can improve NUPA a lot on many but not all tasks, and 2) surprisingly, techniques designed to enhance NUPA prove ineffective for finetuning pretrained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/number-cookbook-number-understanding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Model Adaptation at Test Time: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-model-adaptation-at-test-time-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithms have achieved remarkable success across various disciplines, use cases and applications, under the prevailing assumption that training and test samples are drawn from the same distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-model-adaptation-at-test-time-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touchstone Benchmark: Are We on the Right Way for Evaluating AI Algorithms for Medical Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/touchstone-benchmark-are-we-on-the-right-way</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are committed to expanding this benchmark to encourage more innovation of AI algorithms for the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/touchstone-benchmark-are-we-on-the-right-way</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRDecoder: High-Resolution Decoder Network for Fundus Image Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrdecoder-high-resolution-decoder-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method effectively improves the overall segmentation accuracy of fundus lesions while consuming reasonable memory and computational overhead, and maintaining satisfying inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrdecoder-high-resolution-decoder-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA3DIP: Segment Any 3D Instance with Potential 3D Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa3dip-segment-any-3d-instance-with-potential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we present ScanNetV2-INS with complete ground truth labels and supplement additional instances for 3D class-agnostic instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa3dip-segment-any-3d-instance-with-potential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic doubly robust inference for linear functionals via calibrated debiased machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-doubly-robust-inference-for-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For learning such estimands, in this work, we propose novel debiased machine learning estimators that are doubly robust asymptotically linear, thus providing not only doubly robust consistency but also facilitating doubly robust inference (e. g., confidence intervals and hypothesis tests).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-doubly-robust-inference-for-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Plot Design with an LLM-powered Assistant: An Empirical Study with Game Designers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-plot-design-with-an-llm-powered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GamePlot, an LLM-powered assistant that supports game designers in crafting immersive narratives for turn-based games, and allows them to test these games through a collaborative game play and refine the plot throughout the process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-plot-design-with-an-llm-powered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V-DPO: Mitigating Hallucination in Large Vision Language Models via Vision-Guided Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-dpo-mitigating-hallucination-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research indicates that the over-reliance on the Large Language Model (LLM) backbone, as one cause of the LVLM hallucination, inherently introduces bias from language priors, leading to insufficient context attention to the visual inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-dpo-mitigating-hallucination-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Context: The Influence of Context on Feature Attribution Methods for Object Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-context-the-influence-of-context-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates how context manipulation influences both model accuracy and feature attribution, providing insights into the reliance of object recognition models on contextual information as understood through the lens of feature attribution methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-context-the-influence-of-context-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynthSet: Generative Diffusion Model for Semantic Segmentation in Precision Agriculture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthset-generative-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a methodology for generating synthetic annotated data to address data scarcity in semantic segmentation tasks within the precision agriculture domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthset-generative-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation of Object Detection Performance with Visual Saliency and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-of-object-detection-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As object detection techniques continue to evolve, understanding their relationships with complementary visual tasks becomes crucial for optimising model architectures and computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-of-object-detection-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks against Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-against-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision-language models (VLLMs) exhibit promising capabilities for processing multi-modal tasks across various application scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-against-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADOPT: Modified Adam Can Converge with Any $β_2$ with the Optimal Rate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adopt-modified-adam-can-converge-with-any-b-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adam is one of the most popular optimization algorithms in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adopt-modified-adam-can-converge-with-any-b-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreasonable Effectiveness of LLMs for Query Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work in database query optimization has used complex machine learning strategies, such as customized reinforcement learning schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-effectiveness-of-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMoA: Improving Multi-agent Large Language Models with Sparse Mixture-of-Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoa-improving-multi-agent-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While multi-agent systems have been shown to significantly enhance the performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) across various tasks and applications, the dense interaction between scaling agents potentially hampers their efficiency and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoa-improving-multi-agent-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDFAV: Remote Sensing Large Vision Language Models Dataset and Evaluation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddfav-remote-sensing-large-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, a training instruction set is produced based on some high-quality remote sensing images selected from the proposed dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddfav-remote-sensing-large-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiVOS: Light Video Object Segmentation with Gated Linear Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livos-light-video-object-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised video object segmentation (VOS) has been largely driven by space-time memory (STM) networks, which store past frame features in a spatiotemporal memory to segment the current frame via softmax attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livos-light-video-object-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathway-Guided Optimization of Deep Generative Molecular Design Models for Cancer Therapy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathway-guided-optimization-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the potential of our proposed approach, we show how a pharmacodynamic model, assessing the therapeutic efficacy of a drug-like small molecule by predicting how it modulates a cancer pathway, can be incorporated for effective LSO of data-driven models for GMD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathway-guided-optimization-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Aesthetics in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-aesthetics-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image aesthetics is a crucial metric in the field of image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-aesthetics-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting the Failure of Invariant Learning on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-the-failure-of-invariant-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enhancing node-level Out-Of-Distribution (OOD) generalization on graphs remains a crucial area of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-the-failure-of-invariant-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Dynamic Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-dynamic-image-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The decomposed components represent the effective information from the source data, thus the gap between them reflects the Relative Dominability (RD) of the uni-source data in constructing the fusion image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-dynamic-image-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Calibrated Tuning of Vision-Language Models for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-calibrated-tuning-of-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is crucial for deploying reliable machine learning models in open-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-calibrated-tuning-of-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep-Based Approach for Multi-Descriptor Feature Extraction: Applications on SAR Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-based-approach-for-multi-descriptor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges of SAR images, we utilize the R2D2 network and propose a training scheme specifically tailored for these images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-based-approach-for-multi-descriptor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the power of novel conditional generative approaches for new materials discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-power-of-novel-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a very long time, computational approaches to the design of new materials have relied on an iterative process of finding a candidate material and modeling its properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-power-of-novel-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DA-MoE: Addressing Depth-Sensitivity in Graph-Level Analysis through Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-moe-addressing-depth-sensitivity-in-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, fewer layers are sufficient for message passing in smaller graphs, while larger graphs typically require deeper networks to capture long-range dependencies and global features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-moe-addressing-depth-sensitivity-in-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding Natural Language to SQL Translation with Data-Based Self-Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-natural-language-to-sql-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural Language Interfaces for Databases empower non-technical users to interact with data using natural language (NL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-natural-language-to-sql-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Reconstruction of Wavefronts using an Over-Complete Phase Dictionary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-reconstruction-of-wavefronts-using-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Zernike basis efficiently represents common optical aberrations but struggles with complex or non-standard wavefronts such as optical vortices, Bessel beams, or wavefronts with sharp discontinuities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-reconstruction-of-wavefronts-using-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Graph-Based Machine Learning with Fully Homomorphic Encryption for Collaborative Anti-Money Laundering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-graph-based-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combating money laundering has become increasingly complex with the rise of cybercrime and digitalization of financial transactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-graph-based-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Machine Learning Approach for the Efficient Estimation of Ground-Level Air Temperature in Urban Areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-machine-learning-approach-for-the-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the obtained results, deep neural networks are confirmed to be faster and less computationally expensive alternative for ground-level air temperature compared to numerical models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-machine-learning-approach-for-the-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-Causal VAE: Robust Financial Time Series Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-causal-vae-robust-financial-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build a time-causal variational autoencoder (TC-VAE) for robust generation of financial time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-causal-vae-robust-financial-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Audio-Visual Sound Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-audio-visual-sound-separation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task is inherently challenging as our models must not only effectively utilize information from both modalities in current tasks but also preserve their cross-modal association in old tasks to mitigate catastrophic forgetting during audio-visual continual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-audio-visual-sound-separation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
