<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 21:06:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Avicenna: a challenge dataset for natural language generation toward commonsense syllogistic reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avicenna-a-challenge-dataset-for-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Avicenna corpus was developed as a benchmark for syllogistic NLG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avicenna-a-challenge-dataset-for-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProgNet: A Transferable Deep Network for Aircraft Engine Damage Propagation Prognosis under Real Flight Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognet-a-transferable-deep-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, ProgNet is transferred to the target domain of obtained degradation features for fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognet-a-transferable-deep-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual News Location Detection using an Entity-Based Siamese Network with Semi-Supervised Contrastive Learning and Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-news-location-detection-using-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the effectiveness of our approach, and due to the lack of datasets in this area, we also contribute to the research community with a gold-standard multilingual news-location dataset, NewsLOC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-news-location-detection-using-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHLE: Devices Tracking and Depth Filtering for Stereo-based Height Limit Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shle-devices-tracking-and-depth-filtering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In stage 1, a novel devices detection and tracking scheme is introduced, which accurately locate the height limit devices in the left or right image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shle-devices-tracking-and-depth-filtering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-High-Definition Low-Light Image Enhancement: A Benchmark and Transformer-Based Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-definition-low-light-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider the task of low-light image enhancement (LLIE) and introduce a large-scale database consisting of images at 4K and 8K resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-definition-low-light-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Colorization of Structured Mobile Web Pages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-colorization-of-structured-mobile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The web page colorization problem is then formalized as a task of estimating plausible color styles for a given web page content with a given hierarchical structure of the elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-colorization-of-structured-mobile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Reasoning over Incomplete Knowledge Graphs for Conversational Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-reasoning-over-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a variational Bayesian method to approximate posterior distributions over dialogue-specific subgraphs, which not only leverages the dialogue corpus for restructuring missing entity relations but also dynamically selects knowledge based on the dialogue context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-reasoning-over-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransPath: Learning Heuristics For Grid-Based Pathfinding via Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transpath-learning-heuristics-for-grid-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we suggest learning the instance-dependent heuristic proxies that are supposed to notably increase the efficiency of the search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transpath-learning-heuristics-for-grid-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Annotating Indoor Images with CAD Models via RGB-D Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-annotating-indoor-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an automatic method for annotating images of indoor scenes with the CAD models of the objects by relying on RGB-D scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-annotating-indoor-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jamdani Motif Generation using Conditional GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamdani-motif-generation-using-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results of the pix2pix model on this dataset show satisfactory outputs of computer-generated images of Jamdani motifs and we believe that our work will open a new avenue for further research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamdani-motif-generation-using-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-Aware Paced-Curriculum Learning by Label Smoothing for Surgical Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-paced-curriculum-learning-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we design a paced curriculum by label smoothing (P-CBLS) using paced learning with uniform label smoothing (ULS) for classification tasks and fuse uniform and spatially varying label smoothing (SVLS) for semantic segmentation tasks in a curriculum manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-paced-curriculum-learning-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renormalization in the neural network-quantum field theory correspondence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renormalization-in-the-neural-network-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A statistical ensemble of neural networks can be described in terms of a quantum field theory (NN-QFT correspondence).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renormalization-in-the-neural-network-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Certified Policy Smoothing for Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-policy-smoothing-for-cooperative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that our method produces meaningful guaranteed robustness for all models and environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/certified-policy-smoothing-for-cooperative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot human motion prediction for heterogeneous sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-human-motion-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human motion prediction is a complex task as it involves forecasting variables over time on a graph of connected sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-human-motion-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-queue Momentum Contrast for Microvideo-Product Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-queue-momentum-contrast-for-microvideo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The booming development and huge market of micro-videos bring new e-commerce channels for merchants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-queue-momentum-contrast-for-microvideo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind Your Heart: Stealthy Backdoor Attack on Dynamic Deep Neural Network in Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-your-heart-stealthy-backdoor-attack-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transforming off-the-shelf deep neural network (DNN) models into dynamic multi-exit architectures can achieve inference and transmission efficiency by fragmenting and distributing a large DNN model in edge computing scenarios (e. g., edge devices and cloud servers).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-your-heart-stealthy-backdoor-attack-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictive Coding Based Multiscale Network with Encoder-Decoder LSTM for Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-coding-based-multiscale-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a predictive coding model, it is updated by a combination of bottom-up and top-down information flows, which is different from traditional bottom-up training style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictive-coding-based-multiscale-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Meta-Representation Learning via Global Label Inference and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-meta-representation-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, MeLa outperforms existing methods across a diverse range of benchmarks, in particular under a more challenging setting where the number of training tasks is limited and labels are task-specific.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-meta-representation-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crowd Score: A Method for the Evaluation of Jokes using Large Language Model AI Voters as Judges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowd-score-a-method-for-the-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We tested our methodology on 52 jokes in a crowd of four AI voters with different humour types: affiliative, self-enhancing, aggressive and self-defeating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowd-score-a-method-for-the-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining User-aware Multi-Relations for Fake News Detection in Large Scale Online Social Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-user-aware-multi-relations-for-fake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we construct a dual-layer graph (i. e., the news layer and the user layer) to extract multiple relations of news and users in social networks to derive rich information for detecting fake news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-user-aware-multi-relations-for-fake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards dynamic stability analysis of sustainable power grids using graph neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-dynamic-stability-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate climate change, the share of renewable needs to be increased.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-dynamic-stability-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Narrative Relationship Embeddings by Training with Additional Inverse-Relationship Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-narrative-relationship-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of embedding character-entity relationships from the reduced semantic space of narratives, proposing and evaluating the assumption that these relationships hold under a reflection operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-narrative-relationship-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Prototype-based Cleaner for Label Noise Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-prototype-based-cleaner-for-label-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised learning based methods are current SOTA solutions to the noisy-label learning problem, which rely on learning an unsupervised label cleaner first to divide the training samples into a labeled set for clean data and an unlabeled set for noise data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-prototype-based-cleaner-for-label-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Audio-Visual Speech Separation Model Inspired by Cortico-Thalamo-Cortical Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-audio-visual-speech-separation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, inspired by the large number of connections between cortical regions and the thalamus, the model fuses the auditory and visual information in a thalamic subnetwork through top-down connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-audio-visual-speech-separation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Highlighter: Localizing Regions on 3D Shapes via Text Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-highlighter-localizing-regions-on-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key feature of our system is the ability to interpret "out-of-domain" localizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-highlighter-localizing-regions-on-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLGTformer: An Attention-Based Approach to Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slgtformer-an-attention-based-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this frontal appearance can be quantified as a temporal sequence of human body pose, leading to Sign Language Recognition through the learning of spatiotemporal dynamics of skeleton keypoints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slgtformer-an-attention-based-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TMS-Net: A Segmentation Network Coupled With A Run-time Quality Control Method For Robust Cardiac Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tms-net-a-segmentation-network-coupled-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from previous multi-view networks, TMS-Net has a single encoder and three decoders, leading to better noise robustness, segmentation performance and run-time quality estimation in our experiments on the segmentation of the left atrium on STACOM 2013 and STACOM 2018 challenge datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tms-net-a-segmentation-network-coupled-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Images to Textual Prompts: Zero-shot VQA with Frozen Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-images-to-textual-prompts-zero-shot-vqa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose \emph{Img2Prompt}, a plug-and-play module that provides the prompts that can bridge the aforementioned modality and task disconnections, so that LLMs can perform zero-shot VQA tasks without end-to-end training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-images-to-textual-prompts-zero-shot-vqa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Contrastive Learning: A Variational Generative Model for Multilingual Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-contrastive-learning-a-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning has been successfully used for retrieval of semantically aligned sentences, but it often requires large batch sizes or careful engineering to work well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-contrastive-learning-a-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating music with sentiment using Transformer-GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-music-with-sentiment-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of Automatic Music Generation has seen significant progress thanks to the advent of Deep Learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-music-with-sentiment-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Semantic Modeling for Structural Data Source with the Prior Knowledge from Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-semantic-modeling-for-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, an automatic approach for learning the semantics of a data source is desirable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-semantic-modeling-for-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Poison: Machine Unlearning Enables Camouflaged Poisoning Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-poison-machine-unlearning-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce camouflaged data poisoning attacks, a new attack vector that arises in the context of machine unlearning and other settings when model retraining may be induced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-poison-machine-unlearning-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Content Relationships for Distilling Efficient GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-content-relationships-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a content relationship distillation (CRD) to tackle the over-parameterized generative adversarial networks (GANs) for the serviceability in cutting-edge devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-content-relationships-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Mix-based Data Augmentation: Taxonomy, Methods, Applications, and Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-mix-based-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Owing to its generalization, MixDA has penetrated a variety of applications which are also completely reviewed in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-mix-based-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighboring state-based RL Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighboring-state-based-rl-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning is a powerful tool to model decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighboring-state-based-rl-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Residual Networks for Adversarial Robustness: An Architectural Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-residual-networks-for-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, little attention was devoted to analyzing the role of architectural elements (such as topology, depth, and width) on adversarial robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-residual-networks-for-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameters in Contextual RL are Highly Situational</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameters-in-contextual-rl-are-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although Reinforcement Learning (RL) has shown impressive results in games and simulation, real-world application of RL suffers from its instability under changing environment conditions and hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameters-in-contextual-rl-are-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Decoding for Pixel, Image, and Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-decoding-for-pixel-image-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present X-Decoder, a generalized decoding model that can predict pixel-level segmentation and language tokens seamlessly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-decoding-for-pixel-image-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Unfolded Tensor Robust PCA with Self-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unfolded-tensor-robust-pca-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tensor robust principal component analysis (RPCA), which seeks to separate a low-rank tensor from its sparse corruptions, has been crucial in data science and machine learning where tensor structures are becoming more prevalent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-unfolded-tensor-robust-pca-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncontrolled Lexical Exposure Leads to Overestimation of Compositional Generalization in Pretrained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncontrolled-lexical-exposure-leads-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human linguistic capacity is often characterized by compositionality and the generalization it enables -- human learners can produce and comprehend novel complex expressions by composing known parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncontrolled-lexical-exposure-leads-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Semantic Faithfulness of Language Models via Input Intervention on Conversational Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-semantic-faithfulness-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While transformer models achieve high performance on standard question answering tasks, we show that they fail to be semantically faithful once we perform these interventions for a significant number of cases (~50% for deletion intervention, and ~20% drop in accuracy for negation intervention).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-semantic-faithfulness-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgAsk: An Agent to Help Answer Farmer's Questions From Scientific Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agask-an-agent-to-help-answer-farmer-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the basis of these needs we release an information retrieval test collection comprising real questions, a large collection of scientific documents split in passages, and ground truth relevance assessments indicating which passages are relevant to each question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agask-an-agent-to-help-answer-farmer-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training language models for deeper understanding improves brain alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-for-deeper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that training language models for deeper narrative understanding results in richer representations that have improved alignment to human brain activity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-for-deeper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy- and Distance-Based Predictors From GPT-2 Attention Patterns Predict Reading Times Over and Above GPT-2 Surprisal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-and-distance-based-predictors-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based large language models are trained to make predictions about the next word by aggregating representations of previous tokens through their self-attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropy-and-distance-based-predictors-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Linguistic Syntactic Difference in Multilingual BERT: How Good is It and How Does It Affect Transfer?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-linguistic-syntactic-difference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that the distance between the distributions of different languages is highly consistent with the syntactic difference in terms of linguistic formalisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-linguistic-syntactic-difference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Learning of Monocular Depth Estimation via Consistency Regularization with K-way Disjoint Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-of-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-Supervised Learning (SSL) has recently accomplished successful achievements in various fields such as image classification, object detection, and semantic segmentation, which typically require a lot of labour to construct ground-truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-of-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Emotion Modelling in Written Stories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-emotion-modelling-in-written</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Telling stories is an integral part of human communication which can evoke emotions and influence the affective states of the audience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-emotion-modelling-in-written</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control of Continuous Quantum Systems with Many Degrees of Freedom based on Convergent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-of-continuous-quantum-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although there have been a few successful applications of deep RL to quantum control problems, most of the existing RL algorithms suffer from instabilities and unsatisfactory reproducibility, and require a large amount of fine-tuning and a large computational budget, both of which limit their applicability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-of-continuous-quantum-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When and Why Test Generators for Deep Learning Produce Invalid Inputs: an Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-why-test-generators-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate to what extent TIGs can generate valid inputs, according to both automated and human validators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-why-test-generators-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it worth it? An experimental comparison of six deep- and classical machine learning methods for unsupervised anomaly detection in time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-it-worth-it-an-experimental-comparison-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection of anomalies in time series data is crucial in a wide range of applications, such as system monitoring, health care or cyber security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-it-worth-it-an-experimental-comparison-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
