<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 21:09:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SMPISD-MTPNet: Scene Semantic Prior-Assisted Infrared Ship Detection Using Multi-Task Perception Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpisd-mtpnet-scene-semantic-prior-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose the Scene Semantic Prior-Assisted Multi-Task Perception Network (SMPISD-MTPNet), which includes three stages: scene semantic extraction, deep feature extraction, and prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpisd-mtpnet-scene-semantic-prior-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Cross-Domain Point Classification via Distilling Relational Priors from 2D Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-cross-domain-point-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic pattern of an object point cloud is determined by its topological configuration of local geometries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-cross-domain-point-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is larger always better? Evaluating and prompting large language models for non-generative medical tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-larger-always-better-evaluating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of Large Language Models (LLMs) in medicine is growing, but their ability to handle both structured Electronic Health Record (EHR) data and unstructured clinical notes is not well-studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-larger-always-better-evaluating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Decoupling Learning and Metric-Adaptive Thresholding for Semi-Supervised Multi-Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-decoupling-learning-and-metric-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a dual-perspective method to generate high-quality pseudo-labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-decoupling-learning-and-metric-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Dependence Measures to Prevent Shortcut Learning in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-dependence-measures-to-prevent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical imaging cohorts are often confounded by factors such as acquisition devices, hospital sites, patient backgrounds, and many more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-dependence-measures-to-prevent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Universal Prompting Strategy for Extracting Process Model Information from Natural Language Text using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-prompting-strategy-for-extracting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past decade, extensive research efforts have been dedicated to the extraction of information from textual process descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-prompting-strategy-for-extracting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness Definitions in Language Models Explained</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-definitions-in-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we begin with a brief introduction to LMs and fairness in LMs, followed by a comprehensive, up-to-date overview of existing fairness notions in LMs and the introduction of a novel taxonomy that categorizes these concepts based on their foundational principles and operational distinctions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-definitions-in-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Flexible and Scalable Approach for Collecting Wildlife Advertisements on the Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-and-scalable-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, given that the volume of data is staggering, we need scalable mechanisms to acquire, filter, and store the ads, as well as to make them available for analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-flexible-and-scalable-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridDepth: Robust Depth Fusion for Mobile AR by Leveraging Depth from Focus and Single-Image Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybriddepth-robust-depth-fusion-for-mobile-ar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through comprehensive quantitative and qualitative analyses, we demonstrate that HYBRIDDEPTH not only outperforms state-of-the-art (SOTA) models in common datasets (DDFF12, NYU Depth v2) and a real-world AR dataset ARKitScenes but also demonstrates strong zero-shot generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybriddepth-robust-depth-fusion-for-mobile-ar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Molecule Optimization with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-molecule-optimization-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models have opened new possibilities for generative molecular drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-molecule-optimization-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOoSE: Multi-Orientation Sharing Experts for Open-set Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moose-multi-orientation-sharing-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first propose a Multi-Oriented Open-Set Text Recognition task (MOOSTR) to model the challenges of both novel characters and writing direction variety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moose-multi-orientation-sharing-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning for predicting the occurrence of tipping points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-predicting-the-occurrence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to predict the occurrence of tipping points from time series data remains an outstanding challenge and a major interest in a broad range of research fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-predicting-the-occurrence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Really Need Graph Convolution During Training? Light Post-Training Graph-ODE for Efficient Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-graph-convolution-during</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficiency and scalability of graph convolution networks (GCNs) in training recommender systems (RecSys) have been persistent concerns, hindering their deployment in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-really-need-graph-convolution-during</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Trajectory Prediction with Difficulty-Guided Feature Enhancement Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-trajectory-prediction-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods usually perform holistic inference on the trajectories of agents, neglecting the differences in prediction difficulty among agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-trajectory-prediction-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Robustification via Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustification-via-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial robustness has been conventionally believed as a challenging property to encode for neural networks, requiring plenty of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustification-via-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AppWorld: A Controllable World of Apps and People for Benchmarking Interactive Coding Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appworld-a-controllable-world-of-apps-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this gap, we built $\textbf{AppWorld Engine}$, a high-quality execution environment (60K lines of code) of 9 day-to-day apps operable via 457 APIs and populated with realistic digital activities simulating the lives of ~100 fictitious users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/appworld-a-controllable-world-of-apps-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Dysarthric Speech Recognition for Unseen Speakers via Prototype-Based Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dysarthric-speech-recognition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce a prototype-based approach that markedly improves DSR performance for unseen dysarthric speakers without additional fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-dysarthric-speech-recognition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReALFRED: An Embodied Instruction Following Benchmark in Photo-Realistic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realfred-an-embodied-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap between these learning environments and deploying (i. e., real) environments, we propose the ReALFRED benchmark that employs real-world scenes, objects, and room layouts to learn agents to complete household tasks by understanding free-form language instructions and interacting with objects in large, multi-room and 3D-captured scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realfred-an-embodied-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Structure as Prompt: Improving Small Language Models Capabilities for Knowledge-based Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-structure-as-prompt-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the capabilities of Small Language Models (SLMs, defined as LLMs with fewer than 1 billion parameters) with prompt-based learning for knowledge-based causal discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-structure-as-prompt-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Scalable Quantum Non-local Neural Network for Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-scalable-quantum-non-local-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-local operations play a crucial role in computer vision enabling the capture of long-range dependencies through weighted sums of features across the input, surpassing the constraints of traditional convolution operations that focus solely on local neighborhoods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-scalable-quantum-non-local-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSSD: Vision Mamba with Non-Casual State Space Duality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vssd-vision-mamba-with-non-casual-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, State Space Duality (SSD), an improved variant of SSMs, was introduced in Mamba2 to enhance model performance and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vssd-vision-mamba-with-non-casual-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Role-specific Guided Large Language Model for Ophthalmic Consultation Based on Stylistic Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-role-specific-guided-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ophthalmology consultations are crucial for diagnosing, treating, and preventing eye diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-role-specific-guided-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Temporal Causality for Advanced Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-temporal-causality-for-advanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a fundamental task in long-form video understanding, temporal action detection (TAD) aims to capture inherent temporal relations in untrimmed videos and identify candidate actions with precise boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-temporal-causality-for-advanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>factgenie: A Framework for Span-based Evaluation of Generated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factgenie-a-framework-for-span-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present factgenie: a framework for annotating and visualizing word spans in textual model outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factgenie-a-framework-for-span-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Training Data with Lossy Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-training-data-with-lossy-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to capture this trade-off and optimize storage of training data, we propose a `storage scaling law' that describes the joint evolution of test error with sample size and number of bits per image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-training-data-with-lossy-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Graph Summarization with Neural Networks: 2012, 2022, and a Time Warp</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-graph-summarization-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the heterogeneity of web graphs, in some snapshots, the $2$-hop summary produces over ten times more vertex summaries than the $1$-hop summary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-graph-summarization-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-MIL: A Spatial Contextual Aware Multiple Instance Learning Approach for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-mil-a-spatial-contextual-aware-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current MIL models predominantly rely on instance-level features derived from pretrained models such as ResNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-mil-a-spatial-contextual-aware-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariance of deep image quality metrics to affine transformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariance-of-deep-image-quality-metrics-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This methodology involves transforming the distance measured by an arbitrary metric to a common distance representation based on available subjectively rated databases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariance-of-deep-image-quality-metrics-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint RGB-Spectral Decomposition Model Guided Image Enhancement in Mobile Photography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-rgb-spectral-decomposition-model-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of miniaturized spectrometers into mobile devices offers new avenues for image quality enhancement and facilitates novel downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-rgb-spectral-decomposition-model-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Driven Neural Collaborative Filtering Model for Paper Source Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-neural-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying significant references within the complex interrelations of a citation knowledge graph is challenging, which encompasses connections through citations, authorship, keywords, and other relational attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-driven-neural-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapTune: Advancing ASIC Technology Mapping via Reinforcement Learning Guided Library Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptune-advancing-asic-technology-mapping-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of MapTune is evaluated on a wide range of benchmarks, different technology libraries and technology mappers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptune-advancing-asic-technology-mapping-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Description-Augmented Dataless Intent Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-description-augmented-dataless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work shows promising results for dataless classification scaling to a large number of unseen intents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-description-augmented-dataless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVM-1: Large-scale video models pretrained with nearly 5000 hours of human-like video data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvm-1-large-scale-video-models-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Human-like Video Models (HVM-1), large-scale video models pretrained with nearly 5000 hours of curated human-like video data (mostly egocentric, temporally extended, continuous video recordings), using the spatiotemporal masked autoencoder (ST-MAE) algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvm-1-large-scale-video-models-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stage Face-Voice Association Learning with Keynote Speaker Diarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-face-voice-association-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a ``Multi-stage Face-voice Association Learning with Keynote Speaker Diarization''~(MFV-KSD) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-face-voice-association-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Data Labeling for Software Vulnerability Prediction Models: How Far Are We?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-data-labeling-for-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Background: Software Vulnerability (SV) prediction needs large-sized and high-quality data to perform well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-data-labeling-for-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRA-Pro: Are Low-Rank Adapters Properly Optimized?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-pro-are-low-rank-adapters-properly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method constrains the optimization process, shrinking the performance gap between LoRA and full fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lora-pro-are-low-rank-adapters-properly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weighted Risk Invariance: Domain Generalization under Invariant Feature Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-risk-invariance-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Invariant models are also supposed to generalize to shifts in the marginal distribution $p(X_{\text{inv}})$ of the extracted features $X_{\text{inv}}$, a type of shift we call an $\textit{invariant covariate shift}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weighted-risk-invariance-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HANNA: Hard-constraint Neural Network for Consistent Activity Coefficient Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hanna-hard-constraint-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first hard-constraint neural network for predicting activity coefficients (HANNA), a thermodynamic mixture property that is the basis for many applications in science and engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hanna-hard-constraint-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Training with Direct Preference Optimization Improves Chain-of-Thought Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-direct-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show that the conventional self-training can be further augmented by a preference learning algorithm called Direct Preference Optimization (DPO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-training-with-direct-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I can listen but cannot read: An evaluation of two-tower multimodal systems for instrument recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-can-listen-but-cannot-read-an-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an evaluation and analysis of two-tower systems for zero-shot instrument recognition and a detailed analysis of the properties of the pre-joint and joint embeddings spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-can-listen-but-cannot-read-an-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling A Simple Approach to Zero-Shot Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-a-simple-approach-to-zero-shot-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite rapid progress in increasing the language coverage of automatic speech recognition, the field is still far from covering all languages with a known writing script.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-a-simple-approach-to-zero-shot-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LKCell: Efficient Cell Nuclei Instance Segmentation with Large Convolution Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkcell-efficient-cell-nuclei-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our method on the most challenging benchmark and achieve state-of-the-art results (0. 5080 mPQ) in cell nuclei instance segmentation with only 21. 6% FLOPs compared with the previous leading method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lkcell-efficient-cell-nuclei-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Spectral bias Alleviation by Normalizations in Coordinate Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-spectral-bias-alleviation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This problem is caused by the pathological distribution of the neural tangent kernel's (NTK's) eigenvalues of coordinate networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-spectral-bias-alleviation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mew: Multiplexed Immunofluorescence Image Analysis through an Efficient Multiplex Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mew-multiplexed-immunofluorescence-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in graph-based approaches for multiplexed immunofluorescence (mIF) images have significantly propelled the field forward, offering deeper insights into patient-level phenotyping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mew-multiplexed-immunofluorescence-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-Preserving Downsampling of Binary Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-preserving-downsampling-of-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel discrete optimization-based approach to generate downsampled versions of binary images that are guaranteed to have the same topology as the original, measured by the zeroth and first Betti numbers of the black regions, while having good similarity to the original image as measured by IoU and Dice scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-preserving-downsampling-of-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDS-ED: Multimodal Decision Support in the Emergency Department -- a Benchmark Dataset for Diagnoses and Deterioration Prediction in Emergency Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mds-ed-multimodal-decision-support-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: We introduce a dataset based on MIMIC-IV, benchmarking protocol, and initial results for evaluating multimodal decision support in the emergency department (ED).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mds-ed-multimodal-decision-support-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Sensitivity Analysis on Latent Embeddings and Dimensionality Reductions for Text Spatializations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-sensitivity-analysis-on-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we analyzed the resulting 42817 tabular data points in a descriptive statistical analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-sensitivity-analysis-on-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dark Side of Function Calling: Pathways to Jailbreaking Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dark-side-of-function-calling-pathways-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities, but their power comes with significant security considerations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dark-side-of-function-calling-pathways-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Limitations of Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks in Classification: Insights to Software Training and Hardware Implementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-limitations-of-kolmogorov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks (KANs), a novel type of neural network, have recently gained popularity and attention due to the ability to substitute multi-layer perceptions (MLPs) in artificial intelligence (AI) with higher accuracy and interoperability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-limitations-of-kolmogorov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RefMask3D: Language-Guided Transformer for 3D Referring Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refmask3d-language-guided-transformer-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D referring segmentation is an emerging and challenging vision-language task that aims to segment the object described by a natural language expression in a point cloud scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refmask3d-language-guided-transformer-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
