<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2024 09:16:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CALE: Continuous Arcade Learning Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cale-continuous-arcade-learning-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Continuous Arcade Learning Environment (CALE), an extension of the well-known Arcade Learning Environment (ALE) [Bellemare et al., 2013].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cale-continuous-arcade-learning-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Twigs with Loop Guidance for Conditional Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-twigs-with-loop-guidance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel score-based diffusion framework named Twigs that incorporates multiple co-evolving flows for enriching conditional generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-twigs-with-loop-guidance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Language Models Perform Robust Reasoning in Chain-of-thought Prompting with Noisy Rationales?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-perform-robust-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose the method of contrastive denoising with noisy chain-of-thought (CD-CoT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-perform-robust-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Better Deep Image Priors between Over- and Under-parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chasing-better-deep-image-priors-between-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we also extend LIP to compressive sensing image reconstruction, where a pre-trained GAN generator is used as the prior (in contrast to untrained DIP or deep decoder), and confirm its validity in this setting too.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chasing-better-deep-image-priors-between-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImOV3D: Learning Open-Vocabulary Point Clouds 3D Object Detection from Only 2D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imov3d-learning-open-vocabulary-point-clouds</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a novel framework ImOV3D to leverage pseudo multimodal representation containing both images and point clouds (PC) to close the modality gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imov3d-learning-open-vocabulary-point-clouds</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Wrong with Perplexity for Long-context Language Modeling?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-wrong-with-perplexity-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose \textbf{LongPPL}, a novel metric that focuses on key tokens by employing a long-short context contrastive method to identify them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-wrong-with-perplexity-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Motion in Text-to-Video Generation with Decomposed Encoding and Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-motion-in-text-to-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This issue stems from the internal biases in text encoding, which overlooks motions, and inadequate conditioning mechanisms in T2V generation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-motion-in-text-to-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian-guided Label Mapping for Visual Reprogramming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-guided-label-mapping-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When adapting the output interface, label mapping methods transform the pretrained labels to downstream labels by establishing a gradient-free one-to-one correspondence between the two sets of labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-guided-label-mapping-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabM: Advancing Tabular Deep Learning with Parameter-Efficient Ensembling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabm-advancing-tabular-deep-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning architectures for supervised learning on tabular data range from simple multilayer perceptrons (MLP) to sophisticated Transformers and retrieval-augmented methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabm-advancing-tabular-deep-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Positional Bias of Faithfulness for Long-form Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-positional-bias-of-faithfulness-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) often exhibit positional bias in long-context settings, under-attending to information in the middle of inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-positional-bias-of-faithfulness-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DetectRL: Benchmarking LLM-Generated Text Detection in Real-World Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detectrl-benchmarking-llm-generated-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More importantly, we analyzed the potential impact of writing styles, model types, attack methods, the text lengths, and real-world human writing factors on different types of detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detectrl-benchmarking-llm-generated-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-DiFuse: An Interactive Multi-Modal Image Fusion Framework based on Text-modulated Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-difuse-an-interactive-multi-modal-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, by embedding the combination of the text and zero-shot location model into the diffusion fusion process, a text-controlled fusion re-modulation strategy is developed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-difuse-an-interactive-multi-modal-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Deep Equilibrium Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-deep-equilibrium-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Quantum Deep Equilibrium Models (QDEQs): a training paradigm that learns parameters of a quantum machine learning model given by a PQC using DEQs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-deep-equilibrium-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GlotCC: An Open Broad-Coverage CommonCrawl Corpus and Pipeline for Minority Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glotcc-an-open-broad-coverage-commoncrawl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The need for large text corpora has increased with the advent of pretrained language models and, in particular, the discovery of scaling laws for these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glotcc-an-open-broad-coverage-commoncrawl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamical similarity analysis uniquely captures how computations develop in RNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-similarity-analysis-uniquely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, we develop test cases that showcase how DSA's enhanced ability to detect dynamical motifs makes it highly effective for identifying ongoing computations in RNNs and revealing how networks learn tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-similarity-analysis-uniquely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Chess Reinforcement Learning with Graph Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chess-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments, performed on smaller networks than the initial AlphaZero paper, show that this new architecture outperforms previous architectures with a similar number of parameters, being able to increase playing strength an order of magnitude faster.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-chess-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffPano: Scalable and Consistent Text to Panorama Generation with Spherical Epipolar-Aware Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffpano-scalable-and-consistent-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose a novel text-driven panoramic generation framework, termed DiffPano, to achieve scalable, consistent, and diverse panoramic scene generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffpano-scalable-and-consistent-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasons and Solutions for the Decline in Model Performance after Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasons-and-solutions-for-the-decline-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to investigate the reasons for the performance decline of the edited model and optimize the editing method, this work explores the underlying reasons from both data and model perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasons-and-solutions-for-the-decline-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ada-MSHyper: Adaptive Multi-Scale Hypergraph Transformer for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-mshyper-adaptive-multi-scale-hypergraph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose Adaptive Multi-Scale Hypergraph Transformer (Ada-MSHyper) for time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-mshyper-adaptive-multi-scale-hypergraph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context LoRA for Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-lora-for-diffusion-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While task-specific in terms of tuning data, our framework remains task-agnostic in architecture and pipeline, offering a powerful tool for the community and providing valuable insights for further research on product-level task-agnostic generation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-lora-for-diffusion-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Matrix Product Operator: A Multi-Dimensionally Integrable Machine Learning Potential</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-matrix-product-operator-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A neural network-based machine learning potential energy surface (PES) expressed in a matrix product operator (NN-MPO) is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-matrix-product-operator-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDT: An Efficient Diffusion Transformer Framework Inspired by Human-like Sketching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edt-an-efficient-diffusion-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based Diffusion Probabilistic Models (DPMs) have shown more potential than CNN-based DPMs, yet their extensive computational requirements hinder widespread practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edt-an-efficient-diffusion-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Ontology Learning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-ontology-learning-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ontologies are useful for automatic machine processing of domain knowledge as they represent it in a structured format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-ontology-learning-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-Glance: Non-semantic context vectors and the applications in supervising image reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-glance-non-semantic-context-vectors-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, we propose a biologically informed non-semantic context descriptor, \textbf{MS-Glance}, along with the Glance Index Measure for comparing two images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-glance-non-semantic-context-vectors-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Visual Case Study of the Training Dynamics in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-visual-case-study-of-the-training-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a visual sandbox designed to explore the training dynamics of a small-scale transformer model, with the embedding dimension constrained to $d=2$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-visual-case-study-of-the-training-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan-on-Graph: Self-Correcting Adaptive Planning of Large Language Model on Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-on-graph-self-correcting-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose a novel self-correcting adaptive planning paradigm for KG-augmented LLM named Plan-on-Graph (PoG), which first decomposes the question into several sub-objectives and then repeats the process of adaptively exploring reasoning paths, updating memory, and reflecting on the need to self-correct erroneous reasoning paths until arriving at the answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plan-on-graph-self-correcting-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning Gradients as Vitamin for Online Finetuning Decision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-gradients-as-vitamin</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As suggested by our analysis, in our experiments, we hence find that simply adding TD3 gradients to the finetuning process of ODT effectively improves the online finetuning performance of ODT, especially if ODT is pretrained with low-reward offline data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-gradients-as-vitamin</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction-Tuning Llama-3-8B Excels in City-Scale Mobility Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-tuning-llama-3-8b-excels-in-city</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human mobility prediction plays a critical role in applications such as disaster response, urban planning, and epidemic forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-tuning-llama-3-8b-excels-in-city</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Large Language Models for Code Translation and Software Development in Scientific Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-large-language-models-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of foundational models and generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) is poised to transform productivity in scientific computing, especially in code development, refactoring, and translating from one programming language to another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-large-language-models-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EZ-HOI: VLM Adaptation via Guided Prompt Learning for Zero-Shot HOI Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ez-hoi-vlm-adaptation-via-guided-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, fine-tuning on task-specific datasets often leads to overfitting to seen classes and suboptimal performance on unseen classes, due to the absence of unseen class labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ez-hoi-vlm-adaptation-via-guided-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual MRI Data Augmentation using Conditional Denoising Diffusion Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-mri-data-augmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) models in medical imaging face challenges in generalizability and robustness due to variations in image acquisition parameters (IAP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-mri-data-augmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Cross-Modal Text-Molecule Retrieval with Better Modality Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-modal-text-molecule-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal text-molecule retrieval model aims to learn a shared feature space of the text and molecule modalities for accurate similarity calculation, which facilitates the rapid screening of molecules with specific properties and activities in drug design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-modal-text-molecule-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Embodied Reinforcement Learning Agents: Informativeness and Diversity of Language Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-embodied-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world scenarios, it is desirable for embodied agents to have the ability to leverage human language to gain explicit or implicit knowledge for learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-embodied-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Learning for Numeric Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-learning-for-numeric-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph learning is naturally well suited for use in symbolic, object-centric planning due to its ability to exploit relational structures exhibited in planning domains and to take as input planning instances with arbitrary numbers of objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-learning-for-numeric-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitStack: Fine-Grained Size Control for Compressed Large Language Models in Variable Memory Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitstack-fine-grained-size-control-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging weight decomposition, BitStack can dynamically adjust the model size with minimal transmission between running memory and storage devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitstack-fine-grained-size-control-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wide Two-Layer Networks can Learn from Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wide-two-layer-networks-can-learn-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This hypothesis is supported by the success of perturbation learning, where classifiers trained solely on adversarial examples and the corresponding incorrect labels generalize well to correctly labeled test data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wide-two-layer-networks-can-learn-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGU-SLAM: Learnable Gaussian Uncertainty Matching with Deformable Correlation Sampling for Deep Visual SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgu-slam-learnable-gaussian-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In general, they heavily rely on global visual similarity matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgu-slam-learnable-gaussian-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUZZ: Beehive-structured Sparse KV Cache with Segmented Heavy Hitters for Efficient LLM Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buzz-beehive-structured-sparse-kv-cache-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key-value (KV) cache mechanism reduces computational overhead in transformer models, but challenges in maintaining contextual understanding remain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buzz-beehive-structured-sparse-kv-cache-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReasoningRec: Bridging Personalized Recommendations and Human-Interpretable Explanations through LLM Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoningrec-bridging-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ReasoningRec, a reasoning-based recommendation framework that leverages Large Language Models (LLMs) to bridge the gap between recommendations and human-interpretable explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoningrec-bridging-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossEarth: Geospatial Vision Foundation Model for Domain Generalizable Remote Sensing Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossearth-geospatial-vision-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of Remote Sensing Domain Generalization (RSDG) has emerged as a critical and valuable research frontier, focusing on developing models that generalize effectively across diverse scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crossearth-geospatial-vision-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-Free Training of Neural ODEs on Paired Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-free-training-of-neural-odes-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate a method for simulation-free training of Neural Ordinary Differential Equations (NODEs) for learning deterministic mappings between paired data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-free-training-of-neural-odes-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAMITA: Bayesian Multiple Imputation for Tensor Arrays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bamita-bayesian-multiple-imputation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For two microbiome applications, it is shown to accurately capture uncertainty in the full microbiome profile at missing timepoints and used to infer trends in species diversity for the population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bamita-bayesian-multiple-imputation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of Prompt Engineering Techniques for Task Planning and Execution in Service Robotics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-prompt-engineering-techniques</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in LLM have been instrumental in autonomous robot control and human-robot interaction by leveraging their vast general knowledge and capabilities to understand and reason across a wide range of tasks and scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-prompt-engineering-techniques</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$100K or 100 Days: Trade-offs when Pre-Training with Academic Resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/100k-or-100-days-trade-offs-when-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a benchmark to measure the time to pre-train models on given GPUs and also identify ideal settings for maximizing training speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/100k-or-100-days-trade-offs-when-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Segmentation of Cardiac Images Leveraging Metadata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-segmentation-of-cardiac-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by coarse-to-fine approaches in image analysis, we propose a novel multitask compositional segmentation approach that can simultaneously localize the heart in a cardiac image and perform part-based segmentation of different regions of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-segmentation-of-cardiac-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIS: NL2SQL Service Evaluation Benchmark for Business Intelligence Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bis-nl2sql-service-evaluation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NL2SQL (Natural Language to Structured Query Language) transformation has seen wide adoption in Business Intelligence (BI) applications in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bis-nl2sql-service-evaluation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tangent Space Causal Inference: Leveraging Vector Fields for Causal Discovery in Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangent-space-causal-inference-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery with time series data remains a challenging yet increasingly important task across many scientific domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangent-space-causal-inference-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuseAnyPart: Diffusion-Driven Facial Parts Swapping via Multiple Reference Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuseanypart-diffusion-driven-facial-parts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial parts swapping aims to selectively transfer regions of interest from the source image onto the target image while maintaining the rest of the target image unchanged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuseanypart-diffusion-driven-facial-parts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfolding Target Detection with State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfolding-target-detection-with-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement a lightweight model of only 260K parameters and conduct real-world experiments for human target detection using FMCW radars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfolding-target-detection-with-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TokenFormer: Rethinking Transformer Scaling with Tokenized Model Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenformer-rethinking-transformer-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By treating model parameters as tokens, we replace all the linear projections in Transformers with our token-parameter attention layer, where input tokens act as queries and model parameters as keys and values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenformer-rethinking-transformer-scaling</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
