<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 21:07:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Penalised regression with multiple sources of prior effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penalised-regression-with-multiple-sources-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many high-dimensional prediction or classification tasks, complementary data on the features are available, e. g. prior biological knowledge on (epi)genetic markers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penalised-regression-with-multiple-sources-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating Road Spray Effects in Automotive Lidar Sensor Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-road-spray-effects-in-automotive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model conforms to the Open Simulation Interface (OSI) standard and is based on the formation of detection clusters within a spray plume.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-road-spray-effects-in-automotive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLASER: A Text-Free Speech-to-Speech Translation Evaluation Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blaser-a-text-free-speech-to-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a text-free evaluation metric for end-to-end S2ST, named BLASER, to avoid the dependency on ASR systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blaser-a-text-free-speech-to-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Learning of Dynamic Hand Gesture Recognition with Few-Shot Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-learning-of-dynamic-hand-gesture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Savings were defined as the number of additional observations required when a Deep Learning model is trained on new hand gestures instead of a Few Shot Learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-learning-of-dynamic-hand-gesture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform Sequence Better: Time Interval Aware Data Augmentation for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-sequence-better-time-interval-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we observe that the time interval in a sequence may vary significantly different, and thus result in the ineffectiveness of user modeling due to the issue of \emph{preference drift}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-sequence-better-time-interval-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azimuth: Systematic Error Analysis for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/azimuth-systematic-error-analysis-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to other stages of the ML development cycle, such as model training and hyper-parameter tuning, the process and tooling for the error analysis stage are less mature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/azimuth-systematic-error-analysis-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POTATO: The Portable Text Annotation Tool</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/potato-the-portable-text-annotation-tool</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present POTATO, the Portable text annotation tool, a free, fully open-sourced annotation system that 1) supports labeling many types of text and multimodal data; 2) offers easy-to-configure features to maximize the productivity of both deployers and annotators (convenient templates for common ML/NLP tasks, active learning, keypress shortcuts, keyword highlights, tooltips); and 3) supports a high degree of customization (editable UI, inserting pre-screening questions, attention and qualification tests).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/potato-the-portable-text-annotation-tool</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCo: Reliable Causal Chain Reasoning via Structural Causal Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reco-reliable-causal-chain-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal chain reasoning (CCR) is an essential ability for many decision-making AI systems, which requires the model to build reliable causal chains by connecting causal pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reco-reliable-causal-chain-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Xception to NEXcepTion: New Design Decisions and Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-xception-to-nexception-new-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a modified Xception architecture, the NEXcepTion network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-xception-to-nexception-new-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to disagree well: Investigating the dispute tactics used on Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-disagree-well-investigating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Disagreements are frequently studied from the perspective of either detecting toxicity or analysing argument structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-disagree-well-investigating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Conditionally Invariant Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-conditionally-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The procedure requires just a single ridge regression from $Y$ to kernelized features of $Z$, which can be done in advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-conditionally-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEDCNet: A Lightweight and Efficient Semantic Segmentation Algorithm Using Dual Context Module for Extracting Ground Objects from UAV Aerial Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ledcnet-a-lightweight-and-efficient-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to make the model lightweight and improve a certain accuracy, this research developed a new lightweight and efficient network for the extraction of ground features from UAV aerial remote sensing images, called LDMCNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ledcnet-a-lightweight-and-efficient-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Stage Cascade Refinement Networks for Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-stage-cascade-refinement-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we present a new research benchmark for infrared small target detection, consisting of the SIRST-V2 dataset of real-world, high-resolution single-frame targets, the normalized contrast evaluation metric, and the DeepInfrared toolkit for detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-stage-cascade-refinement-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolution-enhanced Evolving Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolution-enhanced-evolving-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first work that explicitly models the layer-wise evolution of attention maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolution-enhanced-evolving-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-form 3D Scene Inpainting with Dual-stream GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-form-3d-scene-inpainting-with-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we present a novel task named free-form 3D scene inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-form-3d-scene-inpainting-with-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Explanation Constraints for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-explanation-constraints-for-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Post-hoc explanation methods are used with the intent of providing insights about neural networks and are sometimes said to help engender trust in their outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-explanation-constraints-for-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homonymy Information for English WordNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homonymy-information-for-english-wordnet-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The outcome of our work is a high-quality homonymy annotation layer for Princeton WordNet, which we release.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homonymy-information-for-english-wordnet-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ensemble neural network approach to forecast Dengue outbreak based on climatic condition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-neural-network-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In comparison with statistical, machine learning, and deep learning methods, our proposed XEWNet performs better in 75% of the cases for short-term and long-term forecasting of dengue incidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ensemble-neural-network-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Human Motion Synthesis and Style Transfer with Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-human-motion-synthesis-and-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve high-quality results, we design a multi-task architecture of diffusion model that strategically generates aspects of human motions for local guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-human-motion-synthesis-and-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An estimator for the recombination rate from a continuously observed diffusion of haplotype frequencies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-estimator-for-the-recombination-rate-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimators for the recombination rate, which are usually based on the idea of integrating over the unobserved possible evolutionary histories of a sample, can therefore be noisy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-estimator-for-the-recombination-rate-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injecting Domain Knowledge in Language Models for Task-Oriented Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecting-domain-knowledge-in-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained language models (PLM) have advanced the state-of-the-art across NLP applications, but lack domain-specific knowledge that does not naturally occur in pre-training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecting-domain-knowledge-in-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF-Art: Text-Driven Neural Radiance Fields Stylization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-art-text-driven-neural-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a powerful representation of 3D scenes, the neural radiance field (NeRF) enables high-quality novel view synthesis from multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-art-text-driven-neural-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-SHAP: A Performance-agnostic Metric for Measuring Multimodal Contributions in Vision and Language Models &amp; Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-shap-a-performance-agnostic-metric-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[But how to quantify the amount of unimodal collapse reliably, at dataset and instance-level, to diagnose and combat unimodal collapse in a targeted way?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-shap-a-performance-agnostic-metric-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian posterior approximation with stochastic ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-posterior-approximation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ensembles of stochastic neural networks to approximate the Bayesian posterior, combining stochastic methods such as dropout with deep ensembles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-posterior-approximation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Gold Standard: Grounding Summarization Evaluation with Robust Human Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-gold-standard-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[4) We evaluate existing automatic metrics using the collected human annotations across evaluation protocols and demonstrate how our benchmark leads to more statistically stable and significant results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-gold-standard-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-stage Contextual Transformer-based Convolutional Neural Network for Airway Extraction from CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-contextual-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, the total airway mask and CT images are provided to the subnetwork, and the intrapulmonary airway mask and corresponding CT scans to the subnetwork in the second stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-contextual-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging POMDPs and Bayesian decision making for robust maintenance planning under model uncertainty: An application to railway systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-pomdps-and-bayesian-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a framework to estimate POMDP transition and observation model parameters directly from available data, via Markov Chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) sampling of a Hidden Markov Model (HMM) conditioned on actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-pomdps-and-bayesian-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-like Adaptive Modeling Multi-Agent Learning System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-like-adaptive-modeling-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a self-supervised multi-agent system, termed a memory-like adaptive modeling multi-agent learning system (MAMMALS), that realizes online learning towards behavioral pattern clustering tasks for time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-like-adaptive-modeling-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RWEN-TTS: Relation-aware Word Encoding Network for Natural Text-to-Speech Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rwen-tts-relation-aware-word-encoding-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of deep learning, a huge number of text-to-speech (TTS) models which produce human-like speech have emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rwen-tts-relation-aware-word-encoding-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saved You A Click: Automatically Answering Clickbait Titles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saved-you-a-click-automatically-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Often clickbait articles have a title that is phrased as a question or vague teaser that entices the user to click on the link and read the article to find the explanation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saved-you-a-click-automatically-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effects of In-domain Corpus Size on pre-training BERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effects-of-in-domain-corpus-size-on-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many prior language modeling efforts have shown that pre-training on an in-domain corpus can significantly improve performance on downstream domain-specific NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effects-of-in-domain-corpus-size-on-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Training of Query-Based Object Detection via Selective Query Recollection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-training-of-query-based-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates a phenomenon where query-based object detectors mispredict at the last decoding stage while predicting correctly at an intermediate stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-training-of-query-based-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-and-Language Understanding from Pixels Only</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-and-language-understanding-from-pixels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal models are becoming increasingly effective, in part due to unified components, such as the Transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-and-language-understanding-from-pixels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-based Visual Tracking in Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-visual-tracking-in-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual object tracking under challenging conditions of motion and light can be hindered by the capabilities of conventional cameras, prone to producing images with motion blur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-visual-tracking-in-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QueryPose: Sparse Multi-Person Pose Regression via Spatial-Aware Part-Level Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/querypose-sparse-multi-person-pose-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing end-to-end methods rely on dense representations to preserve the spatial detail and structure for precise keypoint localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/querypose-sparse-multi-person-pose-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexiViT: One Model for All Patch Sizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexivit-one-model-for-all-patch-sizes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers convert images to sequences by slicing them into patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexivit-one-model-for-all-patch-sizes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Object Localization: Observing the Background to Discover Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-object-localization-observing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This way, the salient objects emerge as a by-product without any strong assumption on what an object should be.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-object-localization-observing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Resolution Online Deterministic Annealing: A Hierarchical and Progressive Learning Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-online-deterministic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This simulates an annealing process and defines a robust and interpretable heuristic method to gradually increase the complexity of the learning architecture in a task-agnostic manner, giving emphasis to regions of the data space that are considered more important according to a predefined criterion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-online-deterministic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-IID Transfer Learning on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-iid-transfer-learning-on-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, in this paper, we propose rigorous generalization bounds and algorithms for cross-network transfer learning from a source graph to a target graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-iid-transfer-learning-on-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepLSD: Line Segment Detection and Refinement with Deep Image Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplsd-line-segment-detection-and-refinement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Their learned counterparts are more repeatable and can handle challenging images, but at the cost of a lower accuracy and a bias towards wireframe lines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplsd-line-segment-detection-and-refinement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localizing Scan Targets from Human Pose for Autonomous Lung Ultrasound Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-scan-targets-from-human-pose-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound is progressing toward becoming an affordable and versatile solution to medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-scan-targets-from-human-pose-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Indic Handwritten Text Recognition Using Global Semantic Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-indic-handwritten-text-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a semantic module in an encoder-decoder framework for extracting global semantic information to recognize the Indic handwritten texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-indic-handwritten-text-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You were saying? - Spoken Language in the V3C Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-were-saying-spoken-language-in-the-v3c</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an analysis of the distribution of spoken language in the V3C video retrieval benchmark dataset based on automatically generated transcripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-were-saying-spoken-language-in-the-v3c</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Put Attention to Temporal Saliency Patterns of Multi-Horizon Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-attention-to-temporal-saliency-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the mentioned observation, in this paper, we propose a novel architecture, Temporal Saliency Detection (TSD), on top of the attention mechanism and apply it to multi-horizon time series prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-attention-to-temporal-saliency-patterns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROSCOE: A Suite of Metrics for Scoring Step-by-Step Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roscoe-a-suite-of-metrics-for-scoring-step-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models show improved downstream task performance when prompted to generate step-by-step reasoning to justify their final answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roscoe-a-suite-of-metrics-for-scoring-step-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Pre-training of Masked Language Model via Concept-based Curriculum Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pre-training-of-masked-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Masked language modeling (MLM) has been widely used for pre-training effective bidirectional representations, but incurs substantial training costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pre-training-of-masked-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constitutional AI: Harmlessness from AI Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constitutional-ai-harmlessness-from-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the RL phase, we sample from the finetuned model, use a model to evaluate which of the two samples is better, and then train a preference model from this dataset of AI preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constitutional-ai-harmlessness-from-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BNSynth: Bounded Boolean Functional Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bnsynth-bounded-boolean-functional-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a tool BNSynth, that is the first to solve the BFS problem under a given bound on the solution space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bnsynth-bounded-boolean-functional-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitY: Two-pass Direct Speech-to-speech Translation with Discrete Units</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unity-two-pass-direct-speech-to-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We enhance the model performance by subword prediction in the first-pass decoder, advanced two-pass decoder architecture design and search strategy, and better training regularization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unity-two-pass-direct-speech-to-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Vision Transformers for MobileNet Size and Speed</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-vision-transformers-for-mobilenet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the success of Vision Transformers (ViTs) in computer vision tasks, recent arts try to optimize the performance and complexity of ViTs to enable efficient deployment on mobile devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-vision-transformers-for-mobilenet</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
