<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 21:05:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SparseGNV: Generating Novel Views of Indoor Scenes with Sparse Input Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsegnv-generating-novel-views-of-indoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study to generate novel views of indoor scenes given sparse input views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsegnv-generating-novel-views-of-indoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment and Track Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-and-track-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report presents a framework called Segment And Track Anything (SAMTrack) that allows users to precisely and effectively segment and track any object in a video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-and-track-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PVT-SSD: Single-Stage 3D Object Detector with Point-Voxel Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pvt-ssd-single-stage-3d-object-detector-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to associating the two different representations is our introduced input-dependent Query Initialization module, which could efficiently generate reference points and content queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pvt-ssd-single-stage-3d-object-detector-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Inverse Scaling Law for CLIP Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-inverse-scaling-law-for-clip-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CLIP, the first foundation model that connects images and text, has enabled many recent breakthroughs in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-inverse-scaling-law-for-clip-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAHE: Hierarchical Attention for Hyper-Relational Knowledge Graphs in Global and Local Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hahe-hierarchical-attention-for-hyper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global-level attention can model the graphical structure of HKG using hypergraph dual-attention layers, while the local-level attention can learn the sequential structure inside H-Facts via heterogeneous self-attention layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hahe-hierarchical-attention-for-hyper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SalienDet: A Saliency-based Feature Enhancement Algorithm for Object Detection for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliendet-a-saliency-based-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unknown objects are one of the reasons that hinder autonomous vehicles from driving beyond the operational domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliendet-a-saliency-based-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Forward-Looking Active REtrieval augmented generation (FLARE), a generic retrieval-augmented generation method which iteratively uses a prediction of the upcoming sentence to anticipate future content, which is then utilized as a query to retrieve relevant documents to regenerate the sentence if it contains low-confidence tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuManiFlow: Ancestor-Conditioned Normalising Flows on SO(3) Manifolds for Human Pose and Shape Distribution Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humaniflow-ancestor-conditioned-normalising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular 3D human pose and shape estimation is an ill-posed problem since multiple 3D solutions can explain a 2D image of a subject.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humaniflow-ancestor-conditioned-normalising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Continual Relation Extraction by Distinguishing Analogous Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continual-relation-extraction-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel continual extraction model for analogous relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continual-relation-extraction-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Framework for Visualizing Embedding Spaces of Neural Survival Analysis Models Based on Angular Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-visualizing-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then show how these visualization ideas extend to handling raw inputs that are images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-visualizing-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpropagation-Free 4D Continuous Ant-Based Neural Topology Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backpropagation-free-4d-continuous-ant-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuous Ant-based Topology Search (CANTS) is a previously introduced novel nature-inspired neural architecture search (NAS) algorithm that is based on ant colony optimization (ACO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backpropagation-free-4d-continuous-ant-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look at LLM-Powered Generative News Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-llm-powered-generative-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized news recommendation systems have become essential tools for users to navigate the vast amount of online news content, yet existing news recommenders face significant challenges such as the cold-start problem, user profile modeling, and news content understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-llm-powered-generative-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fast topological approach for predicting anomalies in time-varying graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-topological-approach-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past decade, a persistence diagram (PD) from topological data analysis (TDA) has become a popular descriptor of shape of data with a well-defined distance between points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-topological-approach-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BanglaBook: A Large-scale Bangla Dataset for Sentiment Analysis from Book Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglabook-a-large-scale-bangla-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of consumer sentiment, as expressed through reviews, can provide a wealth of insight regarding the quality of a product.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglabook-a-large-scale-bangla-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THUIR@COLIEE 2023: More Parameters and Legal Knowledge for Legal Case Entailment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-more-parameters-and-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the approach of the THUIR team at the COLIEE 2023 Legal Case Entailment task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-more-parameters-and-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial Contrastive Knowledge Distillation for Continual Few-shot Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/serial-contrastive-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual few-shot relation extraction (RE) aims to continuously train a model for new relations with few labeled training data, of which the major challenges are the catastrophic forgetting of old relations and the overfitting caused by data sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/serial-contrastive-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THUIR@COLIEE 2023: Incorporating Structural Knowledge into Pre-trained Language Models for Legal Case Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-incorporating-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Legal case retrieval techniques play an essential role in modern intelligent legal systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-incorporating-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subword Segmental Machine Translation: Unifying Segmentation and Target Sentence Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subword-segmental-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a departure from this paradigm, called subword segmental machine translation (SSMT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subword-segmental-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General-Purpose Multilingual Document Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-purpose-multilingual-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While a large body of work leveraged MMTs to mine parallel data and induce bilingual document embeddings, much less effort has been devoted to training general-purpose (massively) multilingual document encoder that can be used for both supervised and unsupervised document-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-purpose-multilingual-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover Deepfakes: Detecting Fake Segments in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/undercover-deepfakes-detecting-fake-segments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a deepfake detection method able to address this issue by performing both frame and video level deepfake prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/undercover-deepfakes-detecting-fake-segments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collection Space Navigator: An Interactive Visualization Interface for Multidimensional Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collection-space-navigator-an-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Collection Space Navigator (CSN), a browser-based visualization tool to explore, research, and curate large collections of visual digital artifacts that are associated with multidimensional data, such as vector embeddings or tables of metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collection-space-navigator-an-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructBLIP: Towards General-purpose Vision-Language Models with Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructblip-towards-general-purpose-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct a systematic and comprehensive study on vision-language instruction tuning based on the pre-trained BLIP-2 models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructblip-towards-general-purpose-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParamNet: A Parameter-variable Network for Fast Stain Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paramnet-a-parameter-variable-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The feature of parameter variable ensures that our network has a sufficient capability for various stain normalization tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paramnet-a-parameter-variable-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fused Gromov-Wasserstein Framework for Unsupervised Knowledge Graph Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fused-gromov-wasserstein-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce FGWEA, an unsupervised entity alignment framework that leverages the Fused Gromov-Wasserstein (FGW) distance, allowing for a comprehensive comparison of entity semantics and KG structures within a joint optimization framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fused-gromov-wasserstein-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermal Bridges on Building Rooftops</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-bridges-on-building-rooftops</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thermal Bridges on Building Rooftops (TBBR) is a multi-channel remote sensing dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-bridges-on-building-rooftops</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Fine-Gray: Monotonic neural networks for competing risks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fine-gray-monotonic-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-to-event modelling, known as survival analysis, differs from standard regression as it addresses censoring in patients who do not experience the event of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fine-gray-monotonic-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfriQA: Cross-lingual Open-Retrieval Question Answering for African Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afriqa-cross-lingual-open-retrieval-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[African languages have far less in-language content available digitally, making it challenging for question answering systems to satisfy the information needs of users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afriqa-cross-lingual-open-retrieval-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebCPM: Interactive Web Search for Chinese Long-form Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webcpm-interactive-web-search-for-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We recruit annotators to search for relevant information using our interface and then answer questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webcpm-interactive-web-search-for-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data quality dimensions for fair AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-quality-dimensions-for-fair-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article we consider the problem of bias in AI systems from the point of view of Information Quality dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-quality-dimensions-for-fair-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientViT: Memory Efficient Vision Transformer with Cascaded Group Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientvit-memory-efficient-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive experiments demonstrate EfficientViT outperforms existing efficient models, striking a good trade-off between speed and accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientvit-memory-efficient-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Incremental Lifelong Learning in an Open World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-incremental-lifelong-learning-in-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we dedicate task-level prompts to capture task-specific knowledge to retain high LL performances and maintain instance-level prompts to learn knowledge shared across input samples to improve the model's generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-incremental-lifelong-learning-in-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMATCH++: Standardized and Extended Evaluation of Semantic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smatch-standardized-and-extended-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For safer and enhanced alignment, we show the feasibility of optimal alignment in a standard evaluation setup, and develop a lossless graph compression method that shrinks the search space and significantly increases efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smatch-standardized-and-extended-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Question Answering in an Open World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-question-answering-in-an-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A retrieve-then-rerank frame is further introduced to select in-context examples, which guild the LM to generate text that express knowledge for QA tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-question-answering-in-an-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Chained Image-Language Model for Video Localization and Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-chained-image-language-model-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show a comprehensive analysis, e. g., the impact of Localizer, comparisons of Localizer with other temporal localization models, pre-training/self-refinement of Localizer, and varying the number of keyframes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-chained-image-language-model-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Dense Retrieval Training with Web Anchors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dense-retrieval-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on their commonalities, we train an unsupervised dense retriever, Anchor-DR, with a contrastive learning task that matches the anchor text and the linked document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dense-retrieval-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditing Cross-Cultural Consistency of Human-Annotated Labels for Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-cross-cultural-consistency-of-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation systems increasingly depend on massive human-labeled datasets; however, the human annotators hired to generate these labels increasingly come from homogeneous backgrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-cross-cultural-consistency-of-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Scalable Adaptive Learning with Graph Neural Networks and Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scalable-adaptive-learning-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model is a sequential recommender system based on a graph neural network, which we evaluate on a population of simulated learners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scalable-adaptive-learning-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combo of Thinking and Observing for Outside-Knowledge VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combo-of-thinking-and-observing-for-outside</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some existing solutions draw external knowledge into the cross-modality space which overlooks the much vaster textual knowledge in natural-language space, while others transform the image into a text that further fuses with the textual knowledge into the natural-language space and completely abandons the use of visual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combo-of-thinking-and-observing-for-outside</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Robot Coordination and Layout Design for Automated Warehousing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-robot-coordination-and-layout-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that, even with state-of-the-art MAPF algorithms, commonly used human-designed layouts can lead to congestion for warehouses with large numbers of robots and thus have limited scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-robot-coordination-and-layout-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vārta: A Large-Scale Headline-Generation Dataset for Indic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varta-a-large-scale-headline-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present V\=arta, a large-scale multilingual dataset for headline generation in Indic languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varta-a-large-scale-headline-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say What You Mean! Large Language Models Speak Too Positively about Negative Commonsense Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/say-what-you-mean-large-language-models-speak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been widely studied for their ability to store and utilize positive knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/say-what-you-mean-large-language-models-speak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanRF: High-Fidelity Neural Radiance Fields for Humans in Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanrf-high-fidelity-neural-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To close the gap to production-level quality, we introduce HumanRF, a 4D dynamic neural scene representation that captures full-body appearance in motion from multi-view video input, and enables playback from novel, unseen viewpoints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanrf-high-fidelity-neural-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summarizing, Simplifying, and Synthesizing Medical Evidence Using GPT-3 (with Varying Success)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-simplifying-and-synthesizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models, particularly GPT-3, are able to produce high quality summaries of general domain news articles in few- and zero-shot settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-simplifying-and-synthesizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHS-Net: Learning Signed Hyper Surfaces for Oriented Normal Estimation of Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shs-net-learning-signed-hyper-surfaces-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce signed hyper surfaces (SHS), which are parameterized by multi-layer perceptron (MLP) layers, to learn to estimate oriented normals from point clouds in an end-to-end manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shs-net-learning-signed-hyper-surfaces-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Graph Representation Learning with Parameterized Decomposition &amp; Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-graph-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Proposing an effective and flexible matrix to represent a graph is a fundamental challenge that has been explored from multiple perspectives, e. g., filtering in Graph Fourier Transforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-graph-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Prompt with Depth Partitioned Cross-Modal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-prompt-with-depth-partitioned-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, soft prompt learning methods have been proposed to fine-tune large-scale vision-language pre-trained models for various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-prompt-with-depth-partitioned-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Similarity of Neural Network Models: A Survey of Functional and Representational Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-of-neural-network-models-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measuring similarity of neural networks has become an issue of great importance and research interest to understand and utilize differences of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-of-neural-network-models-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2X-Seq: A Large-Scale Sequential Dataset for Vehicle-Infrastructure Cooperative Perception and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-seq-a-large-scale-sequential-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing infrastructure and vehicle-side information to track and forecast the behaviors of surrounding traffic participants can significantly improve decision-making and safety in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-seq-a-large-scale-sequential-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CosmoPower-JAX: high-dimensional Bayesian inference with differentiable cosmological emulators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmopower-jax-high-dimensional-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then consider a combination of three Stage IV surveys, each performing a joint cosmic shear and galaxy clustering (3x2pt) analysis, for a total of 157 model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmopower-jax-high-dimensional-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optical Aberration Correction in Postprocessing using Imaging Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-aberration-correction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the spatial variation in optical aberrations, which cannot be avoided during the lens design process, recent commercial cameras have shifted some of these correction tasks from optical design to postprocessing systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-aberration-correction-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
