<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 09:16:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TextRegion: Text-Aligned Region Tokens from Frozen Image-Text Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textregion-text-aligned-region-tokens-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-text models excel at image-level tasks but struggle with detailed visual understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textregion-text-aligned-region-tokens-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZPressor: Bottleneck-Aware Compression for Scalable Feed-Forward 3DGS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zpressor-bottleneck-aware-compression-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feed-forward 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) models have recently emerged as a promising solution for novel view synthesis, enabling one-pass inference without the need for per-scene 3DGS optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zpressor-bottleneck-aware-compression-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Correcting Code Generation Using Small Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-correcting-code-generation-using-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response, we introduce CoCoS, an approach designed to enhance the ability of small language models for multi-turn code correction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-correcting-code-generation-using-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperMotion: DiT-Based Pose-Guided Human Image Animation of Complex Motions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypermotion-dit-based-pose-guided-human-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in diffusion models have significantly improved conditional video generation, particularly in the pose-guided human image animation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypermotion-dit-based-pose-guided-human-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebDancer: Towards Autonomous Information Seeking Agency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webdancer-towards-autonomous-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We instantiate this framework in a web agent based on the ReAct, WebDancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webdancer-towards-autonomous-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoMatching++: Parameter- and Data-Efficient Arbitrary-Shaped Video Text Spotting and Benchmarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gomatching-parameter-and-data-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that GoMatching++ and the ArTVideo benchmark will drive future advancements in video text spotting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gomatching-parameter-and-data-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoKI: Low-damage Knowledge Implanting of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loki-low-damage-knowledge-implanting-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning adapts pretrained models for specific tasks but poses the risk of catastrophic forgetting (CF), where critical knowledge from pre-training is overwritten.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loki-low-damage-knowledge-implanting-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniTalk: Towards Universal Active Speaker Detection in Real World Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitalk-towards-universal-active-speaker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present UniTalk, a novel dataset specifically designed for the task of active speaker detection, emphasizing challenging scenarios to enhance model generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitalk-towards-universal-active-speaker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatPD: An LLM-driven Paper-Dataset Networking System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatpd-an-llm-driven-paper-dataset-networking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific research heavily depends on suitable datasets for method validation, but existing academic platforms with dataset management like PapersWithCode suffer from inefficiencies in their manual workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatpd-an-llm-driven-paper-dataset-networking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shapley Value-driven Data Pruning for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-value-driven-data-pruning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we propose Shapley Value-driven Valuation (SVV), a framework that evaluates interactions based on their objective impact on model training rather than subjective intent assumptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapley-value-driven-data-pruning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Isotropic Median Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-isotropic-median-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Median filtering is a cornerstone of computational image processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-isotropic-median-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RenderFormer: Transformer-based Neural Rendering of Triangle Meshes with Global Illumination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renderformer-transformer-based-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present RenderFormer, a neural rendering pipeline that directly renders an image from a triangle-based representation of a scene with full global illumination effects and that does not require per-scene training or fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/renderformer-transformer-based-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Vision Encoder Grafting via LLM Surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-vision-encoder-grafting-via-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision encoders trained on the surrogate can then be directly transferred to the larger model, a process we call zero-shot grafting -- when plugged directly into the full-size target LLM, the grafted pair surpasses the encoder-surrogate pair and, on some benchmarks, even performs on par with full decoder training with the target LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-vision-encoder-grafting-via-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIGNETTE: Socially Grounded Bias Evaluation for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vignette-socially-grounded-bias-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While bias in large language models (LLMs) is well-studied, similar concerns in vision-language models (VLMs) have received comparatively less attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vignette-socially-grounded-bias-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VME: A Satellite Imagery Dataset and Benchmark for Detecting Vehicles in the Middle East and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vme-a-satellite-imagery-dataset-and-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we present the Vehicles in the Middle East (VME) dataset, designed explicitly for vehicle detection in high-resolution satellite images from Middle Eastern countries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vme-a-satellite-imagery-dataset-and-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoLLaVA-8K: Scaling Remote-Sensing Multimodal Large Language Models to 8K Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geollava-8k-scaling-remote-sensing-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address data scarcity, we introduce SuperRS-VQA (avg.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geollava-8k-scaling-remote-sensing-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLMC-based Resource Adequacy Assessment with Active Learning Trained Surrogate Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlmc-based-resource-adequacy-assessment-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For large-scale systems, the efficiency gains from surrogate models are often offset by the substantial time required for labeling training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlmc-based-resource-adequacy-assessment-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand, Think, and Answer: Advancing Visual Reasoning with Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understand-think-and-answer-advancing-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) have recently demonstrated remarkable visual understanding performance on both vision-language and vision-centric tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understand-think-and-answer-advancing-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stationary MMD Points for Cubature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stationary-mmd-points-for-cubature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Approximation of a target probability distribution using a finite set of points is a problem of fundamental importance, arising in cubature, data compression, and optimisation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stationary-mmd-points-for-cubature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling External Knowledge Input Beyond Context Windows of LLMs via Multi-Agent Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-external-knowledge-input-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the limited context window of LLMs obstructs scaling the amount of external knowledge input, prohibiting further improvement, especially for tasks requiring significant amount of external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-external-knowledge-input-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Polarization Stacked Intelligent Metasurfaces for Holographic MIMO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-polarization-stacked-intelligent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the limited wave domain signal processing capabilities of traditional single-polarized stacked intelligent metasurfaces (SIMs) in holographic multiple-input multiple-output (HMIMO) systems, which stems from limited integration space, this paper proposes a dual-polarized SIM (DPSIM) architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-polarization-stacked-intelligent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Multi-player Bandits for Explainable Recommendation Diversification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-multi-player-bandits-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing recommender systems tend to prioritize items closely aligned with users' historical interactions, inevitably trapping users in the dilemma of ``filter bubble''.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-multi-player-bandits-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor expansion-based Kolmogorov-Arnold network for blind image quality assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taylor-expansion-based-kolmogorov-arnold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kolmogorov-Arnold Network (KAN) has attracted growing interest for its strong function approximation capability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taylor-expansion-based-kolmogorov-arnold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Representation Steering for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-representation-steering-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Steering methods for language models (LMs) seek to provide fine-grained and interpretable control over model generations by variously changing model inputs, weights, or representations to adjust behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-representation-steering-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVERT: A Benchmark for Over-Refusal Evaluation on Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overt-a-benchmark-for-over-refusal-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-Image (T2I) models have achieved remarkable success in generating visual content from text inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overt-a-benchmark-for-over-refusal-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardiac Digital Twins at Scale from MRI: Open Tools and Representative Models from ~55000 UK Biobank Participants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardiac-digital-twins-at-scale-from-mri-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A cardiac digital twin is a virtual replica of a patient's heart for screening, diagnosis, prognosis, risk assessment, and treatment planning of cardiovascular diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardiac-digital-twins-at-scale-from-mri-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSocial: Blockchain-based Decentralized Social Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desocial-blockchain-based-decentralized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Web 2. 0 social platforms are inherently centralized, with user data and algorithmic decisions controlled by the platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desocial-blockchain-based-decentralized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A domain adaptation neural network for digital twin-supported fault diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-domain-adaptation-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, applying DANN to a baseline CNN model improves its accuracy from 70. 00% to 80. 22% on real-world test data, demonstrating the effectiveness of domain adaptation in bridging the sim-to-real gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-domain-adaptation-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastFace: Tuning Identity Preservation in Distilled Diffusion via Guidance and Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastface-tuning-identity-preservation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In latest years plethora of identity-preserving adapters for a personalized generation with diffusion models have been released.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastface-tuning-identity-preservation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoBiS: Robust Binary Segmentation for High-Resolution Industrial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robis-robust-binary-segmentation-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust unsupervised anomaly detection (AD) in real-world scenarios is an important task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robis-robust-binary-segmentation-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Where to Learn: Training Distribution Selection for Provable OOD Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-where-to-learn-training-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) generalization remains a fundamental challenge in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-where-to-learn-training-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeatInv: Spatially resolved mapping from feature space to input space using conditional diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featinv-spatially-resolved-mapping-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Internal representations are crucial for understanding deep neural networks, such as their properties and reasoning patterns, but remain difficult to interpret.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/featinv-spatially-resolved-mapping-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SageAttention2++: A More Efficient Implementation of SageAttention2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention2-a-more-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further accelerate SageAttention2, we propose to utilize the faster instruction of FP8 Matmul accumulated in FP16.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention2-a-more-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVP: Multi-source Voice Pathology detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvp-multi-source-voice-pathology-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice disorders significantly impact patient quality of life, yet non-invasive automated diagnosis remains under-explored due to both the scarcity of pathological voice data, and the variability in recording sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvp-multi-source-voice-pathology-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Active Inference Agents for Delayed and Long-Horizon Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-active-inference-agents-for-delayed-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent success of world-model agents, which extend the core idea of model-based reinforcement learning by learning a differentiable model for sample-efficient control across diverse tasks, active inference (AIF) offers a complementary, neuroscience-grounded paradigm that unifies perception, learning, and action within a single probabilistic framework powered by a generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-active-inference-agents-for-delayed-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on Strong-Weak Model Collaboration for Repo-level Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-strong-weak-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study cost-efficient collaboration between strong and weak language models for repository-level code generation, where the weak model handles simpler tasks at lower cost, and the most challenging tasks are delegated to the strong model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-strong-weak-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExAnte: A Benchmark for Ex-Ante Inference in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exante-a-benchmark-for-ex-ante-inference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) face significant challenges in ex-ante reasoning, where analysis, inference, or predictions must be made without access to information from future events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exante-a-benchmark-for-ex-ante-inference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAME-MoE: A Transparent End-to-End Research Platform for Mixture-of-Experts Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flame-moe-a-transparent-end-to-end-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent large language models such as Gemini-1. 5, DeepSeek-V3, and Llama-4 increasingly adopt Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) architectures, which offer strong efficiency-performance trade-offs by activating only a fraction of the model per token.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flame-moe-a-transparent-end-to-end-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISCOVER: Automated Curricula for Sparse-Reward Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discover-automated-curricula-for-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that solving complex and high-dimensional tasks requires solving simpler tasks that are relevant to the target task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discover-automated-curricula-for-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMPerspective: Do MLLMs Understand Perspective? A Comprehensive Benchmark for Perspective Perception, Reasoning, and Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmperspective-do-mllms-understand-perspective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding perspective is fundamental to human visual perception, yet the extent to which multimodal large language models (MLLMs) internalize perspective geometry remains unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmperspective-do-mllms-understand-perspective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alita: Generalist Agent Enabling Scalable Agentic Reasoning with Minimal Predefinition and Maximal Self-Evolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alita-generalist-agent-enabling-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For Maximal self-evolution, we enable the creativity of Alita by providing a suite of general-purpose components to autonomously construct, refine, and reuse external capabilities by generating task-related model context protocols (MCPs) from open source, which contributes to scalable agentic reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alita-generalist-agent-enabling-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MineAnyBuild: Benchmarking Spatial Planning for Open-world AI Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineanybuild-benchmarking-spatial-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a step further to build a comprehensive benchmark called MineAnyBuild, aiming to evaluate the spatial planning ability of open-world AI agents in the Minecraft game.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineanybuild-benchmarking-spatial-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TrojanStego: Your Language Model Can Secretly Be A Steganographic Privacy Leaking Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trojanstego-your-language-model-can-secretly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) become integrated into sensitive workflows, concerns grow over their potential to leak confidential information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trojanstego-your-language-model-can-secretly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Extrapolative Sequence Transformations from Markov Chains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-extrapolative-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our approach uses selected states from Markov chains as a source of training data for an autoregressive model, which is then able to efficiently generate novel sequences that extrapolate along the sequence-level properties of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-extrapolative-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Trust Bellman Updates: Selective State-Adaptive Regularization for Offline RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-trust-bellman-updates-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline reinforcement learning (RL) aims to learn an effective policy from a static dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-trust-bellman-updates-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Interference and Correlation in Spatial Experimental Designs: A Causal Graph Cut Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-interference-and-correlation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the design of spatial experiments to optimize the amount of information derived from the experimental data and enhance the accuracy of the resulting causal effect estimator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-interference-and-correlation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinLoRA: Benchmarking LoRA Methods for Fine-Tuning LLMs on Financial Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finlora-benchmarking-lora-methods-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the open-source FinLoRA project that benchmarks LoRA methods on both general and highly professional financial tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finlora-benchmarking-lora-methods-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoiceStar: Robust Zero-Shot Autoregressive TTS with Duration Control and Extrapolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voicestar-robust-zero-shot-autoregressive-tts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CPM training also helps to mitigate the training/inference mismatch, and significantly improves the quality of the generated speech in terms of speaker similarity and intelligibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voicestar-robust-zero-shot-autoregressive-tts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Freezing: Sparse Tuning Enhances Plasticity in Continual Learning with Pre-Trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-freezing-sparse-tuning-enhances</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning with Pre-trained Models holds great promise for efficient adaptation across sequential tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-freezing-sparse-tuning-enhances</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grokking ExPLAIND: Unifying Model, Data, and Training Attribution to Study Model Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokking-explaind-unifying-model-data-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Post-hoc interpretability methods typically attribute a model's behavior to its components, data, or training trajectory in isolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grokking-explaind-unifying-model-data-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
