<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 21:07:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>WSI-VQA: Interpreting Whole Slide Images by Generative Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wsi-vqa-interpreting-whole-slide-images-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abundant experience is required for pathologists to achieve accurate and reliable diagnostic results of whole slide images (WSI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wsi-vqa-interpreting-whole-slide-images-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iLLM-TSC: Integration reinforcement learning and large language model for traffic signal control policy improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illm-tsc-integration-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the existing RL-based TSC system often overlooks imperfect observations caused by degraded communication, such as packet loss, delays, and noise, as well as rare real-life events not included in the reward function, such as unconsidered emergency vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illm-tsc-integration-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Continual Knowledge Graph Embedding via Incremental LoRA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-continual-knowledge-graph-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a fast CKGE framework (\model), incorporating an incremental low-rank adapter (\mec) mechanism to efficiently acquire new knowledge while preserving old knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-continual-knowledge-graph-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stranger Danger! Identifying and Avoiding Unpredictable Pedestrians in RL-based Social Robot Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stranger-danger-identifying-and-avoiding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning (RL) methods for social robot navigation show great success navigating robots through large crowds of people, but the performance of these learning-based methods tends to degrade in particularly challenging or unfamiliar situations due to the models' dependency on representative training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stranger-danger-identifying-and-avoiding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Physical Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyber-physical-games</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe a formulation of multi-agents operating within a Cyber-Physical System, resulting in collaborative or adversarial games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyber-physical-games</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaPI: Facilitating DNN Model Adaptivity for Efficient Private Inference in Edge Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapi-facilitating-dnn-model-adaptivity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Private inference (PI) has emerged as a promising solution to execute computations on encrypted data, safeguarding user privacy and model parameters in edge computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapi-facilitating-dnn-model-adaptivity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Vessel Graph Generation Using Denoising Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vessel-graph-generation-using-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blood vessel networks, represented as 3D graphs, help predict disease biomarkers, simulate blood flow, and aid in synthetic image generation, relevant in both clinical and pre-clinical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vessel-graph-generation-using-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGRNet: Local-Global Reciprocal Network for Uterine Fibroid Segmentation in Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgrnet-local-global-reciprocal-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we collect and annotate the first ultrasound video dataset with 100 videos for uterine fibroid segmentation (UFUV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lgrnet-local-global-reciprocal-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-STaR: Self-Training Enables Video Instruction Tuning with Any Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-star-self-training-enables-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of Large Vision Language Models (LVLMs) is dependent on the size and quality of their training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-star-self-training-enables-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking Trees for Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-trees-for-tabular-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We herein describe UnmaskingTrees, a method and open-source software package for tabular data generation and, especially, imputation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-trees-for-tabular-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D Contrastive Superflows are Dense 3D Representation Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-contrastive-superflows-are-dense-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of autonomous driving, accurate 3D perception is the foundation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-contrastive-superflows-are-dense-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Vision and Language Pretraining with Large-Scale Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vision-and-language-pretraining-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Vision-Language Pre-training (3D-VLP) aims to provide a pre-train model which can bridge 3D scenes with natural language, which is an important technique for embodied intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vision-and-language-pretraining-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning local equivariant representations for quantum operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-local-equivariant-representations-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting quantum operator matrices such as Hamiltonian, overlap, and density matrices in the density functional theory (DFT) framework is crucial for understanding material properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-local-equivariant-representations-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deciphering the Role of Representation Disentanglement: Investigating Compositional Generalization in CLIP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deciphering-the-role-of-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study reveals that the disentanglement of image and text representations, particularly with respect to their compositional elements, plays a crucial role in improving the generalization of CLIP models in out-of-distribution settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deciphering-the-role-of-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Semantic Profiling Abilities of LLMs for Natural Language Utterances in Data Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-semantic-profiling-abilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we evaluate four publicly available LLMs (GPT-4, Gemini-Pro, Llama3, and Mixtral), investigating their ability to comprehend utterances even in the presence of uncertainty and identify the relevant data context and visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-semantic-profiling-abilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPFF: Hierarchical Locally Supervised Learning with Patch Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpff-hierarchical-locally-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we propose a novel model called HPFF that performs hierarchical locally supervised learning and patch-level feature computation on the auxiliary networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpff-hierarchical-locally-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVWorld: A Multimodal World Model for Autonomous Driving via Unified BEV Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevworld-a-multimodal-world-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The world model consists of two parts: the multi-modal tokenizer and the latent BEV sequence diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevworld-a-multimodal-world-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One system for learning and remembering episodes and rules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-system-for-learning-and-remembering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans can learn individual episodes and generalizable rules and also successfully retain both kinds of acquired knowledge over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-system-for-learning-and-remembering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedMRL: Data Heterogeneity Aware Federated Multi-agent Deep Reinforcement Learning for Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmrl-data-heterogeneity-aware-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assess our approach using two publicly available real-world medical datasets, and the results demonstrate that FedMRL significantly outperforms state-of-the-art techniques, showing its efficacy in addressing data heterogeneity in federated learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmrl-data-heterogeneity-aware-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momentum Auxiliary Network for Supervised Local Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/momentum-auxiliary-network-for-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supervised local learning, which segments the network into multiple local blocks updated by independent auxiliary networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/momentum-auxiliary-network-for-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$R^2$-Guard: Robust Reasoning Enabled LLM Guardrail via Knowledge-Enhanced Logical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-2-guard-robust-reasoning-enabled-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then encode safety knowledge among different categories as first-order logical rules and embed them into a probabilistic graphic model (PGM) based reasoning component.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-2-guard-robust-reasoning-enabled-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba-FSCIL: Dynamic Adaptation with Selective State Space Model for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-fscil-dynamic-adaptation-with-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dual design enables the model to maintain the robust features of base classes, while adaptively learning distinctive feature shifts for novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-fscil-dynamic-adaptation-with-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Multi-View Hand Reconstruction Using Inverse Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-multi-view-hand-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing high-fidelity hand models with intricate textures plays a crucial role in enhancing human-object interaction and advancing real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-multi-view-hand-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wavelet Convolutions for Large Receptive Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-convolutions-for-large-receptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there have been attempts to increase the kernel size of Convolutional Neural Nets (CNNs) to mimic the global receptive field of Vision Transformers' (ViTs) self-attention blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavelet-convolutions-for-large-receptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Representation Learning for Probabilistic Travel Time Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, we estimate the probability distribution of the travel time of a queried trip conditional on the completed trips that are spatiotemporally adjacent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes to Seconds: Speeded-up DDPM-based Image Inpainting with Coarse-to-Fine Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minutes-to-seconds-speeded-up-ddpm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we introduce a skip-step sampling scheme of Denoising Diffusion Implicit Models (DDIM) for the denoising process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minutes-to-seconds-speeded-up-ddpm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dynamic Net Architecture: Learning Robust and Holistic Visual Representations Through Self-Organizing Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dynamic-net-architecture-learning-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel intelligent-system architecture called "Dynamic Net Architecture" (DNA) that relies on recurrence-stabilized networks and discuss it in application to vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dynamic-net-architecture-learning-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadiomicsFill-Mammo: Synthetic Mammogram Mass Manipulation with Radiomics Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiomicsfill-mammo-synthetic-mammogram-mass</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach also allows for the incorporation of essential clinical variables, such as BI-RADS and breast density, alongside radiomics features as conditions for mass generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiomicsfill-mammo-synthetic-mammogram-mass</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANOLE: An Open, Autoregressive, Native Large Multimodal Models for Interleaved Image-Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anole-an-open-autoregressive-native-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous open-source large multimodal models (LMMs) have faced several limitations: (1) they often lack native integration, requiring adapters to align visual representations with pre-trained large language models (LLMs); (2) many are restricted to single-modal generation; (3) while some support multimodal generation, they rely on separate diffusion models for visual modeling and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anole-an-open-autoregressive-native-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSN: Infinite Representations of Dynamic 3D Scenes from Monocular Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osn-infinite-representations-of-dynamic-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has long been challenging to recover the underlying dynamic 3D scene representations from a monocular RGB video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osn-infinite-representations-of-dynamic-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenCIL: Benchmarking Out-of-Distribution Detection in Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencil-benchmarking-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class incremental learning (CIL) aims to learn a model that can not only incrementally accommodate new classes, but also maintain the learned knowledge of old classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencil-benchmarking-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How DNNs break the Curse of Dimensionality: Compositionality and Symmetry Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-dnns-break-the-curse-of-dimensionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that deep neural networks (DNNs) can efficiently learn any composition of functions with bounded $F_{1}$-norm, which allows DNNs to break the curse of dimensionality in ways that shallow networks cannot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-dnns-break-the-curse-of-dimensionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-clue Consistency Learning to Bridge Gaps Between General and Oriented Object in Semi-supervised Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-clue-consistency-learning-to-bridge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We experimentally find three gaps between general and oriented object detection in semi-supervised learning: 1) Sampling inconsistency: the common center sampling is not suitable for oriented objects with larger aspect ratios when selecting positive labels from labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-clue-consistency-learning-to-bridge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-term Object Interaction Anticipation with Disentangled Object Detection @ Ego4D Short Term Object Interaction Anticipation Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-term-object-interaction-anticipation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Short-term object interaction anticipation is an important task in egocentric video analysis, including precise predictions of future interactions and their timings as well as the categories and positions of the involved active objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-term-object-interaction-anticipation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AID-AppEAL: Automatic Image Dataset and Algorithm for Content Appeal Enhancement and Assessment Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aid-appeal-automatic-image-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Image Content Appeal Assessment (ICAA), a novel metric that quantifies the level of positive interest an image's content generates for viewers, such as the appeal of food in a photograph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aid-appeal-automatic-image-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KG-FPQ: Evaluating Factuality Hallucination in LLMs with Knowledge Graph-based False Premise Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-fpq-evaluating-factuality-hallucination-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have demonstrated that large language models (LLMs) are susceptible to being misled by false premise questions (FPQs), leading to errors in factual knowledge, know as factuality hallucination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-fpq-evaluating-factuality-hallucination-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-based Benchmarking for Causal Structure Learning in Gene Perturbation Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-benchmarking-for-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we present $\textit{CausalRegNet}$, a multiplicative effect structural causal model that allows for generating observational and interventional data incorporating context-specific properties, with a focus on the setting of gene perturbation experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-benchmarking-for-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change-Point Detection in Industrial Data Streams based on Online Dynamic Mode Decomposition with Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-point-detection-in-industrial-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel change-point detection method based on online Dynamic Mode Decomposition with control (ODMDwC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-point-detection-in-industrial-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLIM: Spuriousness Mitigation with Minimal Human Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-spuriousness-mitigation-with-minimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies highlight that deep learning models often learn spurious features mistakenly linked to labels, compromising their reliability in real-world scenarios where such correlations do not hold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-spuriousness-mitigation-with-minimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus on the Whole Character: Discriminative Character Modeling for Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-on-the-whole-character-discriminative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above issues, we propose a novel method that enriches the character features to enhance the discriminability of characters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-on-the-whole-character-discriminative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fostering Trust and Quantifying Value of AI and ML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fostering-trust-and-quantifying-value-of-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Producing ever more trustworthy machine learning inferences is a path to increase the value of products (i. e., increased trust in the results) and to engage in conversations with users to gather feedback to improve products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fostering-trust-and-quantifying-value-of-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMBox: A Comprehensive Library for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmbox-a-comprehensive-library-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the research on large language models (LLMs), this paper presents a comprehensive and unified library, LLMBox, to ease the development, use, and evaluation of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmbox-a-comprehensive-library-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pan-denoising: Guided Hyperspectral Image Denoising via Weighted Represent Coefficient Total Variation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pan-denoising-guided-hyperspectral-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel paradigm for hyperspectral image (HSI) denoising, which is termed \textit{pan-denoising}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pan-denoising-guided-hyperspectral-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C2C: Component-to-Composition Learning for Zero-Shot Compositional Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2c-component-to-composition-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For evaluating the task, we construct a new benchmark, Something-composition (Sth-com), based on the widely used Something-Something V2 dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2c-component-to-composition-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme Analysis using LLM-based Contextual Information and U-net Encapsulated Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meme-analysis-using-llm-based-contextual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A meme is social media content with which the creator tries to convey a certain idea in public via the internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meme-analysis-using-llm-based-contextual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonrigid Reconstruction of Freehand Ultrasound without a Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonrigid-reconstruction-of-freehand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by a) the observed nonrigid deformation due to soft tissue motion during scanning, and b) the highly sensitive prediction of rigid transformation, this study investigates the methods and their benefits in predicting nonrigid transformations for reconstructing 3D US.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonrigid-reconstruction-of-freehand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural Generalization in Autonomous Cyber Incident Response with Message-Passing Neural Networks and Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-generalization-in-autonomous-cyber</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that agents for automated incident response based on machine learning need to handle changes in network structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-generalization-in-autonomous-cyber</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-label Learning with Random Circular Vectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-learning-with-random-circular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The extreme multi-label classification~(XMC) task involves learning a classifier that can predict from a large label set the most relevant subset of labels for a data instance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-learning-with-random-circular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RHRSegNet: Relighting High-Resolution Night-Time Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhrsegnet-relighting-high-resolution-night</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model then feeds the lightened scene feature maps into a high-resolution network for scene segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhrsegnet-relighting-high-resolution-night</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Loops to Oops: Fallback Behaviors of Language Models Under Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-loops-to-oops-fallback-behaviors-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments reveal a clear and consistent ordering of fallback behaviors, across all these axes: the more advanced an LLM is (i. e., trained on more tokens, has more parameters, or instruction-tuned), its fallback behavior shifts from sequence repetitions, to degenerate text, and then to hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-loops-to-oops-fallback-behaviors-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
