<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:12:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Diffusion Models with State Space Backbone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-diffusion-models-with-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We endeavor to train diffusion models for image data, wherein the traditional U-Net backbone is supplanted by a state space backbone, functioning on raw patches or latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-diffusion-models-with-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Route Among Specialized Experts for Zero-Shot Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-route-among-specialized-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike past methods that learn to route among specialized models, PHATGOOSE explores the possibility that zero-shot generalization will be improved if different experts can be adaptively chosen for each token and at each layer in the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-route-among-specialized-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REMEDI: Corrective Transformations for Improved Neural Entropy Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remedi-corrective-transformations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The approach combines the minimization of the cross-entropy for simple, adaptive base models and the estimation of their deviation, in terms of the relative entropy, from the data density.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remedi-corrective-transformations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate LoRA-Finetuning Quantization of LLMs via Information Retention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-lora-finetuning-quantization-of-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel IR-QLoRA for pushing quantized LLMs with LoRA to be highly accurate through information retention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-lora-finetuning-quantization-of-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classifying Nodes in Graphs without GNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifying-nodes-in-graphs-without-gnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, distillation methods succeeded in eliminating the use of GNNs at test time but they still require them during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifying-nodes-in-graphs-without-gnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking Neural Network Enhanced Hand Gesture Recognition Using Low-Cost Single-photon Avalanche Diode Array</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-network-enhanced-hand-gesture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a compact spiking convolutional neural network (SCNN) and spiking multilayer perceptron (SMLP) to recognize ten different gestures in dark and bright light environments, using a $9. 6 single-photon avalanche diode (SPAD) array.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-network-enhanced-hand-gesture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Timescale Ensemble Q-learning for Markov Decision Process Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-timescale-ensemble-q-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning (RL) is a classical tool to solve network control or policy optimization problems in unknown environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-timescale-ensemble-q-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Contrastive Alignment of Language Models with Explicit Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-contrastive-alignment-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing alignment methods, such as Direct Preference Optimization (DPO), are mainly tailored for pairwise preference data where rewards are implicitly defined rather than explicitly given.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-contrastive-alignment-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Need One Color Space: An Efficient Network for Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-need-one-color-space-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we design a novel Color and Intensity Decoupling Network (CIDNet) with two branches dedicated to processing the decoupled image brightness and color in the HVI space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-need-one-color-space-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Chain-of-Thought Reasoning Guided by Evolutionary Algorithms in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-chain-of-thought-reasoning-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance across diverse tasks and exhibited impressive reasoning abilities by applying zero-shot Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-chain-of-thought-reasoning-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPHINX-X: Scaling Data and Parameters for a Family of Multi-modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sphinx-x-scaling-data-and-parameters-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SPHINX-X, an extensive Multimodality Large Language Model (MLLM) series developed upon SPHINX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sphinx-x-scaling-data-and-parameters-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftEDA: Rethinking Rule-Based Data Augmentation with Soft Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softeda-rethinking-rule-based-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rule-based text data augmentation is widely used for NLP tasks due to its simplicity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softeda-rethinking-rule-based-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Optimization for Jailbreaking LLMs via Subconscious Exploitation and Echopraxia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-optimization-for-jailbreaking-llms-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have become prevalent across diverse sectors, transforming human life with their extraordinary reasoning and comprehension abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-optimization-for-jailbreaking-llms-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing for ROC Curves on Class-Imbalanced Data by Training over a Family of Loss Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-for-roc-curves-on-class-imbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although binary classification is a well-studied problem in computer vision, training reliable classifiers under severe class imbalance remains a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-for-roc-curves-on-class-imbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Prune Now: Structured Pruning of LLMs with only Forward Passes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-prune-now-structured-pruning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the generational gap in available hardware between lay practitioners and the most endowed institutions, LLMs are becoming increasingly inaccessible as they grow in size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-prune-now-structured-pruning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIGC: Multi-Instance Generation Controller for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/migc-multi-instance-generation-controller-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we aggregate all the shaded instances to provide the necessary information for accurately generating multiple instances in stable diffusion (SD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/migc-multi-instance-generation-controller-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ordinal Regression Framework for a Deep Learning Based Severity Assessment for Chest Radiographs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ordinal-regression-framework-for-a-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the application of ordinal regression methods for categorizing disease severity in chest radiographs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ordinal-regression-framework-for-a-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptCrypt: Prompt Encryption for Secure Communication with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptcrypt-prompt-encryption-for-secure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these models offer substantial benefits in terms of accessibility and functionality, they also introduce significant privacy concerns: the transmission and storage of user data in cloud infrastructures pose substantial risks of data breaches and unauthorized access to sensitive information; even if the transmission and storage of data is encrypted, the LLM service provider itself still knows the real contents of the data, preventing individuals or entities from confidently using such LLM services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptcrypt-prompt-encryption-for-secure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Sensitive Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning in Network Aggregative Markov Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-multi-agent-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under a set of assumptions, we prove the convergence of the algorithm to a subjective notion of Markov perfect Nash equilibrium in NAMGs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-multi-agent-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get What You Want, Not What You Don't: Image Content Suppression for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get-what-you-want-not-what-you-don-t-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these models struggle to effectively suppress the generation of undesired content, which is explicitly requested to be omitted from the generated image in the prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get-what-you-want-not-what-you-don-t-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTSA-SNN: A Multi-modal Time Series Analysis Model Based on Spiking Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtsa-snn-a-multi-modal-time-series-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a Multi-modal Time Series Analysis Model Based on Spiking Neural Network (MTSA-SNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtsa-snn-a-multi-modal-time-series-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffSpeaker: Speech-Driven 3D Facial Animation with Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffspeaker-speech-driven-3d-facial-animation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We suspect this is due to a shortage of paired audio-4D data, which is crucial for the Transformer to effectively perform as a denoiser within the Diffusion framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffspeaker-speech-driven-3d-facial-animation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining Gender and Racial Bias in Large Vision-Language Models Using a Novel Dataset of Parallel Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-gender-and-racial-bias-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following on recent advances in large language models (LLMs) and subsequent chat models, a new wave of large vision-language models (LVLMs) has emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-gender-and-racial-bias-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Activation Functions for Predictive Modeling with Sparse Experimental Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-activation-functions-for-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A pivotal aspect in the design of neural networks lies in selecting activation functions, crucial for introducing nonlinear structures that capture intricate input-output patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-activation-functions-for-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Permute-and-Flip: An optimally robust and watermarkable decoder for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/permute-and-flip-an-optimally-robust-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new decoding method called Permute-and-Flip (PF) decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/permute-and-flip-an-optimally-robust-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Large Language Models for Reasoning through Reverse Curriculum Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-large-language-models-for-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose R$^3$: Learning Reasoning through Reverse Curriculum Reinforcement Learning (RL), a novel method that employs only outcome supervision to achieve the benefits of process supervision for large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-large-language-models-for-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Temporally-Aware Reinforcement Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-temporally-aware-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple augmentation to two existing objective discovery approaches that allows the discovered algorithm to dynamically update its objective function throughout the agent's training procedure, resulting in expressive schedules and increased generalization across different training horizons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-temporally-aware-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirichlet Flow Matching with Applications to DNA Sequence Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirichlet-flow-matching-with-applications-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we provide distilled Dirichlet flow matching, which enables one-step sequence generation with minimal performance hits, resulting in $O(L)$ speedups compared to autoregressive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirichlet-flow-matching-with-applications-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting Fairness: Artificial Intelligence as Game Players</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-fairness-artificial-intelligence-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilitarian games such as dictator games to measure fairness have been studied in the social sciences for decades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-fairness-artificial-intelligence-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UAV-Rain1k: A Benchmark for Raindrop Removal from UAV Aerial Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uav-rain1k-a-benchmark-for-raindrop-removal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Raindrops adhering to the lens of UAVs can obstruct visibility of the background scene and degrade image quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uav-rain1k-a-benchmark-for-raindrop-removal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden in Plain Sight: Undetectable Adversarial Bias Attacks on Vulnerable Patient Populations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-in-plain-sight-undetectable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proliferation of artificial intelligence (AI) in radiology has shed light on the risk of deep learning (DL) models exacerbating clinical biases towards vulnerable patient populations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-in-plain-sight-undetectable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual E5 Text Embeddings: A Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-e5-text-embeddings-a-technical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report presents the training methodology and evaluation results of the open-source multilingual E5 text embedding models, released in mid-2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-e5-text-embeddings-a-technical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoAugment Is What You Need: Enhancing Rule-based Augmentation Methods in Low-resource Regimes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoaugment-is-what-you-need-enhancing-rule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text data augmentation is a complex problem due to the discrete nature of sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoaugment-is-what-you-need-enhancing-rule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A High Dimensional Model for Adversarial Training: Geometry and Trade-Offs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-high-dimensional-model-for-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work investigates adversarial training in the context of margin-based linear classifiers in the high-dimensional regime where the dimension $d$ and the number of data points $n$ diverge with a fixed ratio $\alpha = n / d$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-high-dimensional-model-for-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Multigrid Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-multigrid-architectures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that a fixed neural network without dense layers can not realize an efficient iterative method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-multigrid-architectures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Propagation for Unsupervised Graph Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-propagation-for-unsupervised-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by our empirical analysis, we reevaluate the role of GNNs in graph domain adaptation and uncover the pivotal role of the propagation process in GNNs for adapting to different graph domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-propagation-for-unsupervised-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graphs Meet Multi-Modal Learning: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graphs-meet-multi-modal-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we carefully review over 300 articles, focusing on KG-aware research in two principal aspects: KG-driven Multi-Modal (KG4MM) learning, where KGs support multi-modal tasks, and Multi-Modal Knowledge Graph (MM4KG), which extends KG studies into the MMKG realm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graphs-meet-multi-modal-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating White-Box Attacks for On-Device Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-white-box-attacks-for-on-device</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings emphasize the need for developers to carefully consider their model deployment strategies, and use white-box methods to evaluate the vulnerability of on-device models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-white-box-attacks-for-on-device</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Synthetic Continual Semantic Segmentation for Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-synthetic-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem becomes worse when it limits releasing the dataset of the old instruments for the old model due to privacy concerns and the unavailability of the data for the new or updated version of the instruments for the continual learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-synthetic-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandwiched Compression: Repurposing Standard Codecs with Neural Network Wrappers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sandwiched-compression-repurposing-standard</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through a variety of examples, we apply the sandwich architecture to sources with different numbers of channels, higher resolution, higher dynamic range, and perceptual distortion measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sandwiched-compression-repurposing-standard</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPTs Are Multilingual Annotators for Sequence Generation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpts-are-multilingual-annotators-for-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the conventional approach of data annotation through crowdsourcing is both time-consuming and expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpts-are-multilingual-annotators-for-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Gradient Flow for Robust N:M Sparsity Training in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-gradient-flow-for-robust-n-m</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the effectiveness of existing sparse training recipes at \textit{high-sparsity regions} and argue that these methods fail to sustain the model quality on par with low-sparsity regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-gradient-flow-for-robust-n-m</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics Informed and Data Driven Simulation of Underwater Images via Residual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-and-data-driven-simulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a deep learning-based architecture to automatically simulate the underwater effects where only a dehazing-like image formation equation is known to the network, and the additional degradation due to the other unknown factors if inferred in a data-driven way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-and-data-driven-simulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moco: A Learnable Meta Optimizer for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moco-a-learnable-meta-optimizer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach, Moco, learns a graph neural network that updates the solution construction procedure based on features extracted from the current search state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moco-a-learnable-meta-optimizer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Sampling Temperature on Problem Solving in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-sampling-temperature-on-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research study, we empirically investigate the effect of sampling temperature on the performance of Large Language Models (LLMs) on various problem-solving tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-sampling-temperature-on-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triplet Interaction Improves Graph Transformers: Accurate Molecular Graph Learning with Triplet Graph Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-interaction-improves-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also obtain SOTA results on QM9, MOLPCBA, and LIT-PCBA molecular property prediction benchmarks via transfer learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-interaction-improves-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientViT-SAM: Accelerated Segment Anything Model Without Performance Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientvit-sam-accelerated-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the training, we begin with the knowledge distillation from the SAM-ViT-H image encoder to EfficientViT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientvit-sam-accelerated-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bayesian Approach to Online Learning for Contextual Restless Bandits with Applications to Public Health</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-online-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Restless multi-armed bandits (RMABs) are used to model sequential resource allocation in public health intervention programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-online-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-efficient Large Vision Models through Sequential Autoregression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-large-vision-models-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training general-purpose vision models on purely sequential visual data, eschewing linguistic inputs, has heralded a new frontier in visual understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-large-vision-models-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Path Coupled Image Deraining Network via Spatial-Frequency Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-path-coupled-image-deraining-network-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have recently emerged as a significant force in the field of image deraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-path-coupled-image-deraining-network-via</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
