<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 09:12:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A framework for benchmarking class-out-of-distribution detection and its application to ImageNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-benchmarking-class-out-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a novel framework to benchmark the ability of image classifiers to detect class-out-of-distribution instances (i. e., instances whose true labels do not appear in the training distribution) at various levels of detection difficulty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-benchmarking-class-out-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Manifold Dimensions with Conditional Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-manifold-dimensions-with-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the variational autoencoder (VAE) and its conditional extension (CVAE) are capable of state-of-the-art results across multiple domains, their precise behavior is still not fully understood, particularly in the context of data (like images) that lie on or near a low-dimensional manifold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-manifold-dimensions-with-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Adaptive Conformal Prediction Using Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adaptive-conformal-prediction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the use of self-supervision beyond model pretraining and representation learning has been largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adaptive-conformal-prediction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding Graph Network Simulators using Physical Sensor Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-graph-network-simulators-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method results in utilization of additional point cloud information to accurately predict stable simulations where existing Graph Network Simulators fail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-graph-network-simulators-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Can We Learn From The Selective Prediction And Uncertainty Estimation Performance Of 523 Imagenet Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-we-learn-from-the-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we examine the relationship between deep architectures and their respective training regimes, with their corresponding selective prediction and uncertainty estimation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-can-we-learn-from-the-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set Features for Fine-grained Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set-features-for-fine-grained-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained anomaly detection has recently been dominated by segmentation based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set-features-for-fine-grained-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightCTS: A Lightweight Framework for Correlated Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightcts-a-lightweight-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many deep learning models have been proposed to improve the accuracy of CTS forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightcts-a-lightweight-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptation via Distilled Discriminative Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-via-distilled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differently, motivated by the fundamental assumption for domain adaptability, we re-cast the domain adaptation problem as discriminative clustering of target data, given strong privileged information provided by the closely related, labeled source data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-via-distilled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep OC-SORT: Multi-Pedestrian Tracking by Adaptive Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-oc-sort-multi-pedestrian-tracking-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion-based association for Multi-Object Tracking (MOT) has recently re-achieved prominence with the rise of powerful object detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-oc-sort-multi-pedestrian-tracking-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Plot is Worth a Thousand Words: Model Information Stealing Attacks via Scientific Plots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-plot-is-worth-a-thousand-words-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the simplicity and effectiveness of the attack method, our study indicates scientific plots indeed constitute a valid side channel for model information stealing attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-plot-is-worth-a-thousand-words-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Region-Aware Diffusion for Zero-shot Text-driven Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-aware-diffusion-for-zero-shot-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from current mask-based image editing methods, we propose a novel region-aware diffusion model (RDM) for entity-level image editing, which could automatically locate the region of interest and replace it following given text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/region-aware-diffusion-for-zero-shot-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Visual Representations via Language-Guided Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-representations-via-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although an object may appear in numerous contexts, we often describe it in a limited number of ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-visual-representations-via-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosodic features improve sentence segmentation and parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prosodic-features-improve-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parsing spoken dialogue presents challenges that parsing text does not, including a lack of clear sentence boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prosodic-features-improve-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change is Hard: A Closer Look at Subpopulation Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-is-hard-a-closer-look-at-subpopulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning models often perform poorly on subgroups that are underrepresented in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-is-hard-a-closer-look-at-subpopulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Paradigm Analysis of Thai Capital Market Linkages: Bivariate/Vine Copulas, Granger Causality, Network Centrality, and Graph Neural Network/Graph Embedding Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-paradigm-analysis-of-thai-capital</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analytically thorough understanding of causal, probabilistic, and informational linkages amongst modern, highly-interconnected capital markets is fundamental to the promotion of capital-market innovation, efficiency, and resilience; whereupon innovative, efficient, and resilient capital markets are fundamental to the sustainable economic development of any nation and the robust financial stability of her economy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-paradigm-analysis-of-thai-capital</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Deep Learning Learn to Abstract? A Systematic Probing Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-deep-learning-learn-to-abstract-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstraction is a desirable capability for deep learning models, which means to induce abstract concepts from concrete instances and flexibly apply them beyond the learning context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-deep-learning-learn-to-abstract-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Guided Ensemble Self-Training for Semi-Supervised Global Field Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-ensemble-self-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recovering a globally accurate complex physics field from limited sensor is critical to the measurement and control in the aerospace engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-ensemble-self-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiTs: Fine-grained Two-stage Training for Knowledge-aware Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fits-fine-grained-two-stage-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the promising result of recent KAQA systems which tend to integrate linguistic knowledge from pre-trained language models (PLM) and factual knowledge from knowledge graphs (KG) to answer complex questions, a bottleneck exists in effectively fusing the representations from PLMs and KGs because of (i) the semantic and distributional gaps between them, and (ii) the difficulties in joint reasoning over the provided knowledge from both modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fits-fine-grained-two-stage-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoxFormer: Sparse Voxel Transformer for Camera-based 3D Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxformer-sparse-voxel-transformer-for-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable such capability in AI systems, we propose VoxFormer, a Transformer-based semantic scene completion framework that can output complete 3D volumetric semantics from only 2D images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxformer-sparse-voxel-transformer-for-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MossFormer: Pushing the Performance Limit of Monaural Speech Separation using Gated Single-Head Transformer with Convolution-Augmented Joint Self-Attentions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mossformer-pushing-the-performance-limit-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To effectively solve the indirect elemental interactions across chunks in the dual-path architecture, MossFormer employs a joint local and global self-attention architecture that simultaneously performs a full-computation self-attention on local chunks and a linearised low-cost self-attention over the full sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mossformer-pushing-the-performance-limit-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Social Media for Early Detection of Depression in COVID-19 Patients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-social-media-for-early-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, We conducted an extensive analysis of this dataset to investigate the characteristic of COVID-19 patients with a higher risk of depression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-social-media-for-early-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Adapter Network for Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side-adapter-network-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A side network is attached to a frozen CLIP model with two branches: one for predicting mask proposals, and the other for predicting attention bias which is applied in the CLIP model to recognize the class of masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side-adapter-network-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCWDST: a Minimum-Cost Weighted Directed Spanning Tree Algorithm for Real-Time Fake News Mitigation in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcwdst-a-minimum-cost-weighted-directed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread availability of internet access and handheld devices confers to social media a power similar to the one newspapers used to have.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcwdst-a-minimum-cost-weighted-directed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Domain Robustness via Targeted Augmentations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-domain-robustness-via-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models trained on one set of domains often suffer performance drops on unseen domains, e. g., when wildlife monitoring models are deployed in new camera locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-domain-robustness-via-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Observability Analysis for Nonlinear Stochastic Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-observability-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Establishing these properties is challenging, especially when no analytical model is available and they are to be inferred directly from measurement data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-observability-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying &amp; Modeling Feature Interactions: An Information Decomposition Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-modeling-feature-interactions-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent explosion of interest in multimodal applications has resulted in a wide selection of datasets and methods for representing and integrating information from different signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-modeling-feature-interactions-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Structure Scores for Probabilistic Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-structure-scores-for-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic circuits (PCs) are a prominent representation of probability distributions with tractable inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-structure-scores-for-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KHAN: Knowledge-Aware Hierarchical Attention Networks for Political Stance Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/khan-knowledge-aware-hierarchical-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, in this work, we conduct a user study to investigate important factors in political stance prediction, and observe that the context and tone of a news article (implicit) and external knowledge for real-world entities appearing in the article (explicit) are important in determining its political stance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/khan-knowledge-aware-hierarchical-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Gumbel-Softmax in MADDPG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-gumbel-softmax-in-maddpg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method, however, is statistically biased, and a recent MARL benchmarking paper suggests that this bias makes MADDPG perform poorly in grid-world situations, where the action space is discrete.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-gumbel-softmax-in-maddpg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple and Scalable Nearest Neighbor Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-and-scalable-nearest-neighbor-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[$k$NN-MT is a straightforward yet powerful approach for fast domain adaptation, which directly plugs pre-trained neural machine translation (NMT) models with domain-specific token-level $k$-nearest-neighbor ($k$NN) retrieval to achieve domain adaptation without retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-and-scalable-nearest-neighbor-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Span-Based Continual Named Entity Recognition Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-span-based-continual-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named Entity Recognition (NER) models capable of Continual Learning (CL) are realistically valuable in areas where entity types continuously increase (e. g., personal assistants).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-span-based-continual-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securely implementing and managing neighborhood solar with storage and peer to peer transactive energy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securely-implementing-and-managing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed infrastructure would (i) increase the resilience of the customers in case the utility grid becomes unavailable, (ii) reduce AC/DC conversion losses since a majority of the DER generation is in DC, and (iii) with the help of BESS, the customers will have a lesser impact on the utility grid in terms of California 'duck curve.']]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/securely-implementing-and-managing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Policy Optimization for Structured Action Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-policy-optimization-for-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple and effective RL method, Diverse Policy Optimization (DPO), to model the policies in structured action space as the energy-based models (EBM) by following the probabilistic RL framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-policy-optimization-for-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teacher Intervention: Improving Convergence of Quantization Aware Training for Ultra-Low Precision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-intervention-improving-convergence-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Transformer models such as BERT have shown great success in a wide range of applications, but at the cost of substantial increases in model complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teacher-intervention-improving-convergence-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArtiFact: A Large-Scale Dataset with Artificial and Factual Images for Generalizable and Robust Synthetic Image Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-a-large-scale-dataset-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic image generation has opened up new opportunities but has also created threats in regard to privacy, authenticity, and security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-a-large-scale-dataset-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPINDLE: Spinning Raw Text into Lambda Terms with Graph Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spindle-spinning-raw-text-into-lambda-terms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes SPINDLE - an open source Python module implementing an efficient and accurate parser for written Dutch that transforms raw text input to programs for meaning composition, expressed as {\lambda} terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spindle-spinning-raw-text-into-lambda-terms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTM: A Frame-level Timeline Modeling Method for Temporal Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ftm-a-frame-level-timeline-modeling-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing neighborhood aggregation strategies fail to capture either the short-term features or the long-term features of temporal graph attributes, leading to unsatisfactory model performance and even poor robustness and domain generality of the representation learning method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ftm-a-frame-level-timeline-modeling-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than you've asked for: A Comprehensive Analysis of Novel Prompt Injection Threats to Application-Integrated Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-than-you-ve-asked-for-a-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In such attacks, an adversary can prompt the LLM to produce malicious content or override the original instructions and the employed filtering schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-than-you-ve-asked-for-a-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Might Say All You Need Is Sum</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-might-say-all-you-need-is-sum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that under certain restrictions, every Mean or Max GNNs can be approximated by a Sum GNN, but even there, a combination of (Sum, [Mean/Max]) is more expressive than Sum alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-might-say-all-you-need-is-sum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Projection Forest Initialization for Graph Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-projection-forest-initialization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a $k$-nn graph, points are restricted to have a fixed number of edges, and all edges in the graph have equal weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-projection-forest-initialization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Construction using Principal Axis Trees for Simple Graph Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-construction-using-principal-axis-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a graph construction scheme that construct the adjacency matrix $A$ using unsupervised and supervised information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-construction-using-principal-axis-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A critical look at the evaluation of GNNs under heterophily: are we really making progress?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-critical-look-at-the-evaluation-of-gnns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs without this property are called heterophilous, and it is typically assumed that specialized methods are required to achieve strong performance on such graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-critical-look-at-the-evaluation-of-gnns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Privacy-Preserving Framework for Cross-Silo Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-privacy-preserving-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) is recently surging as a promising decentralized deep learning (DL) framework that enables DL-based approaches trained collaboratively across clients without sharing private data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-privacy-preserving-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Theory Inspired Pattern Analysis for Time-series Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-theory-inspired-pattern-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For applications with stochastic state transitions, features are developed based on Shannon's entropy of Markov chains, entropy rates of Markov chains, entropy production of Markov chains, and von Neumann entropy of Markov chains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-theory-inspired-pattern-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximate spectral clustering density-based similarity for noisy datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-spectral-clustering-density-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, CONN could be tricked by noisy density between clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-spectral-clustering-density-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNA secondary structures: from ab initio prediction to better compression, and back</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rna-secondary-structures-from-ab-initio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we use the biological domain knowledge incorporated into stochastic models for ab initio RNA secondary-structure prediction to improve the state of the art in joint compression of RNA sequence and structure data (Liu et al., BMC Bioinformatics, 2008).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rna-secondary-structures-from-ab-initio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUAA_BIGSCity: Spatial-Temporal Graph Neural Network for Wind Power Forecasting in Baidu KDD CUP 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buaa-bigscity-spatial-temporal-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, organizers provide a wind power dataset containing historical data from 134 wind turbines and launch the Baidu KDD Cup 2022 to examine the limitations of current methods for wind power forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buaa-bigscity-spatial-temporal-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generalize Provably in Learning to Optimize</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-provably-in-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the optimizer generalization has been recently studied, the optimizee generalization (or learning to generalize) has not been rigorously studied in the L2O context, which is the aim of this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-provably-in-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Visual Appearance and Geometry for Multi-modality 6DoF Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-visual-appearance-and-geometry-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a multi-modality tracker that fuses information from visual appearance and geometry to estimate object poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-visual-appearance-and-geometry-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNG: Taxonomy Expansion by Exploring the Intrinsic Directed Structure on Non-Gaussian Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dng-taxonomy-expansion-by-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the inherited feature originates from "parent" nodes and is weighted by an inheritance factor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dng-taxonomy-expansion-by-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
