<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 09:14:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SLIM: Sparsified Late Interaction for Multi-Vector Retrieval with Inverted Indexes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-sparsified-late-interaction-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among them, ColBERT is probably the most established method which is based on the late interaction of contextualized token embeddings of pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-sparsified-late-interaction-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Anatomical Federated Network (Dafne): an open client/server framework for the continuous collaborative improvement of deep-learning-based medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-anatomical-federated-network-dafne-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation is a crucial step to extract quantitative information from medical (and, specifically, radiological) images to aid the diagnostic process, clinical follow-up.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-anatomical-federated-network-dafne-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CholecTriplet2022: Show me a tool and tell me the triplet -- an endoscopic vision challenge for surgical action triplet detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cholectriplet2022-show-me-a-tool-and-tell-me</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the CholecTriplet2022 challenge, which extends surgical action triplet modeling from recognition to detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cholectriplet2022-show-me-a-tool-and-tell-me</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELEA -- Build your own Evolutionary Algorithm in your Browser</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elea-build-your-own-evolutionary-algorithm-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide an open source framework to experiment with evolutionary algorithms which we call "Experimenting and Learning toolkit for Evolutionary Algorithms (ELEA)".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elea-build-your-own-evolutionary-algorithm-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Can't Discourse Parsing Generalize? A Thorough Investigation of the Impact of Data Diversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-can-t-discourse-parsing-generalize-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this study is the first to fully evaluate cross-corpus RST parsing generalizability on complete trees, examine between-genre degradation within an RST corpus, and investigate the impact of genre diversity in training data composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-can-t-discourse-parsing-generalize-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Scale Multi-Lingual Multi-Modal Summarization Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-lingual-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant developments in techniques such as encoder-decoder models have enabled us to represent information comprising multiple modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-lingual-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA-DepthNet: A Variational Approach to Single Image Depth Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/va-depthnet-a-variational-approach-to-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While state-of-the-art deep neural network methods for SIDP learn the scene depth from images in a supervised setting, they often overlook the invaluable invariances and priors in the rigid scene space, such as the regularity of the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/va-depthnet-a-variational-approach-to-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishability Calibration to In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishability-calibration-to-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When using prompt-based learning for text classification, the goal is to use a pre-trained language model (PLM) to predict a missing token in a pre-defined template given an input text, which can be mapped to a class label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishability-calibration-to-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comp2Comp: Open-Source Body Composition Assessment on Computed Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comp2comp-open-source-body-composition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting quantitative body composition measures manually from CT scans is a cumbersome and time-consuming task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comp2comp-open-source-body-composition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising the Cost of Malicious AI-Powered Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raising-the-cost-of-malicious-ai-powered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an approach to mitigating the risks of malicious image editing posed by large diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raising-the-cost-of-malicious-ai-powered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Circuits That Know What They Don't Know</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-circuits-that-know-what-they</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to neural networks, they are often assumed to be well-calibrated and robust to out-of-distribution (OOD) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-circuits-that-know-what-they</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Noise Filtering with Dynamic Sparse Training in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-noise-filtering-with-dynamic-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tomorrow's robots will need to distinguish useful information from noise when performing different tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-noise-filtering-with-dynamic-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AbLit: A Resource for Analyzing and Generating Abridged Versions of English Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablit-a-resource-for-analyzing-and-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset captures passage-level alignments between the original and abridged texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablit-a-resource-for-analyzing-and-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot Federated Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a conformal prediction method to construct prediction sets in a oneshot federated learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Type-Aware Decomposed Framework for Few-Shot Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/type-aware-decomposed-framework-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the recent success achieved by several two-stage prototypical networks in few-shot named entity recognition (NER) task, the over-detected false spans at span detection stage and the inaccurate and unstable prototypes at type classification stage remain to be challenging problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/type-aware-decomposed-framework-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contour Context: Abstract Structural Distribution for 3D LiDAR Loop Detection and Metric Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contour-context-abstract-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes \textit{Contour Context}, a simple, effective, and efficient topological loop closure detection pipeline with accurate 3-DoF metric pose estimation, targeting the urban utonomous driving scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contour-context-abstract-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge from Large-Scale Protein Contact Prediction Models Can Be Transferred to the Data-Scarce RNA Contact Prediction Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-from-large-scale-protein-contact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings indicate that the learned structural patterns of proteins can be transferred to RNAs, opening up potential new avenues for research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-from-large-scale-protein-contact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous-time convolutions model of event sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-time-convolutions-model-of-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Massive samples of event sequences data occur in various domains, including e-commerce, healthcare, and finance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-time-convolutions-model-of-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniAdapter: Unified Parameter-Efficient Transfer Learning for Cross-modal Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniadapter-unified-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, on the MSRVTT retrieval task, UniAdapter achieves 49. 7% recall@1 with 2. 2% model parameters, outperforming the latest competitors by 2. 0%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniadapter-unified-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Recommendation Fairness via Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-fairness-via-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We augment imbalanced training data towards balanced data distribution to improve fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-fairness-via-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GFlowNet-EM for learning compositional latent variable models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gflownet-em-for-learning-compositional-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Latent variable models (LVMs) with discrete compositional latents are an important but challenging setting due to a combinatorially large number of possible configurations of the latents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gflownet-em-for-learning-compositional-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optical Flow estimation with Event-based Cameras and Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-flow-estimation-with-event-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-based sensors are an excellent fit for Spiking Neural Networks (SNNs), since the coupling of an asynchronous sensor with neuromorphic hardware can yield real-time systems with minimal power requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optical-flow-estimation-with-event-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Arbitrary Shaped Clustering through Correlated Gaussian Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-arbitrary-shaped-clustering-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is no convincing evidence that backpropagation is a biologically plausible mechanism, and further studies of alternative learning methods are needed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-arbitrary-shaped-clustering-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Local Visual Modeling for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-local-visual-modeling-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the local visual modeling with grid features for image captioning, which is critical for generating accurate and detailed captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-local-visual-modeling-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFNet: Cascade Fusion Network for Dense Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfnet-cascade-fusion-network-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-scale features are essential for dense prediction tasks, including object detection, instance segmentation, and semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfnet-cascade-fusion-network-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Class Distribution Shift for Reliable Domain Adaptive Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-class-distribution-shift-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we propose a framework for explicitly addressing class distribution shift to improve pseudo-label reliability in self-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-class-distribution-shift-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Strategic Classification: A Tale of Two Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-strategic-classification-a-tale-of-two</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When users can benefit from certain predictive outcomes, they may be prone to act to achieve those outcome, e. g., by strategically modifying their features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-strategic-classification-a-tale-of-two</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Instance Learning with Trainable Decision Tree Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-with-trainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The whole STE-MIL model, including soft decision trees, neural networks, the attention mechanism and a classifier, is trained in an end-to-end manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-with-trainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preconditioned Score-based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preconditioned-score-based-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with the latest generative models (\eg, CLD-SGM, DDIM, and Analytic-DDIM), PDS can achieve the best sampling quality on CIFAR-10 at a FID score of 1. 99.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preconditioned-score-based-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Based Defect Recognitions for Autonomous UAV Inspections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-defect-recognitions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have summarized the existing crack detection and segmentation datasets and established the largest existing benchmark dataset on the internet for crack detection and segmentation, which is open-sourced for the research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-defect-recognitions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GPT-3 Perform Statutory Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-perform-statutory-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By also posing the same questions when the synthetic statutes are written in sentence form, we find that some of GPT-3's poor performance results from difficulty in parsing the typical structure of statutes, containing subsections and paragraphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-perform-statutory-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGER: Temporal Interaction Graph Embedding with Restarts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiger-temporal-interaction-graph-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the entangled temporal and structural dependencies, existing methods have to process the sequence of events chronologically and consecutively to ensure node representations are up-to-date.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiger-temporal-interaction-graph-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliability Assurance for Deep Neural Network Architectures Against Numerical Defects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-assurance-for-deep-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assure high reliability against numerical defects, in this paper, we propose the RANUM approach including novel techniques for three reliability assurance tasks: detection of potential numerical defects, confirmation of potential-defect feasibility, and suggestion of defect fixes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-assurance-for-deep-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Noisy Crowd Labels with Logics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-crowd-labels-with-logics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the integration of symbolic logic knowledge into deep neural networks for learning from noisy crowd labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-crowd-labels-with-logics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Bayesian Neural Networks via Resolution of Singularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-neural-networks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we advocate for the importance of singular learning theory (SLT) as it pertains to the theory and practice of variational inference in Bayesian neural networks (BNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-neural-networks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SubTuning: Efficient Finetuning for Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subtuning-efficient-finetuning-for-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finetuning a pretrained model has become a standard approach for training neural networks on novel tasks, resulting in fast convergence and improved performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subtuning-efficient-finetuning-for-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threatening Patch Attacks on Object Detection in Optical Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threatening-patch-attacks-on-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advanced Patch Attacks (PAs) on object detection in natural images have pointed out the great safety vulnerability in methods based on deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threatening-patch-attacks-on-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlabeled Imperfect Demonstrations in Adversarial Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlabeled-imperfect-demonstrations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The trajectories of an initial agent policy could be closer to those non-optimal expert demonstrations, but within the framework of adversarial imitation learning, agent policy will be optimized to cheat the discriminator and produce trajectories that are similar to those optimal expert demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlabeled-imperfect-demonstrations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Motion Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-motion-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthesizing realistic animations of humans, animals, and even imaginary creatures, has long been a goal for artists and computer graphics professionals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-motion-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupling the Skeleton Parsing and Schema Linking for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-the-skeleton-parsing-and-schema</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the structural property of the SQL queries, the seq2seq model takes the responsibility of parsing both the schema items (i. e., tables and columns) and the skeleton (i. e., SQL keywords).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-the-skeleton-parsing-and-schema</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Fraud Detection using Deep Boosting Decision Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fraud-detection-using-deep-boosting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose deep boosting decision trees (DBDT), a novel approach for fraud detection based on gradient boosting and neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fraud-detection-using-deep-boosting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising and Prompt-Tuning for Multi-Behavior Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-and-prompt-tuning-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practical recommendation scenarios, users often interact with items under multi-typed behaviors (e. g., click, add-to-cart, and purchase).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-and-prompt-tuning-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USER: Unsupervised Structural Entropy-based Robust Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-unsupervised-structural-entropy-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose USER, an unsupervised robust version of graph neural networks that is based on structural entropy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-unsupervised-structural-entropy-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flag Aggregator: Scalable Distributed Training under Failures and Augmented Losses using Convex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flag-aggregator-scalable-distributed-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, to scale computation and data, these models are inevitably trained in a distributed manner in clusters of nodes, and their updates are aggregated before being applied to the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flag-aggregator-scalable-distributed-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unsupervised learning approach for predicting wind farm power and downstream wakes using weather patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-unsupervised-learning-approach-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we develop a novel wind energy workflow that for the first time combines weather patterns derived from unsupervised clustering techniques with numerical weather prediction models (here WRF) to obtain efficient and accurate long-term predictions of power and downstream wakes from an entire wind farm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-unsupervised-learning-approach-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware AB3DMOT by Variational 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-ab3dmot-by-variational-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving needs to rely on high-quality 3D object detection to ensure safe navigation in the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-ab3dmot-by-variational-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Voxel Pseudo Image Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-voxel-pseudo-image-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty estimation is an important task for critical problems, such as robotics and autonomous driving, because it allows creating statistically better perception models and signaling the model's certainty in its predictions to the decision method or a human supervisor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-voxel-pseudo-image-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Network-Inspired Kernels for Gaussian Processes in Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-inspired-kernels-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian processes (GPs) are an attractive class of machine learning models because of their simplicity and flexibility as building blocks of more complex Bayesian models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-network-inspired-kernels-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Effectiveness of the Underlying Reasoning Tasks in Multi-hop Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effectiveness-of-the-underlying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explain the predicted answers and evaluate the reasoning abilities of models, several studies have utilized underlying reasoning (UR) tasks in multi-hop question answering (QA) datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-effectiveness-of-the-underlying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Extended Sequence Tagging Vocabulary for Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extended-sequence-tagging-vocabulary-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend a current sequence-tagging approach to Grammatical Error Correction (GEC) by introducing specialised tags for spelling correction and morphological inflection using the SymSpell and LemmInflect algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extended-sequence-tagging-vocabulary-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
