<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 09:12:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Latent Variable Models for Few-Shot High-Dimensional Time-Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared the presented framework with a comprehensive set of baseline models trained 1) globally on the large meta-training set with diverse dynamics, and 2) individually on single dynamics, both with and without fine-tuning to k-shot support series used by the meta-models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Product Classification on Leaflet Advertisements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-product-classification-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show, that the combination of image and text as input improves the classification of visual difficult to distinguish products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-product-classification-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowText: Synthesizing Realistic Scene Text Video with Optical Flow Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowtext-synthesizing-realistic-scene-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel video text synthesis technique called FlowText, which utilizes optical flow estimation to synthesize a large amount of text video data at a low cost for training robust video text spotters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowtext-synthesizing-realistic-scene-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining bias-target Alignment from Voronoi Cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-bias-target-alignment-from-voronoi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant research efforts, deep neural networks are still vulnerable to biases: this raises concerns about their fairness and limits their generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-bias-target-alignment-from-voronoi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-free Reinforcement Learning of Semantic Communication by Stochastic Policy Gradient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-reinforcement-learning-of-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the recent success of Machine Learning tools in wireless communications, the idea of semantic communication by Weaver from 1949 has gained attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-reinforcement-learning-of-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Segment Anything Model (SAM) Boost Medical Image Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-segment-anything-model-sam-boost-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the flexibility of prompting, foundation models have become the dominant force in the domains of natural language processing and image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-segment-anything-model-sam-boost-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Topological Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-topological-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze the sensitivity of persistence diagrams in terms of the bottleneck distance, and we show that the commonly used \v{C}ech complex has sensitivity that does not decrease as the sample size $n$ increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-topological-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Hyperparameters with Conformal Quantile Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-hyperparameters-with-conformal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many state-of-the-art hyperparameter optimization (HPO) algorithms rely on model-based optimizers that learn surrogate models of the target function to guide the search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-hyperparameters-with-conformal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAANet: Ghost Auto Anchor Network for Detecting Varying Size Drones in Dark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaanet-ghost-auto-anchor-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome those limitations and improve the detection accuracy at night, we propose an object detector called Ghost Auto Anchor Network (GAANet) for infrared (IR) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaanet-ghost-auto-anchor-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White-Box Multi-Objective Adversarial Attack on Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/white-box-multi-objective-adversarial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such language models are, however, vulnerable to various adversarial samples as studied in traditional tasks such as text classification, which inspires our curiosity about their robustness in DG systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/white-box-multi-objective-adversarial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduction of Class Activation Uncertainty with Background Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduction-of-class-activation-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multitask learning is a popular approach to training high-performing neural networks with improved generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduction-of-class-activation-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verify-and-Edit: A Knowledge-Enhanced Chain-of-Thought Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verify-and-edit-a-knowledge-enhanced-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) have become the norm in NLP, demonstrating good performance in generation and reasoning tasks, one of its most fatal disadvantages is the lack of factual correctness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verify-and-edit-a-knowledge-enhanced-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransESC: Smoothing Emotional Support Conversation via Turn-Level State Transition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transesc-smoothing-emotional-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we construct the state transition graph with a two-step way, named transit-then-interact, to grasp such three types of turn-level transition information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transesc-smoothing-emotional-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Idleness in Financial Cloud via Multi-objective Evolutionary Reinforcement Learning based Load Balancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-idleness-in-financial-cloud-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, various companies started to shift their data services from traditional data centers onto cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-idleness-in-financial-cloud-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Semantic Similarity Measurement for Unsupervised Word Sense Disambiguation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-semantic-similarity-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The issue of word sense ambiguity poses a significant challenge in natural language processing due to the scarcity of annotated data to feed machine learning models to face the challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-semantic-similarity-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large Cross-Modal Video Retrieval Dataset with Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-cross-modal-video-retrieval-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing cross-modal language-to-video retrieval (VR) research focuses on single-modal input from video, i. e., visual representation, while the text is omnipresent in human environments and frequently critical to understand video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-cross-modal-video-retrieval-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Inference for Fairness Auditing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-fairness-auditing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our methods can be used to flag subpopulations affected by model underperformance, and certify subpopulations for which the model performs adequately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-fairness-auditing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HD2Reg: Hierarchical Descriptors and Detectors for Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd2reg-hierarchical-descriptors-and-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature Descriptors and Detectors are two main components of feature-based point cloud registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd2reg-hierarchical-descriptors-and-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSPDet3D: Dynamic Spatial Pruning for 3D Small Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspdet3d-dynamic-spatial-pruning-for-3d-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With in-depth study, we find increasing the spatial resolution of the feature maps significantly boosts the performance of 3D small object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspdet3d-dynamic-spatial-pruning-for-3d-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindGames: Targeting Theory of Mind in Large Language Models with Dynamic Epistemic Modal Logic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindgames-targeting-theory-of-mind-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theory of Mind (ToM) is a critical component of intelligence, yet accurately measuring it continues to be a subject of debate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindgames-targeting-theory-of-mind-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAMO-NLP at SemEval-2023 Task 2: A Unified Retrieval-augmented System for Multilingual Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-nlp-at-semeval-2023-task-2-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, we discover that the limited context length causes the retrieval knowledge to be invisible to the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-nlp-at-semeval-2023-task-2-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLI4CT: Multi-Evidence Natural Language Inference for Clinical Trial Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nli4ct-multi-evidence-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel resource to advance research on NLI for reasoning on CTRs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nli4ct-multi-evidence-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Decision Trees with Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-decision-trees-with-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decision Trees (DTs) are commonly used for many machine learning tasks due to their high degree of interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-decision-trees-with-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Acquisition of Fine-grained Visual Concepts by Exploiting Semantics of Generic Characterizations in Discourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-acquisition-of-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interactive Task Learning (ITL) concerns learning about unforeseen domain concepts via natural interactions with human users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-acquisition-of-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuromodulation Gated Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromodulation-gated-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel architecture, the Neuromodulation Gated Transformer (NGT), which is a simple implementation of neuromodulation in transformers via a multiplicative effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromodulation-gated-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generic and Robust Root Cause Localization for Multi-Dimensional Data in Online Service Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-and-robust-root-cause-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such attribute combinations are substantial clues to the underlying root causes and thus are called root causes of multidimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-and-robust-root-cause-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composite Motion Learning with Task Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-motion-learning-with-task-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to existing data-driven approaches using reinforcement learning that imitate full-body motions, we learn decoupled motions for specific body parts from multiple reference motions simultaneously and directly by leveraging the use of multiple discriminators in a GAN-like setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-motion-learning-with-task-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Personalized Federated Learning via Sparse Model-Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-personalized-federated-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these challenges, we propose a novel approach named pFedGate for efficient personalized FL by adaptively and efficiently learning sparse local models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-personalized-federated-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Domain Adaptation via Prototype-based Multi-level Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-via-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the inter-domain level, we propose a cross-domain alignment loss to help the model use the target prototype for cross-domain knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-via-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperNOVA: Design Strategies and Opportunities for Interactive Visualization in Computational Notebooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supernova-design-strategies-and-opportunities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through this work, we identify unique design opportunities and considerations for future notebook VA tools, such as using and manipulating multimodal data in notebooks as well as balancing the degree of visualization-notebook integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supernova-design-strategies-and-opportunities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentence Embedding Leaks More Information than You Expect: Generative Embedding Inversion Attack to Recover the Whole Sentence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-embedding-leaks-more-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we further investigate the information leakage issue and propose a generative embedding inversion attack (GEIA) that aims to reconstruct input sequences based only on their sentence embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-embedding-leaks-more-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-aware Generation of Multi-view Portrait Drawings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-generation-of-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our motivation is that facial semantic labels are view-consistent and correlate with drawing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-generation-of-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Oops, Did I Just Say That?" Testing and Repairing Unethical Suggestions of Large Language Models with Suggest-Critique-Reflect Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oops-did-i-just-say-that-testing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a novel on-the-fly (OTF) repairing scheme that repairs unethical suggestions made by LLMs in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oops-did-i-just-say-that-testing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalize Segment Anything Model with One Shot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalize-segment-anything-model-with-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driven by large-data pre-training, Segment Anything Model (SAM) has been demonstrated as a powerful and promptable framework, revolutionizing the segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalize-segment-anything-model-with-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGB: A PubMed Graph Benchmark for Heterogeneous Network Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgb-a-pubmed-graph-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although graph mining research via heterogeneous graph neural networks has taken center stage, it remains unclear whether these approaches capture the heterogeneity of the PubMed database, a vast digital repository containing over 33 million articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgb-a-pubmed-graph-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Waiting Time in Transaction Fee Mechanism: An Interdisciplinary Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understand-waiting-time-in-transaction-fee</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study identified NFT drops as a unique source of market congestion -- holiday effects -- beyond trend and season effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understand-waiting-time-in-transaction-fee</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Question Answering with Monte-Carlo Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FAME (FAithful question answering with MontE-carlo planning) to answer questions based on faithful reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarially-Guided Portrait Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-guided-portrait-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We utilize this model to provide image-mask pairs for the StyleGAN3- based network (StyleMatteGAN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarially-guided-portrait-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuttlefish: Low-Rank Model Training without All the Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cuttlefish leverages the observation that after a few epochs of full-rank training, the stable rank (i. e., an approximation of the true rank) of each layer stabilizes at a constant value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiance Field Gradient Scaling for Unbiased Near-Camera Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiance-field-gradient-scaling-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NeRF acquisition typically requires careful choice of near planes for the different cameras or suffers from background collapse, creating floating artifacts on the edges of the captured scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiance-field-gradient-scaling-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary-aware Backward-Compatible Representation via Adversarial Learning in Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-backward-compatible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For traditional model upgrades, the old model will not be replaced by the new one until the embeddings of all the images in the database are re-computed by the new model, which takes days or weeks for a large amount of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-aware-backward-compatible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised 3D Scene Flow Estimation Guided by Superpoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-3d-scene-flow-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our superpoint generation module, we utilize the bidirectional flow information at the previous iteration to obtain the matching points of points and superpoint centers for soft point-to-superpoint association construction, in which the superpoints are generated for pairwise point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-3d-scene-flow-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCBO: Reaching Group Consensus in Clustered Federated Learning through Consensus-based Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is an important framework in modern machine learning that seeks to integrate the training of learning models from multiple users, each user having their own local data set, in a way that is sensitive to data privacy and to communication loss constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Reinforcement Learning via a Causal World Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-reinforcement-learning-via-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating explanations for reinforcement learning (RL) is challenging as actions may produce long-term effects on the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-reinforcement-learning-via-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NatCS: Eliciting Natural Customer Support Dialogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natcs-eliciting-natural-customer-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing task-oriented dialogue datasets, which were collected to benchmark dialogue systems mainly in written human-to-bot settings, are not representative of real customer support conversations and do not provide realistic benchmarks for systems that are applied to natural data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natcs-eliciting-natural-customer-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Graph Learning and Model Fitting in Laplacian Regularized Stratified Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laplacian regularized stratified models (LRSM) are models that utilize the explicit or implicit network structure of the sub-problems as defined by the categorical features called strata (e. g., age, region, time, forecast horizon, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZipIt! Merging Models from Different Tasks without Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While this works for models trained on the same task, we find that this fails to account for the differences in models trained on disjoint tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional and Residual Methods in Scalable Coding for Humans and Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-and-residual-methods-in-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present methods for conditional and residual coding in the context of scalable coding for humans and machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-and-residual-methods-in-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caption Anything: Interactive Image Description with Diverse Multimodal Controls</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-interactive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controllable image captioning is an emerging multimodal topic that aims to describe the image with natural language following human purpose, $\textit{e. g.}$, looking at the specified regions or telling in a particular text style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-interactive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LatentAugment: Dynamically Optimized Latent Probabilities of Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although data augmentation is a powerful technique for improving the performance of image classification tasks, it is difficult to identify the best augmentation policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
