<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 21:06:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PIAFusion: A progressive infrared and visible image fusion network based on illumination aware</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piafusion-a-progressive-infrared-and-visible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we utilize the illumination probability to construct an illumination-aware loss to guide the training of the fusion network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piafusion-a-progressive-infrared-and-visible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetry Disentanglement Network for Interpretable Acute Ischemic Stroke Infarct Segmentation in Non-Contrast CT Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetry-disentanglement-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Asymmetry Disentanglement Network (ADN) to automatically separate pathological asymmetries and intrinsic anatomical asymmetries in NCCTs for more effective and interpretable AIS segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetry-disentanglement-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Future World Events with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-future-world-events-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We test language models on our forecasting task and find that performance is far below a human expert baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-future-world-events-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifts 2.0: Extending The Dataset of Real Distributional Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifts-2-0-extending-the-dataset-of-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This creates a need to be able to assess how robustly ML models generalize as well as the quality of their uncertainty estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifts-2-0-extending-the-dataset-of-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroC: A Neuro-Symbolic Model for Zero-shot Concept Recognition and Acquisition at Inference Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroc-a-neuro-symbolic-model-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Zero-shot Concept Recognition and Acquisition (ZeroC), a neuro-symbolic architecture that can recognize and acquire novel concepts in a zero-shot way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zeroc-a-neuro-symbolic-model-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Entity Candidate Generation for Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-entity-candidate-generation-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a light-weight and simple solution based on the construction of indexes whose design is motivated by more complex transfer learning based neural approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-entity-candidate-generation-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiclass-SGCN: Sparse Graph-based Trajectory Prediction with Agent Class Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiclass-sgcn-sparse-graph-based-trajectory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trajectory prediction of road users in real-world scenarios is challenging because their movement patterns are stochastic and complex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiclass-sgcn-sparse-graph-based-trajectory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Part-Of-Speech Model: Does Modeling Long Context Help Unsupervised POS-tagging?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-part-of-speech-model-does-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MPoSM can model arbitrary tag dependency and perform POS induction through the objective of masked POS reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-part-of-speech-model-does-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grouped Pointwise Convolutions Reduce Parameters in Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grouped-pointwise-convolutions-reduce</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Deep Convolutional Neural Networks (DCNNs), the parameter count in pointwise convolutions quickly grows due to the multiplication of the filters and input channels from the preceding layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grouped-pointwise-convolutions-reduce</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFGC 2022: The Second DeepFake Game Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfgc-2022-the-second-deepfake-game</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a two-party game between DeepFake creators and defenders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfgc-2022-the-second-deepfake-game</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing and addressing the fragility of neural networks in digital pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-and-addressing-the-fragility-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we develop a new method for evaluating neural network models' ability to generalise by generating a large number of distribution-shifted datasets, which can be used to thoroughly investigate their robustness to variability encountered in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-and-addressing-the-fragility-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking the Robustness of Deep Neural Networks to Common Corruptions in Digital Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluated on two resulting benchmark datasets, we find that (1) a variety of deep neural network models suffer from a significant accuracy decrease (double the error on clean images) and the unreliable confidence estimation on corrupted images; (2) A low correlation between the validation and test errors while replacing the validation set with our benchmark can increase the correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-robustness-of-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified End-to-End Retriever-Reader Framework for Knowledge-based VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-end-to-end-retriever-reader</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, pertaining to the implicit knowledge, the multi-modal implicit knowledge for knowledge-based VQA still remains largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-end-to-end-retriever-reader</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Rendering for Stereo 3D Reconstruction of Deformable Tissues in Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-rendering-for-stereo-3d-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstruction of the soft tissues in robotic surgery from endoscopic stereo videos is important for many applications such as intra-operative navigation and image-guided robotic surgery automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-rendering-for-stereo-3d-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localizing the Recurrent Laryngeal Nerve via Ultrasound with a Bayesian Shape Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-the-recurrent-laryngeal-nerve-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tumor infiltration of the recurrent laryngeal nerve (RLN) is a contraindication for robotic thyroidectomy and can be difficult to detect via standard laryngoscopy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-the-recurrent-laryngeal-nerve-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton-based Action Recognition via Adaptive Cross-Form Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-based-action-recognition-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, each GCN model in ACFL not only learns action representation from the single-form skeletons, but also adaptively mimics useful representations derived from other forms of skeletons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-based-action-recognition-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Regularized Re-Balancing for Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-regularized-re-balancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Re-balancing methods are used to alleviate the influence of data imbalance; however, we empirically discover that they would under-fit new classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-regularized-re-balancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The (de)biasing effect of GAN-based augmentation methods on skin lesion images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-de-biasing-effect-of-gan-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we examined classification models trained on both real and synthetic data with counterfactual bias explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-de-biasing-effect-of-gan-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEAD: A Multi-Armed Approach for Evaluation of Adversarial Examples Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mead-a-multi-armed-approach-for-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detection of adversarial examples has been a hot topic in the last years due to its importance for safely deploying machine learning algorithms in critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mead-a-multi-armed-approach-for-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRFuser: A Multi-resolution Sensor Fusion Architecture for 2D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrfuser-a-multi-resolution-sensor-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides standard cameras, autonomous vehicles typically include multiple additional sensors, such as lidars and radars, which help acquire richer information for perceiving the content of the driving scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrfuser-a-multi-resolution-sensor-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Anomaly Detection in Echocardiograms with Dynamic Variational Trajectory Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-anomaly-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel anomaly detection method for echocardiogram videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-anomaly-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BigBIO: A Framework for Data-Centric Biomedical Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigbio-a-framework-for-data-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training and evaluating language models increasingly requires the construction of meta-datasets --diverse collections of curated data with clear provenance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigbio-a-framework-for-data-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laplacian Autoencoders for Learning Stochastic Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-autoencoders-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning has become a practical family of methods for building rich parametric codifications of massive high-dimensional data while succeeding in the reconstruction side.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laplacian-autoencoders-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable K-FAC Training for Deep Neural Networks with Distributed Preconditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-k-fac-training-for-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second-order optimization methods, notably the D-KFAC (Distributed Kronecker Factored Approximate Curvature) algorithms, have gained traction on accelerating deep neural network (DNN) training on GPU clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-k-fac-training-for-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnoShift: A Distribution Shift Benchmark for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoshift-a-distribution-shift-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the performance degradation over time with diverse models (MLM to classical Isolation Forest).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anoshift-a-distribution-shift-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoised MDPs: Learning World Models Better Than the World Itself</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to separate signal from noise, and reason with clean abstractions, is critical to intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Functions on Multiple Sets using Multi-Set Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functions-on-multiple-sets-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general deep architecture for learning functions on multiple permutation-invariant sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-functions-on-multiple-sets-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Ensemble Distillation With Weight Averaging and Diversifying Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-ensemble-distillation-with-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensembles of deep neural networks have demonstrated superior performance, but their heavy computational cost hinders applying them for resource-limited environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-ensemble-distillation-with-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark Dataset for Precipitation Forecasting by Post-Processing the Numerical Weather Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-dataset-for-precipitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a hybrid NWP-DL workflow to fill the gap between standalone NWP and DL approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-dataset-for-precipitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Learning and Learnablity of Quasimetrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-and-learnablity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, our proposed Poisson Quasimetric Embedding (PQE) is the first quasimetric learning formulation that both is learnable with gradient-based optimization and enjoys strong performance guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-and-learnablity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Copilot AI pair programmer: Asset or Liability?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-ai-pair-programmer-asset-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the capabilities of Copilot in two different programming tasks: (1) generating (and reproducing) correct and efficient solutions for fundamental algorithmic problems, and (2) comparing Copilot's proposed solutions with those of human programmers on a set of programming tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/github-copilot-ai-pair-programmer-asset-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning with Deep Tabular Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-deep-tabular-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate that upstream data gives tabular neural networks a decisive advantage over widely used GBDT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-with-deep-tabular-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Instance-Level Impact of Fairness Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-instance-level-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A variety of fairness constraints have been proposed in the literature to mitigate group-level statistical bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-instance-level-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-aware two-branch DCNN for efficient plant disease classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep convolutional neural networks (DCNNs) have been successfully applied to plant disease detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-aware-two-branch-dcnn-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LViT: Language meets Vision Transformer in Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvit-language-meets-vision-transformer-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our model, medical text annotation is introduced to compensate for the quality deficiency in image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvit-language-meets-vision-transformer-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C2FTrans: Coarse-to-Fine Transformers for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2ftrans-coarse-to-fine-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most recent transformer-based methods for medical image segmentation directly apply vanilla transformers as an auxiliary module in CNN-based methods, resulting in severe detail loss due to the rigid patch partitioning scheme in transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2ftrans-coarse-to-fine-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards out of distribution generalization for problems in mechanics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-out-of-distribution-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we investigate the performance of OOD generalization methods for regression problems in mechanics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-out-of-distribution-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An extensible Benchmarking Graph-Mesh dataset for studying Steady-State Incompressible Navier-Stokes Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensible-benchmarking-graph-mesh-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in \emph{Geometric Deep Learning} (GDL) has shown its potential to provide powerful data-driven models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-extensible-benchmarking-graph-mesh-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Model Failures as Directions in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-model-failures-as-directions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods for isolating hard subpopulations and spurious correlations in datasets often require human intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-model-failures-as-directions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Robustness of Dialogue History Representation in Conversational Question Answering: A Comprehensive Study and a New Prompt-based Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-dialogue-history</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that high benchmark scores do not necessarily translate to strong robustness, and that various methods can perform extremely differently under different settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-dialogue-history</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Report for CVPR 2022 LOVEU AQTC Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-for-cvpr-2022-loveu-aqtc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report presents the 2nd winning model for AQTC, a task newly introduced in CVPR 2022 LOng-form VidEo Understanding (LOVEU) challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-for-cvpr-2022-loveu-aqtc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRCN3D: Sparse R-CNN 3D Surround-View Camera Object Detection and Tracking for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srcn3d-sparse-r-cnn-3d-surround-view-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes Sparse R-CNN 3D (SRCN3D), a novel two-stage fully-convolutional mapping pipeline for surround-view camera detection and tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srcn3d-sparse-r-cnn-3d-surround-view-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online vs. Offline Adaptive Domain Randomization Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-vs-offline-adaptive-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, transferring the acquired knowledge to the real world can be challenging due to the reality gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-vs-offline-adaptive-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Foresight With a Local Dynamics Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-foresight-with-a-local-dynamics-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By combining the LDM with model-free policy learning, we can learn policies which can solve complex manipulation tasks using one-step lookahead planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-foresight-with-a-local-dynamics-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summarizing Videos using Concentrated Attention and Considering the Uniqueness and Diversity of the Video Frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-videos-using-concentrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of simply modeling the frames' dependencies based on global attention, our method integrates a concentrated attention mechanism that is able to focus on non-overlapping blocks in the main diagonal of the attention matrix, and to enrich the existing information by extracting and exploiting knowledge about the uniqueness and diversity of the associated frames of the video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarizing-videos-using-concentrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Procrustes Analysis with Deformations: A Closed-Form Solution by Eigenvalue Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procrustes-analysis-with-deformations-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that this property fortunately holds true for most common transformation models, including the affine and TPS models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/procrustes-analysis-with-deformations-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GERNERMED++: Transfer Learning in German Medical NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gernermed-transfer-learning-in-german-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a statistical model for German medical natural language processing trained for named entity recognition (NER) as an open, publicly available model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gernermed-transfer-learning-in-german-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Lighter The Better: Rethinking Transformers in Medical Image Segmentation Through Adaptive Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-lighter-the-better-rethinking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our best knowledge, this is the first work on transformer pruning for medical image analysis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-lighter-the-better-rethinking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Placenta Segmentation in Ultrasound Imaging: Addressing Sources of Uncertainty and Limited Field-of-View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placenta-segmentation-in-ultrasound-imaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic segmentation of the placenta in fetal ultrasound (US) is challenging due to the (i) high diversity of placenta appearance, (ii) the restricted quality in US resulting in highly variable reference annotations, and (iii) the limited field-of-view of US prohibiting whole placenta assessment at late gestation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/placenta-segmentation-in-ultrasound-imaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Non-Random Missing Labels in Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-non-random-missing-labels-in-semi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method is three-fold: 1) We propose Class-Aware Propensity (CAP) that exploits the unlabeled data to train an improved classifier using the biased labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-non-random-missing-labels-in-semi-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
