<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 09:25:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DELAD: Deep Landweber-guided deconvolution with Hessian and sparse prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delad-deep-landweber-guided-deconvolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a model for non-blind image deconvolution that incorporates the classic iterative method into a deep learning application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delad-deep-landweber-guided-deconvolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Progressive Transformations for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-progressive-transformations-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised semantic segmentation (WSSS), which aims to mine the object regions by merely using class-level labels, is a challenging task in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-progressive-transformations-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERNIE-ViL 2.0: Multi-view Contrastive Learning for Image-Text Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-vil-2-0-multi-view-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They attempt to learn cross-modal representation using contrastive learning on image-text pairs, however, the built inter-modal correlations only rely on a single view for each modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-vil-2-0-multi-view-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual Privacy Accounting with Gaussian Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-privacy-accounting-with-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to account for the individual privacy losses in a principled manner, we need a privacy accountant for adaptive compositions of randomised mechanisms, where the loss incurred at a given data access is allowed to be smaller than the worst-case loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-privacy-accounting-with-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmallCap: Lightweight Image Captioning Prompted with Retrieval Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smallcap-lightweight-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in image captioning have focused on scaling the data and model size, substantially increasing the cost of pre-training and finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smallcap-lightweight-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Question Understanding and Answering with Knowledge Grounding and Semantic Self-Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-question-understanding-and-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The system first matches the summarized user question with an FAQ from a trusted medical knowledge base, and then retrieves a fixed number of relevant sentences from the corresponding answer document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-question-understanding-and-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inharmonious Region Localization by Magnifying Domain Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inharmonious-region-localization-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inharmonious region localization aims to localize the region in a synthetic image which is incompatible with surrounding background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inharmonious-region-localization-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExtrudeNet: Unsupervised Inverse Sketch-and-Extrude for Shape Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrudenet-unsupervised-inverse-sketch-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of learning the shape given in the form of point clouds by inverse sketch-and-extrude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extrudenet-unsupervised-inverse-sketch-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MobileViTv3: Mobile-Friendly Vision Transformer with Simple and Effective Fusion of Local, Global and Input Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilevitv3-mobile-friendly-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose changes to the fusion block that are simple and effective to create MobileViTv3-block, which addresses the scaling and simplifies the learning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobilevitv3-mobile-friendly-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Construction and Applications of Open Business Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/construction-and-applications-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Business Knowledge Graph is important to many enterprises today, providing the factual knowledge and structured data that steer many products and make them more intelligent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/construction-and-applications-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Out-of-Distribution Detection Method is Not Robust!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-out-of-distribution-detection-method-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, unlike OOD detection in the standard setting, access to OOD, as well as in-distribution, samples sounds necessary in the adversarial training setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-out-of-distribution-detection-method-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyTurbo: Efficient Turbo Decoders on Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyturbo-efficient-turbo-decoders-on-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a neural-augmented decoder for Turbo codes called TINYTURBO .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyturbo-efficient-turbo-decoders-on-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning: Introducing a New Notion and Standard Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-heterogeneity-in-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though successful, federated learning presents new challenges for machine learning, especially when the issue of data heterogeneity, also known as Non-IID data, arises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-data-heterogeneity-in-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with MISELBO: The Mixture Cookbook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-miselbo-the-mixture-cookbook</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we study the effect of instead using MISELBO as an objective function for learning mixtures, and we propose the first ever mixture of variational approximations for a normalizing flow-based hierarchical variational autoencoder (VAE) with VampPrior and a PixelCNN decoder network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-miselbo-the-mixture-cookbook</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-based Image Translation using Disentangled Style and Content Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-image-translation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based image translation guided by semantic texts or a single target image has enabled flexible style transfer which is not limited to the specific domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-image-translation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabDDPM: Modelling Tabular Data with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabddpm-modelling-tabular-data-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising diffusion probabilistic models are currently becoming the leading paradigm of generative modeling for many important data modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabddpm-modelling-tabular-data-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking skip connection model as a learnable Markov chain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-skip-connection-model-as-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we deep dive into the model's behaviors with skip connections which can be formulated as a learnable Markov chain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-skip-connection-model-as-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable-Based Calibration for Machine Learning Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-based-calibration-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we introduce the notion of variable-based calibration to characterize calibration properties of a model with respect to a variable of interest, generalizing traditional score-based calibration and metrics such as expected calibration error (ECE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-based-calibration-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifiable and Energy Efficient Medical Image Analysis with Quantised Self-attentive Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifiable-and-energy-efficient-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional Neural Networks have played a significant role in various medical imaging tasks like classification and segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifiable-and-energy-efficient-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parea: multi-view ensemble clustering for cancer subtype discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parea-multi-view-ensemble-clustering-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply and validate our methodology on real-world multi-view cancer patient data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parea-multi-view-ensemble-clustering-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metro: Memory-Enhanced Transformer for Retrosynthetic Planning via Reaction Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metro-memory-enhanced-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first develop a benchmark curated for the retrosynthetic planning task, which consists of 124, 869 reaction trees retrieved from the public USPTO-full dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metro-memory-enhanced-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEIM: Multi-partition Embedding Interaction Beyond Block Term Format for Efficient and Expressive Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meim-multi-partition-embedding-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph embedding aims to predict the missing relations between entities in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meim-multi-partition-embedding-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Exploration Method for Reinforcement Learning under Existence of Disturbance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-exploration-method-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define the safety during learning as satisfaction of the constraint conditions explicitly defined in terms of the state and propose a safe exploration method that uses partial prior knowledge of a controlled object and disturbance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-exploration-method-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batch Multivalid Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-multivalid-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivalid coverage guarantees are stronger than marginal coverage guarantees in two ways: (1) They hold even conditional on group membership -- that is, the target coverage level $1-\alpha$ holds conditionally on membership in each of an arbitrary (potentially intersecting) group in a finite collection $\mathcal{G}$ of regions in the feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-multivalid-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Where to Look: Attention Similarity Knowledge Distillation for Low Resolution Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-where-to-look-attention-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has achieved outstanding performance for face recognition benchmarks, but performance reduces significantly for low resolution (LR) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-where-to-look-attention-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Coarse-to-fine Cascaded Evidence-Distillation Neural Network for Explainable Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coarse-to-fine-cascaded-evidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing fake news detection methods aim to classify a piece of news as true or false and provide veracity explanations, achieving remarkable performances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-coarse-to-fine-cascaded-evidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AICCA: AI-driven Cloud Classification Atlas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aicca-ai-driven-cloud-classification-atlas</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clouds play an important role in the Earth's energy budget and their behavior is one of the largest uncertainties in future climate projections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aicca-ai-driven-cloud-classification-atlas</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TERMinator: A system for scientific texts processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/terminator-a-system-for-scientific-texts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is devoted to the extraction of entities and semantic relations between them from scientific texts, where we consider scientific terms as entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/terminator-a-system-for-scientific-texts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>polyBERT: A chemical language model to enable fully machine-driven ultrafast polymer informatics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polybert-a-chemical-language-model-to-enable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[polyBERT is a chemical linguist that treats the chemical structure of polymers as a chemical language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polybert-a-chemical-language-model-to-enable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the temporal understanding of neural networks on event-based action recognition with DVS-Gesture-Chain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-temporal-understanding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A wide range of benchmark datasets is available to allow for the evaluation of such capabilities when using conventional frame-based video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-temporal-understanding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Motion Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Motion Diffusion Model (MDM), a carefully adapted classifier-free diffusion-based generative model for the human motion domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R2C-GAN: Restore-to-Classify GANs for Blind X-Ray Restoration and COVID-19 Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r2c-gan-restore-to-classify-gans-for-blind-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed restoration approach achieves over 90% F1-Score which is significantly higher than the performance of any deep model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r2c-gan-restore-to-classify-gans-for-blind-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compressed Gastric Image Generation Based on Soft-Label Dataset Distillation for Medical Data Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressed-gastric-image-generation-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, our method can extract essential weights of DCNN models to reduce the memory required to save trained models for efficient medical data sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressed-gastric-image-generation-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated Neighborhood Attention Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-neighborhood-attention-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models typically employ localized attention mechanisms, such as the sliding-window Neighborhood Attention (NA) or Swin Transformer's Shifted Window Self Attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-neighborhood-attention-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perturbations and Subpopulations for Testing Robustness in Token-Based Argument Unit Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbations-and-subpopulations-for-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Argument Unit Recognition and Classification aims at identifying argument units from text and classifying them as pro or against.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbations-and-subpopulations-for-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Media Bias Detection Using Distant Supervision With BABE -- Bias Annotations By Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-media-bias-detection-using-distant-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning and evaluating the model on our proposed supervised data set, we achieve a macro F1-score of 0. 804, outperforming existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-media-bias-detection-using-distant-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Small: Training Game Level Generators from Nothing by Learning at Multiple Sizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-small-training-game-level-generators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that our methods can generate high-quality diverse levels for Sokoban, Zelda and Danger Dave for a variety of sizes, after only 3h 29min up to 6h 11min (depending on the game) of training on a single commodity machine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/start-small-training-game-level-generators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing Neural Network Training via Identity-wise Discriminative Feature Suppression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-neural-network-training-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It suppresses features that can be utilized to identify individual instances among samples within each class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-neural-network-training-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spikformer: When Spiking Neural Network Meets Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikformer-when-spiking-neural-network-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spikformer (66. 3M parameters) with comparable size to SEW-ResNet-152 (60. 2M, 69. 26%) can achieve 74. 81% top1 accuracy on ImageNet using 4 time steps, which is the state-of-the-art in directly trained SNNs models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikformer-when-spiking-neural-network-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D UX-Net: A Large Kernel Volumetric ConvNet Modernizing Hierarchical Transformer for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-ux-net-a-large-kernel-volumetric-convnet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical transformers (e. g., Swin Transformers) reintroduced several ConvNet priors and further enhanced the practical viability of adapting volumetric segmentation in 3D medical datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-ux-net-a-large-kernel-volumetric-convnet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source tool for Airway Segmentation in Computed Tomography using 2.5D Modified EfficientDet: Contribution to the ATM22 Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-tool-for-airway-segmentation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Airway segmentation in computed tomography images can be used to analyze pulmonary diseases, however, manual segmentation is labor intensive and relies on expert knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-tool-for-airway-segmentation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proportional Multicalibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proportional-multicalibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multicalibration is a desirable fairness criteria that constrains calibration error among flexibly-defined groups in the data while maintaining overall calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proportional-multicalibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards General-Purpose Representation Learning of Polygonal Geometries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-purpose-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the spatial domain approach, we propose ResNet1D, a 1D CNN-based polygon encoder, which uses circular padding to achieve loop origin invariance on simple polygons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-purpose-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmentation Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentation-backdoors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is well known that backdoors can be inserted into machine learning models through serving a modified dataset to train on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmentation-backdoors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients' Severity States Classification based on Electronic Health Record (EHR) Data using Multiple Machine Learning and Deep Learning Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patients-severity-states-classification-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For implementing Deep Learning we employed a feed-forward neural network (multi-layer) and the Fast Large Margin approach for semi-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patients-severity-states-classification-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online pseudo labeling for polyp segmentation with momentum networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pseudo-labeling-for-polyp-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a new pseudo labeling strategy that enhances the quality of pseudo labels used for training student networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-pseudo-labeling-for-polyp-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Stage Method for Chinese AMR Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-method-for-chinese-amr-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a detailed description of our system at CAMRP-2022 evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-method-for-chinese-amr-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLO: A Contrastive Learning based Re-ranking Framework for One-Stage Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-a-contrastive-learning-based-re-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional training paradigms for extractive and abstractive summarization systems always only use token-level or sentence-level training objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-a-contrastive-learning-based-re-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Stain Normalization for Computational Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-stain-normalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a solution, we propose BottleGAN, a generative model that can computationally align the staining styles of many laboratories and can be trained in a privacy-preserving manner to foster federated learning in computational pathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-stain-normalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Collapse in Non-Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-collapse-in-non-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive methods have led a recent surge in the performance of self-supervised representation learning (SSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-collapse-in-non-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
