<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 21:05:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>vox2vec: A Framework for Self-supervised Contrastive Learning of Voxel-level Representations in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vox2vec-a-framework-for-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces vox2vec - a contrastive method for self-supervised learning (SSL) of voxel-level representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vox2vec-a-framework-for-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Annotation-free Image Captioning with Retrieval-augmented Pseudo Sentence Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-annotation-free-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further show that with a simple extension, the generated pseudo sentences can be deployed as weak supervision to boost the 1% semi-supervised image caption benchmark up to 93. 4 CIDEr score (+8. 9) which showcases the versatility and effectiveness of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-annotation-free-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Strategic Framework for Optimal Decisions in Football 1-vs-1 Shot-Taking Situations: An Integrated Approach of Machine Learning, Theory-Based Modeling, and Game Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-strategic-framework-for-optimal-decisions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we proposed a novel framework to analyze such scenarios based on game theory, where we estimate the expected payoff with machine learning (ML) models, and additional features for ML models were extracted with a theory-based shot block model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-strategic-framework-for-optimal-decisions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxonomy Adaptive Cross-Domain Adaptation in Medical Imaging via Optimization Trajectory Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-adaptive-cross-domain-adaptation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of automated medical image analysis depends on large-scale and expert-annotated training sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-adaptive-cross-domain-adaptation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training Vision Transformers with Very Limited Synthesized Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vision-transformers-with-very</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior work on FDSL has shown that pre-training vision transformers on such synthetic datasets can yield competitive accuracy on a wide range of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vision-transformers-with-very</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Dynamic Range Imaging via Visual Attention Modules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-imaging-via-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to High Dynamic Range (HDR) imaging methods, the scope of photography has seen profound changes recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-imaging-via-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCPA: Multi-scale Cross Perceptron Attention Network for 2D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcpa-multi-scale-cross-perceptron-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Cross Perceptron first captures the local correlations using multiple Multi-scale Cross Perceptron modules, facilitating the fusion of features across scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcpa-multi-scale-cross-perceptron-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RoboDepth Challenge: Methods and Advancements Towards Robust Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-robodepth-challenge-methods-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we summarize the winning solutions from the RoboDepth Challenge -- an academic competition designed to facilitate and advance robust OoD depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-robodepth-challenge-methods-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Silent Failures in Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-silent-failures-in-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the result that none of the benchmarked CSFs can reliably prevent silent failures, we conclude that a deeper understanding of the root causes of failures in the data is required.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-silent-failures-in-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Natural Language Inference in Arabic using Transformer Models and Linguistically Informed Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-natural-language-inference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the classification of Arabic text data in the field of Natural Language Processing (NLP), with a particular focus on Natural Language Inference (NLI) and Contradiction Detection (CD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-natural-language-inference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>360VOT: A New Benchmark Dataset for Omnidirectional Visual Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/360vot-a-new-benchmark-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[360{\deg} images can provide an omnidirectional field of view which is important for stable and long-term scene perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/360vot-a-new-benchmark-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATNilm: Multi-appliance-task Non-intrusive Load Monitoring with Limited Labeled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matnilm-multi-appliance-task-non-intrusive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-intrusive load monitoring (NILM) identifies the status and power consumption of various household appliances by disaggregating the total power usage signal of an entire house.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matnilm-multi-appliance-task-non-intrusive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotion4MIDI: a Lyrics-based Emotion-Labeled Symbolic Music Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion4midi-a-lyrics-based-emotion-labeled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new large-scale emotion-labeled symbolic music dataset consisting of 12k MIDI songs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion4midi-a-lyrics-based-emotion-labeled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread Flaws in Offline Evaluation of Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/widespread-flaws-in-offline-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though offline evaluation is just an imperfect proxy of online performance -- due to the interactive nature of recommenders -- it will probably remain the primary way of evaluation in recommender systems research for the foreseeable future, since the proprietary nature of production recommenders prevents independent validation of A/B test setups and verification of online results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/widespread-flaws-in-offline-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metric-Based In-context Learning: A Case Study in Text Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-based-in-context-learning-a-case-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, determining the best method to select examples for ICL is nontrivial as the results can vary greatly depending on the quality, quantity, and order of examples used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric-based-in-context-learning-a-case-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Time Adaptation for Blind Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-adaptation-for-blind-image-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce two novel quality-relevant auxiliary tasks at the batch and sample levels to enable TTA for blind IQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-adaptation-for-blind-image-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2C: Self-Supervised Point Cloud Completion from Single Partial Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2c-self-supervised-point-cloud-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud completion aims to recover the complete shape based on a partial observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2c-self-supervised-point-cloud-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-guided Foundation Model Adaptation for Pathological Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-foundation-model-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to Connect Image and Text Embeddings (CITE) to enhance pathological image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-foundation-model-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MESED: A Multi-modal Entity Set Expansion Dataset with Fine-grained Semantic Classes and Hard Negative Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesed-a-multi-modal-entity-set-expansion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Entity Set Expansion (ESE) task aims to expand a handful of seed entities with new entities belonging to the same semantic class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesed-a-multi-modal-entity-set-expansion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Aspect-Based Sentiment with End-to-End Semantic Role Labeling Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-aspect-based-sentiment-with-end-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel end-to-end Semantic Role Labeling model that effectively captures most of the structured semantic information within the Transformer hidden state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-aspect-based-sentiment-with-end-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiscale Dynamic Graph Representation for Biometric Recognition with Occlusions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-dynamic-graph-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Occlusion is a common problem with biometric recognition in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-dynamic-graph-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take-A-Photo: 3D-to-2D Generative Pre-training of Point Cloud Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-photo-3d-to-2d-generative-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel 3D-to-2D generative pre-training method that is adaptable to any point cloud model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-photo-3d-to-2d-generative-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Good is Google Bard's Visual Understanding? An Empirical Study on Open Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-is-google-bard-s-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Google's Bard has emerged as a formidable competitor to OpenAI's ChatGPT in the field of conversational AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-is-google-bard-s-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Session-Based Transformer Recommendations using Optimized Negative Sampling and Loss Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-session-based-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces TRON, a scalable session-based Transformer Recommender using Optimized Negative-sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-session-based-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Models of reference production: How do they withstand the test of time?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/models-of-reference-production-how-do-they</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude that GREC can no longer be regarded as offering a reliable assessment of models' ability to mimic human reference production, because the results are highly impacted by the choice of corpus and evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/models-of-reference-production-how-do-they</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinker: Learning to Plan and Act</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinker-learning-to-plan-and-act</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach eliminates the need for hand-crafted planning algorithms by enabling the agent to learn how to plan autonomously and allows for easy interpretation of the agent's plan with visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinker-learning-to-plan-and-act</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal and Transferable Adversarial Attacks on Aligned Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-transferable-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our approach finds a suffix that, when attached to a wide range of queries for an LLM to produce objectionable content, aims to maximize the probability that the model produces an affirmative response (rather than refusing to answer).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-transferable-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Generative Models for Graph-to-Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generative-models-for-graph-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been widely employed for graph-to-text generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generative-models-for-graph-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture of Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose the Gated Self-Supervised Learning method to improve image classification which use more than one transformation as pretext task and uses the Mixture of Expert architecture as a gating network in combining each pretext task so that the model automatically can study and focus more on the most useful augmentations for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Interaction Paradigm for Complex EDA Software Leveraging GPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-interaction-paradigm-for-complex-eda</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly growing field of electronic design automation (EDA), professional software such as KiCad, Cadence , and Altium Designer provide increasingly extensive design functionalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-interaction-paradigm-for-complex-eda</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IML-ViT: Image Manipulation Localization by Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iml-vit-image-manipulation-localization-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, artifacts are sensitive to image resolution, amplified under multi-scale features, and massive at the manipulation border.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iml-vit-image-manipulation-localization-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTNet for micro-expression recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-for-micro-expression-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The transformer layer is used to focus on representing local minor muscle movement with local self-attention in each area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-for-micro-expression-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Spoken Language on Speech Enhancement using Self-Supervised Speech Representation Loss Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-spoken-language-on-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, SE models are trained and tested on a number of different languages, with self-supervised representations which themselves are trained using different language combinations and with differing network structures as loss function representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-spoken-language-on-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BubbleML: A Multi-Physics Dataset and Benchmarks for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bubbleml-a-multi-physics-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of phase change phenomena, the lack of accessible and diverse datasets suitable for machine learning (ML) training poses a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bubbleml-a-multi-physics-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Polyphonic Multitrack Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-polyphonic-multitrack-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs can be leveraged to model polyphonic multitrack symbolic music, where notes, chords and entire sections may be linked at different levels of the musical hierarchy by tonal and rhythmic relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-polyphonic-multitrack-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLDiffusion: Learning Degradation Representations in Diffusion Models for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lldiffusion-learning-degradation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this limitation by proposing a degradation-aware learning scheme for LLIE using diffusion models, which effectively integrates degradation and image priors into the diffusion process, resulting in improved image enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lldiffusion-learning-degradation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised AI for Efficient Analysis of 3D Pathology Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-ai-for-efficient-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human tissue and its constituent cells form a microenvironment that is fundamentally three-dimensional (3D).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-ai-for-efficient-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Restoration in Histology Images with Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-restoration-in-histology-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histological whole slide images (WSIs) can be usually compromised by artifacts, such as tissue folding and bubbles, which will increase the examination difficulty for both pathologists and Computer-Aided Diagnosis (CAD) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-restoration-in-histology-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car-Studio: Learning Car Radiance Fields from Single-View and Endless In-the-wild Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-studio-learning-car-radiance-fields-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, previous studies learned within a sequence of autonomous driving datasets, resulting in unsatisfactory blurring when rotating the car in the simulator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-studio-learning-car-radiance-fields-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug Characterization in Machine Learning-based Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bug-characterization-in-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our results, fixing ML bugs are more costly and ML components are more error-prone, compared to non-ML bugs and non-ML components respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bug-characterization-in-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Problems in Computer Vision for Wilderness SAR and The Search for Patricia Wu-Murad</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-problems-in-computer-vision-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper details the challenges in applying two computer vision systems, an EfficientDET supervised learning model and the unsupervised RX spectral classifier, to 98. 9 GB of drone imagery from the Wu-Murad wilderness search and rescue (WSAR) effort in Japan and identifies 3 directions for future research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-problems-in-computer-vision-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AViT: Adapting Vision Transformers for Small Skin Lesion Segmentation Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avit-adapting-vision-transformers-for-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we employ a shallow CNN as a prompt generator to create a prompt embedding from the input image, which grasps fine-grained information and CNN's inductive biases to guide the segmentation task on small datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avit-adapting-vision-transformers-for-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOBench: Benchmarking Efficient Object Detectors on Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolobench-benchmarking-efficient-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present YOLOBench, a benchmark comprised of 550+ YOLO-based object detection models on 4 different datasets and 4 different embedded hardware platforms (x86 CPU, ARM CPU, Nvidia GPU, NPU).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolobench-benchmarking-efficient-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Birds: Self-Supervised Single-View 3D Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-birds-self-supervised-single-view-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus lies primarily on birds, a popular subject in 3D reconstruction, for which no existing single-view 3D transfer methods have been developed. The method we propose seeks to generate a 3D mesh shape and texture of a bird from two single-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-birds-self-supervised-single-view-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diff-E: Diffusion-based Learning for Decoding Imagined Speech EEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff-e-diffusion-based-learning-for-decoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decoding EEG signals for imagined speech is a challenging task due to the high-dimensional nature of the data and low signal-to-noise ratio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff-e-diffusion-based-learning-for-decoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Deep Learning-based Pansharpening with Jointly-Enhanced Spectral and Spatial Fidelity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-deep-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In latest years, deep learning has gained a leading role in the pansharpening of multiresolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-deep-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrammarGPT: Exploring Open-Source LLMs for Native Chinese Grammatical Error Correction with Supervised Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammargpt-exploring-open-source-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although model parameters are 20x larger than the SOTA baseline, the required amount of data for instruction tuning is 1200x smaller, illustrating the potential of open-source LLMs on native CGEC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammargpt-exploring-open-source-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Position Bias Model for Short-Video Recommendation Feeds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-position-bias-model-for-short</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical insights from a large-scale social media platform show how our probabilistic position bias model more accurately captures empirical exposure than existing models, and paves the way for unbiased evaluation and learning-to-rank.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-position-bias-model-for-short</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Double Descent in Vision Transformers: real or phantom threat?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-double-descent-in-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision transformers (ViT) have been of broad interest in recent theoretical and empirical works.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-double-descent-in-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDE: A Vision-Driven Multi-View, Multi-Modal, Multi-Tasking Dataset for Assistive Driving Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aide-a-vision-driven-multi-view-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driver distraction has become a significant cause of severe traffic accidents over the past decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aide-a-vision-driven-multi-view-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
