<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 21:05:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Localization of Just Noticeable Difference for Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localization-of-just-noticeable-difference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By applying this framework, we created a novel PJND dataset, KonJND++, consisting of 300 source images, compressed versions thereof under JPEG or BPG compression, and an average of 43 ratings of PJND and 129 self-reported locations of JND-critical regions for each source image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localization-of-just-noticeable-difference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galactic: Scaling End-to-End Reinforcement Learning for Rearrangement at 100k Steps-Per-Second</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactic-scaling-end-to-end-reinforcement-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, a Fetch robot (equipped with a mobile base, 7DoF arm, RGBD camera, egomotion, and onboard sensing) is spawned in a home environment and asked to rearrange objects - by navigating to an object, picking it up, navigating to a target location, and then placing the object at the target location.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galactic-scaling-end-to-end-reinforcement-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rank-Aware Negative Training for Semi-Supervised Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-aware-negative-training-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the noisy information, we adapt a reasoning with uncertainty-based approach to rank the unlabeled texts based on the evidential support received from the labeled texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rank-aware-negative-training-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised learning made simple with self-supervised clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-made-simple-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning models have been shown to learn rich visual representations without requiring human annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-made-simple-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DenseLight: Efficient Control for Large-scale Traffic Signals with Dense Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denselight-efficient-control-for-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[1) The travel time of a vehicle is delayed feedback on the effectiveness of TSC policy at each traffic intersection since it is obtained after the vehicle has left the road network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denselight-efficient-control-for-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topic-Centric Explanations for News Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topic-centric-explanations-for-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[News recommender systems (NRS) have been widely applied for online news websites to help users find relevant articles based on their interests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topic-centric-explanations-for-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generated Graph Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generated-graph-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph generative models become increasingly effective for data distribution approximation and data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generated-graph-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question Decomposition Tree for Answering Complex Questions over Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-decomposition-tree-for-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To verify that QDT can enhance KBQA task, we design a decomposition-based KBQA system called QDTQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-decomposition-tree-for-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Von Mises Mixture Distributions for Molecular Conformation Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/von-mises-mixture-distributions-for-molecular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting distribution on geometries $p(x)$ is known as the Boltzmann distribution, and many molecular properties are expectations computed under this distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/von-mises-mixture-distributions-for-molecular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Sometimes Generate Purely Negatively-Reinforced Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-sometimes-generate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When using adversarial training, it is common practice to train against the most egregious failures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-sometimes-generate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRATTA : Sample Re-ATTribution Attack of Secure Aggregation in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sratta-sample-re-attribution-attack-of-secure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider a cross-silo federated learning (FL) setting where a machine learning model with a fully connected first layer is trained between different clients and a central server using FedAvg, and where the aggregation step can be performed with secure aggregation (SA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sratta-sample-re-attribution-attack-of-secure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiating Metropolis-Hastings to Optimize Intractable Densities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiating-metropolis-hastings-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When performing inference on probabilistic models, target densities often become intractable, necessitating the use of Monte Carlo samplers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiating-metropolis-hastings-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omega: Optimistic EMA Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omega-optimistic-ema-gradients</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic min-max optimization has gained interest in the machine learning community with the advancements in GANs and adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omega-optimistic-ema-gradients</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modality Adaption or Regularization? A Case Study on End-to-End Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-adaption-or-regularization-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-training and fine-tuning is a paradigm for alleviating the data scarcity problem in end-to-end speech translation (E2E ST).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-adaption-or-regularization-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSSTRNet: Progressive Segmentation-guided Scene Text Removal Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psstrnet-progressive-segmentation-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In each iteration, the original image, previous text removal result, and text mask are input to the network to extract the rest part of the text segments and cleaner text removal result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psstrnet-progressive-segmentation-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synapse: Leveraging Few-Shot Exemplars for Human-Level Computer Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synapse-leveraging-few-shot-exemplars-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous prompting approaches focus on self-correction, we find that well-structured exemplars alone are sufficient for human-level performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synapse-leveraging-few-shot-exemplars-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Better or Worse: The Impact of Counterfactual Explanations' Directionality on User Behavior in xAI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-better-or-worse-the-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, potential benefits and drawbacks of the directionality of CFEs for user behavior in xAI remain unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-better-or-worse-the-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebGLM: Towards An Efficient Web-Enhanced Question Answering System with Human Preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webglm-towards-an-efficient-web-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present WebGLM, a web-enhanced question-answering system based on the General Language Model (GLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webglm-towards-an-efficient-web-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finite Gaussian Neurons: Defending against adversarial attacks by making neural networks say "I don't know"</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finite-gaussian-neurons-defending-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further validate the capacity of Finite Gaussian Neurons to protect from adversarial attacks, I compare the behavior of FGNs to that of Bayesian Neural Networks against both randomized and adversarial images, and show how the behavior of the two architectures differs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finite-gaussian-neurons-defending-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokenization with Factorized Subword Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenization-with-factorized-subword-encoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, language models have become increasingly larger and more complex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenization-with-factorized-subword-encoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxonomy-Structured Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-structured-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptation aims to mitigate distribution shifts among different domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-structured-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised-Contrastive Loss Learns Orthogonal Frames and Batching Matters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-contrastive-loss-learns-orthogonal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer this question, our main finding is that the geometry of embeddings learned by SCL forms an orthogonal frame (OF) regardless of the number of training examples per class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-contrastive-loss-learns-orthogonal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-for-All: Generalized LoRA for Parameter-Efficient Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-all-generalized-lora-for-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Generalized LoRA (GLoRA), an advanced approach for universal parameter-efficient fine-tuning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-all-generalized-lora-for-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skill Disentanglement for Imitation Learning from Suboptimal Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-disentanglement-for-imitation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imitation learning has achieved great success in many sequential decision-making tasks, in which a neural agent is learned by imitating collected human demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skill-disentanglement-for-imitation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethink the Effectiveness of Text Data Augmentation: An Empirical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethink-the-effectiveness-of-text-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, language models (LMs) have made remarkable progress in advancing the field of natural language processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethink-the-effectiveness-of-text-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoCoLA: The Norwegian Corpus of Linguistic Acceptability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nocola-the-norwegian-corpus-of-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there has been a surge of large language models for Norwegian in recent years, we lack any tool to evaluate their understanding of grammaticality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nocola-the-norwegian-corpus-of-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massively Multilingual Corpus of Sentiment Datasets and Multi-faceted Sentiment Classification Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multilingual-corpus-of-sentiment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents the most extensive open massively multilingual corpus of datasets for training sentiment models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massively-multilingual-corpus-of-sentiment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XrayGPT: Chest Radiographs Summarization using Medical Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xraygpt-chest-radiographs-summarization-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latest breakthroughs in large vision-language models, such as Bard and GPT-4, have showcased extraordinary abilities in performing a wide range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xraygpt-chest-radiographs-summarization-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Missing-half: Graph Complementary Learning for Homophily-prone and Heterophily-prone Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-the-missing-half-graph-complementary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world graphs generally have only one kind of tendency in their connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-the-missing-half-graph-complementary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best-Case Retrieval Evaluation: Improving the Sensitivity of Reciprocal Rank with Lexicographic Precision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-case-retrieval-evaluation-improving-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the lack of sensitivity of reciprocal rank by introducing and connecting it to the concept of best-case retrieval, an evaluation method focusing on assessing the quality of a ranking for the most satisfied possible user across possible recall requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-case-retrieval-evaluation-improving-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Versatile Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning Benchmark for Inventory Management</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-versatile-multi-agent-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) models multiple agents that interact and learn within a shared environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-versatile-multi-agent-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TART: A plug-and-play Transformer module for task-agnostic reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tart-a-plug-and-play-transformer-module-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, we focus on the LLM's reasoning abilities and demonstrate that this performance gap exists due to their inability to perform simple probabilistic reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tart-a-plug-and-play-transformer-module-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Additive Causal Bandits with Unknown Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/additive-causal-bandits-with-unknown-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore algorithms to select actions in the causal bandit setting where the learner can choose to intervene on a set of random variables related by a causal graph, and the learner sequentially chooses interventions and observes a sample from the interventional distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/additive-causal-bandits-with-unknown-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Monte Carlo Search for Conjecture Refutation in Graph Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-monte-carlo-search-for-conjecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The algorithm is further utilized to refute six open conjectures, two of which were chemical graph theory conjectures formulated by Liu et al. in 2021 and four of which were formulated by the AutoGraphiX computer system in 2006.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-monte-carlo-search-for-conjecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMD: Light-weight Prediction Quality Estimation for Object Detection in Lidar Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmd-light-weight-prediction-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address these two issues, we propose LidarMetaDetect (LMD), a light-weight post-processing scheme for prediction quality estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmd-light-weight-prediction-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReadProbe: A Demo of Retrieval-Enhanced Large Language Models to Support Lateral Reading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/readprobe-a-demo-of-retrieval-enhanced-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid growth and spread of online misinformation, people need tools to help them evaluate the credibility and accuracy of online information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/readprobe-a-demo-of-retrieval-enhanced-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unprocessing Seven Years of Algorithmic Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unprocessing-seven-years-of-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unprocessing allows for a direct comparison of methods using different underlying models and levels of relaxation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unprocessing-seven-years-of-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volume-DROID: A Real-Time Implementation of Volumetric Mapping with DROID-SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volume-droid-a-real-time-implementation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Volume-DROID takes camera images (monocular or stereo) or frames from a video as input and combines DROID-SLAM, point cloud registration, an off-the-shelf semantic segmentation network, and Convolutional Bayesian Kernel Inference (ConvBKI) to generate a 3D semantic map of the environment and provide accurate localization for the robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volume-droid-a-real-time-implementation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Hessian's Connection to the Decision Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-hessian-s-connection-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this finding, we provide a new and straightforward approach to studying the complexity of a high-dimensional decision boundary; show that this connection naturally inspires a new generalization measure; and finally, we develop a novel margin estimation technique which, in combination with the generalization measure, precisely identifies minima with simple wide-margin boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-hessian-s-connection-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coupled Attention Networks for Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coupled-attention-networks-for-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a coupled attention-based neural network framework (CAN) for anomaly detection in multivariate time series data featuring dynamic variable relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coupled-attention-networks-for-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Mask and Permute Visual Tokens for Vision Transformer Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-mask-and-permute-visual-tokens</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of self-supervised pre-training has emerged as a promising approach to enhance the performance of visual tasks such as image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-mask-and-permute-visual-tokens</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Forecasts for Heterogeneous Time Series by "Averaging", with Application to Food Demand Forecast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-forecasts-for-heterogeneous-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common forecasting setting in real world applications considers a set of possibly heterogeneous time series of the same domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-forecasts-for-heterogeneous-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Vision Fails: Text Attacks Against ViT and OCR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-vision-fails-text-attacks-against-vit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While text-based machine learning models that operate on visual inputs of rendered text have become robust against a wide range of existing attacks, we show that they are still vulnerable to visual adversarial examples encoded as text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-vision-fails-text-attacks-against-vit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Neural Network Training Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address these challenges, we introduce a new, competitive, time-to-result benchmark using multiple workloads running on fixed hardware, the AlgoPerf: Training Algorithms benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-neural-network-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-precision interpolation of stellar atmospheres with a deep neural network using a 1D convolutional auto encoder for feature extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-interpolation-of-stellar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the widespread availability of grids of models for stellar atmospheres, it is necessary to recover intermediate atmospheric models by means of accurate techniques that go beyond simple linear interpolation and capture the intricacies of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-precision-interpolation-of-stellar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrent Attention Networks for Long-text Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-attention-networks-for-long-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Revisiting the self-attention mechanism and the recurrent structure, this paper proposes a novel long-document encoding model, Recurrent Attention Network (RAN), to enable the recurrent operation of self-attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrent-attention-networks-for-long-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a neural network approach to accelerate disequilibrium chemistry calculations in exoplanet atmospheres</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-neural-network-approach-to-accelerate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that in 90% of the cases, the fully trained model is able to predict the evolved mixing ratios of the species in the hot-Jupiter atmosphere simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-neural-network-approach-to-accelerate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Prototype Alignment for Few-shot Policy Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-prototype-alignment-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptation in reinforcement learning (RL) mainly deals with the changes of observation when transferring the policy to a new environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-prototype-alignment-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employing Crowdsourcing for Enriching a Music Knowledge Base in Higher Education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/employing-crowdsourcing-for-enriching-a-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The campaign's results and the comments gathered through an online survey enable us to draw some useful insights about the benefits and challenges of integrating crowdsourcing into computer science curricula and how this can enhance students' engagement in the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/employing-crowdsourcing-for-enriching-a-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koopman-inspired Implicit Backward Reachable Sets for Unknown Nonlinear Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/koopman-inspired-implicit-backward-reachable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Koopman liftings have been successfully used to learn high dimensional linear approximations for autonomous systems for prediction purposes, or for control systems for leveraging linear control techniques to control nonlinear dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/koopman-inspired-implicit-backward-reachable</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
