<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:10:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Exposure-slot: Exposure-centric representations learning with Slot-in-Slot Attention for Region-aware Exposure Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposure-slot-exposure-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image exposure correction enhances images captured under diverse real-world conditions by addressing issues of under- and over-exposure, which can result in the loss of critical details and hinder content recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposure-slot-exposure-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap Between Open-Source and Proprietary LLMs in Table QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-open-source-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a system developed for SemEval 2025 Task 8: Question Answering (QA) over tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-open-source-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is the Cost of Differential Privacy for Deep Learning-Based Trajectory Generation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-the-cost-of-differential-privacy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conclusion, DP trajectory generation remains a challenging task, and formal guarantees are currently only feasible with large datasets and in constrained use cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-the-cost-of-differential-privacy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisit What You See: Disclose Language Prior in Vision Tokens for Efficient Guided Decoding of LVLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-what-you-see-disclose-language-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach leverages the semantic information embedded within vision tokens by projecting them into the text token distribution space, and dynamically selecting the most relevant vision token at each decoding step through constrained divergence minimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-what-you-see-disclose-language-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Modeling of IRCU Patient Flow in the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-modeling-of-ircu-patient-flow-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study evaluated clinical outcomes and operational dynamics of a new Spanish IRCU with specialized staffing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-modeling-of-ircu-patient-flow-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-Aware Vision-Language Models Fine-Tuning with Geometric Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-vision-language-models-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Models (VLMs) have shown remarkable performance on diverse visual and linguistic tasks, yet they remain fundamentally limited in their understanding of 3D spatial structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-aware-vision-language-models-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AtmosMJ: Revisiting Gating Mechanism for AI Weather Forecasting Beyond the Year Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atmosmj-revisiting-gating-mechanism-for-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has led to the prevailing assumption that such representations are necessary to enforce physical consistency and long-term stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atmosmj-revisiting-gating-mechanism-for-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TACTIC: Translation Agents with Cognitive-Theoretic Interactive Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tactic-translation-agents-with-cognitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using DeepSeek-V3 as the base model, TACTIC surpasses GPT-4. 1 by an average of +0. 6 XCOMET and +1. 18 COMETKIWI-23.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tactic-translation-agents-with-cognitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiscoVLA: Discrepancy Reduction in Vision, Language, and Alignment for Parameter-Efficient Video-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovla-discrepancy-reduction-in-vision-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The parameter-efficient adaptation of the image-text pretraining model CLIP for video-text retrieval is a prominent area of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovla-discrepancy-reduction-in-vision-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Hubs Through Influential Nodes in Transportation Network by Using a Gravity Centrality Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hubs-through-influential-nodes-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hubs are strategic locations that function as central nodes within clusters of cities, playing a pivotal role in the distribution of goods, services, and connectivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hubs-through-influential-nodes-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversity-Guided MLP Reduction for Efficient Large Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-guided-mlp-reduction-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we focus on the recoverability of the compressed models and propose a Diversity-Guided MLP Reduction (DGMR) method to significantly reduce the parameters of large vision transformers with only negligible performance degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-guided-mlp-reduction-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting Vision-Language Foundation Model for Next Generation Medical Ultrasound Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-vision-language-foundation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical ultrasonography is an essential imaging technique for examining superficial organs and tissues, including lymph nodes, breast, and thyroid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-vision-language-foundation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Well Begun is Half Done: Low-resource Preference Alignment by Weak-to-Strong Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/well-begun-is-half-done-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the observation that the difficulty of generating aligned responses is concentrated at the beginning of decoding, we propose a novel framework, Weak-to-Strong Decoding (WSD), to enhance the alignment ability of base models by the guidance of a small aligned model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/well-begun-is-half-done-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Object Stitching for Unsupervised Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-object-stitching-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning for single object centric images has achieved remarkable progress on unsupervised representation, but suffering inferior performance on the widespread images with multiple objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-object-stitching-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniCPM4: Ultra-Efficient LLMs on End Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicpm4-ultra-efficient-llms-on-end-devices</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in terms of model architecture, we propose InfLLM v2, a trainable sparse attention mechanism that accelerates both prefilling and decoding phases for long-context processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicpm4-ultra-efficient-llms-on-end-devices</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open World Scene Graph Generation using Vision Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-scene-graph-generation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene-Graph Generation (SGG) seeks to recognize objects in an image and distill their salient pairwise relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-scene-graph-generation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalPFN: Amortized Causal Effect Estimation via In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalpfn-amortized-causal-effect-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CausalPFN combines ideas from Bayesian causal inference with the large-scale training protocol of prior-fitted networks (PFNs), learning to map raw observations directly to causal effects without any task-specific adjustment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalpfn-amortized-causal-effect-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Phase Deep Learning Framework for Adaptive Time-Stepping in High-Speed Flow Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-phase-deep-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a two-phase machine learning method, known as ShockCast, to model high-speed flows with adaptive time-stepping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-phase-deep-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flowing Datasets with Wasserstein over Wasserstein Gradient Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowing-datasets-with-wasserstein-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many applications in machine learning involve data represented as probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowing-datasets-with-wasserstein-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeGave: 3D Physics Learning from Dynamic Videos by Gaussian Velocity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freegave-3d-physics-learning-from-dynamic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to model 3D scene geometry, appearance, and the underlying physics purely from multi-view videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freegave-3d-physics-learning-from-dynamic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eliciting Fine-Tuned Transformer Capabilities via Inference-Time Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliciting-fine-tuned-transformer-capabilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grounded in the Turing completeness of transformers, these results provide a theoretical foundation for resource-efficient deployment of large language models, with practical techniques like retrieval-augmented generation bridging theory to real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eliciting-fine-tuned-transformer-capabilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete and Continuous Difference of Submodular Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-and-continuous-difference-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For discrete domains, we observe that DS minimization is equivalent to minimizing the difference of two convex (DC) functions, as in the set function case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-and-continuous-difference-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLNet: Direction-Aware Feature Integration for Robust Lane Detection in Complex Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlnet-direction-aware-feature-integration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of autonomous driving systems has created a pressing need for accurate and robust lane detection to ensure driving safety and reliability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlnet-direction-aware-feature-integration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Compact Vision Tokens for Efficient Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-compact-vision-tokens-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a Spatial Token Fusion (STF) method to learn compact vision tokens for short vision token sequence, where spatial-adjacent tokens are fused into one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-compact-vision-tokens-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The influence of cell phenotype on collective cell invasion into the extracellular matrix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-influence-of-cell-phenotype-on-collective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the interactions between cells and the extracellular matrix (ECM) during collective cell invasion is crucial for advancements in tissue engineering, cancer therapies, and regenerative medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-influence-of-cell-phenotype-on-collective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Currents of Conflict: Decomposing Conflict Trends with Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-currents-of-conflict-decomposing-conflict</link>
      <description><![CDATA[I present a novel approach to estimating the temporal and spatial patterns of violent conflict.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-currents-of-conflict-decomposing-conflict</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Potential of Consistency Learning for Detecting and Grounding Multi-Modal Media Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-consistency-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the threat of fake news, the task of detecting and grounding multi-modal media manipulation DGM4 has received increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-consistency-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDS-Net: Shallow-Deep Synergism-detection Network for infrared  small target detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sds-net-shallow-deep-synergism-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current CNN-based infrared small target detection (IRSTD) methods generally overlook the heterogeneity between shallow and deep features, leading to inefficient collaboration between shallow fine-grained structural information and deep high-level semantic representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sds-net-shallow-deep-synergism-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eigenspectrum Analysis of Neural Networks without Aspect Ratio Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenspectrum-analysis-of-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate our approach across various optimization techniques and application domains that involve eigenspectrum analysis of weights, including image classification in computer vision (CV) models, scientific machine learning (SciML) model training, and large language model (LLM) pruning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenspectrum-analysis-of-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TissUnet: Improved Extracranial Tissue and Cranium Segmentation for Children through Adulthood</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tissunet-improved-extracranial-tissue-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a second validation using expert manual annotations, median Dice was 0. 83 [IQR: 0. 83-0. 84] in healthy individuals and 0. 81 [IQR: 0. 78-0. 83] in tumor cases, outperforming previous state-of-the-art method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tissunet-improved-extracranial-tissue-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge-Enabled Collaborative Object Detection for Real-Time Multi-Vehicle Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-enabled-collaborative-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce an innovative framework, Edge-Enabled Collaborative Object Detection (ECOD) for CAVs, that leverages edge computing and multi-CAV collaboration for real-time, multi-perspective object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge-enabled-collaborative-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference economics of language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-economics-of-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a theoretical model that addresses the economic trade-off between cost per token versus serial token generation speed when deploying LLMs for inference at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-economics-of-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight analyses of first-order methods with error feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-analyses-of-first-order-methods-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication between agents often constitutes a major computational bottleneck in distributed learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-analyses-of-first-order-methods-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBER2024 -- A Benchmark Dataset for Holistic Evaluation of Malware Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ember2024-a-benchmark-dataset-for-holistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A lack of accessible data has historically restricted malware analysis research, and practitioners have relied heavily on datasets provided by industry sources to advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ember2024-a-benchmark-dataset-for-holistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OGGSplat: Open Gaussian Growing for Generalizable Reconstruction with Expanded Field-of-View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oggsplat-open-gaussian-growing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate our method, we establish a Gaussian Outpainting (GO) benchmark that assesses both semantic and generative quality of reconstructed open-vocabulary scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oggsplat-open-gaussian-growing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exp4Fuse: A Rank Fusion Framework for Enhanced Sparse Retrieval using Large Language Model-based Query Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exp4fuse-a-rank-fusion-framework-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the efficacy of this method is highly dependent on the quality of the generated documents, which often requires complex prompt strategies and the integration of advanced dense retrieval techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exp4fuse-a-rank-fusion-framework-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Tempering Sampler with Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tempering-sampler-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a novel method to combine high-temperature diffusion models to generate approximate lower-temperature samples, which are minimally refined using MCMC and used to train the next diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tempering-sampler-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time to Talk: LLM Agents for Asynchronous Group Communication in Mafia Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-to-talk-llm-agents-for-asynchronous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, in group chats, online team meetings, or social games, there is no inherent notion of turns; therefore, the decision of when to speak forms a crucial part of the participant's decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-to-talk-llm-agents-for-asynchronous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AliTok: Towards Sequence Modeling Alignment between Tokenizer and Autoregressive Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alitok-towards-sequence-modeling-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive image generation aims to predict the next token based on previous ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alitok-towards-sequence-modeling-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs for sensory-motor control: Combining in-context and iterative learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-for-sensory-motor-control-combining-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method that enables large language models (LLMs) to control embodied agents by directly mapping continuous observation vectors to continuous action vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-for-sensory-motor-control-combining-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting Logical Reasoning in LLMs: A Fine-Grained Evaluation and Supervision Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-logical-reasoning-in-llms-a-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Logical reasoning is a core capability for many applications of large language models (LLMs), yet existing benchmarks often rely solely on final-answer accuracy, failing to capture the quality and structure of the reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-logical-reasoning-in-llms-a-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMSU: A Massive Multi-task Spoken Language Understanding and Reasoning Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmsu-a-massive-multi-task-spoken-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce MMSU, a comprehensive benchmark designed specifically for understanding and reasoning in spoken language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmsu-a-massive-multi-task-spoken-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI for Intent-Based Industrial Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentic-ai-for-intent-based-industrial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent development of Agentic AI systems, empowered by autonomous large language models (LLMs) agents with planning and tool-usage capabilities, enables new possibilities for the evolution of industrial automation and reduces the complexity introduced by Industry 4. 0.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentic-ai-for-intent-based-industrial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOLFer: Smaller LM-Generated Documents Hallucination Filter &amp; Combiner for Query Expansion in Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/golfer-smaller-lm-generated-documents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs)-based query expansion for information retrieval augments queries with generated hypothetical documents with LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/golfer-smaller-lm-generated-documents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Play to Replay: Composed Video Retrieval for Temporally Fine-Grained Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-play-to-replay-composed-video-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Composed Video Retrieval (CoVR) retrieves a target video given a query video and a modification text describing the intended change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-play-to-replay-composed-video-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth in the Few: High-Value Data Selection for Efficient Multi-Modal Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-in-the-few-high-value-data-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) have made significant progress in complex reasoning tasks via reinforcement learning, it is commonly believed that extensive training data is necessary for improving multi-modal reasoning ability, inevitably leading to data redundancy and substantial computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-in-the-few-high-value-data-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashDMoE: Fast Distributed MoE in a Single Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashdmoe-fast-distributed-moe-in-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The computational sparsity of Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) models enables sub-linear growth in compute cost as model size increases, thus offering a scalable path to training massive neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashdmoe-fast-distributed-moe-in-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Appearance Codes and Bilateral Grids for Driving Scene Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-appearance-codes-and-bilateral-grids</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel multi-scale bilateral grid that unifies appearance codes and bilateral grids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-appearance-codes-and-bilateral-grids</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Channel Allocation for IEEE 802.11be Multi-Link Operation: When MAB Meets LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-channel-allocation-for-ieee-802</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further reduce sample complexity and enhance generalizability across diverse network scenarios, we put forth LLM-BAI-MCTS, an intelligent algorithm for the dynamic channel allocation problem by integrating the Large Language Model (LLM) into the BAI-MCTS algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-channel-allocation-for-ieee-802</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User Altruism in Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-altruism-in-recommendation-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the users' social welfare under truthful preference reporting and under a class of strategies capturing user altruism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-altruism-in-recommendation-systems</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
