<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 09:12:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adjustment Identification Distance: A gadjid for Causal Structure Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjustment-identification-distance-a-gadjid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating graphs learned by causal discovery algorithms is difficult: The number of edges that differ between two graphs does not reflect how the graphs differ with respect to the identifying formulas they suggest for causal effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjustment-identification-distance-a-gadjid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Multi-Task Transfer Learning for Soft Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-multi-task-transfer-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that when we extract knowledge from source tasks via training source prompts, we need to consider this correlation among source tasks for better transfer to target tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-multi-task-transfer-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Model on Million-Length Video And Language With RingAttention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/world-model-on-million-length-video-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work paves the way for training on massive datasets of long video and language to develop understanding of both human knowledge and the multimodal world, and broader capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/world-model-on-million-length-video-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Higher Layers Need More LoRA Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higher-layers-need-more-lora-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel parameter-efficient MoE method, \textit{\textbf{M}oE-L\textbf{o}RA with \textbf{L}ayer-wise Expert \textbf{A}llocation (MoLA)} for Transformer-based models, where each model layer has the flexibility to employ a varying number of LoRA experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higher-layers-need-more-lora-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually Dehallucinative Instruction Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-dehallucinative-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, we compare synthetic visual instruction datasets that share the same source data by visual instruction tuning and conduct general visual recognition tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-dehallucinative-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept-1K: A Novel Benchmark for Instance Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-1k-a-novel-benchmark-for-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing IL scenarios and datasets are unqualified for assessing forgetting in PLMs, giving an illusion that PLMs do not suffer from catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-1k-a-novel-benchmark-for-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Assessment and Selection under Temporal Distribution Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-assessment-and-selection-under-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate model assessment and selection in a changing environment, by synthesizing datasets from both the current time period and historical epochs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-assessment-and-selection-under-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaGA: Large Language and Graph Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llaga-large-language-and-graph-assistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have empowered the advance in graph-structured data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llaga-large-language-and-graph-assistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verified Multi-Step Synthesis using Large Language Models and Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verified-multi-step-synthesis-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The base model with VMCTS is even competitive with ChatGPT4 augmented with plugins and multiple re-tries on these problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verified-multi-step-synthesis-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Factual Error Correction for Abstractive Summarization via Data Distillation and Conditional-generation Cloze</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-factual-error-correction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Improving factual consistency in abstractive summarization has been a focus of current research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-factual-error-correction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pix2Code: Learning to Compose Neural Visual Concepts as Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2code-learning-to-compose-neural-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The challenge in learning abstract concepts from images in an unsupervised fashion lies in the required integration of visual perception and generalizable relational reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pix2code-learning-to-compose-neural-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery under Off-Target Interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-under-off-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal graph discovery is a significant problem with applications across various disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-under-off-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Produce Semi-dense Correspondences for Visual Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-produce-semi-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we propose a novel localization method that extracts reliable semi-dense 2D-3D matching points based on dense keypoint matches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-produce-semi-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translating Images to Road Network:A Non-Autoregressive Sequence-to-Sequence Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translating-images-to-road-network-a-non-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, our work establishes a unified representation of both types of data domain by projecting both Euclidean and non-Euclidean data into an integer series called RoadNet Sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translating-images-to-road-network-a-non-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Logical Approach to Criminal Case Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-logical-approach-to-criminal-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We created an ontology of motives and methods of murder from dictionaries and dictionaries, added it to the knowledge graph of ``The Adventure of the Speckled Band'', and applied scripts to determine motives, opportunities, and methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-logical-approach-to-criminal-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ant Colony Optimization for Cooperative Inspection Path Planning Using Multiple Unmanned Aerial Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-cooperative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new swarm intelligence-based approach to deal with the cooperative path planning problem of unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs), which is essential for the automatic inspection of infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-cooperative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel-friendly Spatio-Temporal Graph Learning for Photovoltaic Degradation Analysis at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-friendly-spatio-temporal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further verify the generality and effectiveness of ST-GTrend for trend analysis using financial and economic datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-friendly-spatio-temporal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dense Reward View on Aligning Text-to-Image Diffusion with Preference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-reward-view-on-aligning-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aligning text-to-image diffusion model (T2I) with preference has been gaining increasing research attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dense-reward-view-on-aligning-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COLD-Attack: Jailbreaking LLMs with Stealthiness and Controllability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-attack-jailbreaking-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this connection, we adapt the Energy-based Constrained Decoding with Langevin Dynamics (COLD), a state-of-the-art, highly efficient algorithm in controllable text generation, and introduce the COLD-Attack framework which unifies and automates the search of adversarial LLM attacks under a variety of control requirements such as fluency, stealthiness, sentiment, and left-right-coherence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-attack-jailbreaking-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Smith: A Single Image Can Jailbreak One Million Multimodal LLM Agents Exponentially Fast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-smith-a-single-image-can-jailbreak-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A multimodal large language model (MLLM) agent can receive instructions, capture images, retrieve histories from memory, and decide which tools to use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-smith-a-single-image-can-jailbreak-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimized Information Flow for Transformer Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimized-information-flow-for-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One-stream Transformer trackers have shown outstanding performance in challenging benchmark datasets over the last three years, as they enable interaction between the target template and search region tokens to extract target-oriented features with mutual guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimized-information-flow-for-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Backdoor Attacks on Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-backdoor-attacks-on-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backdoor attacks are commonly executed by contaminating training data, such that a trigger can activate predetermined harmful effects during the test phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-backdoor-attacks-on-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera Calibration through Geometric Constraints from Rotation and Projection Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-calibration-through-geometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The process of camera calibration involves estimating the intrinsic and extrinsic parameters, which are essential for accurately performing tasks such as 3D reconstruction, object tracking and augmented reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-calibration-through-geometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Distributional Analogue to the Successor Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-distributional-analogue-to-the-successor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper contributes a new approach for distributional reinforcement learning which elucidates a clean separation of transition structure and reward in the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-distributional-analogue-to-the-successor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Behavior Prediction by Episodic-Memory Implanted NDT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vehicle-behavior-prediction-by-episodic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the interpretability of behavior prediction of target vehicles by an Episodic Memory implanted Neural Decision Tree (abbrev.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vehicle-behavior-prediction-by-episodic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Data Poisoning on Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-data-poisoning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual explanations provide a popular method for analyzing the predictions of black-box systems, and they can offer the opportunity for computational recourse by suggesting actionable changes on how to change the input to obtain a different (i. e. more favorable) system output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-data-poisoning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSC-CPI: Multi-Scale Protein Sequence-Structure Contrasting for Efficient and Generalizable Compound-Protein Interaction Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psc-cpi-multi-scale-protein-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compound-Protein Interaction (CPI) prediction aims to predict the pattern and strength of compound-protein interactions for rational drug discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psc-cpi-multi-scale-protein-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedLPS: Heterogeneous Federated Learning for Multiple Tasks with Local Parameter Sharing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlps-heterogeneous-federated-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FedLPS leverages principles from transfer learning to facilitate the deployment of multiple tasks on a single device by dividing the local model into a shareable encoder and task-specific encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlps-heterogeneous-federated-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Mamba: Towards Learning on Graphs with State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mamba-towards-learning-on-graphs-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the recent success of State Space Models (SSMs), such as Mamba, we present Graph Mamba Networks (GMNs), a general framework for a new class of GNNs based on selective SSMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-mamba-towards-learning-on-graphs-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Position Embedding of Graphs with Landmarks and Clustering for Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-position-embedding-of-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HPLC leverages the positional information of nodes based on landmarks at various levels of hierarchy such as nodes' distances to landmarks, inter-landmark distances and hierarchical grouping of clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-position-embedding-of-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BdSLW60: A Word-Level Bangla Sign Language Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bdslw60-a-word-level-bangla-sign-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sign language discourse is an essential mode of daily communication for the deaf and hard-of-hearing people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bdslw60-a-word-level-bangla-sign-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plausible Extractive Rationalization through Semi-Supervised Entailment Signal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plausible-extractive-rationalization-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing use of complex and opaque black box models requires the adoption of interpretable measures, one such option is extractive rationalizing models, which serve as a more interpretable alternative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plausible-extractive-rationalization-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Neural Expert Processes for Learning from Demonstration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-neural-expert-processes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we compare the performance of CNEP with another LfD framework, namely Conditional Neural Movement Primitives (CNMP), on a range of tasks, including experiments on a real robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-neural-expert-processes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for the Automated Analysis of Optimization Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-the-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability of Large Language Models (LLMs) to generate high-quality text and code has fuelled their rise in popularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-the-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoMathText: Autonomous Data Selection with Language Models for Mathematical Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automathtext-autonomous-data-selection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve language models' proficiency in mathematical reasoning via continual pretraining, we introduce a novel strategy that leverages base language models for autonomous data selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automathtext-autonomous-data-selection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Recommendation with Personal Popularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-recommendation-with-personal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many methods have been proposed to reduce GP bias but they fail to notice the fundamental problem of GP, i. e., it considers popularity from a \textit{global} perspective of \textit{all users} and uses a single set of popular items, and thus cannot capture the interests of individual users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-recommendation-with-personal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Moving-Band Statistical Arbitrages via Convex-Concave Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-moving-band-statistical-arbitrages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new method for finding statistical arbitrages that can contain more assets than just the traditional pair.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-moving-band-statistical-arbitrages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tighter Bounds on the Information Bottleneck with Application to Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tighter-bounds-on-the-information-bottleneck</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These advancements strengthen the case for the IB and its variational approximations as a data modeling framework, and provide a simple method to significantly enhance the adversarial robustness of classifier DNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tighter-bounds-on-the-information-bottleneck</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Digital Cousins for Ensemble Q-Learning in Large-Scale Wireless Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-digital-cousins-for-ensemble-q</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Herein, a novel ensemble Q-learning algorithm that addresses the performance and complexity challenges of the traditional Q-learning algorithm for optimizing wireless networks is presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-digital-cousins-for-ensemble-q</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Careless Whisper: Speech-to-Text Hallucination Harms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/careless-whisper-speech-to-text-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech-to-text services aim to transcribe input audio as accurately as possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/careless-whisper-speech-to-text-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring trustworthy and ethical behaviour in intelligent logical agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-trustworthy-and-ethical-behaviour-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous Intelligent Agents are employed in many applications upon which the life and welfare of living beings and vital social functions may depend.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensuring-trustworthy-and-ethical-behaviour-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only the Curve Shape Matters: Training Foundation Models for Zero-Shot Multivariate Time Series Forecasting through Next Curve Shape Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/only-the-curve-shape-matters-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present General Time Transformer (GTT), an encoder-only style foundation model for zero-shot multivariate time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/only-the-curve-shape-matters-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AYDIV: Adaptable Yielding 3D Object Detection via Integrated Contextual Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aydiv-adaptable-yielding-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining LiDAR and camera data has shown potential in enhancing short-distance object detection in autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aydiv-adaptable-yielding-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accuracy of TextFooler black box adversarial attacks on 01 loss sign activation neural network ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-of-textfooler-black-box-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We ask the following question in this study: are 01 loss sign activation neural networks hard to deceive with a popular black box text adversarial attack program called TextFooler?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accuracy-of-textfooler-black-box-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Decentralized Learning with Random Walks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-decentralized-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The popularity of federated learning comes from the possibility of better scalability and the ability for participants to keep control of their data, improving data security and sovereignty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-decentralized-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoisonedRAG: Knowledge Poisoning Attacks to Retrieval-Augmented Generation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisonedrag-knowledge-poisoning-attacks-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate knowledge poisoning attacks as an optimization problem, whose solution is a set of poisoned texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisonedrag-knowledge-poisoning-attacks-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extensible Multi-Granularity Fusion Network for Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extensible-multi-granularity-fusion-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the Extensible Multi-Granularity Fusion (EMGF) network, which integrates information from dependency and constituent syntactic, attention semantic , and external knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extensible-multi-granularity-fusion-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Scalable Fine-Tune of Language Models for Genome Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-scalable-fine-tune-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Impressively, applying these adapters on natural language foundation models matched or even exceeded the performance of DNA foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-scalable-fine-tune-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCR: Video representation for Contextual Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcr-video-representation-for-contextual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Streamlining content discovery within media archives requires integrating advanced data representations and effective visualization techniques for clear communication of video topics to users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcr-video-representation-for-contextual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auxiliary Tasks to Boost Biaffine Semantic Dependency Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-to-boost-biaffine-semantic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The biaffine parser of Dozat and Manning (2017) was successfully extended to semantic dependency parsing (SDP) (Dozat and Manning, 2018).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-to-boost-biaffine-semantic-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
