<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 21:06:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal graph models fail to capture global temporal dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-models-fail-to-capture-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We outline our observations and propose a trivial optimization-free baseline of "recently popular nodes" outperforming other methods on all medium and large-size datasets in the Temporal Graph Benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-models-fail-to-capture-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyra: Orchestrating Dual Correction in Automated Theorem Proving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-orchestrating-dual-correction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce Conjecture Correction, an error feedback mechanism designed to interact with prover to refine formal proof conjectures with prover error messages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-orchestrating-dual-correction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C3Net: interatomic potential neural network for prediction of physicochemical properties in heterogenous systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c3net-interatomic-potential-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the interactions of a solute with its environment is of fundamental importance in chemistry and biology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c3net-interatomic-potential-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Streaming Video Temporal Action Segmentation with Reinforce Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-streaming-video-temporal-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The end-to-end SVTAS which regard TAS as an action segment clustering task can expand the application scenarios of TAS; and RL is used to alleviate the problem of inconsistent optimization objective and direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-streaming-video-temporal-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Content-Driven Micro-Video Recommendation Dataset at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-content-driven-micro-video-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Micro-videos have recently gained immense popularity, sparking critical research in micro-video recommendation with significant implications for the entertainment, advertising, and e-commerce industries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-content-driven-micro-video-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLPBench: Evaluating Large Language Models on Solving NLP Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlpbench-evaluating-large-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent developments in large language models (LLMs) have shown promise in enhancing the capabilities of natural language processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlpbench-evaluating-large-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algebraic and Statistical Properties of the Ordinary Least Squares Interpolator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algebraic-and-statistical-properties-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning research has uncovered the phenomenon of benign overfitting for over-parameterized statistical models, which has drawn significant theoretical interest in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algebraic-and-statistical-properties-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-based Analysis of Basins of Attraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-analysis-of-basins-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study showcases the effectiveness of convolutional neural networks (CNNs) in characterizing the complexity and unpredictability of basins of attraction for diverse dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-analysis-of-basins-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Dataset for Localization, Mapping and Crop Monitoring in Citrus Tree Farms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dataset-for-localization-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we introduce the CitrusFarm dataset, a comprehensive multimodal sensory dataset collected by a wheeled mobile robot operating in agricultural fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dataset-for-localization-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Weight Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-weight-entropy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under this paradigm, the epistemic uncertainty is described by the weight distribution of maximal entropy that produces neural networks "consistent" with the training observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-weight-entropy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survey on Deep Face Restoration: From Non-blind to Blind and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-on-deep-face-restoration-from-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also discuss notable benchmarks commonly utilized in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survey-on-deep-face-restoration-from-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Prompt Learning: Addressing Cross-Attention Leakage for Text-Based Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-prompt-learning-addressing-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale text-to-image generative models have been a ground-breaking development in generative AI, with diffusion models showing their astounding ability to synthesize convincing images following an input text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-prompt-learning-addressing-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Feature Fairness in Recommendation via Adversaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-feature-fairness-in-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage the Adaptive Adversarial perturbation based on the widely-applied Factorization Machine (AAFM) as our backbone model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-feature-fairness-in-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatCounselor: A Large Language Models for Mental Health Support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatcounselor-a-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ChatCounselor, a large language model (LLM) solution designed to provide mental health support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatcounselor-a-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the changes in BOLD responses during viewing of images with varied complexity: An fMRI time-series based analysis on human vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-changes-in-bold-responses</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The obtained result of this analysis has established a baseline in studying how differently human brain functions while looking into images of diverse complexities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-changes-in-bold-responses</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics Inspired Hybrid Attention for SAR Target Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-inspired-hybrid-attention-for-sar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been a recent emphasis on integrating physical models and deep neural networks (DNNs) for SAR target recognition, to improve performance and achieve a higher level of physical interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-inspired-hybrid-attention-for-sar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Kinematics-inspired Skeleton-based Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-kinematics-inspired-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous approaches to detecting human anomalies in videos have typically relied on implicit modeling by directly applying the model to video or skeleton data, potentially resulting in inaccurate modeling of motion information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-kinematics-inspired-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OceanBench: The Sea Surface Height Edition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oceanbench-the-sea-surface-height-edition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It provides plug-and-play data and pre-configured pipelines for ML researchers to benchmark their models and a transparent configurable framework for researchers to customize and extend the pipeline for their tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oceanbench-the-sea-surface-height-edition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show-1: Marrying Pixel and Latent Diffusion Models for Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-1-marrying-pixel-and-latent-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we are the first to propose a hybrid model, dubbed as Show-1, which marries pixel-based and latent-based VDMs for text-to-video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-1-marrying-pixel-and-latent-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Canonical Correlation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-canonical-correlation-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates fairness and bias in Canonical Correlation Analysis (CCA), a widely used statistical technique for examining the relationship between two sets of variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-canonical-correlation-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-based Visual Dispersal for Few-shot Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-based-visual-dispersal-for-few-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, recent works consider the Few-shot Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (FUDA) where only a few source samples are labeled, and conduct knowledge transfer via self-supervised learning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-based-visual-dispersal-for-few-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Compressed Video Stream Learning for Generic Event Boundary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-compressed-video-stream-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we use lightweight ConvNets to extract features of the P-frames in the GOPs and spatial-channel attention module (SCAM) is designed to refine the feature representations of the P-frames based on the compressed information with bidirectional information flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-compressed-video-stream-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Facade Parsing with Vision Transformers and Line Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-facade-parsing-with-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Comprehensive Facade Parsing (CFP), a dataset meticulously designed to encompass the intricacies of real-world facade parsing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-facade-parsing-with-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Networks with Oriented 1D Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-networks-with-oriented-1d-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we find that one key ingredient to a high-performing 1D ConvNet is oriented 1D kernels: 1D kernels that are oriented not just horizontally or vertically, but also at other angles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-networks-with-oriented-1d-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNN4EEG: A Benchmark and Toolkit for Electroencephalography Classification with Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn4eeg-a-benchmark-and-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing this shortfall, there has been a burgeoning interest in recent years in harnessing the potential of Graph Neural Networks (GNN) to exploit the topological information by modeling features selected from each EEG channel in a graph structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn4eeg-a-benchmark-and-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Chain of Thought Reasoning: Advances, Frontiers and Future</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-chain-of-thought-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-thought reasoning, a cognitive process fundamental to human intelligence, has garnered significant attention in the realm of artificial intelligence and natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-chain-of-thought-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience and Evidence are the eyes of an excellent summarizer! Towards Knowledge Infused Multi-modal Clinical Conversation Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experience-and-evidence-are-the-eyes-of-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a knowledge-infused, multi-modal, multi-tasking medical domain identification and clinical conversation summary generation (MM-CliConSummation) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experience-and-evidence-are-the-eyes-of-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DifAttack: Query-Efficient Black-Box Attack via Disentangled Feature Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difattack-query-efficient-black-box-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, due to the avoidance of using surrogate models' gradient information when optimizing AEs for black-box models, our proposed DifAttack inherently possesses better attack capability in the open-set scenario, where the training dataset of the victim model is unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difattack-query-efficient-black-box-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Multi-Agent Deep Reinforcement Learning Control with Relative Entropy Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-agent-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It alleviates the inconsistency of multiple agents' policy updates by introducing the relative entropy regularization to the Centralized Training with Decentralized Execution (CTDE) framework with the Actor-Critic (AC) structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-agent-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Flawed Data: Weakly Supervised Automatic Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-flawed-data-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training automatic speech recognition (ASR) systems requires large amounts of well-curated paired data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-flawed-data-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volumetric Semantically Consistent 3D Panoptic Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-semantically-consistent-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an online 2D-to-3D semantic instance mapping algorithm aimed at generating comprehensive, accurate, and efficient semantic 3D maps suitable for autonomous agents in unstructured environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volumetric-semantically-consistent-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Discontinuity Design: With an Application to the Economic Effects of Internet Shutdowns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-discontinuity-design-with-an-application</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thresholds in treatment assignments can produce discontinuities in outcomes, revealing causal insights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-discontinuity-design-with-an-application</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated Corpora and Benchmarks for Long-Form Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/updated-corpora-and-benchmarks-for-long-form</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vast majority of ASR research uses corpora in which both the training and test data have been pre-segmented into utterances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/updated-corpora-and-benchmarks-for-long-form</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Sequential DeepFake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sequential-deepfake-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods only focus on detecting one-step facial manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sequential-deepfake-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Test-Time Adaptation: Tri-Net Self-Training with Balanced Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-test-time-adaptation-tri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-Time Adaptation aims to adapt source domain model to testing data at inference stage with success demonstrated in adapting to unseen corruptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-test-time-adaptation-tri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fastMONAI: A low-code deep learning library for medical image analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastmonai-a-low-code-deep-learning-library</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce fastMONAI, an open-source Python-based deep learning library for 3D medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastmonai-a-low-code-deep-learning-library</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Communication and Computation Framework for Goal-Oriented Semantic Communication with Distortion Rate Resilience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-communication-and-computation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research efforts on semantic communication have mostly considered accuracy as a main problem for optimizing goal-oriented communication systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-communication-and-computation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFORM: Removing False Correlation in Multi-level Interaction for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reform-removing-false-correlation-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a CTR prediction framework that removes false correlation in multi-level feature interaction, termed REFORM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reform-removing-false-correlation-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Stream-based Visual Object Tracking: A High-Resolution Benchmark Dataset and A Novel Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-stream-based-visual-object-tracking-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking using bio-inspired event cameras has drawn more and more attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-stream-based-visual-object-tracking-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthia's Melody: A Benchmark Framework for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthia-s-melody-a-benchmark-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advancements in deep learning for vision and natural language, unsupervised domain adaptation in audio remains relatively unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthia-s-melody-a-benchmark-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Population-Graph Construction Methods and Graph Neural Networks for Brain Age Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-population-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude that static graph construction approaches are potentially insufficient for the task of brain age estimation and make recommendations for alternative research directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-population-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training-free Image Manipulation Localization through Non-Mutually Exclusive Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-free-image-manipulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that contrastive learning is more suitable to tackle the data insufficiency problem for IML.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-free-image-manipulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM-XComposer: A Vision-Language Large Model for Advanced Text-image Comprehension and Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer-a-vision-language-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose InternLM-XComposer, a vision-language large model that enables advanced image-text comprehension and composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer-a-vision-language-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Invariant Transformation for better Adversarial Transferability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-invariant-transformation-for-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we find that the existing input transformation based attacks transform the input image globally, resulting in limited diversity of the transformed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-invariant-transformation-for-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Analysis of Quantum State Learning Process in Quantum Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-analysis-of-quantum-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a quantum analog of probability distribution learning, quantum state learning is theoretically and practically essential in quantum machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-analysis-of-quantum-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unidirectional brain-computer interface: Artificial neural network encoding natural images to fMRI response in the visual cortex</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidirectional-brain-computer-interface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While significant advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) have catalyzed progress across various domains, its full potential in understanding visual perception remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidirectional-brain-computer-interface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Volleyball Stats for All Levels: Automatic Setting Tactic Detection and Classification with a Single Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-volleyball-stats-for-all-levels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our frameworks combine setting ball trajectory recognition with a novel set trajectory classifier to generate comprehensive and advanced statistical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-volleyball-stats-for-all-levels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLIQ: Quantum Image Similarity Networks on Noisy Quantum Computers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliq-quantum-image-similarity-networks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploration into quantum machine learning has grown tremendously in recent years due to the ability of quantum computers to speed up classical programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliq-quantum-image-similarity-networks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Text-To-Image Customization:From LyCORIS Fine-Tuning to Model Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-text-to-image-customization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generative models have garnered immense attention for their ability to produce high-fidelity images from text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-text-to-image-customization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgetting-aware Linear Bias for Attentive Knowledge Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgetting-aware-linear-bias-for-attentive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This problem arises from the bias that overprioritizes the correlation of questions while inadvertently ignoring the impact of forgetting behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgetting-aware-linear-bias-for-attentive</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
