<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 09:11:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Relation Between (De)Motivating Topics and Public Stance toward COVID-19 Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-relation-between-de-motivating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While social media plays a vital role in communication nowadays, misinformation and trolls can easily take over the conversation and steer public opinion on these platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-relation-between-de-motivating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying lottery tickets under label noise: accuracy, calibration, and complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-lottery-tickets-under-label-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pruning deep neural networks is a widely used strategy to alleviate the computational burden in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-lottery-tickets-under-label-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3HAN: A Deep Neural Network for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3han-a-deep-neural-network-for-fake-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid spread of fake news is a serious problem calling for AI solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3han-a-deep-neural-network-for-fake-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving and Generating NPR Sunday Puzzles with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-and-generating-npr-sunday-puzzles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the ability of large language models to solve and generate puzzles from the NPR Sunday Puzzle game show using PUZZLEQA, a dataset comprising 15 years of on-air puzzles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-and-generating-npr-sunday-puzzles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing the Rank Degeneration in Sequential Recommendation via Singular Spectrum Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-the-rank-degeneration-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also establish a correlation between the ranks of sequence and item embeddings and the rank of the user-item preference prediction matrix, which can affect recommendation diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-the-rank-degeneration-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GADBench: Revisiting and Benchmarking Supervised Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gadbench-revisiting-and-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a long history of traditional Graph Anomaly Detection (GAD) algorithms and recently popular Graph Neural Networks (GNNs), it is still not clear (1) how they perform under a standard comprehensive setting, (2) whether GNNs outperform traditional algorithms such as tree ensembles, and (3) their efficiency on large-scale graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gadbench-revisiting-and-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Deep Ensembles -- A Large-Scale Evaluation of Bayesian Deep Learning under Distribution Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-deep-ensembles-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian deep learning (BDL) is a promising approach to achieve well-calibrated predictions on distribution-shifted data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-deep-ensembles-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding human mobility patterns in Chicago: an analysis of taxi data using clustering techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-human-mobility-patterns-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This analysis will provide a sense of which neighborhoods individuals are using taxis to travel between, suggesting regions to focus new public transit development efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-human-mobility-patterns-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Molecular Discovery with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-molecular-discovery-with-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language is expected to be a key medium for various human-machine interactions in the era of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-molecular-discovery-with-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Mitigating Spurious Correlations in the Wild: A Benchmark &amp; a more Realistic Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-mitigating-spurious-correlations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks often exploit non-predictive features that are spuriously correlated with class labels, leading to poor performance on groups of examples without such features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-mitigating-spurious-correlations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic Weights and How to Find Them: Where to Prune in Dynamic Sparse Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-weights-and-how-to-find-them-where</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key components of this framework are the pruning and growing criteria, which are repeatedly applied during the training process to adjust the network's sparse connectivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-weights-and-how-to-find-them-where</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMFlow: An Extensible Toolkit for Finetuning and Inference of Large Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmflow-an-extensible-toolkit-for-finetuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the number of available models and specialized tasks keeps growing, the job of general finetuning becomes highly nontrivial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmflow-an-extensible-toolkit-for-finetuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a speed-up alternative method for this fundamental task with comparable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Interactions Reveal Linguistic Structure in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-interactions-reveal-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study feature interactions in the context of feature attribution methods for post-hoc interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-interactions-reveal-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional End-to-End Learning of Retriever-Reader Paradigm for Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-end-to-end-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity Linking (EL) is a fundamental task for Information Extraction and Knowledge Graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-end-to-end-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark data to study the influence of pre-training on explanation performance in MR image classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-data-to-study-the-influence-of-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a benchmark dataset that allows for quantifying explanation performance in a realistic magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-data-to-study-the-influence-of-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSMT: Real-time Stylized Motion Transition for Characters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsmt-real-time-stylized-motion-transition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Styled online in-between motion generation has important application scenarios in computer animation and games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsmt-real-time-stylized-motion-transition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroCLIP: Neuromorphic Data Understanding by CLIP and SNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroclip-neuromorphic-data-understanding-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle "unseen" recognition for the neuromorphic data, in this paper, we propose NeuroCLIP, which transfers the CLIP's 2D pre-trained knowledge to event spikes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroclip-neuromorphic-data-understanding-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EquiformerV2: Improved Equivariant Transformer for Scaling to Higher-Degree Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equiformerv2-improved-equivariant-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equivariant Transformers such as Equiformer have demonstrated the efficacy of applying Transformers to the domain of 3D atomistic systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equiformerv2-improved-equivariant-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Implicit Image Function for Efficient Arbitrary-Scale Image Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-implicit-image-function-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a Coarse-to-Fine Multilayer Perceptron (C2F-MLP) to perform decoding with dynamic coordinate slicing, where the number of coordinates in each slice varies as the scale factor varies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-implicit-image-function-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient ResNets: Residual Network Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-resnets-residual-network-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our ResNet achieves a test accuracy of 96. 04% on CIFAR-10 which is much higher than ResNet18 (which has greater than 11 million trainable parameters) when equipped with a number of training strategies and suitable ResNet hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-resnets-residual-network-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdCraft: An Advanced Reinforcement Learning Benchmark Environment for Search Engine Marketing Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adcraft-an-advanced-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce \env{}, a novel benchmark environment for the Reinforcement Learning (RL) community distinguished by its stochastic and non-stationary properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adcraft-an-advanced-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StarVQA+: Co-training Space-Time Attention for Video Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starvqa-co-training-space-time-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attention based Transformer has achieved great success in many computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starvqa-co-training-space-time-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-VAAL: Multimodal Variational Adversarial Active Learning for Downstream Medical Image Analysis Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-vaal-multimodal-variational-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acquiring properly annotated data is expensive in the medical field as it requires experts, time-consuming protocols, and rigorous validation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-vaal-multimodal-variational-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambigram Generation by A Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambigram-generation-by-a-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, the pair of 'A' and 'V' shows a high ambigramability (that is, it is easy to generate their ambigrams), and the pair of 'D' and 'K' shows a lower ambigramability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambigram-generation-by-a-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisoGender: A dataset for benchmarking gender bias in image-text pronoun resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visogender-a-dataset-for-benchmarking-gender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VisoGender, a novel dataset for benchmarking gender bias in vision-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visogender-a-dataset-for-benchmarking-gender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking and Analyzing 3D-aware Image Synthesis with a Modularized Codebase</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analyzing-3d-aware-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid advance of 3D-aware image synthesis, existing studies usually adopt a mixture of techniques and tricks, leaving it unclear how each part contributes to the final performance in terms of generality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analyzing-3d-aware-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Attackability in Natural Language Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-attackability-in-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial attack research in natural language processing (NLP) has made significant progress in designing powerful attack methods and defence approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-attackability-in-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Node-based Core Resilience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-node-based-core-resilience</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first show that a previously proposed measure, Core Strength, does not correctly capture the core resilience of a node upon edge removals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-node-based-core-resilience</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Black Box: Analyzing Attention Weights and Hidden States in Pre-trained Language Models for Non-language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-analyzing-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Investigating deep learning language models has always been a significant research area due to the ``black box" nature of most advanced models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-analyzing-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Effective Pruning Approach for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-pruning-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the recent observation of emergent large magnitude features in LLMs, our approach prune weights with the smallest magnitudes multiplied by the corresponding input activations, on a per-output basis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-pruning-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSVD-Indonesian: A Benchmark for Multimodal Video-Text Tasks in Indonesian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msvd-indonesian-a-benchmark-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the availability of the pretraining resources with Indonesian sentences is relatively limited, the applicability of those approaches to our dataset is still questionable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msvd-indonesian-a-benchmark-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quilt-1M: One Million Image-Text Pairs for Histopathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quilt-1m-one-million-image-text-pairs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From YouTube, we curate Quilt: a large-scale vision-language dataset consisting of $768, 826$ image and text pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quilt-1m-one-million-image-text-pairs-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting Sub-model to Improve Main Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-sub-model-to-improve-main-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the main model employs conventional training recipes, the sub-model leverages the benefit of additional regularization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-sub-model-to-improve-main-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenPlot: Increasing the Scale and Diversity of Chart Derendering Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genplot-increasing-the-scale-and-diversity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vertical bars, horizontal bars, dot, scatter, and line plots provide a diverse set of visualizations to represent data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genplot-increasing-the-scale-and-diversity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Wrong Turns: The Simple Geometry Of Neural Networks Optimization Paths</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-wrong-turns-the-simple-geometry-of-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the optimization dynamics of neural networks is necessary for closing the gap between theory and practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-wrong-turns-the-simple-geometry-of-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Video Object Captioning from Disjoint Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-video-object-captioning-from-disjoint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show our task is more general than grounding, and models trained on our task can directly be applied to grounding by finding the bounding box with the maximum likelihood of generating the query sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-video-object-captioning-from-disjoint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Perceiver for Efficient Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-perceiver-for-efficient-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early exits are placed exclusively within the classification branch, thus eliminating the need for linear separability in low-level features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-perceiver-for-efficient-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRFI: An Open Source Multi-Resolution Fault Injection Framework for Neural Network Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrfi-an-open-source-multi-resolution-fault</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It enables users to modify an independent fault configuration file rather than neural network models for the fault injection and vulnerability analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mrfi-an-open-source-multi-resolution-fault</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Double Self-Expressive Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-double-self-expressive-subspace</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key idea of our solution is to view the self-expressive coefficient as a feature representation of the example to get another coefficient matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-double-self-expressive-subspace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-Aware Robustness Certificates for Graph Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-aware-robustness-certificates-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Certifying the robustness of a graph-based machine learning model poses a critical challenge for safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-aware-robustness-certificates-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How can objects help action recognition?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-objects-help-action-recognition-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate how we can use knowledge of objects to design better video models, namely to process fewer tokens and to improve recognition accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-can-objects-help-action-recognition-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Based Transformer for Table Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-based-transformer-for-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel approach toward automatic data wrangling in an attempt to alleviate the effort of end-users, e. g. data analysts, in structuring dynamic views from data lakes in the form of tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-based-transformer-for-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Graphical Modeling Language for Artificial Intelligence Applications in Automation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graphical-modeling-language-for-artificial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper therefore presents a graphical modeling language that enables consistent and understandable modeling of AI applications in automation systems at system level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graphical-modeling-language-for-artificial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransRef: Multi-Scale Reference Embedding Transformer for Reference-Guided Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transref-multi-scale-reference-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For precise utilization of the reference features for guidance, a reference-patch alignment (Ref-PA) module is proposed to align the patch features of the reference and corrupted images and harmonize their style differences, while a reference-patch transformer (Ref-PT) module is proposed to refine the embedded reference feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transref-multi-scale-reference-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Neural Representation for Sequential Video Compilation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-neural-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Implicit Representations (NIR) have gained significant attention recently due to their ability to represent complex and high-dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-neural-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeFNet: Bridging Tabular Datasets with Semantic Feature Nets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sefnet-bridging-tabular-datasets-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an example of SeFNet prepared for a collection of predictive tasks in healthcare, with the features' relations derived from the SNOMED-CT ontology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sefnet-bridging-tabular-datasets-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Fidelity Active Learning with GFlowNets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-fidelity-active-learning-with-gflownets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, in scientific discovery, we are often faced with the problem of exploring very large, high-dimensional spaces, where querying a high fidelity, black-box objective function is very expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-fidelity-active-learning-with-gflownets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSTL: A Comprehensive Benchmark of Spatio-Temporal Predictive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstl-a-comprehensive-benchmark-of-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatio-temporal predictive learning is a learning paradigm that enables models to learn spatial and temporal patterns by predicting future frames from given past frames in an unsupervised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstl-a-comprehensive-benchmark-of-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Quantum Federated Learning for Metaverse: Analysis, Design and Implementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-quantum-federated-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we develop a decentralized and trustworthy quantum federated learning (QFL) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-quantum-federated-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
