<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 21:06:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Initialization for Personalized Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-initialization-for-personalized-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, a fast version of our method allows for capturing an input image in roughly 26 seconds, while surpassing the baseline methods in terms of both reconstruction and editability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-initialization-for-personalized-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAL: Balancing Diversity and Novelty for Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bal-balancing-diversity-and-novelty-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that, when labeling 80% of the samples, the performance of the current SOTA method declines by 0. 74%, whereas our proposed BAL achieves performance comparable to the full dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bal-balancing-diversity-and-novelty-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimistic and Pessimistic Actor in RL:Decoupling Exploration and Utilization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimistic-and-pessimistic-actor-in-rl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OPARL employs a unique dual-actor approach: an optimistic actor dedicated to exploration and a pessimistic actor focused on utilization, thereby effectively differentiating between exploration and utilization strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimistic-and-pessimistic-actor-in-rl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of Phylogenetic Trees via Split-Weight Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-phylogenetic-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main reason for the delay in adoption of unsupervised learning in phylogenetics is the lack of a meaningful, yet simple, way of embedding phylogenetic trees into a vector space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-phylogenetic-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social-Transmotion: Promptable Human Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-transmotion-promptable-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model exhibits flexibility and adaptability by capturing spatiotemporal interactions between pedestrians based on the available visual cues, whether they are poses, bounding boxes, or a combination thereof.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-transmotion-promptable-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implied volatility (also) is path-dependent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implied-volatility-also-is-path-dependent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we show that up to four years of the past evolution of the underlying price should be used for the prediction and that this feedback effect gets weaker when the maturity increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implied-volatility-also-is-path-dependent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Align on the Fly: Adapting Chatbot Behavior to Established Norms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-on-the-fly-adapting-chatbot-behavior-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to align large language models with the ever-changing, complex, and diverse human values (e. g., social norms) across time and locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-on-the-fly-adapting-chatbot-behavior-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Down, LiTting Up: Efficient Zero-Shot Listwise Reranking with Seq2seq Encoder-Decoder Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-down-litting-up-efficient-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a range of models from 220M parameters to 3B parameters, all with strong reranking results, challenging the necessity of large-scale models for effective zero-shot reranking and opening avenues for more efficient listwise reranking solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-down-litting-up-efficient-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-To-Rank Approach for Identifying Everyday Objects Using a Physical-World Search Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-rank-approach-for-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we focus on the task of retrieving target objects from open-vocabulary user instructions in a human-in-the-loop setting, which we define as the learning-to-rank physical objects (LTRPO) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-rank-approach-for-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Prompt Learning Framework for Source Code Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prompt-learning-framework-for-source-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PromptCS trains a prompt agent that can generate continuous prompts to unleash the potential for LLMs in code summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prompt-learning-framework-for-source-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C2T-Net: Channel-Aware Cross-Fused Transformer-Style Networks for Pedestrian Attribute Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2t-net-channel-aware-cross-fused-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our performance on the PETA dataset remains competitive, standing on par with other cutting-edge models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2t-net-channel-aware-cross-fused-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Survival Analysis with Adversarial Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-survival-analysis-with-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Survival Analysis (SA) is about modeling the time for an event of interest to occur, which has important applications in many fields, including medicine, defense, finance, and aerospace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-survival-analysis-with-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olfactory Label Prediction on aroma-chemical Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olfactory-label-prediction-on-aroma-chemical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The application of deep learning techniques on aroma-chemicals has resulted in models more accurate than human experts at predicting olfactory qualities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olfactory-label-prediction-on-aroma-chemical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey of Evaluation Techniques for Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following this, we delve into predictive metrics that assess the accuracy of forecasted preferences, ranking metrics that evaluate the order in which recommendations are presented, and business metrics that align system performance with economic objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmbodiedScan: A Holistic Multi-Modal 3D Perception Suite Towards Embodied AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodiedscan-a-holistic-multi-modal-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of computer vision and robotics, embodied agents are expected to explore their environment and carry out human instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodiedscan-a-holistic-multi-modal-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Clustered Orienteering Problem with Subgroups</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-clustered-orienteering-problem-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an extension to the Orienteering Problem (OP), called Clustered Orienteering Problem with Subgroups (COPS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-clustered-orienteering-problem-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principled Instructions Are All You Need for Questioning LLaMA-1/2, GPT-3.5/4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-instructions-are-all-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces 26 guiding principles designed to streamline the process of querying and prompting large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-instructions-are-all-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Fairness in DareFightingICE Agents Evaluation Through a Delay Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-fairness-in-darefightingice-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a delay mechanism to mitigate the impact of latency differences in the gRPC framework--a high-performance, open-source universal remote procedure call (RPC) framework--between different programming languages on the performance of agents in DareFightingICE, a fighting game research platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-fairness-in-darefightingice-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDiT: Interleaving Perception and Decision-making Transformers for Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdit-interleaving-perception-and-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing better deep networks and better reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms are both important for deep RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdit-interleaving-perception-and-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaneSegNet: Map Learning with Lane Segment Perception for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanesegnet-map-learning-with-lane-segment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A map, as crucial information for downstream applications of an autonomous driving system, is usually represented in lanelines or centerlines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanesegnet-map-learning-with-lane-segment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black-Box Tuning of Vision-Language Models with Effective Gradient Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-tuning-of-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) methods have provided an effective way for adapting large vision-language models to specific tasks or scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-tuning-of-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Media Bias Taxonomy: A Systematic Literature Review on the Forms and Automated Detection of Media Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-media-bias-taxonomy-a-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we have identified a lack of interdisciplinarity in existing projects, and a need for more awareness of the various types of media bias to support methodologically thorough performance evaluations of media bias detection systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-media-bias-taxonomy-a-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Deformable Hypothesis Sampling for Accurate PatchMatch Multi-View Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deformable-hypothesis-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a learnable Deformable Hypothesis Sampler (DeformSampler) to address the challenging issue of noisy depth estimation for accurate PatchMatch Multi-View Stereo (MVS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deformable-hypothesis-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Transferability for Cross-domain Trajectory Prediction via Neural Stochastic Differential Equation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transferability-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose a method based on continuous and stochastic representations of Neural Stochastic Differential Equations (NSDE) for alleviating discrepancies due to data acquisition strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transferability-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algebraic Positional Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algebraic-positional-encodings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel positional encoding strategy for Transformer-style models, addressing the shortcomings of existing, often ad hoc, approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algebraic-positional-encodings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models as Traffic Signal Control Agents: Capacity and Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-traffic-signal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging LLMs' impressive generalization and zero-shot reasoning capabilities, LLMLight executes a human-like decision-making process for efficient traffic management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-as-traffic-signal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular 3D Hand Mesh Recovery via Dual Noise Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-3d-hand-mesh-recovery-via-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the fixed hand topology and complex hand poses, current models are hard to generate meshes that are aligned with the image well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-3d-hand-mesh-recovery-via-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Task Representation Learning for Offline Meta-Reinforcement Learning with Data Limitations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-task-representation-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GENTLE employs Task Auto-Encoder~(TAE), which is an encoder-decoder architecture to extract the characteristics of the tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-task-representation-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoTCoder: Elevating Large Language Models with Modular of Thought for Challenging Programming Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motcoder-elevating-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have showcased impressive capabilities in handling straightforward programming tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motcoder-elevating-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the Proximate Long-Tail Distribution in Compositional Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-proximate-long-tail</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this insight, we incorporate visual bias caused by compositions into the classifier's training and inference by estimating it as a proximate class prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-proximate-long-tail</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Heads Are Better Than One: Complementary Experts for Long-Tailed Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-heads-are-better-than-one-complementary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, on CIFAR-10-LT, CPE improves test accuracy by over >2. 22% compared to baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-heads-are-better-than-one-complementary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Stochastically-Descending Unrolled Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-stochastically-descending-unrolled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these problems, we provide deep unrolled architectures with a stochastic descent nature by imposing descending constraints during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-stochastically-descending-unrolled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning-Based Framework for Sim-to-Real Mapping of Lidar Point Clouds in Autonomous Driving Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-based-framework-for-sim</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this potential, this paper focuses on sim-to-real mapping of Lidar point clouds, a widely used perception sensor in automated driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-based-framework-for-sim</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDF-star2Vec: RDF-star Graph Embeddings for Data Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdf-star2vec-rdf-star-graph-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graphs (KGs) such as Resource Description Framework (RDF) data represent relationships between various entities through the structure of triples (<subject, predicate, object>).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdf-star2vec-rdf-star-graph-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Good Data for Alignment? A Comprehensive Study of Automatic Data Selection in Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-good-data-for-alignment-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present deita (short for Data-Efficient Instruction Tuning for Alignment), a series of models fine-tuned from LLaMA and Mistral models using data samples automatically selected with our proposed approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-good-data-for-alignment-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Modal Contrastive Diffusion Model for Therapeutic Peptide Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-contrastive-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therapeutic peptides represent a unique class of pharmaceutical agents crucial for the treatment of human diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-contrastive-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Evaluation of Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning on Software Engineering Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-of-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope that our findings can provide a deeper understanding of PEFT methods on various PTMs and SE downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-evaluation-of-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniRef++: Segment Every Reference Object in Spatial and Temporal Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniref-segment-every-reference-object-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our unified models on various benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniref-segment-every-reference-object-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPE: Leveraging Agent Topology for Cooperative Multi-Agent Policy Gradient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tape-leveraging-agent-topology-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Topology-based multi-Agent Policy gradiEnt (TAPE) for both stochastic and deterministic MAPG methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tape-leveraging-agent-topology-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULASki: Learning inter-rater variability using statistical distances to improve probabilistic segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulaski-learning-inter-rater-variability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the domain of medical imaging, many supervised learning based methods for segmentation face several challenges such as high variability in annotations from multiple experts, paucity of labelled data and class imbalanced datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulaski-learning-inter-rater-variability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rotation Equivariant Proximal Operator for Deep Unfolding Methods in Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotation-equivariant-proximal-operator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In current deep unfolding methods, such a proximal network is generally designed as a CNN architecture, whose necessity has been proven by a recent theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rotation-equivariant-proximal-operator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Blind Face Restoration with Generative Diffusion Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-blind-face-restoration-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blind face restoration is an important task in computer vision and has gained significant attention due to its wide-range applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-blind-face-restoration-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BDIS-SLAM: A lightweight CPU-based dense stereo SLAM for surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bdis-slam-a-lightweight-cpu-based-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusion: The proposed BDIS-SLAM is a lightweight stereo dense SLAM system for MIS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bdis-slam-a-lightweight-cpu-based-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Video Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-video-relation-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A comprehensive understanding of videos is inseparable from describing the action with its contextual action-object interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-video-relation-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Structure and Attention Aware Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-structure-and-attention-aware-subspace</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, previous deep clustering methods, especially image clustering, focus on the features of the data itself and ignore the relationship between the data, which is crucial for clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-structure-and-attention-aware-subspace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negative Controls for Instrumental Variable Designs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negative-controls-for-instrumental-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Studies using instrumental variables (IV) often assess the validity of their identification assumptions using falsification tests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negative-controls-for-instrumental-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleviating Hallucinations of Large Language Models through Induced Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-hallucinations-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on both discrimination-based and generation-based hallucination evaluation benchmarks, such as TruthfulQA and \textsc{FActScore}, demonstrate that our proposed ICD methods can effectively enhance the factuality of LLMs across various model sizes and families.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-hallucinations-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Label Variation in Scientific Information Extraction via Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-label-variation-in-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The complexity of this task is compounded by the necessity for domain-specific knowledge and the limited availability of annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-label-variation-in-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive FSS: A Novel Few-Shot Segmentation Framework via Prototype Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-fss-a-novel-few-shot-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel framework based on the adapter mechanism, namely Adaptive FSS, which can efficiently adapt the existing FSS model to the novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-fss-a-novel-few-shot-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Large Language Models A Better Foundation For Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-large-language-models-a-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLaRA consists of two pretext tasks: EBAE (Embedding-Based Auto-Encoding) and EBAR (Embedding-Based Auto-Regression), where the text embeddings from LLM are used to reconstruct the tokens for the input sentence and predict the tokens for the next sentence, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-large-language-models-a-better</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
