<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 09:12:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>COCO-O: A Benchmark for Object Detectors under Natural Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-o-a-benchmark-for-object-detectors-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To give a more comprehensive robustness assessment, we introduce COCO-O(ut-of-distribution), a test dataset based on COCO with 6 types of natural distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-o-a-benchmark-for-object-detectors-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Medical Report Generation: Disease Revealing Enhancement with Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-medical-report-generation-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graph (KG) plays a crucial role in Medical Report Generation (MRG) because it reveals the relations among diseases and thus can be utilized to guide the generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-medical-report-generation-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the Troublemakers in Described Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-troublemakers-in-described</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we advance them to a more practical setting called Described Object Detection (DOD) by expanding category names to flexible language expressions for OVD and overcoming the limitation of REC to only grounding the pre-existing object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-troublemakers-in-described</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Vertebra Localization and Identification from CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-vertebra-localization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we further propose a Sequence Loss to maintain the sequential structure embedded along the vertebrae.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-vertebra-localization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Delayed Feedback Label Correction for Conversion Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-delayed-feedback-label-correction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To directly introduce the correct feedback label information, we propose an Unbiased delayed feedback Label Correction framework (ULC), which uses an auxiliary model to correct labels for observed negative feedback samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-delayed-feedback-label-correction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwinMM: Masked Multi-view with Swin Transformers for 3D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swinmm-masked-multi-view-with-swin</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we present Masked Multi-view with Swin Transformers (SwinMM), a novel multi-view pipeline for enabling accurate and data-efficient self-supervised medical image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swinmm-masked-multi-view-with-swin</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept-based explainability for an EEG transformer model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-based-explainability-for-an-eeg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models are complex due to their size, structure, and inherent randomness in training procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-based-explainability-for-an-eeg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client-Level Differential Privacy via Adaptive Intermediary in Federated Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-level-differential-privacy-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to optimize the trade-off under the context of client-level DP, which focuses on privacy during communications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-level-differential-privacy-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Language Models with Human: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-with-human-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) Training methodologies: a detailed review of the prevailing training methods employed for LLM alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-with-human-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuation Path Learning for Homotopy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuation-path-learning-for-homotopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Homotopy optimization is a traditional method to deal with a complicated optimization problem by solving a sequence of easy-to-hard surrogate subproblems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuation-path-learning-for-homotopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Punctuation Restoration with Data Generation and Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-punctuation-restoration-with-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Punctuation restoration is an important task in automatic speech recognition (ASR) which aim to restore the syntactic structure of generated ASR texts to improve readability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-punctuation-restoration-with-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Statistical View of Column Subset Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-view-of-column-subset-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of selecting a small subset of representative variables from a large dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-view-of-column-subset-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Skeleton Meta-Prototype Contrastive Learning with Hard Skeleton Mining for Unsupervised Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-skeleton-meta-prototype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then a hierarchical meta-prototype contrastive learning model is proposed to cluster and contrast the most typical skeleton features ("prototypes") from different-level skeletons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-skeleton-meta-prototype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule By Example: Harnessing Logical Rules for Explainable Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-by-example-harnessing-logical-rules-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Rule By Example (RBE): a novel exemplar-based contrastive learning approach for learning from logical rules for the task of textual content moderation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-by-example-harnessing-logical-rules-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact &amp; Capable: Harnessing Graph Neural Networks and Edge Convolution for Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-capable-harnessing-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigate the potential of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) for medical image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-capable-harnessing-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GridMM: Grid Memory Map for Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gridmm-grid-memory-map-for-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-and-language navigation (VLN) enables the agent to navigate to a remote location following the natural language instruction in 3D environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gridmm-grid-memory-map-for-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing the Impact of Localized Training Data in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-the-impact-of-localized-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the challenges posed by localized training data, we approach the problem as an out-of-distribution (OOD) data issue by by aligning the distributions between the training data, which represents a small portion of labeled data, and the graph inference process that involves making predictions for the entire graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-the-impact-of-localized-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG-RCNN: Semantic Surface Point Generation for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-rcnn-semantic-surface-point-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we propose Point Generation R-CNN (PG-RCNN), a novel end-to-end detector that generates semantic surface points of foreground objects for accurate detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-rcnn-semantic-surface-point-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Bio-Sensing: Open Source Benchmark Framework for Fair Evaluation of rPPG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-bio-sensing-open-source-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote Photoplethysmography (rPPG) is a technology that utilizes the light absorption properties of hemoglobin, captured via camera, to analyze and measure blood volume pulse (BVP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-bio-sensing-open-source-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treatment Outcome Prediction for Intracerebral Hemorrhage via Generative Prognostic Model with Imaging and Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treatment-outcome-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose to employ a variational autoencoder model to generate a low-dimensional prognostic score, which can effectively address the selection bias resulting from the non-randomized controlled trials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treatment-outcome-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Evaluation of Temporal Graph Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-evaluation-of-temporal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct an empirical evaluation of Temporal Graph Benchmark (TGB) by extending our Dynamic Graph Library (DyGLib) to TGB.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-evaluation-of-temporal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guidance in Radiology Report Summarization: An Empirical Evaluation and Error Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidance-in-radiology-report-summarization-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically summarizing radiology reports into a concise impression can reduce the manual burden of clinicians and improve the consistency of reporting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guidance-in-radiology-report-summarization-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Connection between One-Step Regularization and Critic Regularization in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-connection-between-one-step-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One-step methods perform regularization by doing just a single step of policy improvement, while critic regularization methods do many steps of policy improvement with a regularized objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-connection-between-one-step-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIOR: Prototype Representation Joint Learning from Medical Images and Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-prototype-representation-joint-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a prototype representation learning framework incorporating both global and local alignment between medical images and reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-prototype-representation-joint-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Continual Learning in Keyword Spotting for Low-Resource Devices via Pooling High-Order Temporal Statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-in-keyword-spotting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keyword Spotting (KWS) models on embedded devices should adapt fast to new user-defined words without forgetting previous ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-continual-learning-in-keyword-spotting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric Linear Feature Learning in Regression Through Regularisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-linear-feature-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a novel method for linear feature learning with non-parametric prediction, which simultaneously estimates the prediction function and the linear subspace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-linear-feature-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Theoretically Guaranteed Quaternion Weighted Schatten p-norm Minimization Method for Color Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretically-guaranteed-quaternion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Very recently, a quaternion-based WNNM approach (QWNNM) has been developed to mitigate this issue, which is capable of representing the color image as a whole in the quaternion domain and preserving the inherent correlation among the three color channels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-theoretically-guaranteed-quaternion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Fair Machine Learning via Rank-Preserving Interventional Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-fair-machine-learning-via-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A decision can be defined as fair if equal individuals are treated equally and unequals unequally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-fair-machine-learning-via-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COCO-O: A Benchmark for Object Detectors under Natural Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-o-a-benchmark-for-object-detectors-under-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To give a more comprehensive robustness assessment, we introduce COCO-O(ut-of-distribution), a test dataset based on COCO with 6 types of natural distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coco-o-a-benchmark-for-object-detectors-under-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost In Translation: Generating Adversarial Examples Robust to Round-Trip Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-translation-generating-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language Models today provide a high accuracy across a large number of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-translation-generating-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: Focus Attention for Efficient DETR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-focus-attention-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DETR-like models have significantly boosted the performance of detectors and even outperformed classical convolutional models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-focus-attention-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR Meta Depth Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-meta-depth-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While using a single model, our method yields significantly better results than a non-adaptive baseline trained on different LiDAR patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-meta-depth-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TF-ICON: Diffusion-Based Training-Free Cross-Domain Image Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tf-icon-diffusion-based-training-free-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose TF-ICON, a novel Training-Free Image COmpositioN framework that harnesses the power of text-driven diffusion models for cross-domain image-guided composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tf-icon-diffusion-based-training-free-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDCT: Fast Depth Completion for Transparent Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdct-fast-depth-completion-for-transparent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a Fast Depth Completion framework for Transparent objects (FDCT), which also benefits downstream tasks like object pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdct-fast-depth-completion-for-transparent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalized Schwarz-type Non-overlapping Domain Decomposition Method using Physics-constrained Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-schwarz-type-non-overlapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure the consistency of solutions across neighboring subdomains, we adopt a generalized Robin-type interface condition, assigning unique Robin parameters to each subdomain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-schwarz-type-non-overlapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Extraction from Remote Sensing Images via an Uncertainty-Aware Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-extraction-from-remote-sensing-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building extraction aims to segment building pixels from remote sensing images and plays an essential role in many applications, such as city planning and urban dynamic monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-extraction-from-remote-sensing-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResShift: Efficient Diffusion Model for Image Super-resolution by Residual Shifting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resshift-efficient-diffusion-model-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based image super-resolution (SR) methods are mainly limited by the low inference speed due to the requirements of hundreds or even thousands of sampling steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resshift-efficient-diffusion-model-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EchoGLAD: Hierarchical Graph Neural Networks for Left Ventricle Landmark Detection on Echocardiograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echoglad-hierarchical-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we introduce an echocardiogram-based, hierarchical graph neural network (GNN) for left ventricle landmark detection (EchoGLAD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echoglad-hierarchical-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RANSAC-NN: Unsupervised Image Outlier Detection using RANSAC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ransac-nn-unsupervised-image-outlier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image outlier detection (OD) is crucial for ensuring the quality and accuracy of image datasets used in computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ransac-nn-unsupervised-image-outlier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expediting Building Footprint Segmentation from High-resolution Remote Sensing Images via progressive lenient supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expediting-building-footprint-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficacy of building footprint segmentation from remotely sensed images has been hindered by model transfer effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expediting-building-footprint-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milimili. Collecting Parallel Data via Crowdsourcing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/milimili-collecting-parallel-data-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a methodology for gathering a parallel corpus through crowdsourcing, which is more cost-effective than hiring professional translators, albeit at the expense of quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/milimili-collecting-parallel-data-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiAMoNDBack: Diffusion-denoising Autoregressive Model for Non-Deterministic Backmapping of Cα Protein Traces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diamondback-diffusion-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The autoregressive generation process proceeds from the protein N-terminus to C-terminus in a residue-by-residue fashion conditioned on the C{\alpha} trace and previously backmapped backbone and side chain atoms within the local neighborhood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diamondback-diffusion-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generic and Controllable Attacks Against Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generic-and-controllable-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a generic white-box attack, LGP (local perturbations with adaptively global attacks), to blind mainstream object detectors with controllable perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generic-and-controllable-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepCL: Deep Change Feature Learning on Remote Sensing Images in the Metric Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepcl-deep-change-feature-learning-on-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we complement the strong temporal modeling ability of metric learning with the prominent fitting ability of segmentation and propose a deep change feature learning (DeepCL) framework for robust and explainable CD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepcl-deep-change-feature-learning-on-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DQ-Det: Learning Dynamic Query Combinations for Transformer-based Object Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dq-det-learning-dynamic-query-combinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based detection and segmentation methods use a list of learned detection queries to retrieve information from the transformer network and learn to predict the location and category of one specific object from each query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dq-det-learning-dynamic-query-combinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right for the Wrong Reason: Can Interpretable ML Techniques Detect Spurious Correlations?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/right-for-the-wrong-reason-can-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such dependencies on confounding information can be difficult to detect using performance metrics if the test data comes from the same distribution as the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/right-for-the-wrong-reason-can-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Navigational Visual Representations with Semantic Map Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-navigational-visual-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being able to perceive the semantics and the spatial structure of the environment is essential for visual navigation of a household robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-navigational-visual-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Robust Visual Grounding with Masked Reference based Centerpoint Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-robust-visual-grounding-with-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed framework is evaluated on five regular VG datasets and two newly constructed robust VG datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-robust-visual-grounding-with-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Offline RL for Dialogue Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-offline-rl-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common training technique for language models is teacher forcing (TF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-offline-rl-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FATRER: Full-Attention Topic Regularizer for Accurate and Robust Conversational Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatrer-full-attention-topic-regularizer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper concentrates on the understanding of interlocutors' emotions evoked in conversational utterances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatrer-full-attention-topic-regularizer-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
