<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 09:12:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Active Statistical Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-statistical-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This means that for the same number of collected samples, active inference enables smaller confidence intervals and more powerful p-values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-statistical-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Defer to a Population: A Meta-Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-defer-to-a-population-a-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The learning to defer (L2D) framework allows autonomous systems to be safe and robust by allocating difficult decisions to a human expert.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-defer-to-a-population-a-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPPA: Pruning Method for Large Language Model to Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dppa-pruning-method-for-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a dual-stage method termed Dynamic Pruning Partition Amplification (DPPA), devised to tackle the challenge of merging complex fine-tuned models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dppa-pruning-method-for-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Spectra to Biophysical Insights: End-to-End Learning with a Biased Radiative Transfer Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-spectra-to-biophysical-insights-end-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in machine learning have boosted the use of Earth observation data for climate change research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-spectra-to-biophysical-insights-end-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Generation with Latent Actions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-generation-with-latent-actions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike language or image generation, decision making requires modeling actions - continuous-valued vectors that are multimodal in their distribution, potentially drawn from uncurated sources, where generation errors can compound in sequential prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-generation-with-latent-actions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Asymptotic Mean Square Error Optimality of Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-asymptotic-mean-square-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion probabilistic models (DPMs) have recently shown great potential for denoising tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-asymptotic-mean-square-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Confidence Estimation: Towards Reliable Failure Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-confidence-estimation-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable confidence estimation is a challenging yet fundamental requirement in many risk-sensitive applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-confidence-estimation-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning Approaches for Identifying ICU Patient Subgroups: Do Results Generalise?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-approaches-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is unclear whether common patient subgroups exist across different ICUs, which would determine whether ICU restructuring could be operationalised in a standardised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-approaches-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Mean-Teacher: An Unbiased Semi-Supervised Framework for Audio-Visual Source Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-mean-teacher-an-unbiased-semi-supervised-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-Visual Source Localization (AVSL) aims to locate sounding objects within video frames given the paired audio clips.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-mean-teacher-an-unbiased-semi-supervised-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards General Computer Control: A Multimodal Agent for Red Dead Redemption II as a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-computer-control-a-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have demonstrated the success of foundation agents in specific tasks or scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-computer-control-a-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLGuard: Byzantine-Robust Federated Learning via Ensemble of Contrastive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flguard-byzantine-robust-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, recent research proposed poisoning attacks that cause a catastrophic loss in the accuracy of the global model when adversaries, posed as benign clients, are present in a group of clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flguard-byzantine-robust-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGD with Partial Hessian for Deep Neural Networks Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgd-with-partial-hessian-for-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with first-order optimizers, it adopts a certain amount of information from the Hessian matrix to assist optimization, while compared with the existing second-order optimizers, it keeps the good generalization performance of first-order optimizers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgd-with-partial-hessian-for-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARADISE: Evaluating Implicit Planning Skills of Language Models with Procedural Warnings and Tips Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paradise-evaluating-implicit-planning-skills</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there has been growing interest within the community regarding whether large language models are capable of planning or executing plans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paradise-evaluating-implicit-planning-skills</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uplift Modeling for Target User Attacks on Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uplift-modeling-for-target-user-attacks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UBA estimates the treatment effect on each target user and optimizes the allocation of fake user budgets to maximize the attack performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uplift-modeling-for-target-user-attacks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recall-Oriented Continual Learning with Generative Adversarial Meta-Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recall-oriented-continual-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The stability-plasticity dilemma is a major challenge in continual learning, as it involves balancing the conflicting objectives of maintaining performance on previous tasks while learning new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recall-oriented-continual-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolution Transformer: In-Context Evolutionary Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-transformer-in-context-evolutionary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a trajectory of evaluations and search distribution statistics, Evolution Transformer outputs a performance-improving update to the search distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-transformer-in-context-evolutionary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preventing Reward Hacking with Occupancy Measure Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preventing-reward-hacking-with-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose regularizing based on the OM divergence between policies instead of AD divergence to prevent reward hacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preventing-reward-hacking-with-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear quadratic control of nonlinear systems with Koopman operator learning and the Nyström method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-quadratic-control-of-nonlinear-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study how the Koopman operator framework can be combined with kernel methods to effectively control nonlinear dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-quadratic-control-of-nonlinear-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Android in the Zoo: Chain-of-Action-Thought for GUI Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/android-in-the-zoo-chain-of-action-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, this work presents Chain-of-Action-Thought (dubbed CoAT), which takes the description of the previous actions, the current screen, and more importantly the action thinking of what actions should be performed and the outcomes led by the chosen action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/android-in-the-zoo-chain-of-action-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove that Square Root: A New Efficient Scale-Invariant Version of AdaGrad</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remove-that-square-root-a-new-efficient-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adaptive methods are extremely popular in machine learning as they make learning rate tuning less expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remove-that-square-root-a-new-efficient-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MADTP: Multimodal Alignment-Guided Dynamic Token Pruning for Accelerating Vision-Language Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/madtp-multimodal-alignment-guided-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel framework named Multimodal Alignment-Guided Dynamic Token Pruning (MADTP) for accelerating various VLTs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/madtp-multimodal-alignment-guided-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimuCourt: Building Judicial Decision-Making Agents with Real-world Judgement Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simucourt-building-judicial-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, (1) we introduce SimuCourt, a judicial benchmark that encompasses 420 judgment documents from real-world, spanning the three most common types of judicial cases, and a novel task Judicial Decision-Making to evaluate the judicial analysis and decision-making power of agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simucourt-building-judicial-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Minimum Information about CLinical Artificial Intelligence (MI-CLAIM) checklist for generative modeling research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/updating-the-minimum-information-about</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to gaps in standards and best practices for the development of clinical AI tools identified by US Executive Order 141103 and several emerging national networks for clinical AI evaluation, we begin to formalize some of these guidelines by building on the "Minimum information about clinical artificial intelligence modeling" (MI-CLAIM) checklist.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/updating-the-minimum-information-about</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedHCDR: Federated Cross-Domain Recommendation with Hypergraph Signal Decoupling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedhcdr-federated-cross-domain-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to address the data heterogeneity across domains, we introduce an approach called hypergraph signal decoupling (HSD) to decouple the user features into domain-exclusive and domain-shared features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedhcdr-federated-cross-domain-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrackNex: a Few-shot Low-light Crack Segmentation Model Based on Retinex Theory for UAV Inspections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cracknex-a-few-shot-low-light-crack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LCSD consists of 102 well-illuminated crack images and 41 low-light crack images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cracknex-a-few-shot-low-light-crack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feast Your Eyes: Mixture-of-Resolution Adaptation for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feast-your-eyes-mixture-of-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrary to previous works, we study this problem from the perspective of image resolution, and reveal that a combination of low- and high-resolution visual features can effectively mitigate this shortcoming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feast-your-eyes-mixture-of-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brand Visibility in Packaging: A Deep Learning Approach for Logo Detection, Saliency-Map Prediction, and Logo Placement Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brand-visibility-in-packaging-a-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the third step, by integrating logo detection with a saliency map generation, the framework provides a comprehensive brand attention score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brand-visibility-in-packaging-a-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning Under Attack: Exposing Vulnerabilities through Data Poisoning Attacks in Computer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-attack-exposing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In LF, we randomly flipped the labels of benign data and trained the model on the manipulated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-attack-exposing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KnowAgent: Knowledge-Augmented Planning for LLM-Based Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowagent-knowledge-augmented-planning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated great potential in complex reasoning tasks, yet they fall short when tackling more sophisticated challenges, especially when interacting with environments through generating executable actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowagent-knowledge-augmented-planning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirichlet-based Per-Sample Weighting by Transition Matrix for Noisy Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirichlet-based-per-sample-weighting-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose good utilization of the transition matrix is crucial and suggest a new utilization method based on resampling, coined RENT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirichlet-based-per-sample-weighting-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do we learn from inverting CLIP models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-we-learn-from-inverting-clip-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ an inversion-based approach to examine CLIP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-we-learn-from-inverting-clip-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Not Use Your Textbook? Knowledge-Enhanced Procedure Planning of Instructional Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-not-use-your-textbook-knowledge-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This knowledge, sourced from training procedure plans and structured as a directed weighted graph, equips the agent to better navigate the complexities of step sequencing and its potential variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-not-use-your-textbook-knowledge-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNNLasso: Scalable Graph Learning for Matrix-Variate Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnnlasso-scalable-graph-learning-for-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of jointly learning row-wise and column-wise dependencies of matrix-variate observations, which are modelled separately by two precision matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dnnlasso-scalable-graph-learning-for-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TESTAM: A Time-Enhanced Spatio-Temporal Attention Model with Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testam-a-time-enhanced-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel deep learning model named TESTAM, which individually models recurring and non-recurring traffic patterns by a mixture-of-experts model with three experts on temporal modeling, spatio-temporal modeling with static graph, and dynamic spatio-temporal dependency modeling with dynamic graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testam-a-time-enhanced-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Weakly Supervised 3D Medical Image Segmentation through Probabilistic-aware Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-weakly-supervised-3d-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D medical image segmentation is a challenging task with crucial implications for disease diagnosis and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-weakly-supervised-3d-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Democratized Flood Risk Management: An Advanced AI Assistant Enabled by GPT-4 for Enhanced Interpretability and Public Engagement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-democratized-flood-risk-management-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This AI Assistant is designed to facilitate effective communication between decision-makers, the general public, and flood forecasters, without the requirement of specialized knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-democratized-flood-risk-management-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaylorShift: Shifting the Complexity of Self-Attention from Squared to Linear (and Back) using Taylor-Softmax</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taylorshift-shifting-the-complexity-of-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quadratic complexity of the attention mechanism represents one of the biggest hurdles for processing long sequences using Transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taylorshift-shifting-the-complexity-of-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Walk: Debiasing Multi-Hop Fact Verification with Front-Door Adjustment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-walk-debiasing-multi-hop-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional multi-hop fact verification models are prone to rely on spurious correlations from the annotation artifacts, leading to an obvious performance decline on unbiased datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-walk-debiasing-multi-hop-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinReport: Explainable Stock Earnings Forecasting via News Factor Analyzing Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finreport-explainable-stock-earnings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, compared with financial institutions, it is not easy for ordinary investors to mine factors and analyze news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finreport-explainable-stock-earnings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptKD: Unsupervised Prompt Distillation for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptkd-unsupervised-prompt-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our best knowledge, we are the first to (1) perform unsupervised domain-specific prompt-driven knowledge distillation for CLIP, and (2) establish a practical pre-storing mechanism of text features as shared class vectors between teacher and student.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptkd-unsupervised-prompt-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AllSpark: Reborn Labeled Features from Unlabeled in Transformer for Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allspark-reborn-labeled-features-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further introduce a Semantic Memory along with a Channel Semantic Grouping strategy to ensure that unlabeled features adequately represent labeled features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allspark-reborn-labeled-features-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Foundation Time Series Model: To Synthesize Or Not To Synthesize?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundation-time-series-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the essential question if it is advantageous to train a foundation model on synthetic data or it is better to utilize only a limited number of real-life examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-foundation-time-series-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Goal-Conditioned Reinforcement Learning for Safety-Critical Tasks with Recovery Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-goal-conditioned-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline goal-conditioned reinforcement learning (GCRL) aims at solving goal-reaching tasks with sparse rewards from an offline dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-goal-conditioned-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OOTDiffusion: Outfitting Fusion based Latent Diffusion for Controllable Virtual Try-on</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ootdiffusion-outfitting-fusion-based-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without an explicit warping process, we propose an outfitting UNet to learn the garment detail features, and merge them with the target human body via our proposed outfitting fusion in the denoising process of diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ootdiffusion-outfitting-fusion-based-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Network Assisted Lifting Steps For Improved Fully Scalable Lossy Image Compression in JPEG 2000</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-assisted-lifting-steps-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach involves two steps, a high-to-low step followed by a low-to-high step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-assisted-lifting-steps-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposing the Deception: Uncovering More Forgery Clues for Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-deception-uncovering-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we try to tackle these challenges through three designs: (1) We present a novel framework to capture broader forgery clues by extracting multiple non-overlapping local representations and fusing them into a global semantic-rich feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exposing-the-deception-uncovering-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recommending Missed Citations Identified by Reviewers: A New Task, Dataset and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recommending-missed-citations-identified-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To help improve citations of full papers, we first define a novel task of Recommending Missed Citations Identified by Reviewers (RMC) and construct a corresponding expert-labeled dataset called CitationR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recommending-missed-citations-identified-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-RWKV: Efficient and Scalable Visual Perception with RWKV-Like Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-rwkv-efficient-and-scalable-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have revolutionized computer vision and natural language processing, but their high computational complexity limits their application in high-resolution image processing and long-context analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-rwkv-efficient-and-scalable-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniCtrl: Improving the Spatiotemporal Consistency of Text-to-Video Diffusion Models via Training-Free Unified Attention Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unictrl-improving-the-spatiotemporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Diffusion Models have been developed for video generation, usually integrating text and image conditioning to enhance control over the generated content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unictrl-improving-the-spatiotemporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Spectral Remote Sensing Image Retrieval Using Geospatial Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-spectral-remote-sensing-image-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image retrieval enables an efficient search through vast amounts of satellite imagery and returns similar images to a query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-spectral-remote-sensing-image-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
