<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 09:14:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Synthetic Image Detection Towards Generalization: An Image Transformation Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-synthetic-image-detection-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we re-examine the SID problem and identify two prevalent biases in current training paradigms, i. e., weakened artifact features and overfitted artifact features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-synthetic-image-detection-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified-IoU: For High-Quality Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-iou-for-high-quality-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the loss function dynamically shifts the model's attention from low-quality prediction boxes to high-quality prediction boxes in a novel way to enhance the model's detection performance on high-precision or intensive datasets and achieve a balance in training speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-iou-for-high-quality-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCLIP++: Learn to Rectify the Bias of CLIP for Unsupervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reclip-learn-to-rectify-the-bias-of-clip-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to explicitly model and rectify the bias existing in CLIP to facilitate the unsupervised semantic segmentation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reclip-learn-to-rectify-the-bias-of-clip-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Continuous Control with Generative Flow Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-continuous-control-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Flow Networks (GFlowNets) aim to generate diverse trajectories from a distribution in which the final states of the trajectories are proportional to the reward, serving as a powerful alternative to reinforcement learning for exploratory control tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-continuous-control-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Cross-Domain Single Blood Cell Image Classification via Large-Scale LoRA-based Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-domain-single-blood-cell-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate classification of blood cells plays a vital role in hematological analysis as it aids physicians in diagnosing various medical conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-domain-single-blood-cell-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The News Comment Gap and Algorithmic Agenda Setting in Online Forums</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-news-comment-gap-and-algorithmic-agenda</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is thus important to understand journalist vs reader comment preferences and how these are served by various comment ranking algorithms that represent discussions differently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-news-comment-gap-and-algorithmic-agenda</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Search for Customized Activation Functions with Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-search-for-customized-activation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different activation functions work best for different deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-search-for-customized-activation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Speaker Identification: Architectural Insights from AB-1 Corpus Analysis and Performance Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-speaker-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the fields of security systems, forensic investigations, and personalized services, the importance of speech as a fundamental human input outweighs text-based interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-speaker-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoFormer: Learning Point Cloud Completion with Tri-Plane Integrated Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoformer-learning-point-cloud-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a GeoFormer that simultaneously enhances the global geometric structure of the points and improves the local details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoformer-learning-point-cloud-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BMX: Entropy-weighted Similarity and Semantic-enhanced Lexical Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bmx-entropy-weighted-similarity-and-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BM25, a widely-used lexical search algorithm, remains crucial in information retrieval despite the rise of pre-trained and large language models (PLMs/LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bmx-entropy-weighted-similarity-and-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActiveNeRF: Learning Accurate 3D Geometry by Active Pattern Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activenerf-learning-accurate-3d-geometry-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design a learnable active pattern rendering pipeline which jointly learns the scene geometry and the active pattern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activenerf-learning-accurate-3d-geometry-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layerwise Recurrent Router for Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerwise-recurrent-router-for-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The scaling of large language models (LLMs) has revolutionized their capabilities in various tasks, yet this growth must be matched with efficient computational strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerwise-recurrent-router-for-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EE3P3D: Event-based Estimation of Periodic Phenomena Frequency using 3D Correlation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ee3p3d-event-based-estimation-of-periodic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method for measuring the frequency of periodic phenomena, e. g., rotation, flicker and vibration, by an event camera, a device asynchronously reporting brightness changes at independently operating pixels with high temporal resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ee3p3d-event-based-estimation-of-periodic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDRGS: High Dynamic Range Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdrgs-high-dynamic-range-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Gaussian Splatting-a recent, high-quality, real-time 3D reconstruction technique-into this domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdrgs-high-dynamic-range-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongWriter: Unleashing 10,000+ Word Generation from Long Context LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longwriter-unleashing-10000-word-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating this dataset into model training, we successfully scale the output length of existing models to over 10, 000 words while maintaining output quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longwriter-unleashing-10000-word-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Agent based on Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-agent-based-on-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the tools module, the causal agent applies causal methods to align tabular data with natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-agent-based-on-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Vision-Language Foundational models show Robust Visual Perception?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-vision-language-foundational-models-show</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it is unclear if these models are robust to distribution shifts, and how their performance and generalization capabilities vary under changes in data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-vision-language-foundational-models-show</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Saliency Ranking and Reinforcement Learning for Enhanced Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-saliency-ranking-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the ever-growing variety of object detection approaches, this study explores a series of experiments that combine reinforcement learning (RL)-based visual attention methods with saliency ranking techniques to investigate transparent and sustainable solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-saliency-ranking-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Dynamic Difficulty Adjustment -- Imitation Learning Meets Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-dynamic-difficulty-adjustment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Balancing game difficulty in video games is a key task to create interesting gaming experiences for players.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-dynamic-difficulty-adjustment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple but Effective Compound Geometric Operations for Temporal Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-but-effective-compound-geometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal knowledge graph completion aims to infer the missing facts in temporal knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-but-effective-compound-geometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs can Schedule</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-schedule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The job shop scheduling problem (JSSP) remains a significant hurdle in optimizing production processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-schedule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sumotosima: A Framework and Dataset for Classifying and Summarizing Otoscopic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sumotosima-a-framework-and-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For summarization, Sumotosima outperformed GPT-4o and LLaVA by 88. 53% and 107. 57% in ROUGE scores, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sumotosima-a-framework-and-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenResearcher: Unleashing AI for Accelerated Scientific Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openresearcher-unleashing-ai-for-accelerated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of scientific literature imposes significant challenges for researchers endeavoring to stay updated with the latest advancements in their fields and delve into new areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openresearcher-unleashing-ai-for-accelerated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large language models can consistently generate high-quality content for election disinformation operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-consistently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in large language models have raised concerns about their potential use in generating compelling election disinformation at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-consistently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLGait: A Global-Local Temporal Receptive Field Network for Gait Recognition in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glgait-a-global-local-temporal-receptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, some Convolution Neural Networks (ConvNets) based methods have been proposed to address the issue of gait recognition in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glgait-a-global-local-temporal-receptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Autonomous Agents: Adaptive-planning, Reasoning, and Acting in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-agents-adaptive-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel in-context learning algorithm for building autonomous decision-making language agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-autonomous-agents-adaptive-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BI-MDRG: Bridging Image History in Multimodal Dialogue Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-mdrg-bridging-image-history-in-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose BI-MDRG that bridges the response generation path such that the image history information is utilized for enhanced relevance of text responses to the image content and the consistency of objects in sequential image responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-mdrg-bridging-image-history-in-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BooW-VTON: Boosting In-the-Wild Virtual Try-On via Mask-Free Pseudo Data Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boow-vton-boosting-in-the-wild-virtual-try-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods always employ an accurate mask to remove the original garment in the source image, thus achieving realistic synthesized images in simple and conventional try-on scenarios based on powerful diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boow-vton-boosting-in-the-wild-virtual-try-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUNE: A Machine Learning Deep UNet++ based Ensemble Approach to Monthly, Seasonal and Annual Climate Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dune-a-machine-learning-deep-unet-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ERA5 monthly mean data is used as input for T2m over land, SST over oceans, and solar radiation at the top of the atmosphere for each month of 40 years to train the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dune-a-machine-learning-deep-unet-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MR3D-Net: Dynamic Multi-Resolution 3D Sparse Voxel Grid Fusion for LiDAR-Based Collective Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr3d-net-dynamic-multi-resolution-3d-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose MR3D-Net, a dynamic multi-resolution 3D sparse voxel grid fusion backbone architecture for LiDAR-based collective perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr3d-net-dynamic-multi-resolution-3d-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisualAgentBench: Towards Large Multimodal Models as Visual Foundation Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualagentbench-towards-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) have ushered in a new era in artificial intelligence, merging capabilities in both language and vision to form highly capable Visual Foundation Agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualagentbench-towards-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-SAM: SVD-based Fine-Tuning of Segment Anything Model for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-sam-svd-based-fine-tuning-of-segment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that S-SAM outperforms state-of-the-art methods as well as existing SAM adaptation methods while tuning a significantly less number of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-sam-svd-based-fine-tuning-of-segment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sharpness Based Loss Function for Removing Out-of-Focus Blur</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sharpness-based-loss-function-for-removing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of modern Deep Neural Network (DNN) approaches can be attributed to the use of complex optimization criteria beyond standard losses such as mean absolute error (MAE) or mean squared error (MSE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sharpness-based-loss-function-for-removing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlNeXt: Powerful and Efficient Control for Image and Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnext-powerful-and-efficient-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ControlNeXt: a powerful and efficient method for controllable image and video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnext-powerful-and-efficient-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FruitNeRF: A Unified Neural Radiance Field based Fruit Counting Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fruitnerf-a-unified-neural-radiance-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce FruitNeRF, a unified novel fruit counting framework that leverages state-of-the-art view synthesis methods to count any fruit type directly in 3D.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fruitnerf-a-unified-neural-radiance-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind-Match: Efficient Homomorphic Encryption-Based 1:N Matching for Privacy-Preserving Biometric Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-match-efficient-homomorphic-encryption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Blind-Match, a novel biometric identification system that leverages homomorphic encryption (HE) for efficient and privacy-preserving 1:N matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-match-efficient-homomorphic-encryption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Case Study on the Performance of Machine Learning Methods on the Classification of Solar Panel Electroluminescence Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-case-study-on-the-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we comprehensively compare different machine learning and deep learning methods under different performance metrics on the classification of solar cell EL images from monocrystalline and polycrystalline modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-case-study-on-the-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Byzantine Robustness in Federated Learning with A Black-box Server</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-byzantine-robustness-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) becomes vulnerable to Byzantine attacks where some of participators tend to damage the utility or discourage the convergence of the learned model via sending their malicious model updates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-byzantine-robustness-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling Surprisal in Music Generation via Information Content Curve Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-surprisal-in-music-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enables the comparison of surprisal across different musical content even if the musical events occur in irregular time intervals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-surprisal-in-music-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Scientist: Towards Fully Automated Open-Ended Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ai-scientist-towards-fully-automated-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach signifies the beginning of a new era in scientific discovery in machine learning: bringing the transformative benefits of AI agents to the entire research process of AI itself, and taking us closer to a world where endless affordable creativity and innovation can be unleashed on the world's most challenging problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ai-scientist-towards-fully-automated-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GFlowNet Training by Policy Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gflownet-training-by-policy-gradients</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Flow Networks (GFlowNets) have been shown effective to generate combinatorial objects with desired properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gflownet-training-by-policy-gradients</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalization capabilities of MeshGraphNets to unseen geometries for fluid dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-capabilities-of-meshgraphnets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our numerical tests, we show that MGNs can sometimes generalize well to various shapes by training on a dataset of one obstacle shape and testing on a dataset of another obstacle shape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-capabilities-of-meshgraphnets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Game-Playing with Size-Constrained State Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strategy-game-playing-with-size-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major challenges is the large search space due to a diverse set of game components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strategy-game-playing-with-size-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClickAttention: Click Region Similarity Guided Interactive Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clickattention-click-region-similarity-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a click attention algorithm that expands the influence range of positive clicks based on the similarity between positively-clicked regions and the whole input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clickattention-click-region-similarity-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyp SAM 2: Advancing Zero shot Polyp Segmentation in Colorectal Cancer Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-sam-2-advancing-zero-shot-polyp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Polyp segmentation plays a crucial role in the early detection and diagnosis of colorectal cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyp-sam-2-advancing-zero-shot-polyp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel transport on matrix manifolds and Exponential Action</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-transport-on-matrix-manifolds-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We express parallel transport for several common matrix Lie groups with a family of pseudo-Riemannian metrics in terms of matrix exponential and exponential actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-transport-on-matrix-manifolds-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth Linear Discriminant Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-linear-discriminant-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces a novel linear discriminant method, called Depth Linear Discriminant Analysis (D-LDA) to enhance the robustness of the original LDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-linear-discriminant-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Vision-Language Representation for Weakly Supervised Temporal Action Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-vision-language-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose a novel framework that aligns human action knowledge and VLP knowledge in a probabilistic embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-vision-language-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RISurConv: Rotation Invariant Surface Attention-Augmented Convolutions for 3D Point Cloud Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risurconv-rotation-invariant-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve an overall accuracy of 96. 0% (+4. 7%) on ModelNet40, 93. 1% (+12. 8%) on ScanObjectNN, and class accuracies of 91. 5% (+3. 6%), 82. 7% (+5. 1%), and 78. 5% (+9. 2%) on the three categories of the FG3D dataset for the fine-grained classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risurconv-rotation-invariant-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Patterns in Ambiguity: Interpretable Stress Testing in the Decision~Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-patterns-in-ambiguity-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing use of deep learning across various domains highlights the importance of understanding the decision-making processes of these black-box models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-patterns-in-ambiguity-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
