<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 21:06:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Graph Mixformer for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-graph-mixformer-for-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we train an estimator model that express the contribution of a node over the desired prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-graph-mixformer-for-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Multi-modal Contrastive Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-multi-modal-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by recent C-MCR, this paper proposes Extending Multimodal Contrastive Representation (Ex-MCR), a training-efficient and paired-data-free method to flexibly learn unified contrastive representation space for more than three modalities by integrating the knowledge of existing MCR spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-multi-modal-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relation-aware Ensemble Learning for Knowledge Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-ensemble-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph (KG) embedding is a fundamental task in natural language processing, and various methods have been proposed to explore semantic patterns in distinctive ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relation-aware-ensemble-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuoBERTa: Training and evaluation of a curated language model for Setswana</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puoberta-training-and-evaluation-of-a-curated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language processing (NLP) has made significant progress for well-resourced languages such as English but lagged behind for low-resource languages like Setswana.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puoberta-training-and-evaluation-of-a-curated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selectivity Drives Productivity: Efficient Dataset Pruning for Enhanced Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectivity-drives-productivity-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim to address the problem of DP for transfer learning, i. e., how to prune a source dataset for improved pretraining efficiency and lossless finetuning accuracy on downstream target tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectivity-drives-productivity-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Multimodal Generation Easier: When Diffusion Models Meet LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-multimodal-generation-easier-when</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present EasyGen, an efficient model designed to enhance multimodal understanding and generation by harnessing the capabilities of diffusion models and large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-multimodal-generation-easier-when</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xDial-Eval: A Multilingual Open-Domain Dialogue Evaluation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xdial-eval-a-multilingual-open-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The English dialogue data are extended to nine other languages with commercial machine translation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xdial-eval-a-multilingual-open-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Example-Based NMT with Multi-Levenshtein Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-example-based-nmt-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Machine Translation (RAMT) is attracting growing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-example-based-nmt-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiamAF: Learning Shared Information from ECG and PPG Signals for Robust Atrial Fibrillation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamaf-learning-shared-information-from-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous deep learning models learn from a single modality, either electrocardiogram (ECG) or photoplethysmography (PPG) signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamaf-learning-shared-information-from-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BibRank: Automatic Keyphrase Extraction Platform Using~Metadata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bibrank-automatic-keyphrase-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic Keyphrase Extraction involves identifying essential phrases in a document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bibrank-automatic-keyphrase-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-in-the-loop Machine Translation with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-machine-translation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large language model (LLM) has garnered significant attention due to its in-context learning mechanisms and emergent capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-machine-translation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster 3D cardiac CT segmentation with Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-3d-cardiac-ct-segmentation-with-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate segmentation of the heart is essential for personalized blood flow simulations and surgical intervention planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-3d-cardiac-ct-segmentation-with-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIDE: Temporally Incremental Disparity Estimation via Pattern Flow in Structured Light System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-temporally-incremental-disparity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from most former disparity estimation methods that operate in a frame-wise manner, our network acquires disparity maps in a temporally incremental way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-temporally-incremental-disparity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Analysis of ICALEPCS and IPAC Conference Proceedings: Revealing Research Trends, Topics, and Collaborations for Future Insights and Advanced Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-analysis-of-icalepcs-and-ipac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show a textual analysis of past ICALEPCS and IPAC conference proceedings to gain insights into the research trends and topics discussed in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-analysis-of-icalepcs-and-ipac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Evolution Algorithm based Hyper-Parameters Selection of Convolutional Neural Network for Speech Command Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech Command Recognition (SCR), which deals with identification of short uttered speech commands, is crucial for various applications, including IoT devices and assistive technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pose-format: Library for Viewing, Augmenting, and Handling .pose Files</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-format-library-for-viewing-augmenting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The library includes a specialized file format that encapsulates various types of pose data, accommodating multiple individuals and an indefinite number of time frames, thus proving its utility for both image and video data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-format-library-for-viewing-augmenting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Graph Distillation See Like Vision Dataset Counterpart?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-graph-distillation-see-like-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the proposed SGDD across 9 datasets and achieve state-of-the-art results on all of them: for example, on the YelpChi dataset, our approach maintains 98. 6% test accuracy of training on the original graph dataset with 1, 000 times saving on the scale of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-graph-distillation-see-like-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METRA: Scalable Unsupervised RL with Metric-Aware Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metra-scalable-unsupervised-rl-with-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through our experiments in five locomotion and manipulation environments, we demonstrate that METRA can discover a variety of useful behaviors even in complex, pixel-based environments, being the first unsupervised RL method that discovers diverse locomotion behaviors in pixel-based Quadruped and Humanoid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metra-scalable-unsupervised-rl-with-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welfare Diplomacy: Benchmarking Language Model Cooperation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/welfare-diplomacy-benchmarking-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing capabilities and increasingly widespread deployment of AI systems necessitate robust benchmarks for measuring their cooperative capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/welfare-diplomacy-benchmarking-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Screening Rules for Optimal Design via Quadratic Lasso Reformulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-screening-rules-for-optimal-design-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problems of Lasso regression and optimal design of experiments share a critical property: their optimal solutions are typically \emph{sparse}, i. e., only a small fraction of the optimal variables are non-zero.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-screening-rules-for-optimal-design-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HierarchicalContrast: A Coarse-to-Fine Contrastive Learning Framework for Cross-Domain Zero-Shot Slot Filling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchicalcontrast-a-coarse-to-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this issue, we present a novel Hierarchical Contrastive Learning Framework (HiCL) for zero-shot slot filling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchicalcontrast-a-coarse-to-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerturbScore: Connecting Discrete and Continuous Perturbations in NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbscore-connecting-discrete-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through experimental results, we find that we can build a connection between discrete and continuous perturbations and use the proposed PerturbScore to learn such correlation, surpassing previous methods used in discrete perturbation measuring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbscore-connecting-discrete-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniParser: Multi-Human Parsing with Unified Correlation Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniparser-multi-human-parsing-with-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-human parsing is an image segmentation task necessitating both instance-level and fine-grained category-level information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniparser-multi-human-parsing-with-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding AMR Parsing with Reverse Graph Linearization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-amr-parsing-with-reverse-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Abstract Meaning Representation (AMR) parsing aims to extract an abstract semantic graph from a given sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-amr-parsing-with-reverse-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subspace Adaptation Prior for Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-adaptation-prior-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gradient-based meta-learning techniques aim to distill useful prior knowledge from a set of training tasks such that new tasks can be learned more efficiently with gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-adaptation-prior-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Generation Alignment for End-to-End Task-Oriented Dialogue System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-generation-alignment-for-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results demonstrate that when combined with meta knowledge, the response generator can effectively leverage high-quality knowledge records from the retriever and enhance the quality of generated responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-generation-alignment-for-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KCTS: Knowledge-Constrained Tree Search Decoding with Token-Level Hallucination Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kcts-knowledge-constrained-tree-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable human-level natural language generation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kcts-knowledge-constrained-tree-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLoRE: Evaluating Logical Reasoning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glore-evaluating-logical-reasoning-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, large language models (LLMs), including notable models such as GPT-4 and burgeoning community models, have showcased significant general language understanding abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glore-evaluating-logical-reasoning-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework for Few-Shot Policy Transfer through Observation Mapping and Behavior Cloning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-few-shot-policy-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) along with a cycle-consistency loss to map the observations between the source and target domains and later use this learned mapping to clone the successful source task behavior policy to the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-few-shot-policy-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypernymy Understanding Evaluation of Text-to-Image Models via WordNet Hierarchy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypernymy-understanding-evaluation-of-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image synthesis has recently attracted widespread attention due to rapidly improving quality and numerous practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypernymy-understanding-evaluation-of-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-BigBench: Evaluating Multimodal Models on Multimodal Content Comprehension Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bigbench-evaluating-multimodal-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, our work complements research on the performance of MLLMs in multimodal comprehension tasks, achieving a more comprehensive and holistic evaluation of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bigbench-evaluating-multimodal-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatKBQA: A Generate-then-Retrieve Framework for Knowledge Base Question Answering with Fine-tuned Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatkbqa-a-generate-then-retrieve-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Base Question Answering (KBQA) aims to derive answers to natural language questions over large-scale knowledge bases (KBs), which are generally divided into two research components: knowledge retrieval and semantic parsing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatkbqa-a-generate-then-retrieve-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BanglaNLP at BLP-2023 Task 2: Benchmarking different Transformer Models for Sentiment Analysis of Bangla Social Media Posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglanlp-at-blp-2023-task-2-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bangla is the 7th most widely spoken language globally, with a staggering 234 million native speakers primarily hailing from India and Bangladesh.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglanlp-at-blp-2023-task-2-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-based Multimodal Change Detection with Multitask Consistency Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multimodal-change-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the current change detection methods struggle with the multitask conflicts between semantic and height change detection tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multimodal-change-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dont Add, dont Miss: Effective Content Preserving Generation from Pre-Selected Text Spans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dont-add-dont-miss-effective-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we substantially improve the silver training data quality via GPT-4 distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dont-add-dont-miss-effective-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Proliferation -- the "Cancer" in StyleGAN and its Treatments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-proliferation-the-cancer-in-stylegan-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to our discovery of Feature Proliferation, the proposed feature rescaling method is less destructive and retains more useful image features than the truncation trick, as it is more fine-grained and works in a lower-level feature space rather than a high-level latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-proliferation-the-cancer-in-stylegan-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational autoencoder with weighted samples for high-dimensional non-parametric adaptive importance sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-autoencoder-with-weighted-samples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this contribution, we suggest to use as the approximating model a distribution parameterised by a variational autoencoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-autoencoder-with-weighted-samples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularization-Based Methods for Ordinal Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularization-based-methods-for-ordinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantification, i. e., the task of training predictors of the class prevalence values in sets of unlabeled data items, has received increased attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularization-based-methods-for-ordinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIDE: Self-supervised Intermediate Domain Exploration for Source-free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side-self-supervised-intermediate-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptation aims to alleviate the domain shift when transferring the knowledge learned from the source domain to the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/side-self-supervised-intermediate-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From CLIP to DINO: Visual Encoders Shout in Multi-modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-clip-to-dino-visual-encoders-shout-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By simply equipping it with an MLP layer for alignment, DINO surpasses CLIP in fine-grained related perception tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-clip-to-dino-visual-encoders-shout-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Recency Bias of Normalization Statistics in Continual Learning: Balance and Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-recency-bias-of-normalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning entails learning a sequence of tasks and balancing their knowledge appropriately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-recency-bias-of-normalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning To Teach Large Language Models Logical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-teach-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have gained enormous attention from both academia and industry, due to their exceptional ability in language generation and extremely powerful generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-teach-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 4-approximation algorithm for min max correlation clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-4-approximation-algorithm-for-min-max</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a lower bounding technique for the min max correlation clustering problem and, based on this technique, a combinatorial 4-approximation algorithm for complete graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-4-approximation-algorithm-for-min-max</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the Stability of Process Outcome Predictions in Online Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-stability-of-process-outcome</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an evaluation framework for assessing the stability of models for online predictive process monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-stability-of-process-outcome</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore-Instruct: Enhancing Domain-Specific Instruction Coverage through Active Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-instruct-enhancing-domain-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction-tuning can be substantially optimized through enhanced diversity, resulting in models capable of handling a broader spectrum of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explore-instruct-enhancing-domain-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeqXGPT: Sentence-Level AI-Generated Text Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqxgpt-sentence-level-ai-generated-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, it is important to build strong AI-generated text (AIGT) detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqxgpt-sentence-level-ai-generated-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Predicting Visual Error for Real-Time Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-predicting-visual-error-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we train and deploy a neural network to estimate the visual error resulting from reusing shading or using reduced shading rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-predicting-visual-error-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasm-iCARE: a portable and privacy-preserving web module to build, validate, and apply absolute risk models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasm-icare-a-portable-and-privacy-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective: Absolute risk models estimate an individual's future disease risk over a specified time interval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasm-icare-a-portable-and-privacy-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QASiNa: Religious Domain Question Answering using Sirah Nabawiyah</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qasina-religious-domain-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This concludes Chat GPT is unsuitable for question answering task in religious domain especially for Islamic religion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qasina-religious-domain-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUSA: Decoupled Unsupervised Sim2Real Adaptation for Vehicle-to-Everything Collaborative Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dusa-decoupled-unsupervised-sim2real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To take full advantage of simulated data, we present a new unsupervised sim2real domain adaptation method for V2X collaborative detection named Decoupled Unsupervised Sim2Real Adaptation (DUSA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dusa-decoupled-unsupervised-sim2real</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
