<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 09:12:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How to Evaluate Entity Resolution Systems: An Entity-Centric Framework with Application to Inventor Name Disambiguation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-evaluate-entity-resolution-systems-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These benchmark data sets can then be used for model training and a variety of evaluation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-evaluate-entity-resolution-systems-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree Search-Based Policy Optimization under Stochastic Execution Delay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-search-based-policy-optimization-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that given observed delay values, it is sufficient to perform a policy search in the class of Markov policies in order to reach optimal performance, thus extending the deterministic fixed delay case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-search-based-policy-optimization-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechAlign: Aligning Speech Generation to Human Preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechalign-aligning-speech-generation-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the integration of human feedback to align speech outputs to human preferences is often neglected.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechalign-aligning-speech-generation-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Open-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-open-vocabulary-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, RALF consists of two modules: Retrieval Augmented Losses (RAL) and Retrieval-Augmented visual Features (RAF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-open-vocabulary-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have You Merged My Model? On The Robustness of Large Language Model IP Protection Methods Against Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/have-you-merged-my-model-on-the-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging is a promising lightweight model empowerment technique that does not rely on expensive computing devices (e. g., GPUs) or require the collection of specific training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/have-you-merged-my-model-on-the-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindSet: Vision. A toolbox for testing DNNs on key psychological experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindset-vision-a-toolbox-for-testing-dnns-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple benchmarks have been developed to assess the alignment between deep neural networks (DNNs) and human vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindset-vision-a-toolbox-for-testing-dnns-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Report: The Graph Spectral Token -- Enhancing Graph Transformers with Spectral Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-the-graph-spectral-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Transformers have emerged as a powerful alternative to Message-Passing Graph Neural Networks (MP-GNNs) to address limitations such as over-squashing of information exchange.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-the-graph-spectral-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Spatial Inconsistency in Classifier-Free Diffusion Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-spatial-inconsistency-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classifier-Free Guidance (CFG) has been widely used in text-to-image diffusion models, where the CFG scale is introduced to control the strength of text guidance on the whole image space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-spatial-inconsistency-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Similarity Transition: Decoupling Class Similarities and Imbalance from Generalized Few-shot Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-similarity-transition-decoupling-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the relevance between base and novel classes, and improves GFSS in two aspects: 1) mining the similarity between base and novel classes to promote the learning of novel classes, and 2) mitigating the class imbalance issue caused by the volume difference between the support set and the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-similarity-transition-decoupling-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-agent Long-term 3D Human Pose Forecasting via Interaction-aware Trajectory Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-long-term-3d-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model effectively handles the multi-modality of human motion and the complexity of long-term multi-agent interactions, improving performance in complex environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-long-term-3d-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Mathematical Reasoning Beyond Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-mathematical-reasoning-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To measure reasoning beyond final-answer accuracy, we introduce ReasonEval, a new methodology for evaluating the quality of reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-mathematical-reasoning-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LayoutLLM: Layout Instruction Tuning with Large Language Models for Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layoutllm-layout-instruction-tuning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of LayoutLLM is a layout instruction tuning strategy, which is specially designed to enhance the comprehension and utilization of document layouts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layoutllm-layout-instruction-tuning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Refinement Strategy for Automated Data Labeling: Facial Landmark Diagnosis in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-refinement-strategy-for-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated data labeling techniques are crucial for accelerating the development of deep learning models, particularly in complex medical imaging applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-refinement-strategy-for-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GloSoFarID: Global multispectral dataset for Solar Farm IDentification in satellite imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glosofarid-global-multispectral-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solar Photovoltaic (PV) technology is increasingly recognized as a pivotal solution in the global pursuit of clean and renewable energy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glosofarid-global-multispectral-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoCodeRover: Autonomous Program Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in Large Language Models (LLMs) has significantly impacted the development process, where developers can use LLM-based programming assistants to achieve automated coding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAF-DPM: A Nonlinear Activation-Free Diffusion Probabilistic Model for Document Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naf-dpm-a-nonlinear-activation-free-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world documents may suffer various forms of degradation, often resulting in lower accuracy in optical character recognition (OCR) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naf-dpm-a-nonlinear-activation-free-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Optics for Video Snapshot Compressive Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optics-for-video-snapshot-compressive-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe this is a milestone for real-world video SCI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optics-for-video-snapshot-compressive-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David and Goliath: An Empirical Evaluation of Attacks and Defenses for QNNs at the Deep Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/david-and-goliath-an-empirical-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we empirically evaluate the effectiveness of attacks and defenses from (full-precision) ANNs on (constrained) QNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/david-and-goliath-an-empirical-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Stream Sampling with Fuzzy Task Boundaries and Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-stream-sampling-with-fuzzy-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of continual learning, the presence of noisy labels within data streams represents a notable obstacle to model reliability and fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-stream-sampling-with-fuzzy-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Diffusion Model for Multi-Contrast MRI Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-model-for-multi-contrast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, diffusion models (DM) have been applied in magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) super-resolution (SR) reconstruction, exhibiting impressive performance, especially with regard to detailed reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-model-for-multi-contrast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Distinction Learning: Adaptive Pseudo Anomalies for Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-distinction-learning-adaptive-pseudo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Dynamic Distinction Learning (DDL) for Video Anomaly Detection, a novel video anomaly detection methodology that combines pseudo-anomalies, dynamic anomaly weighting, and a distinction loss function to improve detection accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-distinction-learning-adaptive-pseudo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Deep Hyperspherical Quantization for Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-deep-hyperspherical-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep quantization methods have shown high efficiency on large-scale image retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-deep-hyperspherical-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniMD: Towards Unifying Moment Retrieval and Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimd-towards-unifying-moment-retrieval-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal Action Detection (TAD) focuses on detecting pre-defined actions, while Moment Retrieval (MR) aims to identify the events described by open-ended natural language within untrimmed videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimd-towards-unifying-moment-retrieval-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SqueezeAttention: 2D Management of KV-Cache in LLM Inference via Layer-wise Optimal Budget</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeezeattention-2d-management-of-kv-cache-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimizing the Key-Value (KV) cache of the Large Language Model (LLM) has been considered critical to saving the cost of inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeezeattention-2d-management-of-kv-cache-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWE+: Dual-Way Matching Enhanced Framework for Multimodal Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwe-dual-way-matching-enhanced-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal entity linking (MEL) aims to utilize multimodal information (usually textual and visual information) to link ambiguous mentions to unambiguous entities in knowledge base.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwe-dual-way-matching-enhanced-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Percentile Criterion Optimization in Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/percentile-criterion-optimization-in-offline-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The percentile criterion is approximately solved by constructing an \emph{ambiguity set} that contains the true model with high probability and optimizing the policy for the worst model in the set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/percentile-criterion-optimization-in-offline-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Learning under Haphazard Input Conditions: A Comprehensive Review and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-learning-under-haphazard-input</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The domain of online learning has experienced multifaceted expansion owing to its prevalence in real-life applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-learning-under-haphazard-input</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allo: A Programming Model for Composable Accelerator Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allo-a-programming-model-for-composable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the GPT2 model, the inference latency of the Allo generated accelerator is 1. 7x faster than the NVIDIA A100 GPU with 5. 4x higher energy efficiency, demonstrating the capability of Allo to handle large-scale designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allo-a-programming-model-for-composable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixup Domain Adaptations for Dynamic Remaining Useful Life Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixup-domain-adaptations-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MDAN encompasses a three-staged mechanism where the mix-up strategy is not only performed to regularize the source and target domains but also applied to establish an intermediate mix-up domain where the source and target domains are aligned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixup-domain-adaptations-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PagPassGPT: Pattern Guided Password Guessing via Generative Pretrained Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pagpassgpt-pattern-guided-password-guessing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amidst the surge in deep learning-based password guessing models, challenges of generating high-quality passwords and reducing duplicate passwords persist.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pagpassgpt-pattern-guided-password-guessing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camera-Based Remote Physiology Sensing for Hundreds of Subjects Across Skin Tones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-based-remote-physiology-sensing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) emerges as a promising method for non-invasive, convenient measurement of vital signs, utilizing the widespread presence of cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camera-based-remote-physiology-sensing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LOGO: A Long-Form Video Dataset for Group Action Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logo-a-long-form-video-dataset-for-group-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Action quality assessment (AQA) has become an emerging topic since it can be extensively applied in numerous scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logo-a-long-form-video-dataset-for-group-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Test-Time Adaptation: Theoretical Analyses and An Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-test-time-adaptation-theoretical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results confirm consistency with our theoretical analyses and show that the proposed ATTA method yields substantial performance improvements over TTA methods while maintaining efficiency and shares similar effectiveness to the more demanding active domain adaptation (ADA) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-test-time-adaptation-theoretical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Decomposition-Driven Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Remote Sensing Image Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-decomposition-driven-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain semantic segmentation of remote sensing (RS) imagery based on unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) techniques has significantly advanced deep-learning applications in the geosciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-decomposition-driven-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Multimodal Learning for Cardiovascular Hemodynamics Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extract spatio-temporal features from CMR scans using tensor-based learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-multimodal-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPB-REC: A Non-parametric Bayesian Deep-learning Approach for Undersampled MRI Reconstruction with Uncertainty Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/npb-rec-a-non-parametric-bayesian-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce "NPB-REC", a non-parametric fully Bayesian framework, for MRI reconstruction from undersampled data with uncertainty estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/npb-rec-a-non-parametric-bayesian-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting Multi-objectivized Software Configuration Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-multi-objectivized-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on several real-world systems, objectives, and budgets show that, for 71% of the cases, AdMMO is considerably superior to MMO and a wide range of state-of-the-art optimizers while achieving generally better efficiency with the best speedup between 2. 2x and 20x.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-multi-objectivized-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IITK at SemEval-2024 Task 2: Exploring the Capabilities of LLMs for Safe Biomedical Natural Language Inference for Clinical Trials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iitk-at-semeval-2024-task-2-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language models (LLMs) have demonstrated state-of-the-art performance in various natural language processing (NLP) tasks across multiple domains, yet they are prone to shortcut learning and factual inconsistencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iitk-at-semeval-2024-task-2-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Self-training for Semi-supervised Landmark Detection: A Selection-free Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-self-training-for-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-training is a simple yet effective method for semi-supervised learning, during which pseudo-label selection plays an important role for handling confirmation bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-self-training-for-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MACM: Utilizing a Multi-Agent System for Condition Mining in Solving Complex Mathematical Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macm-utilizing-a-multi-agent-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, their effectiveness in tackling complex mathematical problems is somewhat constrained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macm-utilizing-a-multi-agent-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Conservatism: A Transductive Approach in Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-conservatism-a-transductive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our COCOA seeks both in-distribution anchors and differences by utilizing the learned reverse dynamics model, encouraging conservatism in the compositional input space for the policy or value function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-conservatism-a-transductive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric Modern Hopfield Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-modern-hopfield-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a nonparametric construction for deep learning compatible modern Hopfield models and utilize this framework to debut an efficient variant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-modern-hopfield-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget NLI, Use a Dictionary: Zero-Shot Topic Classification for Low-Resource Languages with Application to Luxembourgish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-nli-use-a-dictionary-zero-shot-topic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common method for ZSC is to fine-tune a language model on a Natural Language Inference (NLI) dataset and then use it to infer the entailment between the input document and the target labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-nli-use-a-dictionary-zero-shot-topic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoltaVision: A Transfer Learning model for electronic component classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voltavision-a-transfer-learning-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze the effectiveness of transfer learning on classifying electronic components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voltavision-a-transfer-learning-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Factual Accuracy of Neural Table-to-Text Output by Addressing Input Problems in ToTTo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-factual-accuracy-of-neural-table-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Table-to-Text models tend to hallucinate, producing texts that contain factual errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-factual-accuracy-of-neural-table-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCAResNet: A ResNet Variant Optimized for Tiny Object Detection in Transmission and Distribution Towers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaresnet-a-resnet-variant-optimized-for-tiny</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This demonstrates the advantages of our SCAResNet in detecting transmission and distribution towers and its value in tiny object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaresnet-a-resnet-variant-optimized-for-tiny</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Prompt Optimizing for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-prompt-optimizing-for-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Users assign weights or alter the injection time steps of certain words in the text prompts to improve the quality of generated images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-prompt-optimizing-for-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superior Genetic Algorithms for the Target Set Selection Problem Based on Power-Law Parameter Choices and Simple Greedy Heuristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superior-genetic-algorithms-for-the-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides providing a superior algorithm for the TSS problem, this work shows that randomized parameter choices and elementary greedy heuristics can give better results than complex algorithms and costly parameter tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superior-genetic-algorithms-for-the-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning with Weight Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-weight-interpolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning poses a fundamental challenge for modern machine learning systems, requiring models to adapt to new tasks while retaining knowledge from previous ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-weight-interpolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Propagation for Zero-shot Classification with Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-propagation-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage the graph structure of the unlabeled data and introduce ZLaP, a method based on label propagation (LP) that utilizes geodesic distances for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-propagation-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
