<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SeqFusion: Sequential Fusion of Pre-Trained Models for Zero-Shot Time-Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqfusion-sequential-fusion-of-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional time-series forecasting methods that require extensive in-task data for training, zero-shot forecasting can directly predict future values given a target time series without additional training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqfusion-sequential-fusion-of-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning for Privacy-Preserving Feedforward Control in Multi-Agent Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-privacy-preserving-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therein, vehicles equipped with a trajectory-tracking feedback controller are enhanced by FL-based neural FF control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-for-privacy-preserving-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Knowledge Tracing for Alleviating Cognitive Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-knowledge-tracing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of Intelligent Tutoring System (ITS), the accurate assessment of students' knowledge states through Knowledge Tracing (KT) is crucial for personalized learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-knowledge-tracing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MciteBench: A Benchmark for Multimodal Citation Text Generation in MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcitebench-a-benchmark-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce MCiteBench, the first benchmark designed to evaluate and analyze the multimodal citation text generation ability of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcitebench-a-benchmark-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience Replay with Random Reshuffling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experience-replay-with-random-reshuffling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experience replay is a key component in reinforcement learning for stabilizing learning and improving sample efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experience-replay-with-random-reshuffling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smoothing the Shift: Towards Stable Test-Time Adaptation under Complex Multimodal Noises</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothing-the-shift-towards-stable-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenging problem, we propose two novel strategies: sample identification with interquartile range Smoothing and unimodal assistance, and Mutual information sharing (SuMi).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothing-the-shift-towards-stable-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACNN: Residual Attention Convolutional Neural Network for Near-Field Channel Estimation in 6G Wireless Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/racnn-residual-attention-convolutional-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Near-field channel estimation is a fundamental challenge in sixth-generation (6G) wireless communication, where extremely large antenna arrays (ELAA) enable near-field communication (NFC) but introduce significant signal processing complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/racnn-residual-attention-convolutional-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compare different SG-Schemes based on large least square problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compare-different-sg-schemes-based-on-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study reviews some of the popular stochastic gradient-based schemes based on large least-square problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compare-different-sg-schemes-based-on-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseMamba-PCL: Scribble-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation via SAM-Guided Progressive Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsemamba-pcl-scribble-supervised-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scribble annotations significantly reduce the cost and labor required for dense labeling in large medical datasets with complex anatomical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsemamba-pcl-scribble-supervised-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stage Manipulation with Demonstration-Augmented Reward, Policy, and World Model Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-manipulation-with-demonstration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-horizon tasks in robotic manipulation present significant challenges in reinforcement learning (RL) due to the difficulty of designing dense reward functions and effectively exploring the expansive state-action space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-manipulation-with-demonstration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Approach for Air Drawing Using Background Subtraction and Contour Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-approach-for-air-drawing-using-background</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach for air drawing that uses image processing techniques to draw on the screen by moving fingers in the air.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-approach-for-air-drawing-using-background</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DifIISR: A Diffusion Model with Gradient Guidance for Infrared Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difiisr-a-diffusion-model-with-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we incorporate various visual foundational models as the perceptual guidance for downstream visual tasks, infusing generalizable perceptual features beneficial for detection and segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difiisr-a-diffusion-model-with-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex Hull-based Algebraic Constraint for Visual Quadric SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-hull-based-algebraic-constraint-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using Quadrics as the object representation has the benefits of both generality and closed-form projection derivation between image and world spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-hull-based-algebraic-constraint-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowDec: A flow-based full-band general audio codec with high perceptual quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowdec-a-flow-based-full-band-general-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose FlowDec, a neural full-band audio codec for general audio sampled at 48 kHz that combines non-adversarial codec training with a stochastic postfilter based on a novel conditional flow matching method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowdec-a-flow-based-full-band-general-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiss3DGen: Repurposing Image Diffusion Models for 3D Asset Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kiss3dgen-repurposing-image-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The normal maps are then used to reconstruct a 3D mesh, and the multi-view images provide texture mapping, resulting in a complete 3D model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kiss3dgen-repurposing-image-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the Validity of Clustering Validation Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-validity-of-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, it is essential to evaluate and compare datasets regarding their cluster-label matching (CLM), i. e., how well their class labels match actual clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-validity-of-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How simple can you go? An off-the-shelf transformer approach to molecular dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-simple-can-you-go-an-off-the-shelf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While our model exhibits runaway energy increases on larger structures, we show approximately energy-conserving NVE simulations for a range of small structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-simple-can-you-go-an-off-the-shelf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Matryoshka: Revisiting Sparse Coding for Adaptive Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-matryoshka-revisiting-sparse-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many large-scale systems rely on high-quality deep representations (embeddings) to facilitate tasks like retrieval, search, and generative modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-matryoshka-revisiting-sparse-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>m4: A Learned Flow-level Network Simulator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4-a-learned-flow-level-network-simulator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Flow-level simulation is widely used to model large-scale data center networks due to its scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4-a-learned-flow-level-network-simulator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoInD: Enabling Logical Compositions in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coind-enabling-logical-compositions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How can we learn generative models to sample data with arbitrary logical compositions of statistically independent attributes?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coind-enabling-logical-compositions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SePer: Measure Retrieval Utility Through The Lens Of Semantic Perplexity Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seper-measure-retrieval-utility-through-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated improved generation performance by incorporating externally retrieved knowledge, a process known as retrieval-augmented generation (RAG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seper-measure-retrieval-utility-through-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiLiC-Eval: Benchmarking Multilingual LLMs for China's Minority Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/milic-eval-benchmarking-multilingual-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) excel in high-resource languages but struggle with low-resource languages (LRLs), particularly those spoken by minority communities in China, such as Tibetan, Uyghur, Kazakh, and Mongolian.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/milic-eval-benchmarking-multilingual-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prior-Fitted Networks Scale to Larger Datasets When Treated as Weak Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-fitted-networks-scale-to-larger</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through this work, we address the challenges of efficiently handling large datasets via PFN-based models, paving the way for faster and more effective tabular data classification training and prediction process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-fitted-networks-scale-to-larger</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-RFT: Visual Reinforcement Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-rft-visual-reinforcement-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Fine-Tuning (RFT) in Large Reasoning Models like OpenAI o1 learns from feedback on its answers, which is especially useful in applications when fine-tuning data is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-rft-visual-reinforcement-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToLo: A Two-Stage, Training-Free Layout-To-Image Generation Framework For High-Overlap Layouts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tolo-a-two-stage-training-free-layout-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models follow a one-stage framework: Encouraging the model to focus the attention map of each concept on its corresponding region by defining attention map-based losses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tolo-a-two-stage-training-free-layout-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCSegamba: Lightweight Structure-Aware Vision Mamba for Crack Segmentation in Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scsegamba-lightweight-structure-aware-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key insight of GBC lies in its effectiveness in modeling the morphological information of cracks, while the SASS enhances the perception of crack topology and texture by strengthening the continuity of semantic information between crack pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scsegamba-lightweight-structure-aware-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Shared Encoder Approach to Multimodal Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-shared-encoder-approach-to-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a shared encoder framework for multimodal representation learning tailored to the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-shared-encoder-approach-to-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Gadolinium-Free MRI Synthesis: A Transformer with Localization Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-gadolinium-free-mri-synthesis-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrast-enhanced magnetic resonance imaging (CE-MRI) is crucial for tumor detection and diagnosis, but the use of gadolinium-based contrast agents (GBCAs) in clinical settings raises safety concerns due to potential health risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-gadolinium-free-mri-synthesis-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality Measures for Dynamic Graph Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-measures-for-dynamic-graph-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This results in an expressive, scalar, and application-agnostic measure of dynamic graph similarity that overcomes the limitations of traditional methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quality-measures-for-dynamic-graph-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Leaf-Level Dataset for Soybean-Cotton Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-leaf-level-dataset-for-soybean-cotton</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Soybean and cotton are major drivers of many countries' agricultural sectors, offering substantial economic returns but also facing persistent challenges from volunteer plants and weeds that hamper sustainable management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-leaf-level-dataset-for-soybean-cotton</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoLUT: LUT-Based Image Super-Resolution with Automatic Sampling and Adaptive Residual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autolut-lut-based-image-super-resolution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, their reliance on fixed sampling patterns limits both accuracy and the ability to capture fine details in low-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autolut-lut-based-image-super-resolution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MRI super-resolution reconstruction using efficient diffusion probabilistic model with residual shifting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mri-super-resolution-reconstruction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective:This study introduces a residual error-shifting mechanism that drastically reduces sampling steps while preserving critical anatomical details, thus accelerating MRI reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mri-super-resolution-reconstruction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory-Class-Aware Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-class-aware-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically for (c), we introduce a trajectory-class predictor that performs agent-wise predictions on the trajectory class; and we design a trajectory-class representation model for each trajectory class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-class-aware-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot Affordance Grounding of Deformable Objects in Egocentric Organizing Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-affordance-grounding-of-deformable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deformable object manipulation in robotics presents significant challenges due to uncertainties in component properties, diverse configurations, visual interference, and ambiguous prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-affordance-grounding-of-deformable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Representation in a SOTIF-Related Use Case with Dempster-Shafer Theory for LiDAR Sensor-Based Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-representation-in-a-sotif-related</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty in LiDAR sensor-based object detection arises from environmental variability and sensor performance limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-representation-in-a-sotif-related</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cauchy-Schwarz Regularizers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cauchy-schwarz-regularizers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel class of regularization functions, called Cauchy-Schwarz (CS) regularizers, which can be designed to induce a wide range of properties in solution vectors of optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cauchy-schwarz-regularizers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Neural Network Potential for Energetic Materials with C, H, N, and O elements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-neural-network-potential-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work provides an efficient strategy for the design and development of HEMs and proposes a promising framework for integrating DFT, machine learning, and experimental methods in materials research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-neural-network-potential-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provable Benefits of Task-Specific Prompts for In-context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-benefits-of-task-specific-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The in-context learning capabilities of modern language models have motivated a deeper mathematical understanding of sequence models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-benefits-of-task-specific-prompts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSQ: Learning from Important Tokens Leads to Better Quantized LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsq-learning-from-important-tokens-leads-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this finding, we propose RSQ (Rotate, Scale, then Quantize), which (1) applies rotations (orthogonal transformation) to the model to mitigate outliers (those with exceptionally large magnitude), (2) scales the token feature based on its importance, and (3) quantizes the model using the GPTQ framework with the second-order statistics computed by scaled tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsq-learning-from-important-tokens-leads-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composed Multi-modal Retrieval: A Survey of Approaches and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composed-multi-modal-retrieval-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over time, retrieval techniques have evolved from Unimodal Retrieval (UR) to Cross-modal Retrieval (CR) and, more recently, to Composed Multi-modal Retrieval (CMR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composed-multi-modal-retrieval-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Spatial Reasoning Hard for VLMs? An Attention Mechanism Perspective on Focus Areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-is-spatial-reasoning-hard-for-vlms-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By tracing attention distribution over the image through out intermediate layers, we observe that successful spatial reasoning correlates strongly with the model's ability to align its attention distribution with actual object locations, particularly differing between familiar and unfamiliar spatial relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-is-spatial-reasoning-hard-for-vlms-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPGym Arcade: Parallel Pixelated POMDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popgym-arcade-parallel-pixelated-pomdps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce POPGym Arcade, a benchmark consisting of 7 pixel-based environments each with three difficulties, utilizing a single observation and action space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popgym-arcade-parallel-pixelated-pomdps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdSelect: Synthetic Instruction Data Selection with Multi-LLM Wisdom</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdselect-synthetic-instruction-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we investigate more diverse signals to capture comprehensive instruction-response pair characteristics and propose three foundational metrics that leverage Multi-LLM wisdom, informed by (1) diverse LLM responses and (2) reward model assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdselect-synthetic-instruction-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDC: Consistent Direct Time-of-Flight Video Depth Completion with Frequency Selective Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdc-consistent-direct-time-of-flight-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the manufacturing constraints of compact devices and the inherent physical principles of imaging, dToF depth maps are sparse and noisy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdc-consistent-direct-time-of-flight-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconciling Stochastic and Deterministic Strategies for Zero-shot Image Restoration using Diffusion Model in Dual</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-stochastic-and-deterministic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More recently, a sampling-based variant of this approach, which utilizes a pre-trained \textit{generative diffusion model}, has gained great popularity for solving IR problems through stochastic sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconciling-stochastic-and-deterministic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Can You Get Away with Low Memory Adam?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-can-you-get-away-with-low-memory-adam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While various low-memory optimizers have been proposed that sometimes match the performance of Adam, their lack of reliability has left Adam as the default choice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-can-you-get-away-with-low-memory-adam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architectural and Inferential Inductive Biases For Exchangeable Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-and-inferential-inductive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive models have emerged as a powerful framework for modeling exchangeable sequences - i. i. d.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-and-inferential-inductive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-NL Verifier: Leveraging Synthetic Data for Robust Knowledge Graph Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-nl-verifier-leveraging-synthetic-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach relies on large language models (LLMs) to generate semantically precise natural language paraphrases of structured queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-nl-verifier-leveraging-synthetic-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Perception: High-Resolution Image Perception Meets Visual RAG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-perception-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-resolution (HR) image perception remains a key challenge in multimodal large language models (MLLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-perception-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Data Selection for Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-data-selection-for-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, popular deployed instruction-tuned models often train on hundreds of thousands to millions of samples, subsampled from even larger data pools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-data-selection-for-instruction</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
