<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 09:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Adversarial Training at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, by training on DataComp-1B dataset, our AdvXL empowers a vanilla ViT-g model to substantially surpass the previous records of $l_{\infty}$-, $l_{2}$-, and $l_{1}$-robust accuracy by margins of 11. 4%, 14. 2% and 12. 9%, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUNA: A Framework for Language Understanding and Naturalness Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luna-a-framework-for-language-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of Natural Language Generation (NLG) models has gained increased attention, urging the development of metrics that evaluate various aspects of generated text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luna-a-framework-for-language-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Survival Trees: A Dynamic Programming Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-survival-trees-a-dynamic-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Survival analysis studies and predicts the time of death, or other singular unrepeated events, based on historical data, while the true time of death for some instances is unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-survival-trees-a-dynamic-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-aware Sampling for Long-tailed Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-sampling-for-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach allows the model to perceive the uncertainty of pseudo-labels at different training stages, thereby adaptively adjusting the selection thresholds for different classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-sampling-for-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Shot Audio to Audio Emotion Transfer With Speaker Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-audio-to-audio-emotion-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of audio-to-audio (A2A) style transfer involves replacing the style features of the source audio with those from the target audio while preserving the content related attributes of the source audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-audio-to-audio-emotion-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Feedback Network for Unsupervised Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-feedback-network-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Iterative Feedback Network (IFNet) for unsupervised point cloud registration, in which the representation of low-level features is efficiently enriched by rerouting subsequent high-level features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-feedback-network-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGNITE: Individualized GeNeration of Imputations in Time-series Electronic health records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignite-individualized-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In IGNITE, we further propose a novel individualized missingness mask (IMM), which helps our model generate values based on the individual's observed data and missingness patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignite-individualized-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Editing Can Hurt General Abilities of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-editing-can-hurt-general-abilities-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) have opened up new paradigms for accessing the knowledge stored in their parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-editing-can-hurt-general-abilities-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DepressionEmo: A novel dataset for multilabel classification of depression emotions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depressionemo-a-novel-dataset-for-multilabel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Across all emotions, the highest F1-Macro value is achieved by suicide intent, indicating a certain value of our dataset in identifying emotions in individuals with depression symptoms through text analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depressionemo-a-novel-dataset-for-multilabel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer-Learning-Based Autotuning Using Gaussian Copula</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-based-autotuning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the first generative TL-based autotuning approach based on the Gaussian copula (GC) to model the high-performing regions of the search space from prior data and then generate high-performing configurations for new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-based-autotuning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RomniStereo: Recurrent Omnidirectional Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/romnistereo-recurrent-omnidirectional-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap between OSM and RAFT, we mainly propose an opposite adaptive weighting scheme to seamlessly transform the outputs of spherical sweeping of OSM into the required inputs for the recurrent update, thus creating a recurrent omnidirectional stereo matching (RomniStereo) algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/romnistereo-recurrent-omnidirectional-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MST: Adaptive Multi-Scale Tokens Guided Interactive Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mst-adaptive-multi-scale-tokens-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm utilizes a differentiable top-k tokens selection mechanism, allowing for fewer tokens to be used while maintaining efficient multi-scale token interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mst-adaptive-multi-scale-tokens-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAMPAT: Low-Rank Adaption for Multilingual Paraphrasing Using Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lampat-low-rank-adaption-for-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Paraphrases are texts that convey the same meaning while using different words or sentence structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lampat-low-rank-adaption-for-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generic Knowledge Boosted Pre-training For Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-knowledge-boosted-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models are essential for scene classification, change detection, land cover segmentation, and other remote sensing image understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-knowledge-boosted-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Aerial Vision Guidance with Categorical 6D Pose Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-aerial-vision-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the real-world robot task of aerial vision guidance for aerial robotics manipulation, utilizing category-level 6-DoF pose tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-aerial-vision-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic emotion and sentiment modelling of patient-reported experiences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-emotion-and-sentiment-modelling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces a novel methodology for modelling patient emotions from online patient experience narratives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-emotion-and-sentiment-modelling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TechGPT-2.0: A large language model project to solve the task of knowledge graph construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/techgpt-2-0-a-large-language-model-project-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have exhibited robust performance across diverse natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/techgpt-2-0-a-large-language-model-project-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-Free Conformal Joint Prediction Regions for Neural Marked Temporal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-free-conformal-joint-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A primary objective is to generate a distribution-free joint prediction region for the arrival time and mark, with a finite-sample marginal coverage guarantee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-free-conformal-joint-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Robustness of Knowledge-Grounded Dialogue via Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-robustness-of-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge-grounded dialogue (KGD) learns to generate an informative response based on a given dialogue context and external knowledge (\emph{e. g.}, knowledge graphs; KGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-robustness-of-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapAI: Precision in Building Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapai-precision-in-building-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The competition will be held in the fall of 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapai-precision-in-building-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Baseline for Spoken Language to Sign Language Translation with 3D Avatars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-spoken-language-to-sign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of this paper is to develop a functional system for translating spoken languages into sign languages, referred to as Spoken2Sign translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-spoken-language-to-sign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DebugBench: Evaluating Debugging Capability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debugbench-evaluating-debugging-capability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous evaluations of LLMs' debugging ability are significantly limited by the risk of data leakage, the scale of the dataset, and the variety of tested bugs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debugbench-evaluating-debugging-capability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Content-Based Novelty Measure for Scholarly Publications: A Proof of Concept</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-content-based-novelty-measure-for-scholarly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Novelty, akin to gene mutation in evolution, opens possibilities for scientific advancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-content-based-novelty-measure-for-scholarly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-scale Empirical Study on Improving the Fairness of Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-study-on-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we target the widely-used application scenario of image classification, and utilized three different datasets and five commonly-used performance metrics to assess in total 13 methods from diverse categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-study-on-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIER: Text and Image Encoder-based Regression for AIGC Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-text-and-image-encoder-based-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we process the generated images and their corresponding text prompts as inputs, utilizing a text encoder and an image encoder to extract features from these text prompts and generated images, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-text-and-image-encoder-based-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Differential Privacy on Recommendation Accuracy and Popularity Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-differential-privacy-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study how DP impacts recommendation accuracy and popularity bias, when applied to the training data of state-of-the-art recommendation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-differential-privacy-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the structure of dynamic graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-structure-of-dynamic-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic graph embeddings, inductive and incremental learning facilitate predictive tasks such as node classification and link prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-structure-of-dynamic-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gramformer: Learning Crowd Counting via Graph-Modulated Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gramformer-learning-crowd-counting-via-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The graph is building upon the dissimilarities between patches, modulating the attention in an anti-similarity fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gramformer-learning-crowd-counting-via-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved motif-scaffolding with SE(3) flow matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-motif-scaffolding-with-se-3-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first is motif amortization, in which FrameFlow is trained with the motif as input using a data augmentation strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-motif-scaffolding-with-se-3-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A foundation for exact binarized morphological neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-for-exact-binarized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training and running deep neural networks (NNs) often demands a lot of computation and energy-intensive specialized hardware (e. g. GPU, TPU...).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-for-exact-binarized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining the Power of Topological Data Analysis in Graph Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-the-power-of-topological-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, claims regarding the power and usefulness of TDA have only been partially tested in application domains where TDA-based models are compared to other graph machine learning approaches, such as graph neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-the-power-of-topological-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of Neural Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-of-neural-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative AI and transfer learning fields have experienced remarkable advancements in recent years especially in the domain of Natural Language Processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-of-neural-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Test-Time Adaptation of Spatial-Temporal Traffic Flow Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-test-time-adaptation-of-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make the model trained on historical data better adapt to future data in a fully online manner, this paper conducts the first study of the online test-time adaptation techniques for spatial-temporal traffic flow forecasting problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-test-time-adaptation-of-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-light Image Enhancement via CLIP-Fourier Guided Wavelet Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-image-enhancement-via-clip-fourier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design a guided network with a multiscale visual language in the frequency domain based on the wavelet transform to achieve effective image enhancement iteratively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-image-enhancement-via-clip-fourier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4V(ision) is a Human-Aligned Evaluator for Text-to-3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-ision-is-a-human-aligned-evaluator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These metrics lack the flexibility to generalize to different evaluation criteria and might not align well with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4v-ision-is-a-human-aligned-evaluator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Attentional Networks with Self-emerging Token Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-attentional-networks-with-self-emerging-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proposed STL framework, our best model based on FAN-L-Hybrid (77. 3M parameters) achieves 84. 8% Top-1 accuracy and 42. 1% mCE on ImageNet-1K and ImageNet-C, and sets a new state-of-the-art for ImageNet-A (46. 1%) and ImageNet-R (56. 6%) without using extra data, outperforming the original FAN counterpart by significant margins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-attentional-networks-with-self-emerging-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechAgents: Human-Communication Simulation with Multi-Modal Multi-Agent Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechagents-human-communication-simulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose SpeechAgents, a multi-modal LLM based multi-agent system designed for simulating human communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechagents-human-communication-simulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARG: Multi-Agent Review Generation for Scientific Papers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marg-multi-agent-review-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the ability of LLMs to generate feedback for scientific papers and develop MARG, a feedback generation approach using multiple LLM instances that engage in internal discussion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marg-multi-agent-review-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using reinforcement learning to improve drone-based inference of greenhouse gas fluxes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-reinforcement-learning-to-improve-drone</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate mapping of greenhouse gas fluxes at the Earth's surface is essential for the validation and calibration of climate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-reinforcement-learning-to-improve-drone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Detection of Myopic Maculopathy in MMAC 2023: Achievements in Classification, Segmentation, and Spherical Equivalent Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-detection-of-myopic-maculopathy-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As for Task 3 (prediction of spherical equivalent), we have designed a deep regression model based on the data distribution of the dataset and employed an integration strategy to enhance the model's prediction accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-detection-of-myopic-maculopathy-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Analysis and Enhancements for Multi-Aspect Dense Retriever with Aspect Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-analysis-and-enhancements-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRAL was evaluated on proprietary data and its code was not released, making it challenging to validate its effectiveness on other datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-analysis-and-enhancements-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextMachina: Seamless Generation of Machine-Generated Text Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textmachina-seamless-generation-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have led to high-quality Machine-Generated Text (MGT), giving rise to countless new use cases and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textmachina-seamless-generation-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scDiffusion: conditional generation of high-quality single-cell data using diffusion model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scdiffusion-conditional-generation-of-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments showed that scDiffusion can generate single-cell gene expression data closely resembling real scRNA-seq data, surpassing state-of-the-art models in multiple metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scdiffusion-conditional-generation-of-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification on Clinical Trial Outcome Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-on-clinical-trial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selective classification, encompassing a spectrum of methods for uncertainty quantification, empowers the model to withhold decision-making in the face of samples marked by ambiguity or low confidence, thereby amplifying the accuracy of predictions for the instances it chooses to classify.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-on-clinical-trial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Efficient and Effective OpenQA Systems for Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-efficient-and-effective-openqa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SQuAD-TR, a machine translation of SQuAD2. 0, and we build our OpenQA system by adapting ColBERT-QA for Turkish.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-efficient-and-effective-openqa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpecRef: A Fast Training-free Baseline of Specific Reference-Condition Real Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specref-a-fast-training-free-baseline-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To increase user freedom, we propose a new task called Specific Reference Condition Real Image Editing, which allows user to provide a reference image to further control the outcome, such as replacing an object with a particular one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specref-a-fast-training-free-baseline-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soaring from 4K to 400K: Extending LLM's Context with Activation Beacon</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soaring-from-4k-to-400k-extending-llm-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the context window can be extended through fine-tuning, it will result in a considerable cost at both training and inference time, and exert an unfavorable impact to the LLM's original capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soaring-from-4k-to-400k-extending-llm-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Representation Learning for Molecular Property Prediction: Sequence, Graph, Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-representation-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular property prediction refers to the task of labeling molecules with some biochemical properties, playing a pivotal role in the drug discovery and design process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-representation-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BCLNet: Bilateral Consensus Learning for Two-View Correspondence Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bclnet-bilateral-consensus-learning-for-two</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our approach, we design a distinctive self-attention block to capture global context and parallel process it with the established local context learning module, which enables us to simultaneously capture both local and global consensuses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bclnet-bilateral-consensus-learning-for-two</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escalation Risks from Language Models in Military and Diplomatic Decision-Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escalation-risks-from-language-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Governments are increasingly considering integrating autonomous AI agents in high-stakes military and foreign-policy decision-making, especially with the emergence of advanced generative AI models like GPT-4.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escalation-risks-from-language-models-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
