<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 21:06:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MILA: Memory-Based Instance-Level Adaptation for Cross-Domain Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mila-memory-based-instance-level-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A source sample is considered suitable if it differs from the target sample only in domain, without differences in unimportant characteristics such as orientation and color, which can hinder the model’s focus on aligning the domain difference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mila-memory-based-instance-level-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynaPipe: Optimizing Multi-task Training through Dynamic Pipelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynapipe-optimizing-multi-task-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a dynamic micro-batching approach to tackle sequence length variation and enable efficient multi-task model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynapipe-optimizing-multi-task-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOCAL: A Cost-Aware Video Dataset for Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focal-a-cost-aware-video-dataset-for-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the FOCAL (Ford-OLIVES Collaboration on Active Learning) dataset which enables the study of the impact of annotation-cost within a video active learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focal-a-cost-aware-video-dataset-for-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniMOS: A Universal Framework For Multi-Organ Segmentation Over Label-Constrained Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimos-a-universal-framework-for-multi-organ</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the fact that medical image annotation requires a great deal of manpower and expertise, as well as the fact that clinical departments perform image annotation based on task orientation, there is the problem of having fewer medical image annotation data with more unlabeled data and having many datasets that annotate only a single organ.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimos-a-universal-framework-for-multi-organ</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized Energy Marketplace via NFTs and AI-based Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-energy-marketplace-via-nfts-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper introduces an advanced Decentralized Energy Marketplace (DEM) integrating blockchain technology and artificial intelligence to manage energy exchanges among smart homes with energy storage systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-energy-marketplace-via-nfts-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Multimodal Fusion for Enhanced Diagnosis of Multiple Retinal Diseases in Ultra-wide OCTA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-fusion-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The construction of the M3OCTA dataset, the first multimodal OCTA dataset encompassing multiple diseases, aims to advance research in the ophthalmic image analysis community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multimodal-fusion-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using linear initialisation to improve speed of convergence and fully-trained error in Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-linear-initialisation-to-improve-speed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Good weight initialisation is an important step in successful training of Artificial Neural Networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-linear-initialisation-to-improve-speed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EduGym: An Environment Suite for Reinforcement Learning Education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edugym-an-environment-suite-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this issue we introduce EduGym, a set of educational reinforcement learning environments and associated interactive notebooks tailored for education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edugym-an-environment-suite-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex2Vec: Characterizing Users and Items from the Mere Exposure Effect</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ex2vec-characterizing-users-and-items-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since previous research has shown that the magnitude of the effect depends on a number of interesting factors such as stimulus complexity and familiarity, leveraging this effect is a way to not only improve repeated recommendation but to gain a more in-depth understanding of both users and stimuli.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ex2vec-characterizing-users-and-items-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Pool based Class-Incremental Continual Learning for Dialog State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-pool-based-class-incremental-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the recently emerging prompt tuning method that performs well on dialog systems, we propose to use the prompt pool method, where we maintain a pool of key-value paired prompts and select prompts from the pool according to the distance between the dialog history and the prompt keys.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-pool-based-class-incremental-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric Teaching for Multiple Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-teaching-for-multiple-learners</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In MINT, the teacher aims to instruct multiple learners, with each learner focusing on learning a scalar-valued target model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-teaching-for-multiple-learners</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation-Distance Graph Learning for Treatment Response Prediction from rs-fMRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-distance-graph-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome that, we propose a graph learning framework that captures comprehensive features by integrating both correlation and distance-based similarity measures under a contrastive loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-distance-graph-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Maximum a Posteriori Filtering via Adaptive Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-maximum-a-posteriori-filtering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian filtering approximates the true underlying behavior of a time-varying system by inverting an explicit generative model to convert noisy measurements into state estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-maximum-a-posteriori-filtering-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct Amortized Likelihood Ratio Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-amortized-likelihood-ratio-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our estimator is simple to train and estimates the likelihood ratio using a single forward pass of the neural estimator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-amortized-likelihood-ratio-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling and Retrieving Generalizable Knowledge for Robot Manipulation via Language Corrections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-and-retrieving-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DROC is able to respond to a sequence of online language corrections that address failures in both high-level task plans and low-level skill primitives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-and-retrieving-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Principle to Practice: Vertical Data Minimization for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-principle-to-practice-vertical-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel vertical DM (vDM) workflow based on data generalization, which by design ensures that no full-resolution client data is collected during training and deployment of models, benefiting client privacy by reducing the attack surface in case of a breach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-principle-to-practice-vertical-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Word-based Pre-trained Item Representation for Transferable Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-word-based-pre-trained-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CoWPiRec, an approach of Collaborative Word-based Pre-trained item representation for Recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-word-based-pre-trained-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Sparsifications using Neural Network Assisted Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sparsifications-using-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks have been successful for machine learning, as well as for combinatorial and graph problems such as the Subgraph Isomorphism Problem and the Traveling Salesman Problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sparsifications-using-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks for Pressure Estimation in Water Distribution Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-pressure-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our GNN-based model estimates the pressure of a large-scale WDN in The Netherlands with a MAE of 1. 94mH$_2$O and a MAPE of 7%, surpassing the performance of previous studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-pressure-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo Label-Guided Data Fusion and Output Consistency for Semi-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-label-guided-data-fusion-and-output</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by semi-supervised algorithms that use both labeled and unlabeled data for training, we propose the PLGDF framework, which builds upon the mean teacher network for segmenting medical images with less annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-label-guided-data-fusion-and-output</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDMPP: A Device-Model Agnostic Framework for Latency Prediction of Tensor Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdmpp-a-device-model-agnostic-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the large space of DNN models and devices that impede direct profiling of all combinations, recent efforts focus on building a predictor to model the performance of DNN models on different devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdmpp-a-device-model-agnostic-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedAgents: Large Language Models as Collaborators for Zero-shot Medical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medagents-large-language-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs), despite their remarkable progress across various general domains, encounter significant barriers in medicine and healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medagents-large-language-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of a block structure on the Lotka-Volterra model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-a-block-structure-on-the-lotka</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the important case of two communities of interacting species, study how interactions affect their respective equilibrium.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-a-block-structure-on-the-lotka</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JaxMARL: Multi-Agent RL Environments in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxmarl-multi-agent-rl-environments-in-jax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This not only enables GPU acceleration, but also provides a more flexible MARL environment, unlocking the potential for self-play, meta-learning, and other future applications in MARL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxmarl-multi-agent-rl-environments-in-jax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfriMTE and AfriCOMET: Empowering COMET to Embrace Under-resourced African Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrimte-and-africomet-empowering-comet-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we develop AfriCOMET, a COMET evaluation metric for African languages by leveraging DA training data from high-resource languages and African-centric multilingual encoder (AfroXLM-Roberta) to create the state-of-the-art evaluation metric for African languages MT with respect to Spearman-rank correlation with human judgments (+0. 406).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrimte-and-africomet-empowering-comet-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERVENOR: Prompt the Coding Ability of Large Language Models with the Interactive Chain of Repairing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervenor-prompt-the-coding-ability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Code Learner is asked to generate and repair code according to the instructions from the Code Teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervenor-prompt-the-coding-ability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenkai -- Framework For Exploring Beyond Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenkai-framework-for-exploring-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zenkai aims to make it easier to get around these limitations and help researchers more easily explore new frontiers in deep learning that do not strictly adhere to the backpropagation framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenkai-framework-for-exploring-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center Focusing Network for Real-Time LiDAR Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-focusing-network-for-real-time-lidar-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR panoptic segmentation facilitates an autonomous vehicle to comprehensively understand the surrounding objects and scenes and is required to run in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-focusing-network-for-real-time-lidar-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don't need a personality test to know these models are unreliable: Assessing the Reliability of Large Language Models on Psychometric Instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-don-t-need-a-personality-test-to-know</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The versatility of Large Language Models (LLMs) on natural language understanding tasks has made them popular for research in social sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-don-t-need-a-personality-test-to-know</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Symbolic Integration Brings Causal and Reliable Reasoning Proofs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-integration-brings-causal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though prompting LLMs with various reasoning structures produces reasoning proofs along with answers, these proofs are not ensured to be causal and reliable due to the inherent defects of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-integration-brings-causal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLNet: Scale-Modulated Query and Localization Network for Few-Shot Class-Agnostic Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlnet-scale-modulated-query-and-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the localization stage, the Scale-aware Multi-head Localization (SAML) module utilizes the query tensor to predict the confidence, location, and size of each potential object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlnet-scale-modulated-query-and-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention-Based Denoising Framework for Personality Detection in Social Media Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-denoising-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In social media networks, users produce a large amount of text content anytime, providing researchers with a valuable approach to digging for personality-related information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-denoising-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facilitating the sharing of electrophysiology data analysis results through in-depth provenance capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facilitating-the-sharing-of-electrophysiology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Alpaca (Automated Lightweight Provenance Capture), a tool that captures fine-grained provenance information with minimal user intervention when running data analysis pipelines implemented in Python scripts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facilitating-the-sharing-of-electrophysiology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurvTimeSurvival: Survival Analysis On The Patient With Multiple Visits/Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survtimesurvival-survival-analysis-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces "SurvTimeSurvival: Survival Analysis On Patients With Multiple Visits/Records", utilizing the Transformer model to not only handle the complexities of time-varying covariates but also covariates data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survtimesurvival-survival-analysis-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLT: Can Large Language Models Handle Basic Legal Text?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blt-can-large-language-models-handle-basic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the best publicly available LLMs like GPT-4 and PaLM 2 currently perform poorly at basic text handling required of lawyers or paralegals, such as looking up the text at a line of a witness deposition or at a subsection of a contract.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blt-can-large-language-models-handle-basic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICXML: An In-Context Learning Framework for Zero-Shot Extreme Multi-Label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icxml-an-in-context-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the task of Extreme Multi-Label Classification (XMC) whose goal is to predict multiple labels for each instance from an extremely large label space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icxml-an-in-context-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Constitutes a Faithful Summary? Preserving Author Perspectives in News Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-constitutes-a-faithful-summary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a first step towards designing summarization systems that are faithful to the author's opinions and perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-constitutes-a-faithful-summary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-LLaVA: Learning United Visual Representation by Alignment Before Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-llava-learning-united-visual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we unify visual representation into the language feature space to advance the foundational LLM towards a unified LVLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-llava-learning-united-visual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining the Laparoscopic Spatial Sense: AI-based Intra- and Postoperative Measurement from Stereoimages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redefining-the-laparoscopic-spatial-sense-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant challenge in image-guided surgery is the accurate measurement task of relevant structures such as vessel segments, resection margins, or bowel lengths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redefining-the-laparoscopic-spatial-sense-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PWISeg: Point-based Weakly-supervised Instance Segmentation for Surgical Instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwiseg-point-based-weakly-supervised-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel yet effective weakly-supervised surgical instrument instance segmentation approach, named Point-based Weakly-supervised Instance Segmentation (PWISeg).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwiseg-point-based-weakly-supervised-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARES: An Automated Evaluation Framework for Retrieval-Augmented Generation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-an-automated-evaluation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) systems traditionally relies on hand annotations for input queries, passages to retrieve, and responses to generate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-an-automated-evaluation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFPS: A unified framework for partially-annotated federated segmentation in heterogeneous data distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufps-a-unified-framework-for-partially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Unified Federated Partially-labeled Segmentation (UFPS) framework to segment pixels within all classes for partially-annotated datasets by training a totipotential global model without class collision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufps-a-unified-framework-for-partially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inherently Interpretable Time Series Classification via Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherently-interpretable-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional Time Series Classification (TSC) methods are often black boxes that obscure inherent interpretation of their decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherently-interpretable-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Evaluation and Insights into the Use of Deep Neural Networks to Detect and Quantify Lymphoma Lesions in PET/CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-and-insights-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study performs comprehensive evaluation of four neural network architectures (UNet, SegResNet, DynUNet, and SwinUNETR) for lymphoma lesion segmentation from PET/CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-and-insights-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Song Describer Dataset: a Corpus of Audio Captions for Music-and-Language Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-song-describer-dataset-a-corpus-of-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Song Describer dataset (SDD), a new crowdsourced corpus of high-quality audio-caption pairs, designed for the evaluation of music-and-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-song-describer-dataset-a-corpus-of-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reevaluation of Event Extraction: Past, Present, and Future Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reevaluation-of-event-extraction-past</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first identify and discuss these evaluation challenges, including the unfair comparisons resulting from different assumptions about data or different data preprocessing steps, the incompleteness of the current evaluation framework leading to potential dataset bias or data split bias, and low reproducibility of prior studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reevaluation-of-event-extraction-past</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pachinko: Patching Interpretable QA Models through Natural Language Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pachinko-patching-interpretable-qa-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first one, we present users with incorrect answers and corresponding rationales of various formats and ask them to provide natural language feedback to revise the rationale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pachinko-patching-interpretable-qa-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Can We Extract Diverse Perspectives from Large Language Models? Criteria-Based Diversity Prompting!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-extract-diverse-perspectives</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate this problem as diversity extraction in LLMs and propose a criteria-based prompting technique to ground diverse opinions and measure perspective diversity from the generated criteria words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-extract-diverse-perspectives</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On some elusive aspects of databases hindering AI based discovery: A case study on superconducting materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-some-elusive-aspects-of-databases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It stands to reason that the amount and the quality of big data is of key importance for setting up accurate AI-driven models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-some-elusive-aspects-of-databases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepEMD: A Transformer-based Fast Estimation of the Earth Mover's Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepemd-a-transformer-based-fast-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an attention-based model to compute an accurate approximation of the EMD that can be used as a training loss for generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepemd-a-transformer-based-fast-estimation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
