<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 09:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-personalized-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a distributed machine learning approach in which a single server and multiple clients collaboratively build machine learning models without sharing datasets on clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-personalized-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A penalisation method for batch multi-objective Bayesian optimisation with application in heat exchanger design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalisation-method-for-batch-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present HIghly Parallelisable Pareto Optimisation (HIPPO) -- a batch acquisition function that enables multi-objective Bayesian optimisation methods to efficiently exploit parallel processing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-penalisation-method-for-batch-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning of Dynamical Systems with Competitive Federated Reservoir Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-dynamical-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results suggest that reservoir computing is a promising candidate framework for the continual learning of dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-dynamical-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Stochastic Petri Net-based Remaining Time Prediction using k-Nearest Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-stochastic-petri-net-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For realising timely delivery, an accurate prediction of the remaining time of the delivery process is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-stochastic-petri-net-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Calibration for Deep Audio Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-for-deep-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the uncertainty calibration for deep audio classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-calibration-for-deep-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchopt: Reproducible, efficient and collaborative optimization benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchopt-reproducible-efficient-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical validation is at the core of machine learning research as it allows to assess the actual impact of new methods, and to confirm the agreement between theory and practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchopt-reproducible-efficient-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Split Localized Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-localized-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The modified score inherits the spirit of split conformal methods, which is simple and efficient compared with full conformal methods but better approximates conditional coverage guarantee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/split-localized-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Stability Well Predicts Performance of Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-stability-well-predicts-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first give the interpretation of zero stability in the context of deep learning and then investigate the performance of existing first- and second-order CNNs under different zero-stable circumstances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-stability-well-predicts-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centralized and Decentralized Control in Modular Robots and Their Effect on Morphology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-and-decentralized-control-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, if these findings translate to other robot systems, our results and issues encountered can help future researchers make a choice of control method when co-optimizing morphology and control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centralized-and-decentralized-control-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights into Deep Non-linear Filters for Improved Multi-channel Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-deep-non-linear-filters-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key advantage of using multiple microphones for speech enhancement is that spatial filtering can be used to complement the tempo-spectral processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-deep-non-linear-filters-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Deep Input-Output Stable Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-input-output-stable-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method to learn nonlinear systems guaranteeing the input-output stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-deep-input-output-stable-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Semantic Annotations of SMCalFlow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-semantic-annotations-of-smcalflow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SMCalFlow is a large corpus of semantically detailed annotations of task-oriented natural dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-semantic-annotations-of-smcalflow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Representation Learning Framework for Property Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-representation-learning-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning on graphs, also called graph embedding, has demonstrated its significant impact on a series of machine learning applications such as classification, prediction and recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-representation-learning-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditing Visualizations: Transparency Methods Struggle to Detect Anomalous Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-visualizations-transparency-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transparency methods such as model visualizations provide information that outputs alone might miss, since they describe the internals of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-visualizations-transparency-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Bank Learning for Semi-supervised Federated Image Diagnosis with Class Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-bank-learning-for-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent progress on semi-supervised federated learning (FL) for medical image diagnosis, the problem of imbalanced class distributions among unlabeled clients is still unsolved for real-world use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-bank-learning-for-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and Improving the Use of Graph Information in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-improving-the-use-of-graph-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have been widely used for representation learning on graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-improving-the-use-of-graph-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Control Local Search for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-local-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial optimization problems are encountered in many practical contexts such as logistics and production, but exact solutions are particularly difficult to find and usually NP-hard for considerable problem sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-control-local-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBISCape: A Simulated Benchmark for multi-modal SLAM Systems Evaluation in Large-scale Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibiscape-a-simulated-benchmark-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keywords: benchmark, multi-modal, datasets, Odometry, Calibration, DVS, SLAM]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibiscape-a-simulated-benchmark-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pen and Paper Exercises in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pen-and-paper-exercises-in-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a collection of (mostly) pen-and-paper exercises in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pen-and-paper-exercises-in-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic identification of segmentation errors for radiotherapy using geometric learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-identification-of-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed model is trained using self-supervised learning using a synthetically-generated dataset of segmentations of the parotid and with realistic contouring errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-identification-of-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Recipe for Likelihood-free Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-recipe-for-likelihood-free-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To extend BO to a broader class of models and utilities, we propose likelihood-free BO (LFBO), an approach based on likelihood-free inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-recipe-for-likelihood-free-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iExam: A Novel Online Exam Monitoring and Analysis System Based on Face Detection and Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iexam-a-novel-online-exam-monitoring-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose iExam, an intelligent online exam monitoring and analysis system that can not only use face detection to assist invigilators in real-time student identification, but also be able to detect common abnormal behaviors (including face disappearing, rotating faces, and replacing with a different person during the exams) via a face recognition-based post-exam video analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iexam-a-novel-online-exam-monitoring-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Weak Annotations for Robust Maritime Obstacle Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-weak-annotations-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments show that maritime obstacle segmentation networks trained using SLR on weak labels not only match, but outperform the same networks trained with dense ground truth labels, which is a remarkable result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-weak-annotations-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Learning in Remote Sensing: A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-in-remote-sensing-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In deep learning research, self-supervised learning (SSL) has received great attention triggering interest within both the computer vision and remote sensing communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-in-remote-sensing-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iso-CapsNet: Isomorphic Capsule Network for Brain Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iso-capsnet-isomorphic-capsule-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain graph representation learning serves as the fundamental technique for brain diseases diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iso-capsnet-isomorphic-capsule-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency-preserving Visual Question Answering in Medical Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-preserving-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Question Answering (VQA) models take an image and a natural-language question as input and infer the answer to the question.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-preserving-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGNet: Monocular Geometric Scene Understanding for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgnet-monocular-geometric-scene-understanding-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define monocular geometric scene understanding as the combination of two known tasks: Panoptic segmentation and self-supervised monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgnet-monocular-geometric-scene-understanding-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RES: A Robust Framework for Guiding Visual Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/res-a-robust-framework-for-guiding-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the fast progress of explanation techniques in modern Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) where the main focus is handling "how to generate the explanations", advanced research questions that examine the quality of the explanation itself (e. g., "whether the explanations are accurate") and improve the explanation quality (e. g., "how to adjust the model to generate more accurate explanations when explanations are inaccurate") are still relatively under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/res-a-robust-framework-for-guiding-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$u^* = \sqrt{uv}$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-sqrt-uv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The nonproductive use of labor is well measured by the number of jobseekers and vacancies, $u + v$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-sqrt-uv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to Trust Your Simulator: Dynamics-Aware Hybrid Offline-and-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-trust-your-simulator-dynamics-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This brings up a new question: is it possible to combine learning from limited real data in offline RL and unrestricted exploration through imperfect simulators in online RL to address the drawbacks of both approaches?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-trust-your-simulator-dynamics-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARNet: Semantic Augmented Registration of Large-Scale Urban Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarnet-semantic-augmented-registration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Registering urban point clouds is a quite challenging task due to the large-scale, noise and data incompleteness of LiDAR scanning data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarnet-semantic-augmented-registration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Fast, Segment Well: Fast Object Segmentation Learning on the iCub Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-fast-segment-well-fast-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on the instance segmentation task and provide a comprehensive study of different techniques that allow adapting an object segmentation model in presence of novel objects or different domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-fast-segment-well-fast-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Spatial Temporal Graph Convolutional Network for Skeleton-Based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-spatial-temporal-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, we present a multi-scale spatial graph convolution (MS-GC) module and a multi-scale temporal graph convolution (MT-GC) module to enrich the receptive field of the model in spatial and temporal dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-spatial-temporal-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankSEG: A Consistent Ranking-based Framework for Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankseg-a-consistent-ranking-based-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we establish a theoretical foundation of segmentation with respect to the Dice/IoU metrics, including the Bayes rule and Dice/IoU-calibration, analogous to classification-calibration or Fisher consistency in classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankseg-a-consistent-ranking-based-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel Attention Transformer (KAT) for Histopathology Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-attention-transformer-kat-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer has been widely used in histopathology whole slide image (WSI) classification for the purpose of tumor grading, prognosis analysis, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-attention-transformer-kat-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Representation Alignment and Uniformity in Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-representation-alignment-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we empirically analyze the learning dynamics of typical CF methods in terms of quantified alignment and uniformity, which shows that better alignment or uniformity both contribute to higher recommendation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-representation-alignment-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repository-Level Prompt Generation for Large Language Models of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repository-level-prompt-generation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the success of large language models (LLMs) of code and their use as code assistants (e. g. Codex used in GitHub Copilot), techniques for introducing domain-specific knowledge in the prompt design process become important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repository-level-prompt-generation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Instance Learning with Mixed Supervision in Gleason Grading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-with-mixed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve the state-of-the-art performance on the SICAPv2 dataset, and the visual analysis shows the accurate prediction results of instance level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-with-mixed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Aesthetics Assessment Using Graph Attention Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-aesthetics-assessment-using-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a graph neural network architecture that takes this feature-graph and captures the semantic relationship between the different regions of the input image using visual attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-aesthetics-assessment-using-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Healing Robust Neural Networks via Closed-Loop Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-healing-robust-neural-networks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While numerous attack and defense techniques have been developed, this work investigates the robustness issue from a new angle: can we design a self-healing neural network that can automatically detect and fix the vulnerability issue by itself?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-healing-robust-neural-networks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Generation of Product-Image Sequence in E-commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-generation-of-product-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a platform with billions of products, it is extremely time-costly and labor-expensive to manually pick and organize qualified images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-generation-of-product-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual embedding and model weighting by fusing domain knowledge on Biomedical Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-embedding-and-model-weighting-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Biomedical Question Answering aims to obtain an answer to the given question from the biomedical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-embedding-and-model-weighting-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLCap: Vision-Language with Contrastive Learning for Coherent Video Paragraph Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlcap-vision-language-with-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we leverage the human perceiving process, that involves vision and language interaction, to generate a coherent paragraph description of untrimmed videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlcap-vision-language-with-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning neural state-space models: do we need a state estimator?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-neural-state-space-models-do-we-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, several algorithms for system identification with neural state-space models have been introduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-neural-state-space-models-do-we-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Variate Time Series Forecasting on Variable Subsets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-variate-time-series-forecasting-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through systematic experiments across 4 datasets and 5 forecast models, we show that our technique is able to recover close to 95\% performance of the models even when only 15\% of the original variables are present.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-variate-time-series-forecasting-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEVR: Improving Speech Recognition by Token Entropy Variance Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tevr-improving-speech-recognition-by-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents TEVR, a speech recognition model designed to minimize the variation in token entropy w. r. t.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tevr-improving-speech-recognition-by-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-aware Generalization of Decentralized SGD</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-generalization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the algorithmic stability and generalizability of decentralized stochastic gradient descent (D-SGD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-generalization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy-Guided Weakly-Supervised Abnormality Localization in Chest X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-guided-weakly-supervised-abnormality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The critical component in our framework is an anatomy-guided attention module that aids the downstream observation network in focusing on the relevant anatomical regions generated by the anatomy network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-guided-weakly-supervised-abnormality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Semantic Answer Similarity Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-semantic-answer-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To build robust QA systems, we need the ability to have equivalently robust evaluation systems to verify whether model predictions to questions are similar to ground-truth annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-semantic-answer-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Diverse Vocal Bursts with StyleGAN2 and MEL-Spectrograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-diverse-vocal-bursts-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe our approach for the generative emotional vocal burst task (ExVo Generate) of the ICML Expressive Vocalizations Competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-diverse-vocal-bursts-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
