<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 21:08:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Steerers: Leveraging K-Sparse Autoencoders for Controllable Generations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-steerers-leveraging-k-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the remarkable progress in text-to-image generative models, they are prone to adversarial attacks and inadvertently generate unsafe, unethical content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-steerers-leveraging-k-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>s1: Simple test-time scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s1-simple-test-time-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After supervised finetuning the Qwen2. 5-32B-Instruct language model on s1K and equipping it with budget forcing, our model s1 exceeds o1-preview on competition math questions by up to 27% (MATH and AIME24).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s1-simple-test-time-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KBQA-o1: Agentic Knowledge Base Question Answering with Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kbqa-o1-agentic-knowledge-base-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, it employs MCTS, a heuristic search method driven by policy and reward models, to balance agentic exploration's performance and search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kbqa-o1-agentic-knowledge-base-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XRF V2: A Dataset for Action Summarization with Wi-Fi Signals, and IMUs in Phones, Watches, Earbuds, and Glasses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xrf-v2-a-dataset-for-action-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human Action Recognition (HAR) plays a crucial role in applications such as health monitoring, smart home automation, and human-computer interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xrf-v2-a-dataset-for-action-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Reasoning Gap: Small LLMs Can Plan with Generalised Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-reasoning-gap-small-llms-can</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our empirical results from planning and mathematical reasoning tasks demonstrate that these methods improve the performance of less resource-intensive LLMs to levels comparable with their more resource-intensive counterparts, at a fraction of the cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-reasoning-gap-small-llms-can</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single cell resolution 3D imaging and segmentation within intact live tissues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-cell-resolution-3d-imaging-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Epithelial cells form diverse structures from squamous spherical organoids to densely packed pseudostratified tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-cell-resolution-3d-imaging-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\infty$-Video: A Training-Free Approach to Long Video Understanding via Continuous-Time Memory Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infty-video-a-training-free-approach-to-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current video-language models struggle with long-video understanding due to limited context lengths and reliance on sparse frame subsampling, often leading to information loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infty-video-a-training-free-approach-to-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Early Stopping: Refine, Then Calibrate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-early-stopping-refine-then</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning classifiers often produce probabilistic predictions that are critical for accurate and interpretable decision-making in various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-early-stopping-refine-then</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vintix: Action Model via In-Context Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vintix-action-model-via-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-Context Reinforcement Learning (ICRL) represents a promising paradigm for developing generalist agents that learn at inference time through trial-and-error interactions, analogous to how large language models adapt contextually, but with a focus on reward maximization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vintix-action-model-via-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding-based Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-based-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models have recently been shown capable of performing regression tasks wherein numeric predictions are represented as decoded strings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-based-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic Targets for Concept Erasure in Diffusion Models and Where To Find Them</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-targets-for-concept-erasure-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we model the concept space as a graph and empirically analyze the effects of erasing one concept on the remaining concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-targets-for-concept-erasure-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Dense Endoscopic Reconstruction with Gaussian Splatting-driven Surface Normal-aware Tracking and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-dense-endoscopic-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endo-2DTAM incorporates a surface normal-aware pipeline, which consists of tracking, mapping, and bundle adjustment modules for geometrically accurate reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-dense-endoscopic-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VKFPos: A Learning-Based Monocular Positioning with Variational Bayesian Extended Kalman Filter Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vkfpos-a-learning-based-monocular-positioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the challenges in learning-based monocular positioning by proposing VKFPos, a novel approach that integrates Absolute Pose Regression (APR) and Relative Pose Regression (RPR) via an Extended Kalman Filter (EKF) within a variational Bayesian inference framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vkfpos-a-learning-based-monocular-positioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm-Gen: Fast Generation of Diverse Feasible Swarm Behaviors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swarm-gen-fast-generation-of-diverse-feasible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thecinitialization network is trained in a self-supervised manner, taking advantage of the differentiability of the SF solver.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swarm-gen-fast-generation-of-diverse-feasible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context Matters: Query-aware Dynamic Long Sequence Modeling of Gigapixel Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-matters-query-aware-dynamic-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whole slide image (WSI) analysis presents significant computational challenges due to the massive number of patches in gigapixel images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-matters-query-aware-dynamic-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabFSBench: Tabular Benchmark for Feature Shifts in Open Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabfsbench-tabular-benchmark-for-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TabFSBench evaluates impacts of four distinct feature-shift scenarios on four tabular model categories across various datasets and assesses the performance of large language models (LLMs) and tabular LLMs in the tabular benchmark for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabfsbench-tabular-benchmark-for-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Noise in Differentially Private Text Rewriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-noise-in-differentially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of text privatization often leverages the notion of $\textit{Differential Privacy}$ (DP) to provide formal guarantees in the rewriting or obfuscation of sensitive textual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-noise-in-differentially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Inverse Problem for Multi-armed Bandits via Convex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-inverse-problem-for-multi-armed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the inverse problem of multi-armed bandits (IMAB) that are widely used in neuroscience and psychology research for behavior modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-inverse-problem-for-multi-armed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Diffusion Posterior Sampling: From Conditional Score Estimator to Maximizing a Posterior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-posterior-sampling-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in diffusion models have been leveraged to address inverse problems without additional training, and Diffusion Posterior Sampling (DPS) (Chung et al., 2022a) is among the most popular approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-diffusion-posterior-sampling-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secured Communication Schemes for UAVs in 5G: CRYSTALS-Kyber and IDS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secured-communication-schemes-for-uavs-in-5g</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating CRYSTALS-Kyber, the framework mitigates vulnerabilities in ECC against quantum attacks, positioning it as a quantum-resistant alternative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secured-communication-schemes-for-uavs-in-5g</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSTI: Consistency Models for (a faster) Spatio-Temporal Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costi-consistency-models-for-a-faster-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate Time Series Imputation (MTSI) is crucial for many applications, such as healthcare monitoring and traffic management, where incomplete data can compromise decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costi-consistency-models-for-a-faster-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond checkmate: exploring the creative chokepoints in AI text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-checkmate-exploring-the-creative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have revolutionized Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Artificial Intelligence (AI), unlocking unprecedented capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-checkmate-exploring-the-creative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIGNO: A Graph-based framework for robust and accurate operator learning for PDEs on arbitrary domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigno-a-graph-based-framework-for-robust-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model, termed RIGNO, is tested on a challenging suite of benchmarks, composed of various time-dependent and steady PDEs defined on a diverse set of domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigno-a-graph-based-framework-for-robust-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distorting Embedding Space for Safety: A Defense Mechanism for Adversarially Robust Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distorting-embedding-space-for-safety-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DES transforms unsafe embeddings, extracted from a text encoder using unsafe prompts, toward carefully calculated safe embedding regions to prevent unsafe contents generation, while reproducing the original safe embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distorting-embedding-space-for-safety-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMDet: Learning Strong Open-Vocabulary Object Detectors under the Supervision of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmdet-learning-strong-open-vocabulary-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that an open-vocabulary detector co-training with a large language model by generating image-level detailed captions for each image can further improve performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmdet-learning-strong-open-vocabulary-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GestureLSM: Latent Shortcut based Co-Speech Gesture Generation with Spatial-Temporal Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gesturelsm-latent-shortcut-based-co-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive quantitative and qualitative experiments demonstrate the effectiveness of GestureLSM, showcasing its potential for various applications in the development of digital humans and embodied agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gesturelsm-latent-shortcut-based-co-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-scale Representation Guided Network for Retinal Vessel Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-scale-representation-guided-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Passing full-scale information to the attention block allows for the generation of improved attention maps, which are then passed to the attention-guided filter, resulting in performance enhancement of the segmentation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-scale-representation-guided-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PathE: Leveraging Entity-Agnostic Paths for Parameter-Efficient Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathe-leveraging-entity-agnostic-paths-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is often done by allocating and learning embedding tables for all or a subset of the entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathe-leveraging-entity-agnostic-paths-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DINAMO: Dynamic and INterpretable Anomaly MOnitoring for Large-Scale Particle Physics Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dinamo-dynamic-and-interpretable-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring reliable data collection in large-scale particle physics experiments demands Data Quality Monitoring (DQM) procedures to detect possible detector malfunctions and preserve data integrity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dinamo-dynamic-and-interpretable-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPO-VAE: Modeling Explainable Gene Perturbation Responses utilizing GRN-Aligned Parameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpo-vae-modeling-explainable-gene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the most effective ways to achieve explainability is incorporating the concept of gene regulatory networks (GRNs) in designing deep learning models such as VAEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpo-vae-modeling-explainable-gene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAAT-EHR: Cross-Attentional Autoregressive Transformer for Multimodal Electronic Health Record Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caat-ehr-cross-attentional-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electronic health records (EHRs) provide a comprehensive source of longitudinal patient data, encompassing structured modalities such as laboratory results, imaging data, and vital signs, and unstructured clinical notes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caat-ehr-cross-attentional-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR Loop Closure Detection using Semantic Graphs with Graph Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-loop-closure-detection-using-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel loop closure detection algorithm that uses graph attention neural networks to encode semantic graphs to perform place recognition and then use semantic registration to estimate the 6 DoF relative pose constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-loop-closure-detection-using-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Surprising Agreement Between Convex Optimization Theory and Learning-Rate Scheduling for Large Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-agreement-between-convex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that learning-rate schedules for large model training behave surprisingly similar to a performance bound from non-smooth convex optimization theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-surprising-agreement-between-convex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Reasoning with Hidden Thinking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reasoning-with-hidden-thinking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, we design corresponding Heima Decoder with traditional Large Language Models (LLMs) to adaptively interpret the hidden representations into variable-length textual sequence, reconstructing reasoning processes that closely resemble the original CoTs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-reasoning-with-hidden-thinking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Nonparametric Contextual Dynamic Pricing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-nonparametric-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Transfer Learning for Dynamic Pricing (TLDP) algorithm that can effectively leverage pre-collected data from a source domain to enhance pricing decisions in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-nonparametric-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RaySplats: Ray Tracing based Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raysplats-ray-tracing-based-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) is a process that enables the direct creation of 3D objects from 2D images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raysplats-ray-tracing-based-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Track-On: Transformer-based Online Point Tracking with Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-on-transformer-based-online-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider the problem of long-term point tracking, which requires consistent identification of points across multiple frames in a video, despite changes in appearance, lighting, perspective, and occlusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-on-transformer-based-online-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatIR: A Hybrid Mamba-Transformer Image Restoration Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matir-a-hybrid-mamba-transformer-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Transformers-based models have made significant progress in the field of image restoration by leveraging their inherent ability to capture complex contextual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matir-a-hybrid-mamba-transformer-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Cryptocurrency Transaction Analysis: A Bitcoin Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-cryptocurrency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cryptocurrencies are widely used, yet current methods for analyzing transactions heavily rely on opaque, black-box models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-cryptocurrency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GuardReasoner: Towards Reasoning-based LLM Safeguards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardreasoner-towards-reasoning-based-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we introduce reasoning SFT to unlock the reasoning capability of guard models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guardreasoner-towards-reasoning-based-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Transformer for High Resolution Image Motion Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformer-for-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also provide detailed ablation studies analyzing the impact of our modifications on model behavior and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformer-for-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Projection-based Data Transfer for Cross-Lingual Named Entity Recognition in Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-projection-based-data-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings highlight the robustness of projection-based data transfer as an alternative to model-based methods for crosslingual named entity recognition in lowresource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-projection-based-data-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-T2M: Frequency Enhanced Text-to-Motion Diffusion Model With Consistency Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-t2m-frequency-enhanced-text-to-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid progress in text-to-motion generation has been largely driven by diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-t2m-frequency-enhanced-text-to-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Neural Theorem Proving via Fine-grained Proof Structure Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-neural-theorem-proving-via-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The superiority of our method is validated on the miniF2F-test benchmark using the open-source deepseek-math-7b-base model and the Isabelle proof assistant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-neural-theorem-proving-via-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Multimodal Adaptation and Generalization: From Traditional Approaches to Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-multimodal-adaptation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, the recent advent of large-scale pre-trained multimodal foundation models, such as CLIP, has inspired works leveraging these models to enhance adaptation and generalization performances or adapting them to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-multimodal-adaptation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs can see and hear without any training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-see-and-hear-without-any-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MILS: Multimodal Iterative LLM Solver, a surprisingly simple, training-free approach, to imbue multimodal capabilities into your favorite LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-see-and-hear-without-any-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panacea: Mitigating Harmful Fine-tuning for Large Language Models via Post-fine-tuning Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panacea-mitigating-harmful-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mainstream defenses aim to vaccinate the model such that the later harmful fine-tuning attack is less effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panacea-mitigating-harmful-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illusions of Relevance: Using Content Injection Attacks to Deceive Retrievers, Rerankers, and LLM Judges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illusions-of-relevance-using-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study systematically examines the factors that influence an attack's success, such as the placement of injected content and the balance between relevant and non-relevant material.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illusions-of-relevance-using-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattering approach to diffusion quantifies axonal damage in brain injury</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scattering-approach-to-diffusion-quantifies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early diagnosis and noninvasive monitoring of neurological disorders require sensitivity to elusive cellular-level alterations that occur much earlier than volumetric changes observable with the millimeter-resolution of medical imaging modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scattering-approach-to-diffusion-quantifies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversity By Design: Leveraging Distribution Matching for Offline Model-Based Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-by-design-leveraging-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of offline model-based optimization (MBO) is to propose new designs that maximize a reward function given only an offline dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-by-design-leveraging-distribution</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
