<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 May 2023 09:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MotionBEV: Attention-Aware Online LiDAR Moving Object Segmentation with Bird's Eye View based Appearance and Motion Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionbev-attention-aware-online-lidar-moving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying moving objects is an essential capability for autonomous systems, as it provides critical information for pose estimation, navigation, collision avoidance and static map construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motionbev-attention-aware-online-lidar-moving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-former: An Efficient Transformer for Image Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-former-an-efficient-transformer-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And based on this attention, a network called $T$-former is designed for image inpainting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-former-an-efficient-transformer-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Count: Towards Text-Guided Zero-Shot Object Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-count-towards-text-guided-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in visual-language models have shown remarkable zero-shot text-image matching ability that is transferable to down-stream tasks such as object detection and segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-count-towards-text-guided-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Information Extraction in the Wild: Practical Dataset and End-to-end Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-information-extraction-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the existing end-to-end methods for VIE on the proposed dataset and observe that the performance of these methods has a distinguishable drop from SROIE (a widely used English dataset) to our proposed dataset due to the larger variance of layout and entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-information-extraction-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantile-Based Deep Reinforcement Learning using Two-Timescale Policy Gradient Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-based-deep-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classical reinforcement learning (RL) aims to optimize the expected cumulative reward.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-based-deep-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quaternion-valued Correlation Learning for Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quaternion-valued-correlation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our QCLNet is formulated as a hyper-complex valued network and represents correlation tensors in the quaternion domain, which uses quaternion-valued convolution to explore the external relations of query subspace when considering the hidden relationship of the support sub-dimension in the quaternion space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quaternion-valued-correlation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Progress in Fine-grained Vision-and-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-progress-in-fine-grained-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While pretraining on large-scale image-text data from the Web has facilitated rapid progress on many vision-and-language (V&L) tasks, recent work has demonstrated that pretrained models lack "fine-grained" understanding, such as the ability to recognise relationships, verbs, and numbers in images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-progress-in-fine-grained-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asymmetric feature interaction for interpreting model predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-feature-interaction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an asymmetric feature interaction attribution explanation model that aims to explore asymmetric higher-order feature interactions in the inference of deep neural NLP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymmetric-feature-interaction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSD-MonoDTR: Supervised Scale-constrained Deformable Transformer for Monocular 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssd-monodtr-supervised-scale-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, SSDA presets several masks with different scales and utilizes depth and visual features to predict the local feature for each query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssd-monodtr-supervised-scale-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versatile Audio-Visual Learning for Handling Single and Multi Modalities in Emotion Regression and Classification Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-audio-visual-learning-for-handling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a \emph{versatile audio-visual learning} (VAVL) framework for handling unimodal and multimodal systems for emotion regression and emotion classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-audio-visual-learning-for-handling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HFLIC: Human Friendly Perceptual Learned Image Compression with Reinforced Transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hflic-human-friendly-perceptual-learned-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been rapid development in learned image compression techniques that prioritize ratedistortion-perceptual compression, preserving fine details even at lower bit-rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hflic-human-friendly-perceptual-learned-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device-Robust Acoustic Scene Classification via Impulse Response Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-robust-acoustic-scene-classification-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we also show that DIR augmentation and Freq-MixStyle are complementary, achieving a new state-of-the-art performance on signals recorded by devices unseen during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-robust-acoustic-scene-classification-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Rearrangement Using Hierarchical Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-rearrangement-using-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Music rearrangement involves reshuffling, deleting, and repeating sections of a music piece with the goal of producing a standalone version that has a different duration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/music-rearrangement-using-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActUp: Analyzing and Consolidating tSNE and UMAP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actup-analyzing-and-consolidating-tsne-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[tSNE and UMAP are popular dimensionality reduction algorithms due to their speed and interpretable low-dimensional embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actup-analyzing-and-consolidating-tsne-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-WikiTable: Dataset for Open Domain Question Answering with Complex Reasoning over Table</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-wikitable-dataset-for-open-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent interest in open domain question answering (ODQA) over tables, many studies still rely on datasets that are not truly optimal for the task with respect to utilizing structural nature of table.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-wikitable-dataset-for-open-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Learning to Mitigate Catastrophic Forgetting in Cross-lingual Transfer for Open-domain Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-to-mitigate-catastrophic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue systems for non-English languages have long been under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-learning-to-mitigate-catastrophic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better speech synthesis through scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-speech-synthesis-through-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the field of image generation has been revolutionized by the application of autoregressive transformers and DDPMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-speech-synthesis-through-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT Fair for Recommendation? Evaluating Fairness in Large Language Model Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-fair-for-recommendation-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The remarkable achievements of Large Language Models (LLMs) have led to the emergence of a novel recommendation paradigm -- Recommendation via LLM (RecLLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-fair-for-recommendation-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perturbation-based QE: An Explainable, Unsupervised Word-level Quality Estimation Method for Blackbox Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbation-based-qe-an-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quality Estimation (QE) is the task of predicting the quality of Machine Translation (MT) system output, without using any gold-standard translation references.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perturbation-based-qe-an-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvesting Event Schemas from Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harvesting-event-schemas-from-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event schema provides a conceptual, structural and formal language to represent events and model the world event knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harvesting-event-schemas-from-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What are the Desired Characteristics of Calibration Sets? Identifying Correlates on Long Form Scientific Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-the-desired-characteristics-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summarization models often generate text that is poorly calibrated to quality metrics because they are trained to maximize the likelihood of a single reference (MLE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-the-desired-characteristics-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeXFiles and LegalLAMA: Facilitating English Multinational Legal Language Model Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexfiles-and-legallama-facilitating-english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we release a multinational English legal corpus (LeXFiles) and a legal knowledge probing benchmark (LegalLAMA) to facilitate training and detailed analysis of legal-oriented PLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexfiles-and-legallama-facilitating-english</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrix tri-factorization over the tropical semiring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrix-tri-factorization-over-the-tropical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that triFastSTMF performs similarly to Fast-NMTF in terms of approximation and prediction performance when fitted on the whole network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrix-tri-factorization-over-the-tropical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAHE: Hierarchical Attention for Hyper-Relational Knowledge Graphs in Global and Local Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hahe-hierarchical-attention-for-hyper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global-level attention can model the graphical structure of HKG using hypergraph dual-attention layers, while the local-level attention can learn the sequential structure inside H-Facts via heterogeneous self-attention layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hahe-hierarchical-attention-for-hyper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PVT-SSD: Single-Stage 3D Object Detector with Point-Voxel Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pvt-ssd-single-stage-3d-object-detector-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to associating the two different representations is our introduced input-dependent Query Initialization module, which could efficiently generate reference points and content queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pvt-ssd-single-stage-3d-object-detector-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THUIR@COLIEE 2023: More Parameters and Legal Knowledge for Legal Case Entailment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-more-parameters-and-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the approach of the THUIR team at the COLIEE 2023 Legal Case Entailment task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-more-parameters-and-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HINT: Hierarchical Mixture Networks For Coherent Probabilistic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hint-hierarchical-mixture-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Hierarchical Mixture Networks (HINT), a model family for efficient and accurate coherent forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hint-hierarchical-mixture-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastDiagP: An Algorithm for Parallelized Direct Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastdiagp-an-algorithm-for-parallelized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm extends FastDiag by integrating a parallelization mechanism that anticipates and pre-calculates consistency checks requested by FastDiag.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastdiagp-an-algorithm-for-parallelized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Forward-Looking Active REtrieval augmented generation (FLARE), a generic retrieval-augmented generation method which iteratively uses a prediction of the upcoming sentence to anticipate future content, which is then utilized as a query to retrieve relevant documents to regenerate the sentence if it contains low-confidence tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General Framework for Visualizing Embedding Spaces of Neural Survival Analysis Models Based on Angular Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-visualizing-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then show how these visualization ideas extend to handling raw inputs that are images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-visualizing-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backpropagation-Free 4D Continuous Ant-Based Neural Topology Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backpropagation-free-4d-continuous-ant-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continuous Ant-based Topology Search (CANTS) is a previously introduced novel nature-inspired neural architecture search (NAS) algorithm that is based on ant colony optimization (ACO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backpropagation-free-4d-continuous-ant-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial Contrastive Knowledge Distillation for Continual Few-shot Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/serial-contrastive-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual few-shot relation extraction (RE) aims to continuously train a model for new relations with few labeled training data, of which the major challenges are the catastrophic forgetting of old relations and the overfitting caused by data sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/serial-contrastive-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermal Bridges on Building Rooftops</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-bridges-on-building-rooftops</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thermal Bridges on Building Rooftops (TBBR) is a multi-channel remote sensing dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-bridges-on-building-rooftops</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subword Segmental Machine Translation: Unifying Segmentation and Target Sentence Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subword-segmental-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a departure from this paradigm, called subword segmental machine translation (SSMT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subword-segmental-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuManiFlow: Ancestor-Conditioned Normalising Flows on SO(3) Manifolds for Human Pose and Shape Distribution Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humaniflow-ancestor-conditioned-normalising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular 3D human pose and shape estimation is an ill-posed problem since multiple 3D solutions can explain a 2D image of a subject.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humaniflow-ancestor-conditioned-normalising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A First Look at LLM-Powered Generative News Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-llm-powered-generative-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized news recommendation systems have become essential tools for users to navigate the vast amount of online news content, yet existing news recommenders face significant challenges such as the cold-start problem, user profile modeling, and news content understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-first-look-at-llm-powered-generative-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatE: Embedding $\mathcal{ALC}$ ontologies using category-theoretical semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cate-embedding-mathcal-alc-ontologies-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We developed CatE, which uses the category-theoretical formulation of the semantics of the Description Logic $\mathcal{ALC}$ to generate a graph representation for ontology axioms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cate-embedding-mathcal-alc-ontologies-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalization bounds for neural ordinary differential equations and deep residual networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-bounds-for-neural-ordinary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging the analogy between neural ODEs and deep residual networks, our approach yields in particular a generalization bound for a class of deep residual networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-bounds-for-neural-ordinary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A General-Purpose Multilingual Document Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-purpose-multilingual-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While a large body of work leveraged MMTs to mine parallel data and induce bilingual document embeddings, much less effort has been devoted to training general-purpose (massively) multilingual document encoder that can be used for both supervised and unsupervised document-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-purpose-multilingual-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salient Mask-Guided Vision Transformer for Fine-Grained Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salient-mask-guided-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained visual classification (FGVC) is a challenging computer vision problem, where the task is to automatically recognise objects from subordinate categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salient-mask-guided-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Continual Relation Extraction by Distinguishing Analogous Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continual-relation-extraction-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel continual extraction model for analogous relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continual-relation-extraction-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ConceptARC Benchmark: Evaluating Understanding and Generalization in the ARC Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-conceptarc-benchmark-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we describe an in-depth evaluation benchmark for the Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus (ARC), a collection of few-shot abstraction and analogy problems developed by Chollet [2019].]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-conceptarc-benchmark-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fast topological approach for predicting anomalies in time-varying graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-topological-approach-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past decade, a persistence diagram (PD) from topological data analysis (TDA) has become a popular descriptor of shape of data with a well-defined distance between points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fast-topological-approach-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BanglaBook: A Large-scale Bangla Dataset for Sentiment Analysis from Book Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglabook-a-large-scale-bangla-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of consumer sentiment, as expressed through reviews, can provide a wealth of insight regarding the quality of a product.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banglabook-a-large-scale-bangla-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Inverse Scaling Law for CLIP Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-inverse-scaling-law-for-clip-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CLIP, the first foundation model that connects images and text, has enabled many recent breakthroughs in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-inverse-scaling-law-for-clip-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collection Space Navigator: An Interactive Visualization Interface for Multidimensional Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collection-space-navigator-an-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Collection Space Navigator (CSN), a browser-based visualization tool to explore, research, and curate large collections of visual digital artifacts that are associated with multidimensional data, such as vector embeddings or tables of metadata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collection-space-navigator-an-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Fine-Gray: Monotonic neural networks for competing risks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fine-gray-monotonic-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-to-event modelling, known as survival analysis, differs from standard regression as it addresses censoring in patients who do not experience the event of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fine-gray-monotonic-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Undercover Deepfakes: Detecting Fake Segments in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/undercover-deepfakes-detecting-fake-segments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a deepfake detection method able to address this issue by performing both frame and video level deepfake prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/undercover-deepfakes-detecting-fake-segments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THUIR@COLIEE 2023: Incorporating Structural Knowledge into Pre-trained Language Models for Legal Case Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-incorporating-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Legal case retrieval techniques play an essential role in modern intelligent legal systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-coliee-2023-incorporating-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-level Dynamic Learning for Jointly Multi-modality Image Fusion and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-level-dynamic-learning-for-jointly-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, multi-modality scene perception tasks, e. g., image fusion and scene understanding, have attracted widespread attention for intelligent vision systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-level-dynamic-learning-for-jointly-multi</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
