<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 09:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Knowledge Graph Generation from Tabular Data with RML Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-knowledge-graph-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present our extension of Morph-KGC to efficiently support RML views for tabular sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-knowledge-graph-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRITIC: Large Language Models Can Self-Correct with Tool-Interactive Critiquing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critic-large-language-models-can-self-correct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike these models, humans typically utilize external tools to cross-check and refine their initial content, like using a search engine for fact-checking, or a code interpreter for debugging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critic-large-language-models-can-self-correct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Few-shot NER with Prompt Ordering based Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-ner-with-prompt-ordering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, data augmentation (DA) methods have been proven to be effective for pre-trained language models (PLMs) in low-resource settings, including few-shot named entity recognition (NER).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-ner-with-prompt-ordering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Pruner: On the Structural Pruning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-pruner-on-the-structural-pruning-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With LLM being a general-purpose task solver, we explore its compression in a task-agnostic manner, which aims to preserve the multi-task solving and language generation ability of the original LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-pruner-on-the-structural-pruning-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphFC: Customs Fraud Detection with Label Scarcity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphfc-customs-fraud-detection-with-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Custom officials across the world encounter huge volumes of transactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphfc-customs-fraud-detection-with-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSeTOX: Re-learning attention weights for toxicity mitigation in machine translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resetox-re-learning-attention-weights-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method, ReSeTOX (REdo SEarch if TOXic), addresses the issue of Neural Machine Translation (NMT) generating translation outputs that contain toxic words not present in the input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resetox-re-learning-attention-weights-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUB: Discrete Unit Back-translation for Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dub-discrete-unit-back-translation-for-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key point is to bridge the modality gap between speech and text so that useful MT techniques can be applied to ST.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dub-discrete-unit-back-translation-for-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recycle-and-Distill: Universal Compression Strategy for Transformer-based Speech SSL Models with Attention Map Reusing and Masking Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recycle-and-distill-universal-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based speech self-supervised learning (SSL) models, such as HuBERT, show surprising performance in various speech processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recycle-and-distill-universal-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUEST: A Retrieval Dataset of Entity-Seeking Queries with Implicit Set Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quest-a-retrieval-dataset-of-entity-seeking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study the ability of retrieval systems to meet such information needs, we construct QUEST, a dataset of 3357 natural language queries with implicit set operations, that map to a set of entities corresponding to Wikipedia documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quest-a-retrieval-dataset-of-entity-seeking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Mixed Transformer for Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mixed-transformer-for-single-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose the Mixed Transformer Block (MTB), consisting of multiple consecutive transformer layers, in some of which the Pixel Mixer (PM) is used to replace the Self-Attention (SA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mixed-transformer-for-single-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Claim Verification with Evidence Retrieved in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-claim-verification-with-evidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evidence retrieval is a core part of automatic fact-checking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-claim-verification-with-evidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inside Story: Towards Better Understanding of Machine Translation Neural Evaluation Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inside-story-towards-better-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural metrics for machine translation evaluation, such as COMET, exhibit significant improvements in their correlation with human judgments, as compared to traditional metrics based on lexical overlap, such as BLEU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inside-story-towards-better-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Optimization Using the R2 Utility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-using-the-r2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to solve this vector-valued optimization problem, practitioners often appeal to the use of scalarization functions in order to transform the multi-objective problem into a collection of single-objective problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-optimization-using-the-r2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSGM: A Flexible Framework for Generative Modeling of Synthetic Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsgm-a-flexible-framework-for-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporally indexed data are essential in a wide range of fields and of interest to machine learning researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsgm-a-flexible-framework-for-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAT: Boundary aware transducer for memory-efficient and low-latency ASR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-boundary-aware-transducer-for-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, recurrent neural network transducer (RNN-T) gains increasing popularity due to its natural streaming capability as well as superior performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bat-boundary-aware-transducer-for-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-tailed Visual Recognition via Gaussian Clouded Logit Adjustment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-visual-recognition-via-gaussian-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is unfavorable for training on balanced data, but can be utilized to adjust the validity of the samples in long-tailed data, thereby solving the distorted embedding space of long-tailed problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-visual-recognition-via-gaussian-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Propagation Transformer for Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-propagation-transformer-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core insight of our method is to fully consider the information propagation among nodes and edges in a graph when building the attention module in the transformer blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-propagation-transformer-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttriCLIP: A Non-Incremental Learner for Incremental Knowledge Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attriclip-a-non-incremental-learner-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text consists of a category name and a fixed number of learnable parameters which are selected from our designed attribute word bank and serve as attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attriclip-a-non-incremental-learner-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syllable Discovery and Cross-Lingual Generalization in a Visually Grounded, Self-Supervised Speech Mode</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syllable-discovery-and-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that representations capturing syllabic units emerge when training a self-supervised speech model with a visually-grounded training objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syllable-discovery-and-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Accurate Image Coding: Improved Autoregressive Image Generation with Dynamic Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-image-coding-improved-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing vector quantization (VQ) based autoregressive models follow a two-stage generation paradigm that first learns a codebook to encode images as discrete codes, and then completes generation based on the learned codebook.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-image-coding-improved-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Text Classification via Self-Supervised Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-classification-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new paradigm based on self-supervised learning to solve zero-shot text classification tasks by tuning the language models with unlabeled data, called self-supervised tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-classification-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Screening whilst Exploiting! Multimodal Relation Extraction with Feature Denoising and Multimodal Topic Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-screening-whilst-exploiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we represent the fine-grained semantic structures of the input image and text with the visual and textual scene graphs, which are further fused into a unified cross-modal graph (CMG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-screening-whilst-exploiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Gradient Consistency for Neural Signed Distance Functions via Level Set Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-gradient-consistency-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our insight is to propagate the zero level set to everywhere in the field through consistent gradients to eliminate uncertainty in the field that is caused by the discreteness of 3D point clouds or the lack of observations from multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-gradient-consistency-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Diverse Risk Preferences in Population-based Self-play</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-diverse-risk-preferences-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to introduce diversity from the perspective that agents could have diverse risk preferences in the face of uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-diverse-risk-preferences-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Topology Agnosticism: Enhancing Skeleton-Based Action Recognition through Redefined Skeletal Topology Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-topology-agnosticism-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This finding exposes the limitations of a single adjacency matrix in capturing the variations of relational configurations emblematic of human movement, which we remedy by proposing an efficient refinement to Graph Convolutions (GC) - the BlockGC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-topology-agnosticism-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSFNet: Dual Space Fusion Network for Occlusion-Robust 3D Dense Face Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsfnet-dual-space-fusion-network-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to the proposed fusion module, our method is robust not only to occlusion and large pitch and roll view angles, which is the benefit of our image space approach, but also to noise and large yaw angles, which is the benefit of our model space method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsfnet-dual-space-fusion-network-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PastNet: Introducing Physical Inductive Biases for Spatio-temporal Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pastnet-introducing-physical-inductive-biases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the challenge of spatio-temporal video prediction, which involves generating future videos based on historical data streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pastnet-introducing-physical-inductive-biases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Visual Spatial Description via Holistic 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-visual-spatial-description-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With an external 3D scene extractor, we obtain the 3D objects and scene features for input images, based on which we construct a target object-centered 3D spatial scene graph (Go3D-S2G), such that we model the spatial semantics of target objects within the holistic 3D scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-visual-spatial-description-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LATTE: Label-efficient Incident Phenotyping from Longitudinal Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latte-label-efficient-incident-phenotyping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a LAbel-efficienT incidenT phEnotyping (LATTE) algorithm to accurately annotate the timing of clinical events from longitudinal EHR data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latte-label-efficient-incident-phenotyping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Lexicase Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-lexicase-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lexicase selection is a widely used parent selection algorithm in genetic programming, known for its success in various task domains such as program synthesis, symbolic regression, and machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-lexicase-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructIE: A Chinese Instruction-based Information Extraction Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructie-a-chinese-instruction-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new Information Extraction (IE) task dubbed Instruction-based IE, which aims to ask the system to follow specific instructions or guidelines to extract information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructie-a-chinese-instruction-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetSeg: Efficient Real-Time Semantic Segmentation Model for Low-Power GPU-Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jetseg-efficient-real-time-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The JetNet is designed for GPU-Embedded Systems and includes two main components: a new light-weight efficient block called JetBlock, that reduces the number of parameters minimizing memory usage and inference time without sacrificing accuracy; a new strategy that involves the combination of asymmetric and non-asymmetric convolutions with depthwise-dilated convolutions called JetConv, a channel shuffle operation, light-weight activation functions, and a convenient number of group convolutions for embedded systems, and an innovative loss function named JetLoss, which integrates the Precision, Recall, and IoUB losses to improve semantic segmentation and reduce computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jetseg-efficient-real-time-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Learning with Visual Distribution Calibration and Cross-Modal Distribution Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-learning-with-visual-distribution-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, with only a few training images, there exist two crucial problems: (1) the visual feature distributions are easily distracted by class-irrelevant information in images, and (2) the alignment between the visual and language feature distributions is difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-learning-with-visual-distribution-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decouple knowledge from paramters for plug-and-play language modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decouple-knowledge-from-paramters-for-plug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key intuition is to decouple the knowledge storage from model parameters with an editable and scalable key-value memory and leverage knowledge in an explainable manner by knowledge retrieval in the DPM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decouple-knowledge-from-paramters-for-plug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marginalized Beam Search Algorithms for Hierarchical HMMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginalized-beam-search-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inferring a state sequence from a sequence of measurements is a fundamental problem in bioinformatics and natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginalized-beam-search-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical-VQLA: Transformer with Gated Vision-Language Embedding for Visual Question Localized-Answering in Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqla-transformer-with-gated-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Visual Question Localized-Answering in Robotic Surgery (Surgical-VQLA) to localize the specific surgical area during the answer prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqla-transformer-with-gated-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RxnScribe: A Sequence Generation Model for Reaction Diagram Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rxnscribe-a-sequence-generation-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reaction diagram parsing is the task of extracting reaction schemes from a diagram in the chemistry literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rxnscribe-a-sequence-generation-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the Name of Fairness: Assessing the Bias in Clinical Record De-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-the-name-of-fairness-assessing-the-bias-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data sharing is crucial for open science and reproducible research, but the legal sharing of clinical data requires the removal of protected health information from electronic health records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-the-name-of-fairness-assessing-the-bias-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GETMusic: Generating Any Music Tracks with a Unified Representation and Diffusion Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/getmusic-generating-any-music-tracks-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With separate tracks in GETScore and the non-autoregressive behavior of the model, GETMusic can explicitly control the generation of any target tracks from scratch or conditioning on source tracks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/getmusic-generating-any-music-tracks-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharing Lifelong Reinforcement Learning Knowledge via Modulating Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharing-lifelong-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key idea is that the isolation of specific task knowledge to specific masks allows agents to transfer only specific knowledge on-demand, resulting in robust and effective distributed lifelong learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharing-lifelong-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A benchmark for computational analysis of animal behavior, using animal-borne tags</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-computational-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Animal-borne sensors ('bio-loggers') can record a suite of kinematic and environmental data, which can elucidate animal ecophysiology and improve conservation efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-for-computational-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flatness-Aware Prompt Selection Improves Accuracy and Sample Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flatness-aware-prompt-selection-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide theoretical foundations for this metric and its relationship with other prompt selection metrics, providing a comprehensive understanding of existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flatness-aware-prompt-selection-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPENSER: Towards a NeuroEvolutionary Approach for Convolutional Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spenser-towards-a-neuroevolutionary-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DENSER is a NE framework for the automatic design and parametrization of ANNs, based on the principles of Genetic Algorithms (GA) and Structured Grammatical Evolution (SGE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spenser-towards-a-neuroevolutionary-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Posterior Inference on Infinitely Wide Bayesian Neural Networks under Weights with Unbounded Variance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterior-inference-on-infinitely-wide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the classical and influential works of Neal (1996), it is known that the infinite width scaling limit of a Bayesian neural network with one hidden layer is a Gaussian process, \emph{when the network weights have bounded prior variance}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posterior-inference-on-infinitely-wide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dirichlet Diffusion Score Model for Biological Sequence Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirichlet-diffusion-score-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we applied this approach to develop the first human promoter DNA sequence design model and showed that designed sequences share similar properties with natural promoter sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dirichlet-diffusion-score-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seq-HGNN: Learning Sequential Node Representation on Heterogeneous Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seq-hgnn-learning-sequential-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing HGNNs usually represent each node as a single vector in the multi-layer graph convolution calculation, which makes the high-level graph convolution layer fail to distinguish information from different relations and different orders, resulting in the information loss in the message passing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seq-hgnn-learning-sequential-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Gradient Boosting Decision Tree with Unbiased Feature Importance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-gradient-boosting-decision-tree-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we provide a fine-grained analysis of bias in GBDT and demonstrate that the bias originates from 1) the systematic bias in the gain estimation of each split and 2) the bias in the split finding algorithm resulting from the use of the same data to evaluate the split improvement and determine the best split.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-gradient-boosting-decision-tree-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-dimensional Asymptotics of Denoising Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-asymptotics-of-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of denoising data from a Gaussian mixture using a two-layer non-linear autoencoder with tied weights and a skip connection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-asymptotics-of-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruct2Act: Mapping Multi-modality Instructions to Robotic Actions with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct2act-mapping-multi-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Instruct2Act, a framework that utilizes Large Language Models to map multi-modal instructions to sequential actions for robotic manipulation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct2act-mapping-multi-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quiver: Supporting GPUs for Low-Latency, High-Throughput GNN Serving with Workload Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quiver-supporting-gpus-for-low-latency-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quiver's key idea is to exploit workload metrics for predicting the irregular computation of GNN requests, and governing the use of GPUs for graph sampling and feature aggregation: (1) for graph sampling, Quiver calculates the probabilistic sampled graph size, a metric that predicts the degree of parallelism in graph sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quiver-supporting-gpus-for-low-latency-high</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
