<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:07:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Calc-CMU at SemEval-2024 Task 7: Pre-Calc -- Learning to Use the Calculator Improves Numeracy in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calc-cmu-at-semeval-2024-task-7-pre-calc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantitative and numerical comprehension in language is an important task in many fields like education and finance, but still remains a challenging task for language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calc-cmu-at-semeval-2024-task-7-pre-calc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graphic Design with Large Multimodal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphic-design-with-large-multimodal-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One existing practice is Graphic Layout Generation (GLG), which aims to layout sequential design elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphic-design-with-large-multimodal-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoFInAl: Enhancing Action Quality Assessment with Coarse-to-Fine Instruction Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cofinal-enhancing-action-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this common strategy yields suboptimal results due to the inherent struggle of these backbones to capture the subtle cues essential for AQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cofinal-enhancing-action-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preference Fine-Tuning of LLMs Should Leverage Suboptimal, On-Policy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-fine-tuning-of-llms-should</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main finding is that, in general, approaches that use on-policy sampling or attempt to push down the likelihood on certain responses (i. e., employ a "negative gradient") outperform offline and maximum likelihood objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-fine-tuning-of-llms-should</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VALOR-EVAL: Holistic Coverage and Faithfulness Evaluation of Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valor-eval-holistic-coverage-and-faithfulness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we introduce a multi-dimensional benchmark covering objects, attributes, and relations, with challenging images selected based on associative biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valor-eval-holistic-coverage-and-faithfulness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAVGBench: Benchmarking Text to Audible-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tavgbench-benchmarking-text-to-audible-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To support research in this field, we have developed a comprehensive Text to Audible-Video Generation Benchmark (TAVGBench), which contains over 1. 7 million clips with a total duration of 11. 8 thousand hours.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tavgbench-benchmarking-text-to-audible-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-designing a Sub-millisecond Latency Event-based Eye Tracking System with Submanifold Sparse CNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-designing-a-sub-millisecond-latency-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Eye-tracking technology is integral to numerous consumer electronics applications, particularly in the realm of virtual and augmented reality (VR/AR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-designing-a-sub-millisecond-latency-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multimodal Feature Distillation with CNN-Transformer Network for Brain Tumor Segmentation with Incomplete Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-feature-distillation-with-cnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our ablation study demonstrates the importance of the proposed modules with CNN-Transformer networks and the convolutional blocks in Transformer for improving the performance of brain tumor segmentation with missing modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-feature-distillation-with-cnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gorgeous: Create Your Desired Character Facial Makeup from Any Ideas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gorgeous-create-your-desired-character-facial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contemporary makeup transfer methods primarily focus on replicating makeup from one face to another, considerably limiting their use in creating diverse and creative character makeup essential for visual storytelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gorgeous-create-your-desired-character-facial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Tuple-Table: Towards Information Integration in Text-to-Table Generation via Global Tuple Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-tuple-table-towards-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of condensing large chunks of textual information into concise and structured tables has gained attention recently due to the emergence of Large Language Models (LLMs) and their potential benefit for downstream tasks, such as text summarization and text mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-tuple-table-towards-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Level Sequence Denoising with Cross-Signal Contrastive Learning for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-sequence-denoising-with-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the end, in this paper, we propose a novel model named Multi-level Sequence Denoising with Cross-signal Contrastive Learning (MSDCCL) for sequential recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-sequence-denoising-with-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEED-X: Multimodal Models with Unified Multi-granularity Comprehension and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-x-multimodal-models-with-unified-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope that our work will inspire future research into what can be achieved by versatile multimodal foundation models in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seed-x-multimodal-models-with-unified-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Good Are Low-bit Quantized LLaMA3 Models? An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-low-bit-quantized-llama3-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This exploration holds the potential to unveil new insights and challenges for low-bit quantization of LLaMA3 and other forthcoming LLMs, especially in addressing performance degradation problems that suffer in LLM compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-low-bit-quantized-llama3-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiBooth: Towards Generating All Your Concepts in an Image from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multibooth-towards-generating-all-your</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MultiBooth addresses these issues by dividing the multi-concept generation process into two phases: a single-concept learning phase and a multi-concept integration phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multibooth-towards-generating-all-your</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filtered Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filtered-direct-preference-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the issue of text quality within the preference dataset by focusing on Direct Preference Optimization (DPO), an increasingly adopted reward-model-free RLHF method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filtered-direct-preference-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Alignment with Mutual Information: Learning to Follow Principles without Preference Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-alignment-with-mutual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On single-turn dialogue and summarization, a SAMI-trained mistral-7b outperforms the initial pretrained model, with win rates between 66% and 77%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-alignment-with-mutual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOFTS: Efficient Multivariate Time Series Forecasting with Series-Core Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softs-efficient-multivariate-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate time series forecasting plays a crucial role in various fields such as finance, traffic management, energy, and healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softs-efficient-multivariate-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICST-DNET: An Interpretable Causal Spatio-Temporal Diffusion Network for Traffic Speed Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icst-dnet-an-interpretable-causal-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, making accurate predictions is challenging due to three factors: 1) traffic diffusion, i. e., the spatial and temporal causality existing between the traffic conditions of multiple neighboring roads, 2) the poor interpretability of traffic data with complicated spatio-temporal correlations, and 3) the latent pattern of traffic speed fluctuations over time, such as morning and evening rush.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icst-dnet-an-interpretable-causal-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Scaling: Predicting Patent Approval with Domain-specific Fine-grained Claim Dependency Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-scaling-predicting-patent-approval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve into the patent approval pre-diction task and unveil that simple domain-specific graph methods outperform enlarging the model, using the intrinsic dependencies within the patent data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-scaling-predicting-patent-approval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColA: Collaborative Adaptation with Gradient Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cola-collaborative-adaptation-with-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Collaborative Adaptation (ColA) with Gradient Learning (GL), a parameter-free, model-agnostic fine-tuning approach that decouples the computation of the gradient of hidden representations and parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cola-collaborative-adaptation-with-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeLiCal: Targetless Extrinsic Calibration via Penetrating Lines for RGB-D Cameras with Limited Co-visibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pelical-targetless-extrinsic-calibration-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The extrinsic calibration of these systems introduces additional complexities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pelical-targetless-extrinsic-calibration-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research on Robot Path Planning Based on Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/research-on-robot-path-planning-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project has conducted experimental verification of the Visual SLAM system in a simulation environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/research-on-robot-path-planning-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-based reward driven image analysis in microscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-based-reward-driven-image-analysis-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a methodology based on the concept of a Reward Function coupled with Bayesian Optimization, to optimize image analysis workflows dynamically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-based-reward-driven-image-analysis-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRNet: A Detail-Preserving Network for Unified Image Restoration and Enhancement Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crnet-a-detail-preserving-network-for-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world scenarios, images captured often suffer from blurring, noise, and other forms of image degradation, and due to sensor limitations, people usually can only obtain low dynamic range images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crnet-a-detail-preserving-network-for-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C2F-SemiCD: A Coarse-to-Fine Semi-Supervised Change Detection Method Based on Consistency Regularization in High-Resolution Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2f-semicd-a-coarse-to-fine-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A high-precision feature extraction model is crucial for change detection (CD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c2f-semicd-a-coarse-to-fine-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Disentanglement for Reinforcement Learning with Multiple Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-disentanglement-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these hardware constraints, we propose Multi-View Disentanglement (MVD), which uses multiple cameras to learn a policy that achieves zero-shot generalisation to any single camera from the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-disentanglement-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceByte: Towards Deleting Tokenization from Large Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spacebyte-towards-deleting-tokenization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tokenization is widely used in large language models because it significantly improves performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spacebyte-towards-deleting-tokenization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Synthetic Data by Retrieving and Transforming Existing Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-synthetic-data-by-retrieving-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has studied prompt-driven synthetic data generation using large language models, but these generated datasets tend to lack complexity and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-synthetic-data-by-retrieving-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MARIO Eval: Evaluate Your Math LLM with your Math LLM--A mathematical dataset evaluation toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mario-eval-evaluate-your-math-llm-with-your</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been explored in a variety of reasoning tasks including solving of mathematical problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mario-eval-evaluate-your-math-llm-with-your</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Routing River Water in Land Surface Models with Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-routing-river-water-in-land-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training of such a model over the continental United States has demonstrated that a single set of model parameters can be used across independent catchments, and that RNNs can outperform physics-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-routing-river-water-in-land-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A User-Centric Benchmark for Evaluating Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-centric-benchmark-for-evaluating-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this oversight, we propose benchmarking LLMs from a user perspective in both dataset construction and evaluation designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-centric-benchmark-for-evaluating-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Discovery of Visual Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-discovery-of-visual-circuits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To date, most discoveries of network subcomponents that implement human-interpretable computations in deep vision models have involved close study of single units and large amounts of human labor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-discovery-of-visual-circuits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-preserving neural networks for the regularzied entropy-based closure of the Boltzmann moment system</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-neural-networks-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we derive and investigate a neural network-based approximation to the entropy closure method to accurately compute the solution of the multi-dimensional moment system with a low memory footprint and competitive computational time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-neural-networks-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving linear invariants in ensemble filtering methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-linear-invariants-in-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we assess the benefits of preserving linear invariants for the ensemble Kalman filter and nonlinear ensemble filters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-linear-invariants-in-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Heterogeneous Client Sampling for Federated Learning over Wireless Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-heterogeneous-client-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to design an adaptive client sampling algorithm for FL over wireless networks that tackles both system and statistical heterogeneity to minimize the wall-clock convergence time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-heterogeneous-client-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LVNS-RAVE: Diversified audio generation with RAVE and Latent Vector Novelty Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvns-rave-diversified-audio-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary Algorithms and Generative Deep Learning have been two of the most powerful tools for sound generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvns-rave-diversified-audio-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrated Gradient Correlation: a Dataset-wise Attribution Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrated-gradient-correlation-a-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attribution methods are primarily designed to study the distribution of input component contributions to individual model predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrated-gradient-correlation-a-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaUIE&amp;SR: Unraveling the Ocean's Secrets with Only 2.8 FLOPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambauie-sr-unraveling-the-ocean-s-secrets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, combining CNN and Transformer can effectively combine global and local information for enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambauie-sr-unraveling-the-ocean-s-secrets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimizing Weighted Counterfactual Regret with Optimistic Online Mirror Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimizing-weighted-counterfactual-regret</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual regret minimization (CFR) is a family of algorithms for effectively solving imperfect-information games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimizing-weighted-counterfactual-regret</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interval Abstractions for Robust Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-abstractions-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual Explanations (CEs) have emerged as a major paradigm in explainable AI research, providing recourse recommendations for users affected by the decisions of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interval-abstractions-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic in Static: Hybrid Visual Correspondence for Self-Supervised Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-in-static-hybrid-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this objective, we present a unified self-supervised approach to learn visual representations of static-dynamic feature similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-in-static-hybrid-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLP: Motion Label Prior for Temporal Sentence Localization in Untrimmed 3D Human Motions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlp-motion-label-prior-for-temporal-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address the unexplored question of temporal sentence localization in human motions (TSLM), aiming to locate a target moment from a 3D human motion that semantically corresponds to a text query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlp-motion-label-prior-for-temporal-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards General Conceptual Model Editing via Adversarial Representation Engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-conceptual-model-editing-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has introduced Representation Engineering (RepE) as a promising approach for understanding complex inner workings of large-scale models like Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-conceptual-model-editing-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Principal Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-principal-autoencoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimension reduction techniques usually lose information in the sense that reconstructed data are not identical to the original data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-principal-autoencoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Latent Transformer with the Random Masking Ratio to Advance the Diagnosis of Dental Fluorosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-latent-transformer-with-the-random</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance the diagnosis of dental fluorosis, we propose a pioneering deep learning model called masked latent transformer with the random masking ratio (MLTrMR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-latent-transformer-with-the-random</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Regression with Conditional GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-regression-with-conditional-gans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regression is typically treated as a curve-fitting process where the goal is to fit a prediction function to data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-regression-with-conditional-gans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Unlearning via Null Space Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-unlearning-via-null-space-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current research centres on efficient unlearning to erase the influence of data from the model and neglects the subsequent impacts on the remaining data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-unlearning-via-null-space-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lost in Space: Probing Fine-grained Spatial Understanding in Vision and Language Resamplers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-space-probing-fine-grained-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we use \textit{diagnostic classifiers} to measure the extent to which the visual prompt produced by the resampler encodes spatial information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lost-in-space-probing-fine-grained-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mean Aggregator Is More Robust Than Robust Aggregators Under Label Poisoning Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-aggregator-is-more-robust-than-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robustness to malicious attacks is of paramount importance for distributed learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-aggregator-is-more-robust-than-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Retrieval Quality in Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-retrieval-quality-in-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, evaluation of the retrieval model's performance based on query-document relevance labels shows a small correlation with the RAG system's downstream performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-retrieval-quality-in-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
