<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 09:16:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Auto-Augment with Label Preservation: A Representation Learning Principle Guided Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-auto-augment-with-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments, we show that our method consistently brings non-trivial improvements to the three aforementioned learning tasks from both efficiency and final performance, either or not combined with strong pre-defined augmentations, e. g., on medical images when domain knowledge is unavailable and the existing augmentation techniques perform poorly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-auto-augment-with-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference and Denoise: Causal Inference-based Neural Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-and-denoise-causal-inference-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study addresses the speech enhancement (SE) task within the causal inference paradigm by modeling the noise presence as an intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-and-denoise-causal-inference-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive GAN for Semantic Unconditional Head Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-gan-for-semantic-unconditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the task of unconditional head motion generation to animate still human faces in a low-dimensional semantic space. Deviating from talking head generation conditioned on audio that seldom puts emphasis on realistic head motions, we devise a GAN-based architecture that allows obtaining rich head motion sequences while avoiding known caveats associated with GANs. Namely, the autoregressive generation of incremental outputs ensures smooth trajectories, while a multi-scale discriminator on input pairs drives generation toward better handling of high and low frequency signals and less mode collapse. We demonstrate experimentally the relevance of the proposed architecture and compare with models that showed state-of-the-art performances on similar tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-gan-for-semantic-unconditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic SuperPoint: A Deep Semantic Descriptor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-superpoint-a-deep-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several SLAM methods benefit from the use of semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-superpoint-a-deep-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITT: A Wireless Image Transmission Transformer for Semantic Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/witt-a-wireless-image-transmission</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to redesign the vision Transformer (ViT) as a new backbone to realize semantic image transmission, termed wireless image transmission transformer (WITT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/witt-a-wireless-image-transmission</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CircleSnake: Instance Segmentation with Circle Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circlesnake-instance-segmentation-with-circle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Circle representation has recently been introduced as a medical imaging optimized representation for more effective instance object detection on ball-shaped medical objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circlesnake-instance-segmentation-with-circle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambiguity-Aware Multi-Object Pose Optimization for Visually-Assisted Robot Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguity-aware-multi-object-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tackling these limitations, we present an ambiguity-aware 6D object pose estimation network, PrimA6D++, as a generic uncertainty prediction method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguity-aware-multi-object-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying And Interpreting Neural Networks using Finite Automata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-and-interpreting-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Verifying properties and interpreting the behaviour of deep neural networks (DNN) is an important task given their ubiquitous use in applications, including safety-critical ones, and their blackbox nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-and-interpreting-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new method for determining Wasserstein 1 optimal transport maps from Kantorovich potentials, with deep learning applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-method-for-determining-wasserstein-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In general, a Wasserstein 1 optimal transport map is not unique and is not computable from a potential alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-method-for-determining-wasserstein-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pop2Piano : Pop Audio-based Piano Cover Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pop2piano-pop-audio-based-piano-cover</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The piano cover of pop music is widely enjoyed by people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pop2piano-pop-audio-based-piano-cover</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADPTriage: Approximate Dynamic Programming for Bug Triage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adptriage-approximate-dynamic-programming-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we develop a Markov decision process (MDP) model for an online bug triage task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adptriage-approximate-dynamic-programming-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Active Learning on Heteroskedastic Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-active-learning-on-heteroskedastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we demonstrate the catastrophic failure of these active learning algorithms on heteroskedastic distributions and propose a fine-tuning-based approach to mitigate these failures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-active-learning-on-heteroskedastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Deep Image Compression via Content-Adaptive Optimization with Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-deep-image-compression-via-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task aims to compress images belonging to arbitrary domains, such as natural images, line drawings, and comics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-deep-image-compression-via-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Multimodal Fusion for Generalizable Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-multimodal-fusion-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, in this paper, we propose DMF, a Deep Multimodal Fusion network for the general scenarios on person re-identification task, where rich semantic knowledge is introduced to assist in feature representation learning during the pre-training stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-multimodal-fusion-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exponentially Converging Particle Method for the Mixed Nash Equilibrium of Continuous Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exponentially-converging-particle-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of computing mixed Nash equilibria of two-player zero-sum games with continuous sets of pure strategies and with first-order access to the payoff function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exponentially-converging-particle-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-Based Autoencoders for Volumetric Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-based-autoencoders-for-volumetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoencoders allow to reconstruct a given input from a small set of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-based-autoencoders-for-volumetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thunderstorm nowcasting with deep learning: a multi-hazard data fusion model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thunderstorm-nowcasting-with-deep-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this need, we present a deep learning model that can be adapted to different hazard types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thunderstorm-nowcasting-with-deep-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Winoground Hard? Investigating Failures in Visuolinguistic Compositionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-is-winoground-hard-investigating-failures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent visuolinguistic pre-trained models show promising progress on various end tasks such as image retrieval and video captioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-is-winoground-hard-investigating-failures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2E Refined Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2e-refined-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the well-known MR-to-text E2E dataset has been used by many researchers, its MR-text pairs include many deletion/insertion/substitution errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2e-refined-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact Of Missing Data Imputation On The Fairness And Accuracy Of Graph Node Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-missing-data-imputation-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze the effect on fairness in the context of graph data (node attributes) imputation using different embedding and neural network methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-missing-data-imputation-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Cam: Imaging Periodic Signals in Real-Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-cam-imaging-periodic-signals-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the important design parameters for fullsensor frequency imaging and present Frequency Cam, an open-source implementation as a ROS node that can run on a single core of a laptop CPU at more than 50 million events per second.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-cam-imaging-periodic-signals-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the detection of synthetic images generated by diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-detection-of-synthetic-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past decade, there has been tremendous progress in creating synthetic media, mainly thanks to the development of powerful methods based on generative adversarial networks (GAN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-detection-of-synthetic-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Only Training for Image Captioning using Noise-Injected CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-only-training-for-image-captioning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the task of image-captioning using only the CLIP model and additional text data at training time, and no additional captioned images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-only-training-for-image-captioning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Policies Beat Professional-Level Go AIs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-policies-beat-professional-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, the adversary wins by tricking KataGo into ending the game prematurely at a point that is favorable to the adversary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-policies-beat-professional-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Perturbation Attack on Differentiable No-Reference Image- and Video-Quality Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-perturbation-attack-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indeed, if an attack can confuse the metric, an attacker can easily increase quality scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-perturbation-attack-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Graph Neural Network Inference at Large Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-graph-neural-network-inference-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have demonstrated excellent performance in a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-graph-neural-network-inference-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can maker-taker fees prevent algorithmic cooperation in market making?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-maker-taker-fees-prevent-algorithmic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a semi-realistic market simulator, independent reinforcement learning algorithms may facilitate market makers to maintain wide spreads even without communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-maker-taker-fees-prevent-algorithmic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARO: Learned Acquisition and Reconstruction Optimization to accelerate Quantitative Susceptibility Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laro-learned-acquisition-and-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our new framework, called Learned Acquisition and Reconstruction Optimization (LARO), which aims to accelerate the multi-echo gradient echo (mGRE) pulse sequence for QSM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laro-learned-acquisition-and-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Out-of-Distribution Generalization of Neural Algorithmic Reasoning Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the OOD generalization of neural algorithmic reasoning tasks, where the goal is to learn an algorithm (e. g., sorting, breadth-first search, and depth-first search) from input-output pairs using deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Training with Complementary Labels: On the Benefit of Gradually Informative Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-with-complementary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training (AT) with imperfect supervision is significant but receives limited attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-training-with-complementary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy classification: a deep learning approach for classifying Sloan Digital Sky Survey images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-classification-a-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, after considering the minute information which we know about galaxies, it is necessary to classify galaxies into more than eight classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-classification-a-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-Aware Subgraph Neural Networks with Data-Efficient Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-subgraph-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) Prevailing graph augmentation methods for GEL, including rule-based, sample-based, adaptive, and automated methods, are not suitable for augmenting subgraphs because a subgraph contains fewer nodes but richer information such as position, neighbor, and structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-subgraph-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Deduction with Incomplete Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A growing body of work studies how to answer a question or verify a claim by generating a natural language "proof": a chain of deductive inferences yielding the answer based on a set of premises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Task-Aware Effective Brain Connectivity for fMRI Analysis with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-task-aware-effective-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better adapt GNNs for fMRI analysis, we propose TBDS, an end-to-end framework based on \underline{T}ask-aware \underline{B}rain connectivity \underline{D}AG (short for Directed Acyclic Graph) \underline{S}tructure generation for fMRI analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-task-aware-effective-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchFL: A Performant Library for Bootstrapping Federated Learning Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchfl-a-performant-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increased legislation around data privacy, federated learning (FL) has emerged as a promising technique that allows the clients (end-user) to collaboratively train deep learning (DL) models without transferring and storing the data in a centralized, third-party server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchfl-a-performant-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GMF: General Multimodal Fusion Framework for Correspondence Outlier Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gmf-general-multimodal-fusion-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose General Multimodal Fusion (GMF) to learn to reject the correspondence outliers by leveraging both the structure and texture information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gmf-general-multimodal-fusion-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Variational Autoencoders with Density Gap-based Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-variational-autoencoders-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are effective ways proposed to prevent posterior collapse in VAEs, but we observe that they in essence make trade-offs between posterior collapse and hole problem, i. e., mismatch between the aggregated posterior distribution and the prior distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-variational-autoencoders-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretability in the Wild: a Circuit for Indirect Object Identification in GPT-2 small</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-in-the-wild-a-circuit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research in mechanistic interpretability seeks to explain behaviors of machine learning models in terms of their internal components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-in-the-wild-a-circuit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONDAQA: A Contrastive Reading Comprehension Dataset for Reasoning about Negation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condaqa-a-contrastive-reading-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also have workers make three kinds of edits to the passage -- paraphrasing the negated statement, changing the scope of the negation, and reversing the negation -- resulting in clusters of question-answer pairs that are difficult for models to answer with spurious shortcuts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/condaqa-a-contrastive-reading-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-text based multi-modal training with bidirectional attention for improved speech recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-text-based-multi-modal-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To let the state-of-the-art end-to-end ASR model enjoy data efficiency, as well as much more unpaired text data by multi-modal training, one needs to address two problems: 1) the synchronicity of feature sampling rates between speech and language (aka text data); 2) the homogeneity of the learned representations from two encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-text-based-multi-modal-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composite Feature Selection using Deep Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-feature-selection-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To do so, we define predictive groups in terms of linear and non-linear interactions between features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-feature-selection-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization of Oblivious Decision Tree Ensembles Evaluation for CPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-oblivious-decision-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We increase performance by 20-40% using AVX2 instructions without quality impact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-oblivious-decision-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapter-Based Extension of Multi-Speaker Text-to-Speech Model for New Speakers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapter-based-extension-of-multi-speaker-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the proposed approach, a few small adapter modules are added to the original network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapter-based-extension-of-multi-speaker-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Imbalanced Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-imbalanced-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated Machine Learning has grown very successful in automating the time-consuming, iterative tasks of machine learning model development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-imbalanced-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge the Gap Between Architecture Spaces via A Cross-Domain Predictor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridge-the-gap-between-architecture-spaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this issue, we propose a Cross-Domain Predictor (CDP), which is trained based on the existing NAS benchmark datasets (e. g., NAS-Bench-101), but can be used to find high-performance architectures in large-scale search spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridge-the-gap-between-architecture-spaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Vision-Language Models with Less Bimodal Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-vision-language-models-with-less</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We experiment with a high-performing vision-language model, and analyze the effect of bimodal supervision on three vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-vision-language-models-with-less</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SADT: Combining Sharpness-Aware Minimization with Self-Distillation for Improved Model Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadt-combining-sharpness-aware-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods for improving deep neural network training times and model generalizability consist of various data augmentation, regularization, and optimization approaches, which tend to be sensitive to hyperparameter settings and make reproducibility more challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sadt-combining-sharpness-aware-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARE: Causality Reasoning for Empathetic Responses by Conditional Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-causality-reasoning-for-empathetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches to empathetic response generation incorporate emotion causalities to enhance comprehension of both the user's feelings and experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-causality-reasoning-for-empathetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rating Triggers for Collateral-Inclusive XVA via Machine Learning and SDEs on Lie Groups</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rating-triggers-for-collateral-inclusive-xva</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we model the rating process of an entity by using a geometrical approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rating-triggers-for-collateral-inclusive-xva</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T5lephone: Bridging Speech and Text Self-supervised Models for Spoken Language Understanding via Phoneme level T5</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t5lephone-bridging-speech-and-text-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In Spoken language understanding (SLU), a natural solution is concatenating pre-trained speech models (e. g. HuBERT) and pretrained language models (PLM, e. g. T5).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t5lephone-bridging-speech-and-text-self</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
