<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 09:12:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolution on Rotationally Scanned Photoacoustic Microscopy Images Incorporating Scanning Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-on-rotationally-scanned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there is a trend to incorporate deep learning into the scanning process to further increase the scanning speed. Yet, most such attempts are performed for raster scanning while those for rotational scanning are relatively rare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-on-rotationally-scanned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Novel Object Recognition and Spontaneous Location Recognition Machine Learning Analysis Techniques in Alzheimer's Mice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-novel-object-recognition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding object recognition patterns in mice is crucial for advancing behavioral neuroscience and has significant implications for human health, particularly in the realm of Alzheimer's research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-novel-object-recognition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMS: Redundancy-Minimizing Point Cloud Sampling for Real-Time Pose Estimation in Degenerated Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rms-redundancy-minimizing-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to density normalization, our method builds on the fact that linear and planar surfaces contain a high level of redundancy propagated into iterative estimation pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rms-redundancy-minimizing-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A churn prediction dataset from the telecom sector: a new benchmark for uplift modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-churn-prediction-dataset-from-the-telecom</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uplift modeling, also known as individual treatment effect (ITE) estimation, is an important approach for data-driven decision making that aims to identify the causal impact of an intervention on individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-churn-prediction-dataset-from-the-telecom</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-survey on outlier and anomaly detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-survey-on-outlier-and-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From this comprehensive collection, a subset of 56 papers that claim to be general surveys on outlier detection is selected using a snowball search technique to enhance field coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-survey-on-outlier-and-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeasFire as a Multivariate Earth System Datacube for Wildfire Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seasfire-as-a-multivariate-earth-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global occurrence, scale, and frequency of wildfires pose significant threats to ecosystem services and human livelihoods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seasfire-as-a-multivariate-earth-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTMO: Towards High-Performance One-Stage Real-Time Multi-Person Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmo-towards-high-performance-one-stage-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-time multi-person pose estimation presents significant challenges in balancing speed and precision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmo-towards-high-performance-one-stage-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperRouter: Towards Efficient Training and Inference of Sparse Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperrouter-towards-efficient-training-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By routing input tokens to only a few split experts, Sparse Mixture-of-Experts has enabled efficient training of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperrouter-towards-efficient-training-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Robustness in Multi-label Classification: A Data Augmentation Strategy against Imbalance and Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-robustness-in-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-label classification poses challenges due to imbalanced and noisy labels in training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-robustness-in-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-inspired Computing Based on Machine Learning And Deep Learning:A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-inspired-computing-based-on-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The continuous development of artificial intelligence has a profound impact on biomedical research and other fields. Brain-inspired computing is an important intersection of multimodal technology and biomedical field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-inspired-computing-based-on-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Compression: Reduced Order Modelling of Latent Features in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-compression-reduced-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the substantial scale of Large Language Models (LLMs), the direct application of conventional compression methodologies proves impractical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-compression-reduced-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Conformal Prediction Regions by Optimizing Convex Shape Templates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-conformal-prediction-regions-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, little work has gone into finding non-conformity score functions that produce prediction regions that are multi-modal and practical, i. e., that can efficiently be used in engineering applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-conformal-prediction-regions-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Content Generation with Causal Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-content-generation-with-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering causal reasoning in visual content generation is significant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-content-generation-with-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP in Medical Imaging: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-in-medical-imaging-a-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP), a straightforward yet effective pre-training paradigm, successfully introduces semantic-rich text supervision to vision models and has demonstrated promising results in various tasks due to its generalizability and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-in-medical-imaging-a-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Object Detection in Autonomous Driving using Spiking Neural Networks: Performance, Energy Consumption Analysis, and Insights into Open-set Object Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-object-detection-in-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides performance, efficiency is a key design driver of technologies supporting vehicular perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-object-detection-in-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide-and-Conquer Attack: Harnessing the Power of LLM to Bypass the Censorship of Text-to-Image Generation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-attack-harnessing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce the Divide-and-Conquer Attack to circumvent the safety filters of state-of-the-art text-to-image models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-attack-harnessing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Latent Diffusion with Flow Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-latent-diffusion-with-flow-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that introducing FM between the Diffusion model and the convolutional decoder offers high-resolution image synthesis with reduced computational cost and model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-latent-diffusion-with-flow-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Confidence Multi-View Hashing for Multimedia Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-confidence-multi-view-hashing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, an adaptive confidence multi-view network is employed to measure the confidence of each view and then fuse multi-view features through a weighted summation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-confidence-multi-view-hashing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-MI: Enhancing Model Inversion Attacks via Patch-Based Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mi-enhancing-model-inversion-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach allows the synthesis of images that are similar to the target dataset distribution, even in cases of dissimilar auxiliary dataset distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mi-enhancing-model-inversion-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjustable Robust Transformer for High Myopia Screening in Optical Coherence Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjustable-robust-transformer-for-high-myopia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measurements of spherical equivalent and axial length are the gold standards for identifying high myopia, but the available image data for matching them is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjustable-robust-transformer-for-high-myopia</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-Contextual Discrepancy Information Compensation for GAN Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-contextual-discrepancy-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SDIC follows a "compensate-and-edit" paradigm and successfully bridges the gap in image details between the original image and the reconstructed/edited image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-contextual-discrepancy-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication Cost Reduction for Subgraph Counting under Local Differential Privacy via Hash Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-cost-reduction-for-subgraph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We suggest the use of hash functions to cut down the communication costs when counting subgraphs under edge local differential privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-cost-reduction-for-subgraph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahpatron: A New Budgeted Online Kernel Learning Machine with Tighter Mistake Bound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ahpatron-a-new-budgeted-online-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the mistake bound of online kernel learning on a budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ahpatron-a-new-budgeted-online-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Multi-Task Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-multi-task-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For further speed-up reduced physical models of the system can be incorporated into the optimization to accelerate the process, since the models are able to offer an approximation of the actual system, and sampling from them is significantly cheaper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-multi-task-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Pseudo Labels for Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-pseudo-labels-for-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the pseudo-label method has demonstrated considerable success in semi-supervised object detection tasks, this paper uncovers notable limitations within this approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-pseudo-labels-for-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MWSIS: Multimodal Weakly Supervised Instance Segmentation with 2D Box Annotations for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mwsis-multimodal-weakly-supervised-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instance segmentation is a fundamental research in computer vision, especially in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mwsis-multimodal-weakly-supervised-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perseus: Removing Energy Bloat from Large Model Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perseus-removing-energy-bloat-from-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large AI models on numerous GPUs consumes a massive amount of energy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perseus-removing-energy-bloat-from-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNBG-Generated Test Suite for Box-Constrained Numerical Global Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnbg-generated-test-suite-for-box-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This document introduces a set of 24 box-constrained numerical global optimization problem instances, systematically constructed using the Generalized Numerical Benchmark Generator (GNBG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnbg-generated-test-suite-for-box-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interfacing Foundation Models' Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interfacing-foundation-models-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed interface is adaptive to new tasks, and new models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interfacing-foundation-models-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-Guided Transformer for Federated Multi-Label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-transformer-for-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, it is still challenging for FL to deal with user heterogeneity in their local data distribution in the real-world FL scenario, and this issue becomes even more severe in multi-label image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-transformer-for-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Sequential Recommenders through Distributionally Robust Optimization over System Exposure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-sequential-recommenders-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we introduce a penalty to items with high exposure probability to avoid the overestimation of user preference for biased samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-sequential-recommenders-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toxic language detection: a systematic survey of Arabic datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toxic-language-detection-a-systematic-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper offers a comprehensive survey of Arabic datasets focused on online toxic language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toxic-language-detection-a-systematic-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment for Honesty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-for-honesty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research has made significant strides in applying alignment techniques to enhance the helpfulness and harmlessness of large language models (LLMs) in accordance with human intentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-for-honesty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAC-TCN: Temporal Convolutional Networks with Causal Dilated Neighborhood Attention for Emotion Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nac-tcn-temporal-convolutional-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method known as Neighborhood Attention with Convolutions TCN (NAC-TCN) which incorporates the benefits of attention and Temporal Convolutional Networks while ensuring that causal relationships are understood which results in a reduction in computation and memory cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nac-tcn-temporal-convolutional-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeInit: Bridging Initialization Gap in Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeinit-bridging-initialization-gap-in-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though diffusion-based video generation has witnessed rapid progress, the inference results of existing models still exhibit unsatisfactory temporal consistency and unnatural dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeinit-bridging-initialization-gap-in-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNBG: A Generalized and Configurable Benchmark Generator for Continuous Numerical Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnbg-a-generalized-and-configurable-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To effectively assess, validate, and compare optimization algorithms, it is crucial to use a benchmark test suite that encompasses a diverse range of problem instances with various characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnbg-a-generalized-and-configurable-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gaussian-Linear Hidden Markov model: a Python package</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gaussian-linear-hidden-markov-model-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the Gaussian-Linear Hidden Markov model (GLHMM), a generalisation of different types of HMMs commonly used in neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gaussian-linear-hidden-markov-model-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual large language models leak human stereotypes across language boundaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-large-language-models-leak-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate human stereotypes and stereotypical associations manifested in multilingual large language models such as mBERT, mT5, and ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-large-language-models-leak-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaxQ: Multi-Axis Query for N:M Sparsity Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxq-multi-axis-query-for-n-m-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, a sparsity strategy that gradually increases the percentage of N:M weight blocks is applied, which allows the network to heal from the pruning-induced damage progressively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maxq-multi-axis-query-for-n-m-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartEdit: Exploring Complex Instruction-based Image Editing with Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartedit-exploring-complex-instruction-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both quantitative and qualitative results on this evaluation dataset indicate that our SmartEdit surpasses previous methods, paving the way for the practical application of complex instruction-based image editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartedit-exploring-complex-instruction-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intraoperative 2D/3D Image Registration via Differentiable X-ray Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intraoperative-2d-3d-image-registration-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preoperatively, a CNN is trained to regress the pose of a randomly oriented synthetic X-ray rendered from the preoperative CT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intraoperative-2d-3d-image-registration-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compound Text-Guided Prompt Tuning via Image-Adaptive Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-text-guided-prompt-tuning-via-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce text supervision to the optimization of prompts, which enables two benefits: 1) releasing the model reliance on the pre-defined category names during inference, thereby enabling more flexible prompt generation; 2) reducing the number of inputs to the text encoder, which decreases GPU memory consumption significantly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compound-text-guided-prompt-tuning-via-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Meta-Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-meta-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We call these approaches meta-prompting, or prompting to obtain prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-meta-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupling Meta-Reinforcement Learning with Gaussian Task Contexts and Skills</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-meta-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a framework called decoupled meta-reinforcement learning (DCMRL), which (1) contrastively restricts the learning of task contexts through pulling in similar task contexts within the same task and pushing away different task contexts of different tasks, and (2) utilizes a Gaussian quantization variational autoencoder (GQ-VAE) for clustering the Gaussian distributions of the task contexts and skills respectively, and decoupling the exploration and learning processes of their spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupling-meta-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructAny2Pix: Flexible Visual Editing via Multimodal Instruction Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructany2pix-flexible-visual-editing-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that our system can perform a series of novel instruction-guided editing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructany2pix-flexible-visual-editing-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DYAD: A Descriptive Yet Abjuring Density efficient approximation to linear neural network layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyad-a-descriptive-yet-abjuring-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DYAD is based on a bespoke near-sparse matrix structure which approximates the dense "weight" matrix W that matrix-multiplies the input in the typical realization of such a layer, a. k. a DENSE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyad-a-descriptive-yet-abjuring-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDiff: Spatio-temporal Diffusion for Continuous Stochastic Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stdiff-spatio-temporal-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting future frames of a video is challenging because it is difficult to learn the uncertainty of the underlying factors influencing their contents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stdiff-spatio-temporal-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concrete Subspace Learning based Interference Elimination for Multi-task Model Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concrete-subspace-learning-based-interference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the upper level, we focus on learning a shared Concrete mask to identify the subspace, while at the inner level, model merging is performed to maximize the performance of the merged model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concrete-subspace-learning-based-interference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-MixFormer: UNet-like Transformer with Mix-Attention for Efficient Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-mixformer-unet-like-transformer-with-mix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation has witnessed remarkable advancements with the adaptation of the Transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-mixformer-unet-like-transformer-with-mix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Gaze for Contrastive Learning toward Computer-Assisted Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-gaze-for-contrastive-learning-toward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accordingly, we introduce the Medical contrastive Gaze Image Pre-training (McGIP) as a plug-and-play module for contrastive learning frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-gaze-for-contrastive-learning-toward</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
