<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 21:08:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SmartKex: Machine Learning Assisted SSH Keys Extraction From The Heap Dump</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartkex-machine-learning-assisted-ssh-keys</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A commonly used method in digital forensics is to extract data from the main memory of a digital device.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartkex-machine-learning-assisted-ssh-keys</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Observability during DRL for Robot Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-observability-during-drl-for-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) has made tremendous advances in both simulated and real-world robot control tasks in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-observability-during-drl-for-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Some other poor soul's problems": a peer recommendation intervention for health-related social support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-other-poor-soul-s-problems-a-peer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results support the usefulness and demand for peer recommendation and suggest benefits to evaluating larger peer recommendation interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-other-poor-soul-s-problems-a-peer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication-Efficient and Privacy-Preserving Feature-based Federated Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-and-privacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to improve the communication efficiency, we in this paper propose the feature-based federated transfer learning as an innovative approach to reduce the uplink payload by more than five orders of magnitude compared to that of existing approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-and-privacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switchable Online Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchable-online-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of focusing on the accuracy gap at test phase by the existing arts, the core idea of SwitOKD is to adaptively calibrate the gap at training phase, namely distillation gap, via a switching strategy between two modes -- expert mode (pause the teacher while keep the student learning) and learning mode (restart the teacher).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchable-online-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified State Representation Learning under Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-state-representation-learning-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The capacity for rapid domain adaptation is important to increasing the applicability of reinforcement learning (RL) to real world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-state-representation-learning-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenLoco: Generalized Locomotion Controllers for Quadrupedal Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genloco-generalized-locomotion-controllers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a framework for training generalized locomotion (GenLoco) controllers for quadrupedal robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genloco-generalized-locomotion-controllers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Next Action by Modeling the Abstract Goal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-next-action-by-modeling-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is through the submission of this paper that our method is currently the new state-of-the-art for action anticipation in EK55 and EGTEA Gaze+ https://competitions. codalab. org/competitions/20071#results Code available at https://github. com/debadityaroy/Abstract_Goal]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-next-action-by-modeling-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Allocation to Agents with Restrictions: Maximizing Likelihood with Minimum Compromise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-allocation-to-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus is on resource allocation problems where agents may have restrictions that make them incompatible with some resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-allocation-to-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Network-based Internet Censorship via Latent Feature Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-network-based-internet-censorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To estimate the probability of censorship events from the inferred latent features, we rely on a densely connected multi-layer neural network model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-network-based-internet-censorship</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANCL: Multimodal Review Helpfulness Prediction with Selective Attention and Natural Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sancl-multimodal-review-helpfulness-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the boom of e-commerce, Multimodal Review Helpfulness Prediction (MRHP), which aims to sort product reviews according to the predicted helpfulness scores has become a research hotspot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sancl-multimodal-review-helpfulness-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Much Does Prosody Help Turn-taking? Investigations using Voice Activity Projection Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-does-prosody-help-turn-taking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Turn-taking is a fundamental aspect of human communication and can be described as the ability to take turns, project upcoming turn shifts, and supply backchannels at appropriate locations throughout a conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-much-does-prosody-help-turn-taking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness in Forecasting of Observations of Linear Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-in-forecasting-of-observations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In machine learning, training data often capture the behaviour of multiple subgroups of some underlying human population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-in-forecasting-of-observations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Feature Statistics Mapping for Generalized Screen Content Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-feature-statistics-mapping-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The underlying mechanism of the proposed approach is based upon the wild assumption that the SCIs, which are not physically acquired, still obey certain statistics that could be understood in a learning fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-feature-statistics-mapping-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model interpretation using improved local regression with variable importance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-interpretation-using-improved-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A fundamental question on the use of ML models concerns the explanation of their predictions for increasing transparency in decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-interpretation-using-improved-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexical Simplification Benchmarks for English, Portuguese, and Spanish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexical-simplification-benchmarks-for-english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To showcase the usability of the dataset, we adapt two state-of-the-art lexical simplification systems with differing architectures (neural vs.\ non-neural) to all three languages (English, Spanish, and Brazilian Portuguese) and evaluate their performances on our new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexical-simplification-benchmarks-for-english</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attitude-Guided Loop Closure for Cameras with Negative Plane</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attitude-guided-loop-closure-for-cameras-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we propose a loop closure framework with a new outlier rejection method based on the unit length representation, to improve the accuracy of LF-VIO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attitude-guided-loop-closure-for-cameras-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSL: A Large-scale Chinese Scientific Literature Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csl-a-large-scale-chinese-scientific-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CSL can serve as a Chinese corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csl-a-large-scale-chinese-scientific-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Preserving Adversarial Code Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-preserving-adversarial-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the tremendous success of pre-trained language models (PrLMs) for source code comprehension tasks, current literature studies either ways to further improve the performance (generalization) of PrLMs, or their robustness against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-preserving-adversarial-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiBiNet++:Improving FiBiNet by Greatly Reducing Model Size for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fibinet-improving-fibinet-by-greatly-reducing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Click-Through Rate(CTR) estimation has become one of the most fundamental tasks in many real-world applications and various deep models have been proposed to resolve this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fibinet-improving-fibinet-by-greatly-reducing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Distributional Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-distributional-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this fundamental issue, we propose Wasserstein Distributional Learning (WDL), a flexible density-on-scalar regression modeling framework that starts with the Wasserstein distance $W_2$ as a proper metric for the space of density outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-distributional-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical few-shot segmentation for cross-institution male pelvic structures with spatial registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-few-shot-segmentation-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prowess that makes few-shot learning desirable in medical image analysis is the efficient use of the support image data, which are labelled to classify or segment new classes, a task that otherwise requires substantially more training images and expert annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-few-shot-segmentation-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse Image Frequency for Long-tailed Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-image-frequency-for-long-tailed-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The long-tailed distribution is a common phenomenon in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-image-frequency-for-long-tailed-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Suicide Risk in Online Counseling Services: A Study in a Low-Resource Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-suicide-risk-in-online-counseling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increased awareness of situations of mental crisis and their societal impact, online services providing emergency support are becoming commonplace in many countries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-suicide-risk-in-online-counseling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Pre-trained Language Models' Understanding of Distributivity via Causal Mediation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-pre-trained-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To what extent do pre-trained language models grasp semantic knowledge regarding the phenomenon of distributivity?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-pre-trained-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning When to Say "I Don't Know"</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-when-to-say-i-don-t-know</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new Reject Option Classification technique to identify and remove regions of uncertainty in the decision space for a given neural classifier and dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-when-to-say-i-don-t-know</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenMixup: Open Mixup Toolbox and Benchmark for Visual Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmixup-open-mixup-toolbox-and-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the remarkable progress of deep neural networks in computer vision, data mixing augmentation techniques are widely studied to alleviate problems of degraded generalization when the amount of training data is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmixup-open-mixup-toolbox-and-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning for Optimal Intervention Design in Causal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-for-optimal-intervention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This acquisition function is evaluated in closed form, allowing for efficient optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-for-optimal-intervention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Batch Bayesian Optimization via Particle Gradient Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-bayesian-optimization-via-particle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we reformulate batch BO as an optimisation problem over the space of probability measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/batch-bayesian-optimization-via-particle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Before You Act: Generalising to Novel Environments by Asking Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-before-you-act-generalising-to-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the ability of an RL agent to learn to ask natural language questions as a tool to understand its environment and achieve greater generalisation performance in novel, temporally-extended environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-before-you-act-generalising-to-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Diversity-tolerant RDF-stores</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-diversity-tolerant-rdf-stores</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to designing RDF-stores with the goal of improving the consistency and predictability of query performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-diversity-tolerant-rdf-stores</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subdiffusive semantic evolution in Indo-European languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subdiffusive-semantic-evolution-in-indo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do words change their meaning?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subdiffusive-semantic-evolution-in-indo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IR-LPR: Large Scale of Iranian License Plate Recognition Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-lpr-large-scale-of-iranian-license-plate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, the largest Iranian dataset for recognizing the characters of a license plate has 5, 000 images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ir-lpr-large-scale-of-iranian-license-plate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Neural Kernel Embeddings for General Activations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-neural-kernel-embeddings-for-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, most prior works on neural kernels have focused on the ReLU activation, mainly due to its popularity but also due to the difficulty of computing such kernels for general activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-neural-kernel-embeddings-for-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCIBI++: Soft Mining Contextual Information Beyond Image for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcibi-soft-mining-contextual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel soft mining contextual information beyond image paradigm named MCIBI++ to further boost the pixel-level representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcibi-soft-mining-contextual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granger Causal Chain Discovery for Sepsis-Associated Derangements via Multivariate Hawkes Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granger-causal-chain-discovery-for-sepsis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern health care systems are conducting continuous, automated surveillance of the electronic medical record (EMR) to identify adverse events with increasing frequency; however, many events such as sepsis do not have clearly elucidated prodromes (i. e., event chains) that can be used to identify and intercept the adverse event early in its course.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granger-causal-chain-discovery-for-sepsis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Confidence-guided Shape Completion for Robotic Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-confidence-guided-shape-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many robotic tasks involving some form of 3D visual perception greatly benefit from a complete knowledge of the working environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-confidence-guided-shape-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting to Non-Centered Languages for Zero-shot Multilingual Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-centered-languages-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual neural machine translation can translate unseen language pairs during training, i. e. zero-shot translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-to-non-centered-languages-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retinal Image Restoration and Vessel Segmentation using Modified Cycle-CBAM and CBAM-UNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retinal-image-restoration-and-vessel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The retinal vessel segmentation performance was compared with the ground-truth fundus images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retinal-image-restoration-and-vessel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F-COREF: Fast, Accurate and Easy to Use Coreference Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-coref-fast-accurate-and-easy-to-use</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce fastcoref, a python package for fast, accurate, and easy-to-use English coreference resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-coref-fast-accurate-and-easy-to-use</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Document Scientific Summarization from a Knowledge Graph-Centric View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-scientific-summarization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Document Scientific Summarization (MDSS) aims to produce coherent and concise summaries for clusters of topic-relevant scientific papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-document-scientific-summarization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-Aware JPEG Image Compression: A Multi-Objective Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-aware-jpeg-image-compression-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, two Pareto-based methods, including a non-dominated sorting genetic algorithm (NSGA-II) and a reference-point-based NSGA-II (NSGA-III) are used for the embedding scheme, and two Pareto-based algorithms, EnNSGAII and EnNSGAIII, are presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-aware-jpeg-image-compression-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparsity-guided Network Design for Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-guided-network-design-for-frame</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, we achieve a considerable performance gain with a quarter of the size of the original AdaCoF.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-guided-network-design-for-frame</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEACH: Temporal Action Composition for 3D Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teach-temporal-action-composition-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, our goal is to enable the synthesis of a series of actions, which we refer to as temporal action composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teach-temporal-action-composition-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Alignment of Multi-Task Feature and Label Spaces for Emotion Cause Pair Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-alignment-of-multi-task-feature-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first propose a feature-task alignment to explicitly model the specific emotion-&cause-specific features and the shared interactive feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-alignment-of-multi-task-feature-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoder Based Iterative Modeling and Multivariate Time-Series Subsequence Clustering Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-iterative-modeling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[No meaningful and coherent measurement data which could be used for training a CbM model would emerge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-iterative-modeling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>clusterBMA: Bayesian model averaging for clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clusterbma-bayesian-model-averaging-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we introduce clusterBMA, a method that enables weighted model averaging across results from multiple unsupervised clustering algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clusterbma-bayesian-model-averaging-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelling Patient Trajectories Using Multimodal Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-patient-trajectories-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we demonstrate the potential of the sequence-based architecture using a sliding window mechanism to represent the input data, attaining comparable performances to other existing solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-patient-trajectories-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathology Synthesis of 3D Consistent Cardiac MR Im-ages Using 2D VAEs and GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathology-synthesis-of-3d-consistent-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We devise an approach for label manipulation in the latent space of the trained VAE model, namely pathology synthesis, aiming to synthesize a series of pseudo-pathological synthetic subjects with characteristics of a desired heart disease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathology-synthesis-of-3d-consistent-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MassMIND: Massachusetts Maritime INfrared Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massmind-massachusetts-maritime-infrared</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the dataset focuses on the coastal terrain it can equally help deep sea use cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/massmind-massachusetts-maritime-infrared</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
