<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 21:06:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Domain Adaptation for Breaking the Limits of Low-quality Fundus Image Quality Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-domain-adaptation-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most of the existing image enhancement methods mainly focus on improving the image quality by leveraging the guidance of high-quality images, which is difficult to be collected in medical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-domain-adaptation-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USER: Unified Semantic Enhancement with Momentum Contrast for Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-unified-semantic-enhancement-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) It limits the scale of negative sample pairs by employing the mini-batch based end-to-end training mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/user-unified-semantic-enhancement-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models as a Defense against Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-models-as-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Networks are infamously sensitive to small perturbations in their inputs, making them vulnerable to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-models-as-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Inverse Rendering via Hierarchical Decoupling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-inverse-rendering-via-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous face inverse rendering methods often require synthetic data with ground truth and/or professional equipment like a lighting stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-inverse-rendering-via-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SwaNNFlight System: On-the-Fly Sim-to-Real Adaptation via Anchored Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-swannflight-system-on-the-fly-sim-to-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And (iii) anchor critics to help stabilize the fine-tuning of agents during sim-to-real transfer, online learning from real data while retaining behavior optimized in simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-swannflight-system-on-the-fly-sim-to-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syllable Subword Tokens for Open Vocabulary Speech Recognition in Malayalam</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syllable-subword-tokens-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a hybrid automatic speech recognition (ASR) system, a pronunciation lexicon (PL) and a language model (LM) are essential to correctly retrieve spoken word sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syllable-subword-tokens-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CS-lol: a Dataset of Viewer Comment with Scene in E-sports Live-streaming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cs-lol-a-dataset-of-viewer-comment-with-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Billions of live-streaming viewers share their opinions on scenes they are watching in real-time and interact with the event, commentators as well as other viewers via text comments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cs-lol-a-dataset-of-viewer-comment-with-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reinforcement learning path planning approach for range-only underwater target localization with autonomous vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-path-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underwater target localization using range-only and single-beacon (ROSB) techniques with autonomous vehicles has been used recently to improve the limitations of more complex methods, such as long baseline and ultra-short baseline systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-path-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syntactically Robust Training on Partially-Observed Data for Open Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntactically-robust-training-on-partially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a syntactically robust training framework that enables models to be trained on a syntactic-abundant distribution based on diverse paraphrase generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntactically-robust-training-on-partially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing Firm Conduct</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-firm-conduct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While researchers test conduct via model selection and assessment, we present advantages of Rivers and Vuong (2002) (RV) model selection under misspecification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-firm-conduct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expected Gradients of Maxout Networks and Consequences to Parameter Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expected-gradients-of-maxout-networks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the gradients of a maxout network with respect to inputs and parameters and obtain bounds for the moments depending on the architecture and the parameter distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expected-gradients-of-maxout-networks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Distillation: A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-a-comprehensive-review</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we provide a systematic taxonomy of current methodologies in this area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-a-comprehensive-review</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2nd Swiss German Speech to Standard German Text Shared Task at SwissText 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2nd-swiss-german-speech-to-standard-german</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the results and findings of the 2nd Swiss German speech to Standard German text shared task at SwissText 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2nd-swiss-german-speech-to-standard-german</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the State of German (Abstractive) Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-state-of-german-abstractive-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attribute poor evaluation quality to a variety of different factors, which are investigated in more detail in this work: A lack of qualitative (and diverse) gold data considered for training, understudied (and untreated) positional biases in some of the existing datasets, and the lack of easily accessible and streamlined pre-processing strategies or analysis tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-state-of-german-abstractive-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithms for Acyclic Weighted Finite-State Automata with Failure Arcs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-for-acyclic-weighted-finite-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pathsum in ordinary acyclic WFSAs is efficiently computed by the backward algorithm in time $O(|E|)$, where $E$ is the set of transitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithms-for-acyclic-weighted-finite-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Improving the Explainability of Text-based Information Retrieval with Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-improving-the-explainability-of-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a general architecture to incorporate knowledge graphs for XIR in various steps of the retrieval process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-improving-the-explainability-of-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLIGEN: Open-Set Grounded Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gligen-open-set-grounded-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale text-to-image diffusion models have made amazing advances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gligen-open-set-grounded-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Msanii: High Fidelity Music Synthesis on a Shoestring Budget</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msanii-high-fidelity-music-synthesis-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Msanii, a novel diffusion-based model for synthesizing long-context, high-fidelity music efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msanii-high-fidelity-music-synthesis-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case-Base Neural Networks: survival analysis with time-varying, higher-order interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case-base-neural-networks-survival-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the performance of CBNN to survival methods based on regression and neural networks in two simulations and two real data applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/case-base-neural-networks-survival-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDSTF: Transformer-based Diffusion probabilistic model for Sparse Time series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdstf-transformer-based-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series probabilistic forecasting with multi-dimensional and sporadic data (known as sparse data) has potential to implement monitoring kinds of physiological indices of patients in Intensive Care Unit (ICU).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdstf-transformer-based-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ankh: Optimized Protein Language Model Unlocks General-Purpose Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ankh-optimized-protein-language-model-unlocks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As opposed to scaling-up protein language models (PLMs), we seek improving performance via protein-specific optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ankh-optimized-protein-language-model-unlocks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Predictions for Very Small Data Sets: a case study on Open-Source Project Health Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-predictions-for-very-small-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, we present here a {\em landscape analytics} method (called SNEAK) that (a)~clusters the data to find the general landscape of the hyperparameters; then (b)~explores a few representatives from each part of that landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-predictions-for-very-small-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAGLE: Forensics of Deep Learning Backdoor Attack for Better Defense</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beagle-forensics-of-deep-learning-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attack forensics, a critical counter-measure for traditional cyber attacks, is hence of importance for defending model backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beagle-forensics-of-deep-learning-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAAL: Test-time Augmentation for Active Learning in Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taal-test-time-augmentation-for-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes Test-time Augmentation for Active Learning (TAAL), a novel semi-supervised active learning approach for segmentation that exploits the uncertainty information offered by data transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taal-test-time-augmentation-for-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Uncertain Feature Representation for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-uncertain-feature-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we improve the network generalization ability by modeling domain shifts with uncertainty (DSU), i. e., characterizing the feature statistics as uncertain distributions during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-uncertain-feature-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical and computational aspects of robust optimal transportation, with applications to statistics and machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-and-computational-aspects-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have been remarking that inference based on OT and on $W_p$ is sensitive to outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-and-computational-aspects-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodality Helps Unimodality: Cross-Modal Few-Shot Learning with Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodality-helps-unimodality-cross-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By repurposing class names as additional one-shot training samples, we achieve SOTA results with an embarrassingly simple linear classifier for vision-language adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodality-helps-unimodality-cross-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disambiguation of One-Shot Visual Classification Tasks: A Simplex-Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disambiguation-of-one-shot-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we introduce a downstream classifier meant to exploit the presence of multiple objects to improve the performance of few-shot classification, in the case of extreme settings where only one shot is given for its class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disambiguation-of-one-shot-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximally Compact and Separated Features with Regular Polytope Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximally-compact-and-separated-features-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) trained with the Softmax loss are widely used classification models for several vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximally-compact-and-separated-features-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvoAAA: An evolutionary methodology for automated \neural autoencoder architecture search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evoaaa-an-evolutionary-methodology-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning models work better when curated features are provided to them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evoaaa-an-evolutionary-methodology-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextileNet: A Material Taxonomy-based Fashion Textile Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textilenet-a-material-taxonomy-based-fashion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the same time, Net Zero is a global goal and the fashion industry is undergoing a significant change so that textile materials can be reused, repaired and recycled in a sustainable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textilenet-a-material-taxonomy-based-fashion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic expression generation via Variational Auto-Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-expression-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are many problems in physics, biology, and other natural sciences in which symbolic regression can provide valuable insights and discover new laws of nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-expression-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSVT: Dynamic Sparse Voxel Transformer with Rotated Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsvt-dynamic-sparse-voxel-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the sparse characteristics of point clouds, it is non-trivial to apply a standard transformer on sparse points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsvt-dynamic-sparse-voxel-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical study of the modulus as activation function in computer vision applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-study-of-the-modulus-as-activation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose a new non-monotonic activation function: the modulus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-study-of-the-modulus-as-activation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Diversity-Enhanced Feature Representation of Hyperspectral Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-diversity-enhanced-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of embedding the high-dimensional spatio-spectral information of hyperspectral (HS) images efficiently and effectively, oriented by feature diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-diversity-enhanced-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T2M-GPT: Generating Human Motion from Textual Descriptions with discrete Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2m-gpt-generating-human-motion-from-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we conduct analyses on HumanML3D and observe that the dataset size is a limitation of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t2m-gpt-generating-human-motion-from-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RedBit: An End-to-End Flexible Framework for Evaluating the Accuracy of Quantized CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redbit-an-end-to-end-flexible-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the large strides in accuracy obtained by CNNs have been derived from increasing the complexity of network topologies, which incurs sizeable performance and energy penalties in the training and inference of CNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redbit-an-end-to-end-flexible-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Time Lag in Dynamical Systems with Copula Entropy based Transfer Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-time-lag-in-dynamical-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we propose to use the CE-based estimator of TE to identify time lag in dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-time-lag-in-dynamical-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrysGNN : Distilling pre-trained knowledge to enhance property prediction for crystalline materials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crysgnn-distilling-pre-trained-knowledge-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To leverage these untapped data, this paper presents CrysGNN, a new pre-trained GNN framework for crystalline materials, which captures both node and graph level structural information of crystal graphs using a huge amount of unlabelled material data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crysgnn-distilling-pre-trained-knowledge-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMM: Reinforced Memory Management for Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmm-reinforced-memory-management-for-class-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class-Incremental Learning (CIL) [40] trains classifiers under a strict memory budget: in each incremental phase, learning is done for new data, most of which is abandoned to free space for the next phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmm-reinforced-memory-management-for-class-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge is Power, Understanding is Impact: Utility and Beyond Goals, Explanation Quality, and Fairness in Path Reasoning Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-is-power-understanding-is-impact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Path reasoning is a notable recommendation approach that models high-order user-product relations, based on a Knowledge Graph (KG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-is-power-understanding-is-impact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Spatial Equilibrium Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-spatial-equilibrium-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the spatial disequilibrium problem of modern object detectors and propose to quantify this ``spatial bias'' by measuring the detection performance over zones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-spatial-equilibrium-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-based Transfer Learning for Automatic Optical Inspection based on domain discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-transfer-learning-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, related research enhanced the network models by applying TL without considering the domain similarity among datasets, the data long-tailedness of a source dataset, and mainly used linear transformations to mitigate the lack of samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-based-transfer-learning-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCP: Neural Correspondence Prior for Effective Unsupervised Shape Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ncp-neural-correspondence-prior-for-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Neural Correspondence Prior (NCP), a new paradigm for computing correspondences between 3D shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ncp-neural-correspondence-prior-for-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Trajectory-Conditioned Relations to Predict Pedestrian Crossing Behavior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-trajectory-conditioned-relations-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In smart transportation, intelligent systems avoid potential collisions by predicting the intent of traffic agents, especially pedestrians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-trajectory-conditioned-relations-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTalk: A Multi-Modal Dialogue Dataset for Real-World Chitchat</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiktalk-a-multi-modal-dialogue-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with previous image-based dialogue datasets, the richer sources of context in TikTalk lead to a greater diversity of conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiktalk-a-multi-modal-dialogue-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\texttt{tasksource}$: Structured Dataset Preprocessing Annotations for Frictionless Extreme Multi-Task Learning and Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texttt-tasksource-structured-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release a dataset annotation framework and dataset annotations for more than 400 English tasks (https://github. com/sileod/tasksource).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texttt-tasksource-structured-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Stance of Authorities towards Rumors in Arabic Tweets: A Preliminary Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-stance-of-authorities-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe the task is useful to augment the sources of evidence utilized by existing rumor verification systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-stance-of-authorities-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conceptual Framework and Documentation Standards of Cystoscopic Media Content for Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conceptual-framework-and-documentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Background: The clinical documentation of cystoscopy includes visual and textual materials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conceptual-framework-and-documentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey of Graph-level Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-graph-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional approaches to learning a set of graphs tend to rely on hand-crafted features, such as substructures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-graph-level</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
