<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 09:12:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DA-STC: Domain Adaptive Video Semantic Segmentation via Spatio-Temporal Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-stc-domain-adaptive-video-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the challenge, we propose a novel DA-STC method for domain adaptive video semantic segmentation, which incorporates a bidirectional multi-level spatio-temporal fusion module and a category-aware spatio-temporal feature alignment module to facilitate consistent learning for domain-invariant features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-stc-domain-adaptive-video-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Video Diffusion: Scaling Latent Video Diffusion Models to Large Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-video-diffusion-scaling-latent-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Stable Video Diffusion — a latent video diffusion model for high-resolution, state-of-the-art text-to-video and image-to-video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-video-diffusion-scaling-latent-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attacks of fairness in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacks-of-fairness-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is now well understood that by controlling only a small subset of FL clients, it is possible to introduce a backdoor to a federated learning model, in the presence of certain attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attacks-of-fairness-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carbohydrate NMR chemical shift predictions using E(3) equivariant graph neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carbohydrate-nmr-chemical-shift-predictions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR) spectroscopy plays a crucial role in understanding their intricate molecular arrangements and is essential in assessing and verifying the molecular structure of organic molecules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/carbohydrate-nmr-chemical-shift-predictions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Time Granularity on Temporal Graphs for Dynamic Link Prediction in Real-world Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-time-granularity-on-temporal-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic Graph Neural Networks (DGNNs) have emerged as the predominant approach for processing dynamic graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-time-granularity-on-temporal-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelfOcc: Self-Supervised Vision-Based 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfocc-self-supervised-vision-based-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our SelfOcc outperforms the previous best method SceneRF by 58. 7% using a single frame as input on SemanticKITTI and is the first self-supervised work that produces reasonable 3D occupancy for surround cameras on Occ3D.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfocc-self-supervised-vision-based-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Multimodal Large Language Models for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-multimodal-large-language-models-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first introduce the background of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs), the multimodal models development using LLMs, and the history of autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-multimodal-large-language-models-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The limitation of neural nets for approximation and optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-limitation-of-neural-nets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are interested in assessing the use of neural networks as surrogate models to approximate and minimize objective functions in optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-limitation-of-neural-nets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-resolution Image-based Malware Classification using Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-based-malware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel method of classifying malware into families using high-resolution greyscale images and multiple instance learning to overcome adversarial binary enlargement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-based-malware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Audio-visual Zero-shot Learning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-audio-visual-zero-shot-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-visual zero-shot learning aims to recognize unseen categories based on paired audio-visual sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-audio-visual-zero-shot-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oasis: Data Curation and Assessment System for Pretraining of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oasis-data-curation-and-assessment-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we present a pretraining corpus curation and assessment platform called Oasis -- a one-stop system for data quality improvement and quantification with user-friendly interactive interfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oasis-data-curation-and-assessment-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Home Staging: Inverse Rendering and Editing an Indoor Panorama under Natural Illumination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-home-staging-inverse-rendering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel inverse rendering method that enables the transformation of existing indoor panoramas with new indoor furniture layouts under natural illumination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-home-staging-inverse-rendering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Deconfounding Against Spatio-Temporal Shifts: Theory and Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-deconfounding-against-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It first encodes traffic data into two disentangled representations for associating invariant and variant ST contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-deconfounding-against-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-Guided Discovery of a Real-World Rogue Wave Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-guided-discovery-of-a-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, it is still not clear how we can use the superior pattern matching abilities of machine learning models for scientific discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-guided-discovery-of-a-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LowResource at BLP-2023 Task 2: Leveraging BanglaBert for Low Resource Sentiment Analysis of Bangla Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowresource-at-blp-2023-task-2-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the system of the LowResource Team for Task 2 of BLP-2023, which involves conducting sentiment analysis on a dataset composed of public posts and comments from diverse social media platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lowresource-at-blp-2023-task-2-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic Image Decomposition via Ordinal Shading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-image-decomposition-via-ordinal-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We encourage the model to learn an accurate decomposition by computing losses on the estimated shading as well as the albedo implied by the intrinsic model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-image-decomposition-via-ordinal-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonally weighted $\ell_{2,1}$ regularization for rank-aware joint sparse recovery: algorithm and analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonally-weighted-ell-21-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose and analyze an efficient algorithm for solving the joint sparse recovery problem using a new regularization-based method, named orthogonally weighted $\ell_{2, 1}$ ($\mathit{ow}\ell_{2, 1}$), which is specifically designed to take into account the rank of the solution matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonally-weighted-ell-21-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Linear Projections Loss for Hyperplane-Based Optimization in Regression Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-linear-projections-loss-for-hyperplane</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their popularity across a wide range of domains, regression neural networks are prone to overfitting complex datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-linear-projections-loss-for-hyperplane</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Text Classification with Wasserstein Independence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-text-classification-with-wasserstein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is more suitable for real-life scenarios compared to existing methods that require annotations of sensitive attributes at train time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-text-classification-with-wasserstein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Transformer Architecture in Long-Context Large Language Models: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-transformer-architecture-in-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the bomb ignited by ChatGPT, Transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs) have paved a revolutionary path toward Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) and have been applied in diverse areas as knowledge bases, human interfaces, and dynamic agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-transformer-architecture-in-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Pathology Image Data Deficiency: Generating Images from Pathological Transformation Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-pathology-image-data-deficiency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ADBD is effective for overcoming pathological image data deficiency and supportable for further pathology-related research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-pathology-image-data-deficiency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSVEP-DAN: A Data Alignment Network for SSVEP-based Brain Computer Interfaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssvep-dan-a-data-alignment-network-for-ssvep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Steady-state visual-evoked potential (SSVEP)-based brain-computer interfaces (BCIs) offer a non-invasive means of communication through high-speed speller systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssvep-dan-a-data-alignment-network-for-ssvep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChessVision -- A Dataset for Logically Coherent Multi-label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chessvision-a-dataset-for-logically-coherent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Starting with early successes in computer vision tasks, deep learning based techniques have since overtaken state of the art approaches in a multitude of domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chessvision-a-dataset-for-logically-coherent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Content Augmented Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-augmented-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More precisely, we propose models wherein a structural embedding using a GNN and a content embedding are computed for each node.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/content-augmented-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALPHA: AnomaLous Physiological Health Assessment Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpha-anomalous-physiological-health</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings reveal that LLMs exhibit exceptional performance in determining medical indicators, including a Mean Absolute Error (MAE) of less than 1 beat per minute for heart rate and less than 1% for oxygen saturation (SpO2).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpha-anomalous-physiological-health</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lung cancer detection from thoracic CT scans using an ensemble of deep learning models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lung-cancer-detection-from-thoracic-ct-scans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach leverages deep transfer learning and adopts an ensemble learning approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lung-cancer-detection-from-thoracic-ct-scans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swift Parameter-free Attention Network for Efficient Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-parameter-free-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose the Swift Parameter-free Attention Network (SPAN), a highly efficient SISR model that balances parameter count, inference speed, and image quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-parameter-free-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Weight-Perturbed Deep Neural Networks With Application in Iris Presentation Attack Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-weight-perturbed-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we assess the sensitivity of DNNs against perturbations to their weight and bias parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-weight-perturbed-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Learning Functions with Varying Number of Minima</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-functions-with-varying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our study, we use a formal framework to explore ICL and propose a new task of approximating functions with varying number of minima.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-functions-with-varying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting Definienda in Mathematical Scholarly Articles with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-definienda-in-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider automatically identifying the defined term within a mathematical definition from the text of an academic article.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-definienda-in-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhayaThaiBERT: Enhancing a Pretrained Thai Language Model with Unassimilated Loanwords</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phayathaibert-enhancing-a-pretrained-thai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While WangchanBERTa has become the de facto standard in transformer-based Thai language modeling, it still has shortcomings in regard to the understanding of foreign words, most notably English words, which are often borrowed without orthographic assimilation into Thai in many contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phayathaibert-enhancing-a-pretrained-thai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Impairment and Disease Severity Using AI Models Trained on Healthy Subjects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-impairment-and-disease-severity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We applied the COBRA score to address a key limitation of current clinical evaluation of upper-body impairment in stroke patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-impairment-and-disease-severity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping "Brain Coral" Regions on Mars using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-brain-coral-regions-on-mars-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we use convolutional neural networks to detect surface regions containing "Brain Coral" terrain, a landform on Mars whose similarity in morphology and scale to sorted stone circles on Earth suggests that it may have formed as a consequence of freeze/thaw cycles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-brain-coral-regions-on-mars-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Forecast Reconciliation with Kullback-Leibler Divergence Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-forecast-reconciliation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the popularity of hierarchical point forecast reconciliation methods increases, there is a growing interest in probabilistic forecast reconciliation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-forecast-reconciliation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEND: Benchmarking DNA Language Models on biologically meaningful tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bend-benchmarking-dna-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The genome sequence contains the blueprint for governing cellular processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bend-benchmarking-dna-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning via Consensus Mechanism on Heterogeneous Data: A New Perspective on Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-consensus-mechanism-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically show that the consensus mechanism can guarantee the convergence of the global objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-consensus-mechanism-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"HoVer-UNet": Accelerating HoVerNet with UNet-based multi-class nuclei segmentation via knowledge distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hover-unet-accelerating-hovernet-with-unet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present "HoVer-UNet", an approach to distill the knowledge of the multi-branch HoVerNet framework for nuclei instance segmentation and classification in histopathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hover-unet-accelerating-hovernet-with-unet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLAD: Global-Local View Alignment and Background Debiasing for Unsupervised Video Domain Adaptation with Large Domain Gap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glad-global-local-view-alignment-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We specifically focus on scenarios with a substantial domain gap, in contrast to existing works primarily deal with small domain gaps between labeled source domains and unlabeled target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glad-global-local-view-alignment-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board-to-Board: Evaluating Moonboard Grade Prediction Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/board-to-board-evaluating-moonboard-grade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we apply classical and deep-learning modelling techniques to the 2016, 2017 and 2019 Moonboard datasets, achieving state of the art grade prediction performance with 0. 87 MAE and 1. 12 RMSE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/board-to-board-evaluating-moonboard-grade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViLaM: A Vision-Language Model with Enhanced Visual Grounding and Generalization Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilam-a-vision-language-model-with-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enables us to optimally utilize the knowledge and reasoning capacities of large pre-trained language models for an array of tasks encompassing both language and vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vilam-a-vision-language-model-with-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShareGPT4V: Improving Large Multi-Modal Models with Better Captions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharegpt4v-improving-large-multi-modal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of large multi-modal models (LMMs), efficient modality alignment is crucial yet often constrained by the scarcity of high-quality image-text data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharegpt4v-improving-large-multi-modal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>minimax: Efficient Baselines for Autocurricula in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-efficient-baselines-for-autocurricula</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This compute requirement is a major obstacle to rapid innovation for the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-efficient-baselines-for-autocurricula</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Site-specific Styles for Multi-institutional Unsupervised Cross-modality Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-site-specific-styles-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our solution to tackle the multi-institutional unsupervised domain adaptation for the crossMoDA 2023 challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-site-specific-styles-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges in Video-Based Infant Action Recognition: A Critical Examination of the State of the Art</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-video-based-infant-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated human action recognition, a burgeoning field within computer vision, boasts diverse applications spanning surveillance, security, human-computer interaction, tele-health, and sports analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-video-based-infant-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a more inductive world for drug repurposing approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-inductive-world-for-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first perform an in-depth evaluation of current DTI datasets and prediction models through a robust benchmarking process, and show that DTI prediction methods based on transductive models lack generalization and lead to inflated performance when evaluated as previously done in the literature, hence not being suited for drug repurposing approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-inductive-world-for-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSMeD: Bridging the Dataset Gap in Automated Citation Screening for Systematic Literature Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csmed-bridging-the-dataset-gap-in-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Systematic literature reviews (SLRs) play an essential role in summarising, synthesising and validating scientific evidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csmed-bridging-the-dataset-gap-in-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HierSpeech++: Bridging the Gap between Semantic and Acoustic Representation of Speech by Hierarchical Variational Inference for Zero-shot Speech Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierspeech-bridging-the-gap-between-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we significantly improve the naturalness and speaker similarity of synthetic speech even in zero-shot speech synthesis scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierspeech-bridging-the-gap-between-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning based on Decomposition: A taxonomy and framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-reinforcement-learning-based-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, a clear categorization based on both RL and MOO/D is lacking in the existing literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-reinforcement-learning-based-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIP-RTVE: An Audiovisual Database for Continuous Spanish in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lip-rtve-an-audiovisual-database-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech is considered as a multi-modal process where hearing and vision are two fundamentals pillars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lip-rtve-an-audiovisual-database-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Sliders: LoRA Adaptors for Precise Control in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-sliders-lora-adaptors-for-precise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method to create interpretable concept sliders that enable precise control over attributes in image generations from diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-sliders-lora-adaptors-for-precise</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
