<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 21:05:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FLIP: Cross-domain Face Anti-spoofing with Language Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flip-cross-domain-face-anti-spoofing-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we show that aligning the image representation with an ensemble of class descriptions (based on natural language semantics) improves FAS generalizability in low-data regimes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flip-cross-domain-face-anti-spoofing-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixup Your Own Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixup-your-own-pairs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In representation learning, regression has traditionally received less attention than classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixup-your-own-pairs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Geometrized Cartoon Line Inbetweening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-geometrized-cartoon-line-inbetweening-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To preserve the precision and detail of the line drawings, we propose a new approach, AnimeInbet, which geometrizes raster line drawings into graphs of endpoints and reframes the inbetweening task as a graph fusion problem with vertex repositioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-geometrized-cartoon-line-inbetweening-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlikelihood Tuning on Negative Samples Amazingly Improves Zero-Shot Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlikelihood-tuning-on-negative-samples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot translation (ZST), which is generally based on a multilingual neural machine translation model, aims to translate between unseen language pairs in training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlikelihood-tuning-on-negative-samples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LawBench: Benchmarking Legal Knowledge of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lawbench-benchmarking-legal-knowledge-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope this benchmark provides in-depth understanding of the LLMs' domain-specified capabilities and speed up the development of LLMs in the legal domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lawbench-benchmarking-legal-knowledge-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Heterogeneous Federated Cross-Correlation and Instance Similarity Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-heterogeneous-federated-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is an important privacy-preserving multi-party learning paradigm, involving collaborative learning with others and local updating on private data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-heterogeneous-federated-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dark Side Augmentation: Generating Diverse Night Examples for Metric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dark-side-augmentation-generating-diverse-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to train a GAN-based synthetic-image generator, translating available day-time image examples into night images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dark-side-augmentation-generating-diverse-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTC-DC Net: Monocular Height Estimation from Single Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htc-dc-net-monocular-height-estimation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose a method for monocular height estimation from optical imagery, which is currently one of the richest sources of remote sensing data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htc-dc-net-monocular-height-estimation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-Fathom: Benchmarking Large Language Models to Decipher the Evolutionary Path towards GPT-4 and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-fathom-benchmarking-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid advancement of large language models (LLMs), there is a pressing need for a comprehensive evaluation suite to assess their capabilities and limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-fathom-benchmarking-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORB: A Flat Object Retrieval Benchmark for Universal Image Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forb-a-flat-object-retrieval-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image retrieval is a fundamental task in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forb-a-flat-object-retrieval-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShapeDBA: Generating Effective Time Series Prototypes using ShapeDTW Barycenter Averaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapedba-generating-effective-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach uses a new form of time series average, the ShapeDTW Barycentric Average.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapedba-generating-effective-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Metaheuristic for Amortized Search in High-Dimensional Parameter Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-metaheuristic-for-amortized-search-in-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter inference for dynamical models of (bio)physical systems remains a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-metaheuristic-for-amortized-search-in-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augment to Interpret: Unsupervised and Inherently Interpretable Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augment-to-interpret-unsupervised-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised learning allows us to leverage unlabelled data, which has become abundantly available, and to create embeddings that are usable on a variety of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augment-to-interpret-unsupervised-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Pre-trained Language Models for Time Interval Prediction in Text-Enhanced Temporal Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-pre-trained-language-models-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most knowledge graph completion (KGC) methods learn latent representations of entities and relations of a given graph by mapping them into a vector space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-pre-trained-language-models-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Physics Informed Machine Learning Method for Power System Model Parameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-machine-learning-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a gradient descent based optimization method that relies on automatic differentiation for the computation of gradients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-physics-informed-machine-learning-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AtomSurf : Surface Representation for Learning on Protein Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomsurf-surface-representation-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An essential aspect of learning from protein structures is representing these structures as a geometric object (be it a grid, graph, or surface) and applying a learning method tailored to this representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomsurf-surface-representation-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAFlow: Incorporating Gaussian Attention into Optical Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaflow-incorporating-gaussian-attention-into-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, for reliable motion analysis, we provide a new Gaussian-Guided Attention Module (GGAM) which not only inherits properties from Gaussian distribution to instinctively revolve around the neighbor fields of each point but also is empowered to put the emphasis on contextually related regions during matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaflow-incorporating-gaussian-attention-into-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential 2D Copula Approximating Transforms via Sobolev Training: 2-Cats Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-2d-copula-approximating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Not only do we show that we can estimate the output of a 2d Copula better than the state-of-the-art, our approach is non-parametric and respects the mathematical properties of a Copula $C$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-2d-copula-approximating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Prediction-Powered Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-prediction-powered-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that cross-prediction is consistently more powerful than an adaptation of prediction-powered inference in which a fraction of the labeled data is split off and used to train the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-prediction-powered-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Sculpting of Iterative Generative Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-sculpting-of-iterative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge in composing iterative generative processes, such as GFlowNets and diffusion models, is that to realize the desired target distribution, all steps of the generative process need to be coordinated, and satisfy delicate balance conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-sculpting-of-iterative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamGaussian: Generative Gaussian Splatting for Efficient 3D Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamgaussian-generative-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to the occupancy pruning used in Neural Radiance Fields, we demonstrate that the progressive densification of 3D Gaussians converges significantly faster for 3D generative tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamgaussian-generative-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training a Large Video Model on a Single Machine in a Day</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-large-video-model-on-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Videos are big, complex to pre-process, and slow to train on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-large-video-model-on-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-to-3D using Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-3d-using-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this stage, we increase the number of Gaussians by compactness-based densification to enhance continuity and improve fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-3d-using-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KLoB: a Benchmark for Assessing Knowledge Locating Methods in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/klob-a-benchmark-for-assessing-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[KLoB can serve as a benchmark for evaluating existing locating methods in language models, and can contributes a method to reassessing the validity of locality hypothesis of factual knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/klob-a-benchmark-for-assessing-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the Chameleons: A Benchmark for Out-of-Distribution Detection in Medical Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-the-chameleons-a-benchmark-for-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their success, Machine Learning (ML) models do not generalize effectively to data not originating from the training distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-the-chameleons-a-benchmark-for-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Active Learning Performance Driven by Gaussian Processes or Bayesian Neural Networks for Constrained Trajectory Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-active-learning-performance-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An autonomous robot encoded with a scientific objective and an exploration strategy incurs no communication delays and can fulfill missions more quickly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-active-learning-performance-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Citations: Text-Based Metrics for Assessing Novelty and its Impact in Scientific Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-citations-text-based-metrics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings support the use of text mining both to measure novel scientific ideas at the time of publication and to measure the impact of these new ideas on later scientific work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-citations-text-based-metrics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Which Training Stage Does Cocde Data Help LLMs Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/at-which-training-stage-does-cocde-data-help</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the great success of code data in training LLMs, we naturally wonder at which training stage introducing code data can really help LLMs reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/at-which-training-stage-does-cocde-data-help</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying CLIP Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-clip-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that the main ingredient to the success of CLIP is its data and not the model architecture or pre-training objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-clip-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-and-Align: Prompt-Based Social Alignment for Few-Shot Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-and-align-prompt-based-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable advances in automated fake news detection, due to the timely nature of news, it remains a critical open question how to effectively predict the veracity of news articles based on limited fact-checks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-and-align-prompt-based-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LagrangeBench: A Lagrangian Fluid Mechanics Benchmarking Suite</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lagrangebench-a-lagrangian-fluid-mechanics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning has been successfully applied to grid-based PDE modeling in various scientific applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lagrangebench-a-lagrangian-fluid-mechanics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end Risk Prediction of Atrial Fibrillation from the 12-Lead ECG by Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-risk-prediction-of-atrial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Background: Atrial fibrillation (AF) is one of the most common cardiac arrhythmias that affects millions of people each year worldwide and it is closely linked to increased risk of cardiovascular diseases such as stroke and heart failure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-risk-prediction-of-atrial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QonFusion -- Quantum Approaches to Gaussian Random Variables: Applications in Stable Diffusion and Brownian Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qonfusion-quantum-approaches-to-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The principal theme of our research is the incorporation of Quantum Random Number Generators (QRNGs) into classical models of diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qonfusion-quantum-approaches-to-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-VQ: Linear-Time Transformers via Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-vq-linear-time-transformers-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Transformer-VQ, a decoder-only transformer computing softmax-based dense self-attention in linear time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-vq-linear-time-transformers-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding the Workplace &amp; EOR: An Employee Survey Analysis by Data Science Techniques and Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-the-workplace-eor-an-employee-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research study explores the new dynamics of employee-organi-zation relationships (EOR) [6] using advanced data science methodologies and presents findings through accessible visualizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-the-workplace-eor-an-employee-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trickle-down Impact of Reward (In-)consistency on RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-trickle-down-impact-of-reward-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Contrast Instructions -- a benchmarking strategy for the consistency of RM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-trickle-down-impact-of-reward-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have revolutionized the field of artificial intelligence, enabling natural language processing tasks that were previously thought to be exclusive to humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Text Generation with Residual Memory Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-generation-with-residual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale Causal Language Models (CLMs), e. g., GPT3 and ChatGPT, have brought great success in text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-generation-with-residual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse and Aligned Audio-to-Video Generation via Text-to-Video Model Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-and-aligned-audio-to-video-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is based on a lightweight adaptor network, which learns to map the audio-based representation to the input representation expected by the text-to-video generation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-and-aligned-audio-to-video-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-COL: Generating Counterfactual Explanations for General User Preferences on Variable Machine Learning Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-col-generating-counterfactual-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the application of CEs has been hindered by two main challenges, namely general user preferences and variable ML systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-col-generating-counterfactual-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Equivariance in State-of-the-Art Supervised Depth and Normal Predictors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-equivariance-in-state-of-the-art-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense depth and surface normal predictors should possess the equivariant property to cropping-and-resizing -- cropping the input image should result in cropping the same output image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-equivariance-in-state-of-the-art-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Transform for Generalizable Instance-wise Invariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-transform-for-generalizable-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, too much or too little invariance can hurt, and the correct amount is unknown a priori and dependent on the instance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-transform-for-generalizable-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Terminate in Object Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-terminate-in-object-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper tackles the critical challenge of object navigation in autonomous navigation systems, particularly focusing on the problem of target approach and episode termination in environments with long optimal episode length in Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) based methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-terminate-in-object-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Challenges of Fully Incremental Neural Dependency Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-challenges-of-fully-incremental-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the popularization of BiLSTMs and Transformer-based bidirectional encoders, state-of-the-art syntactic parsers have lacked incrementality, requiring access to the whole sentence and deviating from human language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-challenges-of-fully-incremental-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geodesic Regression Characterizes 3D Shape Changes in the Female Brain During Menstruation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geodesic-regression-characterizes-3d-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We seek to investigate this connection by developing tools that quantify 3D shape changes that occur in the brain during sex hormone fluctuations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geodesic-regression-characterizes-3d-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting transformers with recursively composed multi-grained representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-transformers-with-recursively</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More interestingly, the hierarchical structures induced by ReCAT exhibit strong consistency with human-annotated syntactic trees, indicating good interpretability brought by the CIO layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-transformers-with-recursively</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A More General Theory of Diagnosis from First Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-more-general-theory-of-diagnosis-from-first</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This more general theory of diagnosis from first principles defines the minimal diagnosis as the set of preferred diagnosis candidates in a search space of hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-more-general-theory-of-diagnosis-from-first</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logarithm-transform aided Gaussian Sampling for Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logarithm-transform-aided-gaussian-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods rely on transforming the distributions of experimental data to approximate Gaussian distributions for their functioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logarithm-transform-aided-gaussian-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA2-Net: Scale-aware Attention Network for Microscopic Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa2-net-scale-aware-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose scale-aware attention (SA2) module designed to capture inherent variations in scales and shapes of microscopic regions, such as cells, for accurate segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa2-net-scale-aware-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ModuLoRA: Finetuning 3-Bit LLMs on Consumer GPUs by Integrating with Modular Quantizers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modulora-finetuning-3-bit-llms-on-consumer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a memory-efficient finetuning algorithm for large language models (LLMs) that supports finetuning LLMs with 65B parameters in 3-bit or 4-bit precision on as little as one 48GB GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modulora-finetuning-3-bit-llms-on-consumer</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
