<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2022 21:09:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechCLIP: Integrating Speech with Pre-Trained Vision and Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechclip-integrating-speech-with-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-driven speech processing models usually perform well with a large amount of text supervision, but collecting transcribed speech data is costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechclip-integrating-speech-with-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hypothesis Engineering for Zero-Shot Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesis-engineering-for-zero-shot-hate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the zero-shot baseline used for the initial error analysis already outperforms commercial systems and fine-tuned BERT-based hate speech detection models on HateCheck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypothesis-engineering-for-zero-shot-hate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Bayes Inference in Neural Networks through Adaptive Importance Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-bayes-inference-in-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian neural networks (BNNs) have received an increased interest in the last years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-bayes-inference-in-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effectiveness of Masked Language Modeling and Adapters for Factual Knowledge Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effectiveness-of-masked-language-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the problem of injecting factual knowledge into large pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effectiveness-of-masked-language-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Reinforcement Learning with PID Controllers in the Pendulum Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerate-reinforcement-learning-with-pid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controller-based coaching scheme to expedite reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerate-reinforcement-learning-with-pid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Sounds Right: Auditory Self-Supervision for Dynamic Robot Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/that-sounds-right-auditory-self-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning to produce contact-rich, dynamic behaviors from raw sensory data has been a longstanding challenge in robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/that-sounds-right-auditory-self-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBLab: Scalable Traffic Simulation with Enriched Data Supporting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cblab-scalable-traffic-simulation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining CBEngine and CBData allows researchers to run scalable traffic simulation in the road network of real large-scale cities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cblab-scalable-traffic-simulation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Supervised Learning for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-supervised-learning-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attention is of vital importance in semantic segmentation as it enables modeling of long-range context, which translates into improved performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-supervised-learning-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from the Dark: Boosting Graph Convolutional Neural Networks with Diverse Negative Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-the-dark-boosting-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An interesting way to understand GCNs is to think of them as a message passing mechanism where each node updates its representation by accepting information from its neighbours (also known as positive samples).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-the-dark-boosting-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiGuard: Provably Robust Multi-label Classification against Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiguard-provably-robust-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose MultiGuard, the first provably robust defense against adversarial examples to multi-label classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiguard-provably-robust-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonstationary data stream classification with online active learning and siamese neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonstationary-data-stream-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct an extensive study that compares the role of different active learning budgets and strategies, the performance with/without memory, the performance with/without ensembling, in both synthetic and real-world datasets, under different data nonstationarity characteristics and class imbalance levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonstationary-data-stream-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Physiological Sensing Toolbox</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-physiological-sensing-toolbox</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Camera physiological measurement is a fast growing field of computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-physiological-sensing-toolbox</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDoS: A Graph Neural Network based Drug Synergy Prediction Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddos-a-graph-neural-network-based-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: We introduce a Graph Neural Network (GNN) based model for drug synergy prediction, which utilizes drug chemical structures and cell line gene expression data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddos-a-graph-neural-network-based-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Face to Natural Image: Learning Real Degradation for Blind Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-face-to-natural-image-learning-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, face images, which have the same degradation process with the natural images, can be robustly restored with photo-realistic textures by exploiting their specific structure priors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-face-to-natural-image-learning-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-omics: A Self-supervised Learning Framework for Multi-omics Cancer Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-omics-a-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lack of annotated data is a significant problem in machine learning, and Self-Supervised Learning (SSL) methods are typically used to deal with limited labelled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-omics-a-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi Camera Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Pipeline for Object Detection in Cultural Sites through Adversarial Learning and Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection algorithms allow to enable many interesting applications which can be implemented in different devices, such as smartphones and wearable devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Spatial Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatial-domain-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatial domain generalization is a spatial extension of domain generalization, which can generalize to unseen spatial domains in continuous 2D space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatial-domain-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CERBERUS: Simple and Effective All-In-One Automotive Perception Model with Multi Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerberus-simple-and-effective-all-in-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perceiving the surrounding environment is essential for enabling autonomous or assisted driving functionalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cerberus-simple-and-effective-all-in-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Unified View on Visual Parameter-Efficient Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-view-on-visual-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towards this goal, we propose a framework with a unified view called visual-PETL (V-PETL) to investigate the different aspects affecting the trade-off.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-view-on-visual-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenDexGrasp: Generalizable Dexterous Grasping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendexgrasp-generalizable-dexterous-grasping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging the contact map as a hand-agnostic intermediate representation, GenDexGrasp efficiently generates diverse and plausible grasping poses with a high success rate and can transfer among diverse multi-fingered robotic hands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gendexgrasp-generalizable-dexterous-grasping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fill in Fabrics: Body-Aware Self-Supervised Inpainting for Image-Based Virtual Try-On</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fill-in-fabrics-body-aware-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous virtual try-on methods usually focus on aligning a clothing item with a person, limiting their ability to exploit the complex pose, shape and skin color of the person, as well as the overall structure of the clothing, which is vital to photo-realistic virtual try-on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fill-in-fabrics-body-aware-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Driven Active Vision for Implicit Scene Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-driven-active-vision-for-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our proposed approach on the ABC dataset and the in the wild CO3D dataset, and show that: (1) we are able to obtain high quality state-of-the-art occupancy reconstructions; (2) our perspective conditioned uncertainty definition is effective to drive improvements in next best view selection and outperforms strong baseline approaches; and (3) we can further improve shape understanding by performing a gradient-based search on the view selection candidates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-driven-active-vision-for-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Distillation: self-supervised vision transformer students need more guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-distillation-self-supervised-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments on ImageNet-Subset and ImageNet-1K, we show that our method AttnDistill outperforms existing self-supervised knowledge distillation (SSKD) methods and achieves state-of-the-art k-NN accuracy compared with self-supervised learning (SSL) methods learning from scratch (with the ViT-S model).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-distillation-self-supervised-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP2Point: Transfer CLIP to Point Cloud Classification with Image-Depth Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip2point-transfer-clip-to-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose CLIP2Point, an image-depth pre-training method by contrastive learning to transfer CLIP to the 3D domain, and adapt it to point cloud classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip2point-transfer-clip-to-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Multimodal Change Detection Based on Structural Relationship Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multimodal-change-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, the similarity levels of two structural relationships are calculated from learned graph representations and two difference images are generated based on the similarity levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multimodal-change-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Data Augmentation based Enhancement: A Generalized Enhancement Approach for Medical Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-data-augmentation-based-enhancement-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the generalization of the proposed method, we use four medical datasets and compare its performance with state-of-the-art methods for both classification and segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-data-augmentation-based-enhancement-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPARC: Sparse Render-and-Compare for CAD model alignment in a single RGB image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparc-sparse-render-and-compare-for-cad-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This combined information is the input to a pose prediction network, SPARC-Net which we train to predict a 9 DoF CAD model pose update.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparc-sparse-render-and-compare-for-cad-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Equivariant Segmentation with Instance-Unique Querying</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-equivariant-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prevalent state-of-the-art instance segmentation methods fall into a query-based scheme, in which instance masks are derived by querying the image feature using a set of instance-aware embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-equivariant-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KGP: An R Package with Metadata from the 1000 Genomes Project</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgp-an-r-package-with-metadata-from-the-1000</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The kgp R package provides consistent and comprehensive metadata about samples and populations in the 1000 Genomes Project and other population sequencing data in the International Genome Sample Resource collection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgp-an-r-package-with-metadata-from-the-1000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Robust Video-Based Exercise Classification via Body Pose Tracking and Scalable Multivariate Time Series Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-video-based-exercise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze the accuracy and robustness of BodyMTS and show that it is robust to different types of noise caused by either video quality or pose estimation factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-video-based-exercise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siamese-NAS: Using Trained Samples Efficiently to Find Lightweight Neural Architecture by Prior Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamese-nas-using-trained-samples-efficiently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This idea causes it to surpass the current SOTA predictor on NASBench-201.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamese-nas-using-trained-samples-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation: Solving the Edge-Fattening Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-monocular-depth-estimation-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we redesign the patch-based triplet loss in MDE to alleviate the ubiquitous edge-fattening issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-monocular-depth-estimation-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-graded Safety for Handling Medical Queries in Conversational AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-graded-safety-for-handling-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While individual crowdworkers may be unreliable at grading the seriousness of the prompts, their aggregated labels tend to agree with professional opinion to a greater extent on identifying the medical queries and recognising the risk types posed by the responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-graded-safety-for-handling-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Graphical Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-graphical-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs are ubiquitous and are often used to understand the dynamics of a system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-graphical-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generated Faces in the Wild: Quantitative Comparison of Stable Diffusion, Midjourney and DALL-E 2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generated-faces-in-the-wild-quantitative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we conduct a quantitative comparison of three popular systems including Stable Diffusion, Midjourney, and DALL-E 2 in their ability to generate photorealistic faces in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generated-faces-in-the-wild-quantitative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Occlusion-Aware Crowd Navigation Using People as Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-crowd-navigation-using-people</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this work is the first to use social occlusion inference for crowd navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/occlusion-aware-crowd-navigation-using-people</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Neural Network for Privacy-Preserving Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-neural-network-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel heterogeneous graph neural network privacy-preserving method based on a differential privacy mechanism named HeteDP, which provides a double guarantee on graph features and topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-neural-network-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReAct: A Review Comment Dataset for Actionability (and more)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react-a-review-comment-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We crowd-source annotations for these reviews for actionability and type of comments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react-a-review-comment-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntrinsicNeRF: Learning Intrinsic Neural Radiance Fields for Editable Novel View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsicnerf-learning-intrinsic-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given that intrinsic decomposition is a fundamentally ambiguous and under-constrained inverse problem, we propose a novel distance-aware point sampling and adaptive reflectance iterative clustering optimization method that enables IntrinsicNeRF with traditional intrinsic decomposition constraints to be trained in an unsupervised manner, resulting in temporally consistent intrinsic decomposition results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsicnerf-learning-intrinsic-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-OCTA: Ensemble Deep Learning Approaches for Diabetic Retinopathy Analysis on OCTA Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-octa-ensemble-deep-learning-approaches</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the image quality assessment task, we create an ensemble of InceptionV3, SE-ResNeXt, and Vision Transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-octa-ensemble-deep-learning-approaches</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting More Information in Sparse Point Cloud for 3D Single Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-more-information-in-sparse-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the encoder applies the attention on multi-scale features to compensate for the lack of information caused by the sparsity of point cloud and the single scale of features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-more-information-in-sparse-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Intrinsically Motivated Exploration in Continuous Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-intrinsically-motivated-exploration-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In continuous control, exploration is often performed through undirected strategies in which parameters of the networks or selected actions are perturbed by random noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-intrinsically-motivated-exploration-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Selections Operating on HIV-1 Reverse Transcriptase via Uniform Manifold Approximation and Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-selections-operating-on-hiv-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze 14, 651 HIV1 reverse transcriptase (HIV RT) sequences from the Stanford HIV Drug Resistance Database labeled with treatment regimen in order to study the evolution this enzyme under drug selection in the clinic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-selections-operating-on-hiv-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-Aware NeRF without Posed Camera via Epipolar Constraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-aware-nerf-without-posed-camera-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This two-stage strategy is not convenient to use and degrades the performance because the error in the pose extraction can propagate to the view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-aware-nerf-without-posed-camera-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving practical multi-body dynamics problems using a single neural operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-practical-multi-body-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework integrates mechanics and deep learning technologies and may reveal a new concept for MBD and probabilistic engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-practical-multi-body-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scenes of Gradient Descent: A Trajectory Analysis via Basis Function Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behind-the-scenes-of-gradient-descent-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work analyzes the solution trajectory of gradient-based algorithms via a novel basis function decomposition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behind-the-scenes-of-gradient-descent-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Attacks on Transformers-Based Malware Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-attacks-on-transformers-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Signature-based malware detectors have proven to be insufficient as even a small change in malignant executable code can bypass these signature-based detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-attacks-on-transformers-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptKG: A Prompt Learning Framework for Knowledge Graph Representation Learning and Application</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptkg-a-prompt-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graphs (KGs) often have two characteristics: heterogeneous graph structure and text-rich entity/relation information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptkg-a-prompt-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Handwritten Amharic Character Recognition Using Few-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-handwritten-amharic-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning from a few examples is also an important attempt towards learning like humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-handwritten-amharic-character</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-class-incremental-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, conventional CIL methods consider a balanced distribution for each new task, which ignores the prevalence of long-tailed distributions in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-class-incremental-learning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
