<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 21:06:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Learning from Graphs with Heterophily: Progress and Future</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-from-graphs-with-heterophily</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs are structured data that models complex relations between real-world entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-from-graphs-with-heterophily</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide and not forget: Ensemble of selectively trained experts in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-not-forget-ensemble-of-selectively</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class-incremental learning is becoming more popular as it helps models widen their applicability while not forgetting what they already know.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-not-forget-ensemble-of-selectively</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Self-training Framework for Fine-grained Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-self-training-framework-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a Self-Training framework for SGG (ST-SGG) that assigns pseudo-labels for unannotated triplets based on which the SGG models are trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-self-training-framework-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Image-Text Matching with Adaptive Feature Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-text-matching-with-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-text matching aims to find matched cross-modal pairs accurately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-text-matching-with-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Automated Quality Assessment Network for Interactive Building Segmentation in High-Resolution Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-automated-quality-assessment-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research, we introduce the enhanced automated quality assessment network (IBS-AQSNet), an innovative solution for assessing the quality of interactive building segmentation within high-resolution remote sensing imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-automated-quality-assessment-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Neural Code Completion Models Size up the Situation: Attaining Cheaper and Faster Completion through Dynamic Model Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-neural-code-completion-models-size-up</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings motivate our exploration of dynamic inference in code completion and inspire us to enhance it with a decision-making mechanism that stops the generation of incorrect code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-neural-code-completion-models-size-up</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub2Full: split spectrum to boost OCT despeckling without clean data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sub2full-split-spectrum-to-boost-oct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical coherence tomography (OCT) suffers from speckle noise, causing the deterioration of image quality, especially in high-resolution modalities like visible light OCT (vis-OCT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sub2full-split-spectrum-to-boost-oct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Study on the Performance of Categorical Variable Encoders in Classification and Regression Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-on-the-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study broadly classifies machine learning models into three categories: 1) ATI models that implicitly perform affine transformations on inputs, such as multi-layer perceptron neural network; 2) Tree-based models that are based on decision trees, such as random forest; and 3) the rest, such as kNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-on-the-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicitly Disentangled Representations in Object-Centric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-disentangled-representations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting structured representations from raw visual data is an important and long-standing challenge in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-disentangled-representations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Reasoning with Probabilistic Graphical Models for Analyzing Socioecological Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-reasoning-with-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal and counterfactual reasoning are emerging directions in data science that allow us to reason about hypothetical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-reasoning-with-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison Benchmark for Distributed Hybrid MPC Control Methods: Distributed Vehicle Platooning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-benchmark-for-distributed-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose distributed control of a platoon of autonomous vehicles as a comparison benchmark problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-benchmark-for-distributed-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPNet: A Novel Neural Network Structure for End-to-End Near-Optimal Path Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppnet-a-novel-neural-network-structure-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show PPNet can find a near-optimal solution in 15. 3ms, which is much shorter than the state-of-the-art path planners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppnet-a-novel-neural-network-structure-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chem-FINESE: Validating Fine-Grained Few-shot Entity Extraction through Text Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chem-finese-validating-fine-grained-few-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained few-shot entity extraction in the chemical domain faces two unique challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chem-finese-validating-fine-grained-few-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Viral Rumors and Vulnerable Users for Infodemic Surveillance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-viral-rumors-and-vulnerable-users</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to predict viral rumors and vulnerable users using a unified graph neural network model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-viral-rumors-and-vulnerable-users</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientRec an unlimited user-item scale recommendation system based on clustering and users interaction embedding profile</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientrec-an-unlimited-user-item-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The businesses are constantly growing users and products, causing the number of users and items to continuously increase over time, to very large numbers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientrec-an-unlimited-user-item-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPAvatar: Generalizable and Precise Head Avatar from Image(s)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpavatar-generalizable-and-precise-head</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Head avatar reconstruction, crucial for applications in virtual reality, online meetings, gaming, and film industries, has garnered substantial attention within the computer vision community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpavatar-generalizable-and-precise-head</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R-Judge: Benchmarking Safety Risk Awareness for LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-judge-benchmarking-safety-risk-awareness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce R-Judge, a benchmark crafted to evaluate the proficiency of LLMs in judging safety risks given agent interaction records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-judge-benchmarking-safety-risk-awareness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Explain Transformers by Illuminating Important Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-explain-transformers-by-illuminating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based models excel in various natural language processing (NLP) tasks, attracting countless efforts to explain their inner workings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-explain-transformers-by-illuminating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Compression Techniques in Biometrics Applications: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-compression-techniques-in-biometrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of deep learning algorithms has extensively empowered humanity's task automatization capacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-compression-techniques-in-biometrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Tuning of Denoising Algorithms Parameters Without Ground Truth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-tuning-of-denoising-algorithms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising is omnipresent in image processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-tuning-of-denoising-algorithms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA-SmaAt-GNet: Generative Adversarial Small Attention GNet for Extreme Precipitation Nowcasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ga-smaat-gnet-generative-adversarial-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we propose GA-SmaAt-GNet, a novel generative adversarial architecture that makes use of two methodologies aimed at enhancing the performance of deep learning models for extreme precipitation nowcasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ga-smaat-gnet-generative-adversarial-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAP-SAM: Towards Real-Time All-Purpose Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rap-sam-towards-real-time-all-purpose-segment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM) is one remarkable model that can achieve generalized segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rap-sam-towards-real-time-all-purpose-segment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All in How You Ask for It: Simple Black-Box Method for Jailbreak Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-how-you-ask-for-it-simple-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) like ChatGPT face `jailbreak' challenges, where safeguards are bypassed to produce ethically harmful prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-how-you-ask-for-it-simple-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooperative Edge Caching Based on Elastic Federated and Multi-Agent Deep Reinforcement Learning in Next-Generation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-edge-caching-based-on-elastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a multi-agent deep reinforcement learning (MADRL) based algorithm to decide where the predicted popular contents are collaboratively cached among SBSs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cooperative-edge-caching-based-on-elastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question-Answer Cross Language Image Matching for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-answer-cross-language-image-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class Activation Map (CAM) has emerged as a popular tool for weakly supervised semantic segmentation (WSSS), allowing the localization of object regions in an image using only image-level labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-answer-cross-language-image-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Manga Whisperer: Automatically Generating Transcriptions for Comics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-manga-whisperer-automatically-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past few decades, Japanese comics, commonly referred to as Manga, have transcended both cultural and linguistic boundaries to become a true worldwide sensation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-manga-whisperer-automatically-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Latent Diffusion Approach for Panoptic Segmentation and Mask Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-latent-diffusion-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Panoptic and instance segmentation networks are often trained with specialized object detection modules, complex loss functions, and ad-hoc post-processing steps to handle the permutation-invariance of the instance masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-latent-diffusion-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Extract Distributed Polarization Sensing Data from Noisy Jones Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-extract-distributed-polarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of recovering spatially resolved polarization information from receiver Jones matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-extract-distributed-polarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Efficient Equivariant Operations in the Fourier Basis via Gaunt Tensor Products</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-equivariant-operations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We mathematically connect the commonly used Clebsch-Gordan coefficients to the Gaunt coefficients, which are integrals of products of three spherical harmonics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-equivariant-operations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkyEyeGPT: Unifying Remote Sensing Vision-Language Tasks via Instruction Tuning with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyeyegpt-unifying-remote-sensing-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, after projecting RS visual features to the language domain via an alignment layer, they are fed jointly with task-specific instructions into an LLM-based RS decoder to predict answers for RS open-ended tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyeyegpt-unifying-remote-sensing-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meme-ingful Analysis: Enhanced Understanding of Cyberbullying in Memes Through Multimodal Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meme-ingful-analysis-enhanced-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Contrastive Language-Image Pretraining (CLIP) projection-based multimodal shared-private multitask approach has been proposed for visual and textual explanation of a meme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meme-ingful-analysis-enhanced-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchAD: Patch-based MLP-Mixer for Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchad-patch-based-mlp-mixer-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce PatchAD, a novel multi-scale patch-based MLP-Mixer architecture that leverages contrastive learning for representational extraction and anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchad-patch-based-mlp-mixer-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMamba: Visual State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmamba-visual-state-space-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) and Vision Transformers (ViTs) stand as the two most popular foundation models for visual representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vmamba-visual-state-space-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Hardware Accelerators for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-hardware-accelerators-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a comprehensive survey on hardware accelerators designed to enhance the performance and energy efficiency of Large Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-hardware-accelerators-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code Prompting Elicits Conditional Reasoning Abilities in Text+Code LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-prompting-elicits-conditional-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a chain of prompts that transforms a natural language problem into code and prompts the LLM with the generated code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-prompting-elicits-conditional-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Source Code Clone Detection Using Unsupervised Similarity Measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-code-clone-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessing similarity in source code has gained significant attention in recent years due to its importance in software engineering tasks such as clone detection and code search and recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/source-code-clone-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Fine-tuning in turn Improves Visual Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-fine-tuning-in-turn-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-text training like CLIP has dominated the pretraining of vision foundation models in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-fine-tuning-in-turn-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Brownian Bridge as Texts for Open-vocabulary Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-brownian-bridge-as-texts-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mold instance queries to follow Brownian bridge and accomplish alignment with class texts, we design Bridge-Text Alignment (BTA) to learn discriminative bridge-level representations of instances via contrastive objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-brownian-bridge-as-texts-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMG-Seg: Is One Model Good Enough For All Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omg-seg-is-one-model-good-enough-for-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address various segmentation tasks, each traditionally tackled by distinct or partially unified models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omg-seg-is-one-model-good-enough-for-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep spatial context: when attention-based models meet spatial regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatial-context-when-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The DSCon allows for a quantitative measure of the spatial context's role using three Spatial Context Measures: $SCM_{features}$, $SCM_{targets}$, $SCM_{residuals}$ to distinguish whether the spatial context is observable within the features of neighboring regions, their target values (attention scores) or residuals, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spatial-context-when-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Interleaved: Interleaved Image-Text Generative Modeling via Multi-modal Feature Synchronizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-interleaved-interleaved-image-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing generative models for interleaved image-text data has both research and practical value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-interleaved-interleaved-image-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPCL: Cross-Modal Prototypical Contrastive Learning for Weakly Supervised Text-based Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpcl-cross-modal-prototypical-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised text-based person re-identification (TPRe-ID) seeks to retrieve images of a target person using textual descriptions, without relying on identity annotations and is more challenging and practical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpcl-cross-modal-prototypical-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rigid Protein-Protein Docking via Equivariant Elliptic-Paraboloid Interface Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigid-protein-protein-docking-via-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study of rigid protein-protein docking plays an essential role in a variety of tasks such as drug design and protein engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigid-protein-protein-docking-via-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing ChatGPT: Solving Remote Sensing Tasks with ChatGPT and Visual Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-chatgpt-solving-remote-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the flourishing large language models(LLM), especially ChatGPT, have shown exceptional performance in language understanding, reasoning, and interaction, attracting users and researchers from multiple fields and domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-chatgpt-solving-remote-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENO: Boundary-embedded Neural Operators for Elliptic PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beno-boundary-embedded-neural-operators-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce Boundary-Embedded Neural Operators (BENO), a novel neural operator architecture that embeds the complex geometries and inhomogeneous boundary values into the solving of elliptic PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beno-boundary-embedded-neural-operators-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classification and Reconstruction Processes in Deep Predictive Coding Networks: Antagonists or Allies?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-and-reconstruction-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predictive coding-inspired deep networks for visual computing integrate classification and reconstruction processes in shared intermediate layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-and-reconstruction-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CT Liver Segmentation via PVT-based Encoding and Refined Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-liver-segmentation-via-pvt-based-encoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate liver segmentation from CT scans is essential for computer-aided diagnosis and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ct-liver-segmentation-via-pvt-based-encoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlogger: Make Your Dream A Vlog</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlogger-make-your-dream-a-vlog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More importantly, Vlogger can generate over 5-minute vlogs from open-world descriptions, without loss of video coherence on script and actor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlogger-make-your-dream-a-vlog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex and Bilevel Optimization for Neuro-Symbolic Inference and Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-and-bilevel-optimization-for-neuro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address a key challenge for neuro-symbolic (NeSy) systems by leveraging convex and bilevel optimization techniques to develop a general gradient-based framework for end-to-end neural and symbolic parameter learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-and-bilevel-optimization-for-neuro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MITS-GAN: Safeguarding Medical Imaging from Tampering with Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mits-gan-safeguarding-medical-imaging-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The progress in generative models, particularly Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs), opened new possibilities for image generation but raised concerns about potential malicious uses, especially in sensitive areas like medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mits-gan-safeguarding-medical-imaging-from</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
