<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 09:14:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Why Deep Learning Generalizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-deep-learning-generalizes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Very large deep learning models trained using gradient descent are remarkably resistant to memorization given their huge capacity, but are at the same time capable of fitting large datasets of pure noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-deep-learning-generalizes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalized Latent Factor Model Approach to Mixed-data Matrix Completion with Entrywise Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-latent-factor-model-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Matrix completion is a class of machine learning methods that concerns the prediction of missing entries in a partially observed matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalized-latent-factor-model-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bird's-eye View of Reranking: from List Level to Page Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bird-s-eye-view-of-reranking-from-list</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, simply applying a shared network for all the lists fails to capture the commonalities and distinctions in user behaviors on different lists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bird-s-eye-view-of-reranking-from-list</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Inference for Coadded Astronomical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-coadded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coadded astronomical images are created by stacking multiple single-exposure images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-coadded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Good Practices in Evaluating Transfer Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-good-practices-in-evaluating-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation reveals new important insights: 1) Transferability is highly contextual, and some white-box defenses may give a false sense of security since they are actually vulnerable to (black-box) transfer attacks; 2) All transfer attacks are less stealthy, and their stealthiness can vary dramatically under the same $L_{\infty}$ bound.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-good-practices-in-evaluating-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitoring machine learning (ML)-based risk prediction algorithms in the presence of confounding medical interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monitoring-machine-learning-ml-based-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitoring the performance of machine learning (ML)-based risk prediction models in healthcare is complicated by the issue of confounding medical interventions (CMI): when an algorithm predicts a patient to be at high risk for an adverse event, clinicians are more likely to administer prophylactic treatment and alter the very target that the algorithm aims to predict.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monitoring-machine-learning-ml-based-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Automated Design of Bayesian Optimization via Exploratory Landscape Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-design-of-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian optimization (BO) algorithms form a class of surrogate-based heuristics, aimed at efficiently computing high-quality solutions for numerical black-box optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-automated-design-of-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Trajectory Representation Learning with Temporal Regularities and Travel Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-trajectory-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TRL aims to convert complicated raw trajectories into low-dimensional representation vectors, which can be applied to various downstream tasks, such as trajectory classification, clustering, and similarity computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-trajectory-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniSumm: Unified Few-shot Summarization with Multi-Task Pre-Training and Prefix-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisumm-unified-few-shot-summarization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diverse demands of different summarization tasks and their high annotation costs are driving a need for few-shot summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unisumm-unified-few-shot-summarization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Transformers with Dynamic Token Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformers-with-dynamic-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers achieve unrivalled performance in modelling language, but remain inefficient in terms of memory and time complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-transformers-with-dynamic-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstractive Summarization Guided by Latent Hierarchical Document Structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstractive-summarization-guided-by-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential abstractive neural summarizers often do not use the underlying structure in the input article or dependencies between the input sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstractive-summarization-guided-by-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVDistill: Cross-Modal BEV Distillation for Multi-View 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevdistill-cross-modal-bev-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of directly training a depth prediction network, we unify the image and LiDAR features in the Bird-Eye-View (BEV) space and adaptively transfer knowledge across non-homogenous representations in a teacher-student paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevdistill-cross-modal-bev-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Arbitrary Keypoints on Limbs and Skis with Sparse Partly Correct Segmentation Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-arbitrary-keypoints-on-limbs-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze different training techniques for freely selected and standard keypoints, including pseudo labels, and show in our experiments that only a few partly correct segmentation masks are sufficient for learning to detect arbitrary keypoints on limbs and skis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-arbitrary-keypoints-on-limbs-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternVideo-Ego4D: A Pack of Champion Solutions to Ego4D Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-ego4d-a-pack-of-champion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present our champion solutions to five tracks at Ego4D challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-ego4d-a-pack-of-champion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Commonsense-aware Representation Network for Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-commonsense-aware-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating consecutive descriptions for videos, i. e., Video Captioning, requires taking full advantage of visual representation along with the generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-commonsense-aware-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOTRv2: Bootstrapping End-to-End Multi-Object Tracking by Pretrained Object Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motrv2-bootstrapping-end-to-end-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose MOTRv2, a simple yet effective pipeline to bootstrap end-to-end multi-object tracking with a pretrained object detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motrv2-bootstrapping-end-to-end-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Tree-Structured Prototype Network for End-to-End Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tree-structured-prototype-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design a novel embedding method called tree-structured prototype, producing a set of hierarchical representative embeddings which capture the hierarchical semantic structure in textual space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-tree-structured-prototype-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepPrivacy2: Towards Realistic Full-Body Anonymization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepprivacy2-towards-realistic-full-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) are widely adapted for anonymization of human figures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepprivacy2-towards-realistic-full-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ignore Previous Prompt: Attack Techniques For Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignore-previous-prompt-attack-techniques-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based large language models (LLMs) provide a powerful foundation for natural language tasks in large-scale customer-facing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignore-previous-prompt-attack-techniques-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I see you: A Vehicle-Pedestrian Interaction Dataset from Traffic Surveillance Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-see-you-a-vehicle-pedestrian-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of autonomous vehicles arises new challenges in urban traffic scenarios where vehicle-pedestrian interactions are frequent e. g. vehicle yields to pedestrians, pedestrian slows down due approaching to the vehicle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-see-you-a-vehicle-pedestrian-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionDet: Diffusion Model for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondet-diffusion-model-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In inference, the model refines a set of randomly generated boxes to the output results in a progressive way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondet-diffusion-model-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Adapter for Text-Video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-adapter-for-text-video-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as pre-trained models are scaling up, fully fine-tuning them on text-video retrieval datasets has a high risk of overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-adapter-for-text-video-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DLatNav: Navigating Generative Latent Spaces for Semantic-Aware 3D Object Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dlatnav-navigating-generative-latent-spaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most models do not offer controllability to manipulate the shape semantics of component object parts without extensive semantic attribute labels or other reference point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dlatnav-navigating-generative-latent-spaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientTrain: Exploring Generalized Curriculum Learning for Training Visual Backbones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-exploring-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is inspired by the phenomenon that deep networks mainly learn to recognize some 'easier-to-learn' discriminative patterns within each example at earlier stages of training, e. g., the lower-frequency components of images and the original information before data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-exploring-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni-Perceiver v2: A Generalist Model for Large-Scale Vision and Vision-Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-perceiver-v2-a-generalist-model-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Uni-Perceiver v2, which is the first generalist model capable of handling major large-scale vision and vision-language tasks with competitive performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-perceiver-v2-a-generalist-model-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Dynamic Image Harmonization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-dynamic-image-harmonization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the dynamic deep networks that adapt the model structures or parameters conditioned on the inputs, we propose a hierarchical dynamic network (HDNet) for efficient image harmonization to adapt the model parameters and features from local to global view for better feature transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-dynamic-image-harmonization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaMAE: Adaptive Masking for Efficient Spatiotemporal Learning with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamae-adaptive-masking-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our adaptive masking strategy samples visible tokens based on the semantic context using an auxiliary sampling network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adamae-adaptive-masking-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McNet: Fuse Multiple Cues for Multichannel Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcnet-fuse-multiple-cues-for-multichannel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multichannel speech enhancement, both spectral and spatial information are vital for discriminating between speech and noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcnet-fuse-multiple-cues-for-multichannel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving Feedback on Interactive Student Programs with Meta-Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/giving-feedback-on-interactive-student</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, teaching and giving feedback on such software is time-consuming -- standard approaches require instructors to manually grade student-implemented interactive programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/giving-feedback-on-interactive-student</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Dense and Continuous Optical Flow from an Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dense-and-continuous-optical-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel deep learning-based dense and continuous optical flow estimation framework from a single image with event streams, which facilitates the accurate perception of high-speed motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dense-and-continuous-optical-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person Text-Image Matching via Text-Featur Interpretability Embedding and External Attack Node Implantation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/person-text-image-matching-via-text-featur</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we improve the interpretability of text features by providing them with consistent semantic information with image features to achieve the alignment of text and describe image region features. To address the challenges posed by the diversity of text and the corresponding person images, we treat the variation caused by diversity to features as caused by perturbation information and propose a novel adversarial attack and defense method to solve it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/person-text-image-matching-via-text-featur</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSCD-IME: Correcting Spelling Errors Generated by Pinyin IME</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cscd-ime-correcting-spelling-errors-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In fact, most of Chinese input is based on pinyin input method, so the study of spelling errors in this process is more practical and valuable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cscd-ime-correcting-spelling-errors-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Monosemanticity in Toy Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/engineering-monosemanticity-in-toy-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we report preliminary attempts to engineer monosemanticity in toy models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/engineering-monosemanticity-in-toy-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing geometric representation hypotheses from simulated place cell recordings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-geometric-representation-hypotheses</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hippocampal place cells can encode spatial locations of an animal in physical or task-relevant spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-geometric-representation-hypotheses</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features for the 0-1 knapsack problem based on inclusionwise maximal solutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/features-for-the-0-1-knapsack-problem-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the proposed features contain important information related to the empirical hardness of a problem instance that was missing in earlier features from the literature by training machine learning models that can accurately predict the empirical hardness of a wide variety of 0-1 knapsack problem instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/features-for-the-0-1-knapsack-problem-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Question Answering in Slovene</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-question-answering-in-slovene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most approaches are developed for English, while less-resourced languages are much less researched.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-question-answering-in-slovene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmented Physics-Informed Neural Networks (APINNs): A gating network-based soft domain decomposition methodology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-physics-informed-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show cases where XPINN is already better than PINN, so APINN can still slightly improve XPINN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-physics-informed-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SETAR-Tree: A Novel and Accurate Tree Algorithm for Global Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setar-tree-a-novel-and-accurate-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, in the forecasting community, general-purpose tree-based regression algorithms (forests, gradient-boosting) have become popular recently due to their ease of use and accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/setar-tree-a-novel-and-accurate-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Graph Neural Networks for FMRI analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-graph-neural-networks-for-fmri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have emerged as a powerful tool to learn from graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-graph-neural-networks-for-fmri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetries in the dynamics of wide two-layer neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetries-in-the-dynamics-of-wide-two-layer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the idealized setting of gradient flow on the population risk for infinitely wide two-layer ReLU neural networks (without bias), and study the effect of symmetries on the learned parameters and predictors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetries-in-the-dynamics-of-wide-two-layer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Frontiers in Graph Autoencoders: Joint Community Detection and Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-frontiers-in-graph-autoencoders-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is still unclear to what extent one can improve CD with GAE and VGAE, especially in the absence of node features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-frontiers-in-graph-autoencoders-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Object Representation Learning via Motion and Object Continuity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-object-representation-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent unsupervised multi-object detection models have shown impressive performance improvements, largely attributed to novel architectural inductive biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-object-representation-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squeeze flow of micro-droplets: convolutional neural network with trainable and tunable refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-flow-of-micro-droplets-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the second part of this paper, we introduce a residual convolutional neural network to solve the corresponding inverse problem: to translate a high-resolution (HR) imprint image with a specific liquid film thickness to a low-resolution (LR) droplet pattern image capable of producing the given imprint image for an appropriate spread time of droplets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-flow-of-micro-droplets-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniRel: Unified Representation and Interaction for Joint Relational Triple Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirel-unified-representation-and-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relational triple extraction is challenging for its difficulty in capturing rich correlations between entities and relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unirel-unified-representation-and-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamical Linear Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-linear-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, the hidden state evolves according to a linear dynamics, affected by the performed action too.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamical-linear-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELDA: Using Edges to Have an Edge on Semantic Segmentation Based UDA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elda-using-edges-to-have-an-edge-on-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their effectiveness, using depth as domain invariant information in UDA tasks may lead to multiple issues, such as excessively high extraction costs and difficulties in achieving a reliable prediction quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elda-using-edges-to-have-an-edge-on-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis and Detectability of Offline Data Poisoning Attacks on Linear Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-and-detectability-of-offline-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent body of literature has investigated the effect of data poisoning attacks on data-driven control methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-and-detectability-of-offline-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Measuring the Intrinsic Few-Shot Hardness of Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-measuring-the-intrinsic-few-shot-hardness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While advances in pre-training have led to dramatic improvements in few-shot learning of NLP tasks, there is limited understanding of what drives successful few-shot adaptation in datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-measuring-the-intrinsic-few-shot-hardness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Transformer-Based Model for Ego4D Natural Language Queries Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-transformer-based-model-for-ego4d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report describes Badgers@UW-Madison, our submission to the Ego4D Natural Language Queries (NLQ) Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-transformer-based-model-for-ego4d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Based on the Predictive Uncertainty of Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-based-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) aims to improve the prediction performance in the target domain under distribution shifts from the source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-based-on-the</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
