<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2022 21:07:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Safety-Enhanced Autonomous Driving Using Interpretable Sensor Fusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-enhanced-autonomous-driving-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale deployment of autonomous vehicles has been continually delayed due to safety concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-enhanced-autonomous-driving-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowing Where and What: Unified Word Block Pretraining for Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowing-where-and-what-unified-word-block</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on the embedding learning of word blocks containing text and layout information, and propose UTel, a language model with Unified TExt and Layout pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowing-where-and-what-unified-word-block</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Cross-Person Cues for Body-Part Interactiveness Learning in HOI Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-cross-person-cues-for-body-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though significant progress has been made, interactiveness learning remains a challenging problem in HOI detection: existing methods usually generate redundant negative H-O pair proposals and fail to effectively extract interactive pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-cross-person-cues-for-body-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dive into Machine Learning Algorithms for Influenza Virus Host Prediction with Hemagglutinin Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-machine-learning-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Influenza viruses mutate rapidly and can pose a threat to public health, especially to those in vulnerable groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-machine-learning-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonteBoxFinder: Detecting and Filtering Primitives to Fit a Noisy Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monteboxfinder-detecting-and-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MonteBoxFinder, a method that, given a noisy input point cloud, fits cuboids to the input scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monteboxfinder-detecting-and-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Aligned Matching for Enhanced DETR Convergence and Multi-Scale Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aligned-matching-for-enhanced-detr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently proposed DEtection TRansformer (DETR) has established a fully end-to-end paradigm for object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aligned-matching-for-enhanced-detr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelixFold-Single: MSA-free Protein Structure Prediction by Using Protein Language Model as an Alternative</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-single-msa-free-protein-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method, HelixFold-Single, first pre-trains a large-scale protein language model (PLM) with thousands of millions of primary sequences utilizing the self-supervised learning paradigm, which will be used as an alternative to MSAs and templates for learning the co-evolution information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-single-msa-free-protein-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewriting Geometric Rules of a GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewriting-geometric-rules-of-a-gan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method allows a user to create a model that synthesizes endless objects with defined geometric changes, enabling the creation of a new generative model without the burden of curating a large-scale dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewriting-geometric-rules-of-a-gan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Training of Language Models to Fill in the Middle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-of-language-models-to-fill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we run a series of ablations on key hyperparameters, such as the data transformation frequency, the structure of the transformation, and the method of selecting the infill span.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-of-language-models-to-fill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Recognition by Request</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-by-request</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel protocol of annotation and evaluation for visual recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-by-request</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HorNet: Efficient High-Order Spatial Interactions with Recursive Gated Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the key ingredients behind the vision Transformers, namely input-adaptive, long-range and high-order spatial interactions, can also be efficiently implemented with a convolution-based framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEG2Mel: Reconstructing Sound from Brain Responses to Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg2mel-reconstructing-sound-from-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information retrieval from brain responses to auditory and visual stimuli has shown success through classification of song names and image classes presented to participants while recording EEG signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg2mel-reconstructing-sound-from-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShAPO: Implicit Representations for Multi-Object Shape, Appearance, and Pose Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapo-implicit-representations-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel disentangled shape and appearance database of priors is first learned to embed objects in their respective shape and appearance space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shapo-implicit-representations-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atomic structure generation from reconstructing structural fingerprints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-structure-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods would help identify or, in the case of generative models, even create novel crystal structures of materials with a set of specified functional properties to then be synthesized or isolated in the laboratory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-structure-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift-tolerant Perceptual Similarity Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-tolerant-perceptual-similarity-metric-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the effect of small misalignment, specifically a small shift between the input and reference image, on existing metrics, and accordingly develops a shift-tolerant similarity metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-tolerant-perceptual-similarity-metric-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiRi: A Simple Selective Retraining Mechanism for Transformer-based Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, SiRi conveys a significant principle to the research of visual grounding, i. e., a better initialized vision-language encoder would help the model converge to a better local minimum, advancing the performance accordingly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Trimap Video Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-trimap-video-matting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key of OTVM is the joint modeling of trimap propagation and alpha prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-trimap-video-matting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generator Knows What Discriminator Should Learn in Unconditional GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we explore the efficacy of dense supervision in unconditional generation and find generator feature maps can be an alternative of cost-expensive semantic label maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPS-GLASS: Learning Nighttime Semantic Segmentation Using Daytime Video and GPS data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gps-glass-learning-nighttime-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nighttime semantic segmentation is especially challenging due to a lack of annotated nighttime images and a large domain gap from daytime images with sufficient annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gps-glass-learning-nighttime-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AADG: Automatic Augmentation for Domain Generalization on Retinal Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aadg-automatic-augmentation-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a data manipulation based domain generalization method, called Automated Augmentation for Domain Generalization (AADG).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aadg-automatic-augmentation-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight and Progressively-Scalable Networks for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-progressively-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we thoroughly analyze the design of convolutional blocks (the type of convolutions and the number of channels in convolutions), and the ways of interactions across multiple scales, all from lightweight standpoint for semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-progressively-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Information and Commonsense Based Prompt for Emotion Recognition in Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-information-and-commonsense-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The newly proposed ERC models have leveraged pre-trained language models (PLMs) with the paradigm of pre-training and fine-tuning to obtain good performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-information-and-commonsense-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Hard Noise in Long-Tailed Sample Distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hard-noise-in-long-tailed-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such imbalanced training data makes a classifier less discriminative for the tail classes, whose previously "easy" noises are now turned into "hard" ones -- they are almost as outliers as the clean tail samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-hard-noise-in-long-tailed-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Video Deblurring Guided by Motion Magnitude</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video deblurring is a highly under-constrained problem due to the spatially and temporally varying blur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealTime QA: What's the Answer Right Now?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realtime-qa-what-s-the-answer-right-now</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce RealTime QA, a dynamic question answering (QA) platform that announces questions and evaluates systems on a regular basis (weekly in this version).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realtime-qa-what-s-the-answer-right-now</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast expansion into harmonics on the disk: a steerable basis with fast radial convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a fast and numerically accurate method for expanding digitized $L \times L$ images representing functions on $[-1, 1]^2$ supported on the disk $\{x \in \mathbb{R}^2 : |x|<1\}$ in the harmonics (Dirichlet Laplacian eigenfunctions) on the disk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Combinatorial Optimization Layers: a Probabilistic Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-combinatorial-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial optimization (CO) layers in machine learning (ML) pipelines are a powerful tool to tackle data-driven decision tasks, but they come with two main challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-combinatorial-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concurrent Subsidiary Supervision for Unsupervised Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-subsidiary-supervision-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prime challenge in unsupervised domain adaptation (DA) is to mitigate the domain shift between the source and target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concurrent-subsidiary-supervision-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Pix2Vox++ for 3D Cardiac Reconstruction from 2D echo views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate geometric quantification of the human heart is a key step in the diagnosis of numerous cardiac diseases, and in the management of cardiac patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging GAN Priors for Few-Shot Part Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-gan-priors-for-few-shot-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, this work is an attempt to explore the internal relevance between generation tasks and perception tasks by prompt designing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-gan-priors-for-few-shot-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstracting Sketches through Simple Primitives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Toward equipping machines with such capabilities, we propose the Primitive-based Sketch Abstraction task where the goal is to represent sketches using a fixed set of drawing primitives under the influence of a budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBench: A Framework for Evaluating Active Learning in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the research in this field, this paper contributes an active learning benchmark framework named as ALBench for evaluating active learning in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Multiparty Distance Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of evolutionary multiobjective optimization, the decision maker (DM) concerns conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mid-level Representation Enhancement and Graph Embedded Uncertainty Suppressing for Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, GUS is introduced to suppress the feature ambiguity in the representation space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-specific 6-DoF Object Pose Estimation from Minimal Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-specific-6-dof-object-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many robotic applications, the environment setting in which the 6-DoF pose estimation of a known, rigid object and its subsequent grasping is to be performed, remains nearly unchanging and might even be known to the robot in advance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-specific-6-dof-object-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camouflaged Object Detection via Context-aware Cross-level Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a novel Context-aware Cross-level Fusion Network (C2F-Net), which fuses context-aware cross-level features for accurately identifying camouflaged objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Sample Average Approximation with Covariate Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study optimization for data-driven decision-making when we have observations of the uncertain parameters within the optimization model together with concurrent observations of covariates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransNorm: Transformer Provides a Strong Spatial Normalization Mechanism for a Deep Segmentation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past few years, convolutional neural networks (CNNs), particularly U-Net, have been the prevailing technique in the medical image processing era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Neuroevolution of Low-level Artificial General Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate a method to evolve a biologically-inspired artificial neural network that learns from environment reactions named Neuroevolution of Artificial General Intelligence (NAGI), a framework for low-level AGI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardly Perceptible Trojan Attack against Neural Networks with Bit Flips</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The security of deep neural networks (DNNs) has attracted increasing attention due to their widespread use in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoTransition: Learning to Recommend Video Transition Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First we learn the embedding of video transitions through a video transition classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marker and source-marker reprogramming of Most Permissive Boolean networks and ensembles with BoNesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate how the software BoNesis can be employed to exhaustively identify combinations of perturbations which enforce properties on their fixed points and attractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe and Robust Experience Sharing for Deterministic Policy Gradient Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning in high dimensional continuous tasks is challenging, mainly when the experience replay memory is very limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorial User Modeling with Hierarchical Graph Neural Network for Enhanced Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most sequential recommendation (SR) systems employing graph neural networks (GNNs) only model a user's interaction sequence as a flat graph without hierarchy, overlooking diverse factors in the user's preference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASTA-GAN++: A Versatile Framework for High-Resolution Unpaired Virtual Try-on</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-gan-a-versatile-framework-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a step forwards to explore versatile virtual try-on solutions, which we argue should possess three main properties, namely, they should support unsupervised training, arbitrary garment categories, and controllable garment editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-gan-a-versatile-framework-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Attention of Disentangled Modalities for 3D Human Mesh Recovery with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-of-disentangled-modalities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer encoder architectures have recently achieved state-of-the-art results on monocular 3D human mesh reconstruction, but they require a substantial number of parameters and expensive computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-of-disentangled-modalities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Break and Make: Interactive Structural Understanding Using LEGO Bricks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/break-and-make-interactive-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We pair this simulator with a new dataset of fan-made LEGO creations that have been uploaded to the internet in order to provide complex scenes containing over a thousand unique brick shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/break-and-make-interactive-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Vizier: Distributed Infrastructure and API for Reliable and Flexible Blackbox Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vizier is the de-facto blackbox and hyperparameter optimization service across Google, having optimized some of Google's largest products and research efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physical Systems Modeled Without Physical Laws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physical-systems-modeled-without-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-based simulations typically operate with a combination of complex differentiable equations and many scientific and geometric inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physical-systems-modeled-without-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Synthesis of Artistic Images with Retrieval-Augmented Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In RDMs, a set of nearest neighbors is retrieved from an external database during training for each training instance, and the diffusion model is conditioned on these informative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
