<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 21:08:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Learning for Efficient Fine-Tuning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-for-efficient-fine-tuning-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The research investigates the application of meta-learning strategies to enhance the adaptability and performance of LLMs with limited computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-for-efficient-fine-tuning-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabReD: A Benchmark of Tabular Machine Learning in-the-Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabred-a-benchmark-of-tabular-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine existing tabular benchmarks and find two common characteristics of industry-grade tabular data that are underrepresented in the datasets available to the academic community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabred-a-benchmark-of-tabular-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Illusion of Competence: Evaluating the Effect of Explanations on Users' Mental Models of Visual Question Answering Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-illusion-of-competence-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine how users perceive the limitations of an AI system when it encounters a task that it cannot perform perfectly and whether providing explanations alongside its answers aids users in constructing an appropriate mental model of the system's capabilities and limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-illusion-of-competence-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correspondence-Free Non-Rigid Point Set Registration Using Unsupervised Clustering Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correspondence-free-non-rigid-point-set-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel non-rigid point set registration method that is inspired by unsupervised clustering analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correspondence-free-non-rigid-point-set-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimensions underlying the representational alignment of deep neural networks with humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensions-underlying-the-representational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying this framework to humans and a DNN model of natural images revealed a low-dimensional DNN embedding of both visual and semantic dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensions-underlying-the-representational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suri: Multi-constraint Instruction Following for Long-form Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suri-multi-constraint-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing research on instruction following largely focuses on tasks with simple instructions and short responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suri-multi-constraint-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeaKR: Self-aware Knowledge Retrieval for Adaptive Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seakr-self-aware-knowledge-retrieval-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Self-aware Knowledge Retrieval (SeaKR), a novel adaptive RAG model that extracts self-aware uncertainty of LLMs from their internal states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seakr-self-aware-knowledge-retrieval-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELLO: Causal Evaluation of Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cello-causal-evaluation-of-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work typically focuses on commonsense causality between events and/or actions, which is insufficient for applications like embodied agents and lacks the explicitly defined causal graphs required for formal causal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cello-causal-evaluation-of-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEX-TTS: Diffusion-based EXpressive Text-to-Speech with Style Modeling on Time Variability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-tts-diffusion-based-expressive-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expressive Text-to-Speech (TTS) using reference speech has been studied extensively to synthesize natural speech, but there are limitations to obtaining well-represented styles and improving model generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-tts-diffusion-based-expressive-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Learning Abductive Reasoning using VSA Distributed Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-abductive-reasoning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Abductive Rule Learner with Context-awareness (ARLC), a model that solves abstract reasoning tasks based on Learn-VRF.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-abductive-reasoning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpleFusion: A Simple Fusion Framework for Infrared and Visible Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplefusion-a-simple-fusion-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating visible and infrared images into one high-quality image, also known as visible and infrared image fusion, is a challenging yet critical task for many downstream vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplefusion-a-simple-fusion-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSP: Self-Supervised Prompting for Cross-Lingual Transfer to Low-Resource Languages using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-prompting-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate their effectiveness for NLP tasks in low-resource languages (LRLs), especially in the setting of zero-labelled cross-lingual transfer (0-CLT), where no labelled training data for the target language is available -- however training data from one or more related medium-resource languages (MRLs) is utilized, alongside the available unlabeled test data for a target language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-prompting-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factor multivariate stochastic volatility models of high dimension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factor-multivariate-stochastic-volatility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a two-stage estimation procedure for the fMSV model: the first stage obtains the estimators of the factor model, and the second stage estimates the MSV part using the estimated common factor variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factor-multivariate-stochastic-volatility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding-Time Language Model Alignment with Multiple Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-time-language-model-alignment-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional methods that require careful curation of a mixture of datasets to achieve comprehensive improvement, we can quickly experiment with preference weightings using MOD to find the best combination of models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-time-language-model-alignment-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporally Multi-Scale Sparse Self-Attention for Physical Activity Data Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-multi-scale-sparse-self-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wearable sensors enable health researchers to continuously collect data pertaining to the physiological state of individuals in real-world settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-multi-scale-sparse-self-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMRxRecon2024: A Multi-Modality, Multi-View K-Space Dataset Boosting Universal Machine Learning for Accelerated Cardiac MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmrxrecon2024-a-multi-modality-multi-view-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, the CMRxRecon2024 dataset is the largest and most diverse publicly available cardiac k-space dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmrxrecon2024-a-multi-modality-multi-view-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Anywhere Pointed: Layout-aware GUI Screen Reading with Tree-of-Lens Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-anywhere-pointed-layout-aware-gui-screen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Tree-of-Lens (ToL) agent, utilizing a novel ToL grounding mechanism, to address the SPR task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-anywhere-pointed-layout-aware-gui-screen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HuatuoGPT-Vision, Towards Injecting Medical Visual Knowledge into Multimodal LLMs at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huatuogpt-vision-towards-injecting-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of multimodal large language models (MLLMs), such as GPT-4V, has led to significant advancements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huatuogpt-vision-towards-injecting-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoMambaPro: A Leap Forward for Mamba in Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videomambapro-a-leap-forward-for-mamba-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of high performance and efficiency makes VideoMambaPro an interesting alternative for transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videomambapro-a-leap-forward-for-mamba-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALVe: Semantic Alignment Verification for Floorplan Reconstruction from Sparse Panoramas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salve-semantic-alignment-verification-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once the room poses are computed, room layouts are inferred using HorizonNet, and the floorplan is constructed by stitching the most confident layout boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salve-semantic-alignment-verification-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking 3D: Anomaly Detection with 2D-3D Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-3d-anomaly-detection-with-2d-3d-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic anomaly detection based on visual cues holds practical significance in various domains, such as manufacturing and product quality assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-3d-anomaly-detection-with-2d-3d-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Me If You Can: Aggregating AutoEncoders for Countering Persistent Access Threats Within Highly Imbalanced Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hack-me-if-you-can-aggregating-autoencoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated our tool on a suite of provenance trace databases produced by the DARPA Transparent Computing program, where APT-like attacks constitute as little as 0. 004% of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hack-me-if-you-can-aggregating-autoencoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YZS-model: A Predictive Model for Organic Drug Solubility Based on Graph Convolutional Networks and Transformer-Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yzs-model-a-predictive-model-for-organic-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research not only demonstrates the vast potential of deep learning for improving solubility prediction accuracy but also offers novel insights for drug design and selection in the future.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yzs-model-a-predictive-model-for-organic-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STBench: Assessing the Ability of Large Language Models in Spatio-Temporal Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stbench-assessing-the-ability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of large language models (LLMs) holds promise for reforming the methodology of spatio-temporal data mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stbench-assessing-the-ability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Life: How Well-formed, Self-replicating Programs Emerge from Simple Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-life-how-well-formed-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fields of Origin of Life and Artificial Life both question what life is and how it emerges from a distinct set of "pre-life" dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-life-how-well-formed-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-adaptive Synergetic Two-way Pseudoinverse Learning System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-adaptive-synergetic-two-way</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The whole system is trained using a non-gradient descent learning algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-adaptive-synergetic-two-way</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Formal Characterization of User Simulation Objectives in Conversational Information Access</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-formal-characterization-of-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[User simulation is a promising approach for automatically training and evaluating conversational information access agents, enabling the generation of synthetic dialogues and facilitating reproducible experiments at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-formal-characterization-of-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMG-LLaVA: Bridging Image-level, Object-level, Pixel-level Reasoning and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omg-llava-bridging-image-level-object-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current universal segmentation methods demonstrate strong capabilities in pixel-level image and video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omg-llava-bridging-image-level-object-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Weak-to-Strong Generalization with Reliability-Aware Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-weak-to-strong-generalization-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are now rapidly advancing and surpassing human abilities on many natural language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-weak-to-strong-generalization-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Pronged Human Evaluation of ChatGPT Self-Correction in Radiology Report Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-pronged-human-evaluation-of-chatgpt-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiology reports are highly technical documents aimed primarily at doctor-doctor communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-pronged-human-evaluation-of-chatgpt-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Pareto Set for Multi-Objective Continuous Robot Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pareto-set-for-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a control problem with multiple conflicting objectives, there exists a set of Pareto-optimal policies called the Pareto set instead of a single optimal policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pareto-set-for-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoder based approach for the mitigation of spurious correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-approach-for-the-mitigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have exhibited remarkable performance across various tasks, yet their susceptibility to spurious correlations poses a significant challenge for out-of-distribution (OOD) generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-approach-for-the-mitigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the duration of traffic incidents for Sydney greater metropolitan area using machine learning methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-duration-of-traffic-incidents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results demonstrate that XGBoost and LightGBM outperform conventional models with XGBoost achieving the lowest RMSE of 33. 7 for predicting incident duration and highest classification F1 score of 0. 62 for a 30-minute duration threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-duration-of-traffic-incidents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking Convolutional Neural Networks for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-convolutional-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spiking neural networks (SNNs) offer a promising pathway to implement deep neural networks (DNNs) in a more energy-efficient manner since their neurons are sparsely activated and inferences are event-driven.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-convolutional-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedMLP: Federated Multi-Label Medical Image Classification under Task Heterogeneity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmlp-federated-multi-label-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on two publicly-available medical datasets validate the superiority of FedMLP against the state-of-the-art both federated semi-supervised and noisy label learning approaches under task heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmlp-federated-multi-label-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dysca: A Dynamic and Scalable Benchmark for Evaluating Perception Ability of LVLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dysca-a-dynamic-and-scalable-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, these benchmarks merely focus on evaluating LVLMs on the realistic style images and clean scenarios, leaving the multi-stylized images and noisy scenarios unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dysca-a-dynamic-and-scalable-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUWSOD: Holistic Self-training for Unified Weakly Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huwsod-holistic-self-training-for-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most WSOD methods rely on traditional object proposals to generate candidate regions and are confronted with unstable training, which easily gets stuck in a poor local optimum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huwsod-holistic-self-training-for-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Biased Selective Labels to Pseudo-Labels: An Expectation-Maximization Framework for Learning from Biased Decisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-biased-selective-labels-to-pseudo-labels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by causal models of selective labels, we propose Disparate Censorship Expectation-Maximization (DCEM), an algorithm for learning in the presence of disparate censorship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-biased-selective-labels-to-pseudo-labels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Aware Vision-and-Language Navigation: Bridging Simulation to Reality with Dynamic Human Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-aware-vision-and-language-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-and-Language Navigation (VLN) aims to develop embodied agents that navigate based on human instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-aware-vision-and-language-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReXTime: A Benchmark Suite for Reasoning-Across-Time in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rextime-a-benchmark-suite-for-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This form of reasoning, requiring advanced understanding of cause-and-effect relationships across video segments, poses significant challenges to even the frontier multimodal large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rextime-a-benchmark-suite-for-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPureData: Automated Filtering of Web Data for LLM Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopuredata-automated-filtering-of-web-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Up-to-date and reliable Large Language Models (LLMs) are consistently sought after.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopuredata-automated-filtering-of-web-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiveBench: A Challenging, Contamination-Free LLM Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livebench-a-challenging-contamination-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a new benchmark for LLMs designed to be immune to both test set contamination and the pitfalls of LLM judging and human crowdsourcing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livebench-a-challenging-contamination-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmPO: Theory-Driven Dataset Construction for Empathetic Response Generation through Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empo-theory-driven-dataset-construction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empathetic response generation is a desirable aspect of conversational agents, crucial for facilitating engaging and emotionally intelligent multi-turn conversations between humans and machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empo-theory-driven-dataset-construction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMBROSIA: A Benchmark for Parsing Ambiguous Questions into Database Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambrosia-a-benchmark-for-parsing-ambiguous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Practical semantic parsers are expected to understand user utterances and map them to executable programs, even when these are ambiguous.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambrosia-a-benchmark-for-parsing-ambiguous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Graph Semantic and Structural Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-graph-semantic-and-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, for node-level semantics, we find that contrasting nodes from distinct classes is beneficial to provide a well-performing discrimination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-graph-semantic-and-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoboUniView: Visual-Language Model with Unified View Representation for Robotic Manipulaiton</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robouniview-visual-language-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This unified view representation more accurately mirrors the physical world and is not constrained by the robotic platform's camera parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robouniview-visual-language-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient World Models with Context-Aware Tokenization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-world-models-with-context-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling up deep Reinforcement Learning (RL) methods presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-world-models-with-context-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Fine-Grained Values and Opinions in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-fine-grained-values-and-opinions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For fine-grained analysis, we propose to identify tropes in the responses: semantically similar phrases that are recurrent and consistent across different prompts, revealing patterns in the text that a given LLM is prone to produce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-fine-grained-values-and-opinions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolving Discrepancies in Compute-Optimal Scaling of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-discrepancies-in-compute-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a secondary result, we derive scaling laws for the optimal learning rate and batch size, finding that tuning the AdamW $\beta_2$ parameter is essential at lower batch sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-discrepancies-in-compute-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Surprisingly Simple yet Effective Multi-Query Rewriting Method for Conversational Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-surprisingly-simple-yet-effective-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational passage retrieval is challenging as it often requires the resolution of references to previous utterances and needs to deal with the complexities of natural language, such as coreference and ellipsis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-surprisingly-simple-yet-effective-multi</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
