<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 21:07:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Prioritized Experience Replay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actor-prioritized-experience-replay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A widely-studied deep reinforcement learning (RL) technique known as Prioritized Experience Replay (PER) allows agents to learn from transitions sampled with non-uniform probability proportional to their temporal-difference (TD) error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actor-prioritized-experience-replay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hermes: Accelerating Long-Latency Load Requests via Perceptron-Based Off-Chip Load Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-accelerating-long-latency-load</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a new technique called Hermes, whose key idea is to: 1) accurately predict which load requests might go off-chip, and 2) speculatively fetch the data required by the predicted off-chip loads directly from the main memory, while also concurrently accessing the cache hierarchy for such loads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-accelerating-long-latency-load</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Models and Benchmarks for Representation Learning of Partially Observed Subgraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/models-and-benchmarks-for-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subgraphs are rich substructures in graphs, and their nodes and edges can be partially observed in real-world tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/models-and-benchmarks-for-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negation detection in Dutch clinical texts: an evaluation of rule-based and machine learning methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negation-detection-in-dutch-clinical-texts-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As structured data are often insufficient, labels need to be extracted from free text in electronic health records when developing models for clinical information retrieval and decision support systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negation-detection-in-dutch-clinical-texts-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointCLM: A Contrastive Learning-based Framework for Multi-instance Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointclm-a-contrastive-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-instance point cloud registration is the problem of estimating multiple poses of source point cloud instances within a target point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointclm-a-contrastive-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDEN: Towards Physics-Guided Neural Networks for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stden-towards-physics-guided-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-performance traffic flow prediction model designing, a core technology of Intelligent Transportation System, is a long-standing but still challenging task for industrial and academic communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stden-towards-physics-guided-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Tree Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-tree-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous graph neural networks (HGNNs) have attracted increasing research interest in recent three years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-tree-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Neural Process Family: Survey, Applications and Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-neural-process-family-survey-applications</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We shed light on their potential to bring several recent advances in other deep learning domains under one umbrella.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-neural-process-family-survey-applications</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Pretraining for 2D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-2d-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we elaborate and analyse the effectiveness of supervised and self-supervised pretraining approaches on downstream medical image segmentation, focusing on convergence and data efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-2d-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AccoMontage2: A Complete Harmonization and Accompaniment Arrangement System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accomontage2-a-complete-harmonization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose AccoMontage2, a system capable of doing full-length song harmonization and accompaniment arrangement based on a lead melody.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accomontage2-a-complete-harmonization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensembling Neural Networks for Improved Prediction and Privacy in Early Diagnosis of Sepsis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-neural-networks-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensembling neural networks is a long-standing technique for improving the generalization error of neural networks by combining networks with orthogonal properties via a committee decision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-neural-networks-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Imaging Projection Cloud Scattering Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-imaging-projection-cloud-scattering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper is the first to demonstrate CT of a real cloud using empirical data directly in a DNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-imaging-projection-cloud-scattering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi Camera Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Pipeline for Object Detection in Cultural Sites through Adversarial Learning and Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection algorithms allow to enable many interesting applications which can be implemented in different devices, such as smartphones and wearable devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers are Sample Efficient World Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-sample-efficient-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning agents are notoriously sample inefficient, which considerably limits their application to real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-sample-efficient-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuantNAS for super resolution: searching for efficient quantization-friendly architectures against quantization noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantnas-for-super-resolution-searching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a constant need for high-performing and computationally efficient neural network models for image super-resolution (SR) often used on low-capacity devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantnas-for-super-resolution-searching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree-Based Adaptive Model Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-based-adaptive-model-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend the Kearns-Vazirani learning algorithm to be able to handle systems that change over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-based-adaptive-model-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextualized language models for semantic change detection: lessons learned</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualized-language-models-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that contextualized methods can often predict high change scores for words which are not undergoing any real diachronic semantic shift in the lexicographic sense of the term (or at least the status of these shifts is questionable).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualized-language-models-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Conversational Recommendations: Is Decision Tree All You Need?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-conversational-recommendations-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fourthly, when the user rejects a recommendation, we adaptively choose the next decision tree to improve subsequent questions and recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-conversational-recommendations-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EViT: Privacy-Preserving Image Retrieval via Encrypted Vision Transformer in Cloud Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evit-privacy-preserving-image-retrieval-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, image-encryption-based privacy-preserving image retrieval schemes have been developed, which first extract features from cipher-images, and then build retrieval models based on these features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evit-privacy-preserving-image-retrieval-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NestedFormer: Nested Modality-Aware Transformer for Brain Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nestedformer-nested-modality-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal MR imaging is routinely used in clinical practice to diagnose and investigate brain tumors by providing rich complementary information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nestedformer-nested-modality-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-class Recommendation Systems with the Hinge Pairwise Distance Loss and Orthogonal Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-recommendation-systems-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In one-class recommendation systems, the goal is to learn a model from a small set of interacted users and items and then identify the positively-related user-item pairs among a large number of pairs with unknown interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-recommendation-systems-with-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTorch Image Quality: Metrics for Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-image-quality-metrics-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image Quality Assessment (IQA) metrics are widely used to quantitatively estimate the extent of image degradation following some forming, restoring, transforming, or enhancing algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-image-quality-metrics-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style-Agnostic Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-agnostic-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method of learning style-agnostic representation using both style transfer and adversarial learning in the reinforcement learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-agnostic-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMA Cell: A Modular and Effective Approach for Neural Autoregressive Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arma-cell-a-modular-and-effective-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce the ARMA cell, a simpler, modular, and effective approach for time series modeling in neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arma-cell-a-modular-and-effective-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANIT: Language-Driven Image-to-Image Translation for Unlabeled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanit-language-driven-image-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing techniques for image-to-image translation commonly have suffered from two critical problems: heavy reliance on per-sample domain annotation and/or inability of handling multiple attributes per image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanit-language-driven-image-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ant Colony Optimization for Mining Gradual Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-mining-gradual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gradual pattern extraction is a field in (KDD) Knowledge Discovery in Databases that maps correlations between attributes of a data set as gradual dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-colony-optimization-for-mining-gradual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell-Free Latent Go-Explore</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-free-latent-go-explore</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Latent Go-Explore (LGE), a simple and general approach based on the Go-Explore paradigm for exploration in reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-free-latent-go-explore</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fair Experimental Comparison of Neural Network Architectures for Latent Representations of Multi-Omics for Drug Response Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fair-experimental-comparison-of-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One important parameter is the depth of integration: the point at which the latent representations are computed or merged, which can be either early, intermediate, or late.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fair-experimental-comparison-of-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2BiVQA: Double Bi-LSTM based Video Quality Assessment of UGC Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2bivqa-double-bi-lstm-based-video-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the growing popularity of mobile devices as well as video sharing platforms (e. g., YouTube, Facebook, TikTok, and Twitch), User-Generated Content (UGC) videos have become increasingly common and now account for a large portion of multimedia traffic on the internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2bivqa-double-bi-lstm-based-video-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stationary Kernels and Gaussian Processes on Lie Groups and their Homogeneous Spaces I: the Compact Case</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stationary-kernels-and-gaussian-processes-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The invariance of a Gaussian process' covariance to such symmetries gives rise to the most natural generalization of the concept of stationarity to such spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stationary-kernels-and-gaussian-processes-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Online Clustering of Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-online-clustering-of-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contextual multi-armed bandit (MAB) is an important sequential decision-making problem in recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-online-clustering-of-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Space NeRF: Learning Animatable Avatars and Scene Lighting in Separate Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-nerf-learning-animatable-avatars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods alleviate the inconsistency of lighting by learning a per-frame embedding, but this operation does not generalize to unseen poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-nerf-learning-animatable-avatars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audiogram Digitization Tool for Audiological Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogram-digitization-tool-for-audiological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A number of private and public insurers compensate workers whose hearing loss can be directly attributed to excessive exposure to noise in the workplace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogram-digitization-tool-for-audiological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIM-Trans: Structure Information Modeling Transformer for Fine-grained Visual Categorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-trans-structure-information-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above limitations, we propose the Structure Information Modeling Transformer (SIM-Trans) to incorporate object structure information into transformer for enhancing discriminative representation learning to contain both the appearance information and structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim-trans-structure-information-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving RGB-D Point Cloud Registration by Learning Multi-scale Local Linear Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-rgb-d-point-cloud-registration-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to previous methods that seek correspondences by hand-crafted or learnt geometric features, recent point cloud registration methods have tried to apply RGB-D data to achieve more accurate correspondence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-rgb-d-point-cloud-registration-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiLink: an encyclopedia-based semantic network for design innovation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikilink-an-encyclopedia-based-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing semantic networks for design innovation is built on data source restricted to technological and scientific information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikilink-an-encyclopedia-based-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LINKS: A dataset of a hundred million planar linkage mechanisms for data-driven kinematic design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/links-a-dataset-of-a-hundred-million-planar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LINKS is made up of various components including 100 million mechanisms, the simulation data for each mechanism, normalized paths generated by each mechanism, a curated set of paths, the code used to generate the data and simulate mechanisms, and a live web demo for interactive design of linkage mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/links-a-dataset-of-a-hundred-million-planar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAST-AID Brain: Fast and Accurate Segmentation Tool using Artificial Intelligence Developed for Brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-aid-brain-fast-and-accurate-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel deep learning method is proposed for fast and accurate segmentation of the human brain into 132 regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-aid-brain-fast-and-accurate-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeloForm: Generating Melody with Musical Form based on Expert Systems and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meloform-generating-melody-with-musical-form</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, 1) we design an expert system to generate a melody by developing musical elements from motifs to phrases then to sections with repetitions and variations according to pre-given musical form; 2) considering the generated melody is lack of musical richness, we design a Transformer based refinement model to improve the melody without changing its musical form.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meloform-generating-melody-with-musical-form</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Boosting the Open-Domain Chatbot with Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-boosting-the-open-domain-chatbot-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many open-domain dialogue models pre-trained with social media comments can generate coherent replies but have difficulties producing engaging responses when interacting with real users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-boosting-the-open-domain-chatbot-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthehicle: Multi-Vehicle Multi-Camera Tracking in Virtual Cities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthehicle-multi-vehicle-multi-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Smart City applications such as intelligent traffic routing or accident prevention rely on computer vision methods for exact vehicle localization and tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthehicle-multi-vehicle-multi-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representations for Hyper-Relational Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-hyper-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It motivates us to design a framework that utilizes multiple aggregators to learn representations for hyper-relational facts: one from the perspective of the base triple and the other one from the perspective of the qualifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-for-hyper-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUAHN-VIO: Content-and-Uncertainty-Aware Homography Network for Visual-Inertial Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuahn-vio-content-and-uncertainty-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning-based visual ego-motion estimation is promising yet not ready for navigating agile mobile robots in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuahn-vio-content-and-uncertainty-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Contextual Diversity for Dense Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-contextual-diversity-for-dense-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detection of out-of-distribution (OoD) samples in the context of image classification has recently become an area of interest and active study, along with the topic of uncertainty estimation, to which it is closely related.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-contextual-diversity-for-dense-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prior-Aware Synthetic Data to the Rescue: Animal Pose Estimation with Very Limited Real Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-aware-synthetic-data-to-the-rescue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we present a very data efficient strategy targeted for pose estimation in quadrupeds that requires only a small amount of real images from the target animal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prior-aware-synthetic-data-to-the-rescue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Search Once: On Lightweight Differentiable Architecture Search for Resource-Constrained Embedded Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-search-once-on-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from the search efficiency, differentiable neural architecture search (NAS) has evolved as the most dominant alternative to automatically design competitive deep neural networks (DNNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-search-once-on-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>k-MS: A novel clustering algorithm based on morphological reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-ms-a-novel-clustering-algorithm-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a clusterization algorithm called k-Morphological Sets (k-MS), based on morphological reconstruction and heuristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-ms-a-novel-clustering-algorithm-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric and Online Change Detection in Multivariate Datastreams using QuantTree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-and-online-change-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Like many change-detection algorithms, QT-EWMA builds a model of the data distribution, in our case a QuantTree histogram, from a stationary training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-and-online-change-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Multi-granular Concept Extraction Based on Machine Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-granular-concept-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to supply existing KGs with more fine-grained and new concepts, we propose a novel concept extraction framework, namely MRC-CE, to extract large-scale multi-granular concepts from the descriptive texts of entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-granular-concept-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiGNN: Hierarchical Informative Graph Neural Networks for Molecular Property Prediction Equipped with Feature-Wise Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hignn-hierarchical-informative-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Elucidating and accurately predicting the druggability and bioactivities of molecules plays a pivotal role in drug design and discovery and remains an open challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hignn-hierarchical-informative-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
