<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 09:17:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Channel-aware Contrastive Conditional Diffusion for Multivariate Probabilistic Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-contrastive-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we devise an ad-hoc denoising-based temporal contrastive learning to explicitly amplify the predictive mutual information between past observations and future forecasts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-contrastive-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeJudge: Evaluating Code Generation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codejudge-evaluating-code-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents CodeJudge, a code evaluation framework that leverages LLMs to evaluate the semantic correctness of generated code without the need for test cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codejudge-evaluating-code-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Inference Frame for SMLM (Single-Molecule Localization Microscopy)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-inference-frame-for-smlm-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-molecule localization microscopy (SMLM) surpasses the diffraction limit, achieving subcellular resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-inference-frame-for-smlm-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measurements with Noise: Bayesian Optimization for Co-optimizing Noise and Property Discovery in Automated Experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measurements-with-noise-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have developed a Bayesian optimization (BO) workflow that integrates intra-step noise optimization into automated experimental cycles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measurements-with-noise-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Train Long-Context Language Models (Effectively)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-long-context-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study continued training and supervised fine-tuning (SFT) of a language model (LM) to make effective use of long-context information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-train-long-context-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Searching for Efficient Linear Layers over a Continuous Space of Structured Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-efficient-linear-layers-over-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To analyze the framework, we develop a taxonomy of all such operators based on their computational and algebraic properties and show that differences in the compute-optimal scaling laws are mostly governed by a small number of variables that we introduce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/searching-for-efficient-linear-layers-over-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTARR: A fast and robust method for identifying anatomical regions on CT images via atlas registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctarr-a-fast-and-robust-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method serves as a pre-processing step for any deep learning-based CT image analysis pipeline by automatically identifying the pre-defined anatomical region that is relevant for the follow-up task and removing the rest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctarr-a-fast-and-robust-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey of Mamba Architectures for Medical Image Analysis: Classification, Segmentation, Restoration and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-mamba-architectures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This review aims to demonstrate the transformative potential of Mamba in overcoming existing barriers within medical imaging while paving the way for innovative advancements in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-of-mamba-architectures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POSIX: A Prompt Sensitivity Index For Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posix-a-prompt-sensitivity-index-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their remarkable capabilities, Large Language Models (LLMs) are found to be surprisingly sensitive to minor variations in prompts, often generating significantly divergent outputs in response to minor variations in the prompts, such as spelling errors, alteration of wording or the prompt template.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posix-a-prompt-sensitivity-index-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collective Critics for Creative Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-critics-for-creative-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating a long story of several thousand words with narrative coherence using Large Language Models (LLMs) has been a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collective-critics-for-creative-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Negative Sample Mining for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-negative-sample-mining-for-whole-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised whole slide image (WSI) classification is challenging due to the lack of patch-level labels and high computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-negative-sample-mining-for-whole-slide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinoground: Scrutinizing LMMs over Dense Temporal Reasoning with Short Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vinoground-scrutinizing-lmms-over-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been growing sentiment recently that modern large multimodal models (LMMs) have addressed most of the key challenges related to short video comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vinoground-scrutinizing-lmms-over-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-Stereo Inputs: A Solution to the Occlusion Challenge in Self-Supervised Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-stereo-inputs-a-solution-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed pseudo-stereo inputs strategy, due to its simplicity and effectiveness, has the potential to serve as a new paradigm for direct self-supervised stereo matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-stereo-inputs-a-solution-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining Language Modeling Assumptions Using an Annotated Literary Dialect Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-language-modeling-assumptions-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a dataset of 19th century American literary orthovariant tokens with a novel layer of human-annotated dialect group tags designed to serve as the basis for computational experiments exploring literarily meaningful orthographic variation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-language-modeling-assumptions-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaEdit: Null-Space Constrained Knowledge Editing for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphaedit-null-space-constrained-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce AlphaEdit, a novel solution that projects perturbation onto the null space of the preserved knowledge before applying it to the parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphaedit-null-space-constrained-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L-CiteEval: Do Long-Context Models Truly Leverage Context for Responding?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-citeeval-do-long-context-models-truly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-context models (LCMs) have made remarkable strides in recent years, offering users great convenience for handling tasks that involve long context, such as document summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-citeeval-do-long-context-models-truly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlled Generation of Natural Adversarial Documents for Stealthy Retrieval Poisoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-generation-of-natural-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work showed that retrieval based on embedding similarity (e. g., for retrieval-augmented generation) is vulnerable to poisoning: an adversary can craft malicious documents that are retrieved in response to broad classes of queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-generation-of-natural-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choices are More Important than Efforts: LLM Enables Efficient Multi-Agent Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/choices-are-more-important-than-efforts-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With expansive state-action spaces, efficient multi-agent exploration remains a longstanding challenge in reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/choices-are-more-important-than-efforts-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Med-TTT: Vision Test-Time Training model for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-ttt-vision-test-time-training-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation plays a crucial role in clinical diagnosis and treatment planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-ttt-vision-test-time-training-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical Insights into Fine-Tuning Attention Mechanism: Generalization and Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-insights-into-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a theoretical analysis of these phenomena from two perspectives: (i) Generalization, where we demonstrate that fine-tuning only $\mathbf{W}_q$ and $\mathbf{W}_v$ improves generalization bounds, enhances memory efficiency, and (ii) Optimization, where we emphasize that the feature learning of the attention mechanism is efficient, particularly when using distinct learning rates for the matrices, which leads to more effective fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-insights-into-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature Diversity-Driven Deformation and Domain Alignment for Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-diversity-driven-deformation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach first introduces a \textit{\textbf{Curv}ature Diversity-driven Deformation \textbf{Rec}onstruction (CurvRec)} task, which effectively mitigates the gap between the source and target domains by enabling the model to extract salient features from semantically rich regions of a given point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-diversity-driven-deformation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erasing Conceptual Knowledge from Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-conceptual-knowledge-from-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept erasure in language models has traditionally lacked a comprehensive evaluation framework, leading to incomplete assessments of effectiveness of erasure methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-conceptual-knowledge-from-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Regression 2D-3D Ultrasound Registration for Liver Motion Correction in Focal Tumor Thermal Ablation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-regression-2d-3d-ultrasound-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a 2D-3D US registration approach to enable intra-procedural alignment that mitigates errors caused by liver motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-regression-2d-3d-ultrasound-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Memorization In Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-memorization-in-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) can "memorize" information, i. e., encode training data in their weights in such a way that inference-time queries can lead to verbatim regurgitation of that data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-memorization-in-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Implicit Bias Detection and Mitigation in Multi-Agent LLM Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-implicit-bias-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, our study investigates the presence of implicit gender biases in multi-agent LLM interactions and proposes two strategies to mitigate these biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-implicit-bias-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents' Room: Narrative Generation through Multi-step Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-room-narrative-generation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Writing compelling fiction is a multifaceted process combining elements such as crafting a plot, developing interesting characters, and using evocative language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-room-narrative-generation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynCo: Synthetic Hard Negatives in Contrastive Learning for Better Unsupervised Visual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synco-synthetic-hard-negatives-in-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce SynCo (Synthetic Negatives in Contrastive learning), a novel contrastive learning approach that improves model performance by generating synthetic hard negatives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synco-synthetic-hard-negatives-in-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCA: Highly Efficient Semantic-Consistent Unrestricted Adversarial Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sca-highly-efficient-semantic-consistent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unrestricted adversarial attacks typically manipulate the semantic content of an image (e. g., color or texture) to create adversarial examples that are both effective and photorealistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sca-highly-efficient-semantic-consistent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BadCM: Invisible Backdoor Attack Against Cross-Modal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badcm-invisible-backdoor-attack-against-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel bilateral backdoor to fill in the missing pieces of the puzzle in the cross-modal backdoor and propose a generalized invisible backdoor framework against cross-modal learning (BadCM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badcm-invisible-backdoor-attack-against-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dog-IQA: Standard-guided Zero-shot MLLM for Mix-grained Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dog-iqa-standard-guided-zero-shot-mllm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image quality assessment (IQA) serves as the golden standard for all models' performance in nearly all computer vision fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dog-iqa-standard-guided-zero-shot-mllm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Grasp Legal Theories? Enhance Legal Reasoning with Insights from Multi-Agent Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) could struggle to fully understand legal theories and perform complex legal reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-grasp-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMetrics: Calibrating Metrics For Generation Tasks Using Human Preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metametrics-calibrating-metrics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This makes MetaMetrics a powerful tool for improving the evaluation of generation tasks, ensuring that metrics are more representative of human judgment across diverse contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metametrics-calibrating-metrics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Offline Foundation Features with Tensor Augmentations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-offline-foundation-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Learning from Offline Foundation Features with Tensor Augmentations (LOFF-TA), an efficient training scheme designed to harness the capabilities of foundation models in limited resource settings where their direct development is not feasible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-offline-foundation-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Preference Modeling with Preference Representations for Aligning Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-preference-modeling-with-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce preference representation learning, an approach that embeds responses into a latent space to capture intricate preference structures efficiently, achieving linear query complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-preference-modeling-with-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiddenGuard: Fine-Grained Safe Generation with Specialized Representation Router</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiddenguard-fine-grained-safe-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ideally, LLMs should provide informative responses while avoiding the disclosure of harmful or sensitive information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiddenguard-fine-grained-safe-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReLIC: A Recipe for 64k Steps of In-Context Reinforcement Learning for Embodied AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relic-a-recipe-for-64k-steps-of-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intelligent embodied agents need to quickly adapt to new scenarios by integrating long histories of experience into decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relic-a-recipe-for-64k-steps-of-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Compound Sentences Simple to Analyze: Learning to Split Sentences for Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-compound-sentences-simple-to-analyze</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a plug-and-play module, this approach retains the parameters of the ABSA model while making it easier to identify essential intent within input sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-compound-sentences-simple-to-analyze</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BACKTIME: Backdoor Attacks on Multivariate Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backtime-backdoor-attacks-on-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate Time Series (MTS) forecasting is a fundamental task with numerous real-world applications, such as transportation, climate, and epidemiology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backtime-backdoor-attacks-on-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer-aided Colorization State-of-the-science: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-aided-colorization-state-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reviews published research in the field of computer-aided colorization technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-aided-colorization-state-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting and Editing Vision-Language Representations to Mitigate Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-and-editing-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the internal representations of vision-language models (VLMs) to address hallucinations, a persistent challenge despite advances in model size and training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-and-editing-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Non-Linear Model Predictive Control for Obstacle Avoidance in Indoor and Outdoor Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/custom-non-linear-model-predictive-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Navigating complex environments requires Unmanned Aerial Vehicles (UAVs) and autonomous systems to perform trajectory tracking and obstacle avoidance in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/custom-non-linear-model-predictive-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Light or Light Traffic? Investigating Phrasal Semantics in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-light-or-light-traffic-investigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Phrases are fundamental linguistic units through which humans convey semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-light-or-light-traffic-investigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlAR: Controllable Image Generation with Autoregressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlar-controllable-image-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we explore control encoding for AR models and propose a lightweight control encoder to transform spatial inputs (e. g., canny edges or depth maps) into control tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlar-controllable-image-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter Competition Balancing for Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-competition-balancing-for-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently developed model merging techniques enable the direct integration of multiple models, each fine-tuned for distinct tasks, into a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-competition-balancing-for-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Comprehensive Detection of Chinese Harmful Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-comprehensive-detection-of-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Harmful memes have proliferated on the Chinese Internet, while research on detecting Chinese harmful memes significantly lags behind due to the absence of reliable datasets and effective detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-comprehensive-detection-of-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation and Navigation in the Vocabulary Key Representation Space of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-and-navigation-in-the-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the effect of the key distribution on the NTP distribution, with a focus on whether the similarity between keys will trigger spurious correlations in NTP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-and-navigation-in-the-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-based Extreme Image Compression with Compressed Feature Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-extreme-image-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we design a novel relay residual diffusion that reconstructs the raw image by iteratively removing the added noise and the residual between the compressed and target latent features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-extreme-image-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MANTRA: The Manifold Triangulations Assemblage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mantra-the-manifold-triangulations-assemblage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rising interest in leveraging higher-order interactions present in complex systems has led to a surge in more expressive models exploiting high-order structures in the data, especially in topological deep learning (TDL), which designs neural networks on high-order domains such as simplicial complexes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mantra-the-manifold-triangulations-assemblage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SageAttention: Accurate 8-Bit Attention for Plug-and-play Inference Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention-accurate-8-bit-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although quantization has proven to be an effective method for accelerating model inference, existing quantization methods primarily focus on optimizing the linear layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sageattention-accurate-8-bit-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast nonparametric feature selection with error control using integrated path stability selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-nonparametric-feature-selection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive simulations with RNA sequencing data show that IPSSGB and IPSSRF have better error control, detect more true positives, and are faster than existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-nonparametric-feature-selection-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
