<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 21:06:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Optimal Transport of Abstractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-optimal-transport-of-abstractions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal abstraction (CA) theory establishes formal criteria for relating multiple structural causal models (SCMs) at different levels of granularity by defining maps between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-optimal-transport-of-abstractions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Engineering-assisted Malware Dynamic Analysis Using GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-engineering-assisted-malware-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a significant representation of dynamic malware behavior, the API (Application Programming Interface) sequence, comprised of consecutive API calls, has progressively become the dominant feature of dynamic analysis methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-engineering-assisted-malware-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAMM: Label Alignment for Multi-Modal Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamm-label-alignment-for-multi-modal-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct experiments on 11 downstream vision datasets and demonstrate that our method significantly improves the performance of existing multi-modal prompt learning models in few-shot scenarios, exhibiting an average accuracy improvement of 2. 31(\%) compared to the state-of-the-art methods on 16 shots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamm-label-alignment-for-multi-modal-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdapEdit: Spatio-Temporal Guided Adaptive Editing Algorithm for Text-Based Continuity-Sensitive Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapedit-spatio-temporal-guided-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the great success of text-conditioned diffusion models in creative text-to-image generation, various text-driven image editing approaches have attracted the attentions of many researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapedit-spatio-temporal-guided-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat-3D v2: Bridging 3D Scene and Large Language Models with Object Identifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chat-3d-v2-bridging-3d-scene-and-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These tokens capture the object's attributes and spatial relationships with surrounding objects in the 3D scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chat-3d-v2-bridging-3d-scene-and-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality Analysis for Evaluating the Security of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-analysis-for-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on a layer-level causality analysis, we show that RLHF has the effect of overfitting a model to harmful prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-analysis-for-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphGuard: Detecting and Counteracting Training Data Misuse in Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphguard-detecting-and-counteracting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These limitations call for an effective and comprehensive solution that detects and mitigates data misuse without requiring exact training data while respecting the proprietary nature of such data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphguard-detecting-and-counteracting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLOP: Learning Global Partition and Local Construction for Solving Large-scale Routing Problems in Real-time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glop-learning-global-partition-and-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent end-to-end neural solvers have shown promise for small-scale routing problems but suffered from limited real-time scaling-up performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glop-learning-global-partition-and-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-Efficient Reversible Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-reversible-spiking-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the reversible spiking neural network to reduce the memory cost of intermediate activations and membrane potentials during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-reversible-spiking-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoRTEx: Contrastive Learning for Representing Terms via Explanations with Applications on Constructing Biomedical Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cortex-contrastive-learning-for-representing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to a lack of knowledge, previous contrastive learning models trained with Unified Medical Language System (UMLS) synonyms struggle at clustering difficult terms and do not generalize well beyond UMLS terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cortex-contrastive-learning-for-representing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Inversion for Stable Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-inversion-for-stable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It stems from the fact that during inversion, the irrelevant semantics in the user images are also encoded, forcing the inverted concepts to occupy locations far from the core distribution in the embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-inversion-for-stable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMD: Faster Image Reconstruction with Latent Masking Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmd-faster-image-reconstruction-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we combine the advantages of MAEs and DPMs to design a progressive masking diffusion model, which gradually increases the masking proportion by three different schedulers and reconstructs the latent features from simple to difficult, without sequentially performing denoising diffusion as in DPMs or using fixed high masking ratio as in MAEs, so as to alleviate the high training time-consumption predicament.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmd-faster-image-reconstruction-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erasing Self-Supervised Learning Backdoor by Cluster Activation Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-self-supervised-learning-backdoor-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After obtaining the threat model trained on the poisoned dataset, our method can precisely detect poisonous samples based on the assumption that masking the backdoor trigger can effectively change the activation of a downstream clustering model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-self-supervised-learning-backdoor-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Order Structure Based Middle-Feature Learning for Visible-Infrared Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-order-structure-based-middle-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing VI-ReID methods ignore high-order structure information of features while being relatively difficult to learn a reasonable common feature space due to the large modality discrepancy between VIS and IR images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-order-structure-based-middle-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhance Sketch Recognition's Explainability via Semantic Component-Level Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-sketch-recognition-s-explainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans can recognize varied sketches of a category easily by identifying the concurrence and layout of the intrinsic semantic components of the category, since humans draw free-hand sketches based a common consensus that which types of semantic components constitute each sketch category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-sketch-recognition-s-explainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Incomplete-View CT Reconstruction with Prompted Contextual Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-incomplete-view-ct-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The incomplete-view CT can be divided into two scenarios depending on the sampling of projection, sparse-view CT and limited-angle CT, each encompassing various settings for different clinical requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-incomplete-view-ct-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MToP: A MATLAB Optimization Platform for Evolutionary Multitasking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtop-a-matlab-optimization-platform-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, for comparing MTEAs with traditional evolutionary algorithms, we modified more than 30 popular single-task evolutionary algorithms to be able to solve MTO problems in MToP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtop-a-matlab-optimization-platform-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modality Plug-and-Play: Elastic Modality Adaptation in Multimodal LLMs for Embodied AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-plug-and-play-elastic-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are capable of reasoning over diverse input data modalities through pre-trained encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-plug-and-play-elastic-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Class-Agnostic Motion Prediction with Pseudo Label Regeneration and BEVMix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-class-agnostic-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the quality of pseudo labels, we propose a novel motion selection and re-generation module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-class-agnostic-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptBench: A Unified Library for Evaluation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptbench-a-unified-library-for-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of large language models (LLMs) is crucial to assess their performance and mitigate potential security risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptbench-a-unified-library-for-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Real World Stereo Image Super-Resolution via Hybrid Degradation Model and Discriminator for Implied Stereo Image Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-real-world-stereo-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world stereo image super-resolution has a significant influence on enhancing the performance of computer vision systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-real-world-stereo-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View-Dependent Octree-based Mesh Extraction in Unbounded Scenes for Procedural Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-dependent-octree-based-mesh-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Procedural synthetic data generation has received increasing attention in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-dependent-octree-based-mesh-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conceptualizing Suicidal Behavior: Utilizing Explanations of Predicted Outcomes to Analyze Longitudinal Social Media Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conceptualizing-suicidal-behavior-utilizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The COVID-19 pandemic has escalated mental health crises worldwide, with social isolation and economic instability contributing to a rise in suicidal behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conceptualizing-suicidal-behavior-utilizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhenDiff: Revealing Invisible Phenotypes with Conditional Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phendiff-revealing-invisible-phenotypes-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the lack of robustness to invert a real image into the latent of a trained GAN prevents flexible editing of real images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phendiff-revealing-invisible-phenotypes-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Image Segmentation Techniques for Neural Activity Detection via C-fos Immediate Early Gene Expression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-image-segmentation-techniques-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research contributes to the development of more efficient and automated image segmentation methods, advancing the understanding of neural function in neuroscience research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advanced-image-segmentation-techniques-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Model-Based Data Acquisition for Subjective Multi-Task NLP Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-model-based-data-acquisition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data annotated by humans is a source of knowledge by describing the peculiarities of the problem and therefore fueling the decision process of the trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-model-based-data-acquisition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCTDL: Optical Coherence Tomography Dataset for Image-Based Deep Learning Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octdl-optical-coherence-tomography-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical coherence tomography (OCT) is a non-invasive imaging technique with extensive clinical applications in ophthalmology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/octdl-optical-coherence-tomography-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Socialbots Modeling Based on Structural Information Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-socialbots-modeling-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The importance of effective detection is underscored by the fact that socialbots imitate human behavior to propagate misinformation, leading to an ongoing competition between socialbots and detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-socialbots-modeling-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Silence: the Threats of Using LLMs in Software Engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-silence-the-threats-of-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have gained considerable traction within the Software Engineering (SE) community, impacting various SE tasks from code completion to test generation, from program repair to code summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-silence-the-threats-of-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Preference Learning: Understanding and Accounting for Hidden Context in RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-preference-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that standard applications of preference learning, including reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF), implicitly aggregate over hidden contexts according to a well-known voting rule called Borda count.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-preference-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PySCIPOpt-ML: Embedding Trained Machine Learning Models into Mixed-Integer Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyscipopt-ml-embedding-trained-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we propose a tool for the automatic MIP formulation of trained ML models, allowing easy integration of ML constraints into MIPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyscipopt-ml-embedding-trained-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAT: Reinforcement-Learning-Driven and Adaptive Testing for Vulnerability Discovery in Web Application Firewalls</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rat-reinforcement-learning-driven-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practice, using a brute-force attack to discover vulnerabilities is infeasible due to the wide variety of attack patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rat-reinforcement-learning-driven-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Few-Shot Named Entity Recognition with Boundary Discrimination and Correlation Purification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-few-shot-named-entity-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the present few-shot NER models assume that the labeled data are all clean without noise or outliers, and there are few works focusing on the robustness of the cross-domain transfer learning ability to textual adversarial attacks in Few-shot NER.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-few-shot-named-entity-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept-centric Personalization with Large-scale Diffusion Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-centric-personalization-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the task of customizing large-scale diffusion priors for specific concepts as concept-centric personalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-centric-personalization-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual-Learning Knowledge Distillation for Nighttime UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-learning-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework is constructed to learn a compact and fast nighttime tracker via knowledge transferring from the teacher and knowledge sharing among various students.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-learning-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchHead: Accelerating Transformers with Mixture-of-Experts Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchhead-accelerating-transformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The costly self-attention layers in modern Transformers require memory and compute quadratic in sequence length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchhead-accelerating-transformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling non-genetic information dynamics in cells using reservoir computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-genetic-information-dynamics-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Virtually all cells use energy and ion-specific membrane pumps to maintain large transmembrane gradients of Na$^+$, K$^+$, Cl$^-$, Mg$^{++}$, and Ca$^{++}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-genetic-information-dynamics-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide and Conquer: Hybrid Pre-training for Person Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-hybrid-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first work that investigates how to support full-task pre-training using sub-task data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-hybrid-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn or Recall? Revisiting Incremental Learning with Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-or-recall-revisiting-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most assume that catastrophic forgetting is the biggest obstacle to achieving superior IL performance and propose various techniques to overcome this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-or-recall-revisiting-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPD-DDPM: Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models in the Symmetric Positive Definite Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spd-ddpm-denoising-diffusion-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, the model unconditionally learns the probability distribution of the data $p(X)$ and generates samples that conform to this distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spd-ddpm-denoising-diffusion-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Data: Can We Trust Statistical Estimators?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-can-we-trust-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing interest in data sharing makes synthetic data appealing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-can-we-trust-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uSF: Learning Neural Semantic Field with Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usf-learning-neural-semantic-field-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there has been an increased interest in NeRF methods which reconstruct differentiable representation of three-dimensional scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usf-learning-neural-semantic-field-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Encoder-minimal and Decoder-minimal Framework for Remote Sensing Image Dehazing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encoder-minimal-and-decoder-minimal-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Haze obscures remote sensing images, hindering valuable information extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encoder-minimal-and-decoder-minimal-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mono3DVG: 3D Visual Grounding in Monocular Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mono3dvg-3d-visual-grounding-in-monocular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To foster this task, we propose Mono3DVG-TR, an end-to-end transformer-based network, which takes advantage of both the appearance and geometry information in text embeddings for multi-modal learning and 3D object localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mono3dvg-3d-visual-grounding-in-monocular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLNet: Mutual Learning Network with Neighborhood Invariance for Universal Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlnet-mutual-learning-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Universal domain adaptation (UniDA) is a practical but challenging problem, in which information about the relation between the source and the target domains is not given for knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlnet-mutual-learning-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch-MI: Enhancing Model Inversion Attacks via Patch-Based Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mi-enhancing-model-inversion-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach allows the synthesis of images that are similar to the target dataset distribution, even in cases of dissimilar auxiliary dataset distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patch-mi-enhancing-model-inversion-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextually Affinitive Neighborhood Refinery for Deep Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextually-affinitive-neighborhood-refinery-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous endeavors in self-supervised learning have enlightened the research of deep clustering from an instance discrimination perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextually-affinitive-neighborhood-refinery-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MWSIS: Multimodal Weakly Supervised Instance Segmentation with 2D Box Annotations for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mwsis-multimodal-weakly-supervised-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instance segmentation is a fundamental research in computer vision, especially in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mwsis-multimodal-weakly-supervised-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining propensity score methods with variational autoencoders for generating synthetic data in presence of latent sub-groups</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-propensity-score-methods-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The sources of such heterogeneity might be known, e. g., as indicated by sub-groups labels, or might be unknown and thus reflected only in properties of distributions, such as bimodality or skewness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-propensity-score-methods-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Correspondence, Pose and NeRF for Pose-Free Novel View Synthesis from Stereo Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-correspondence-pose-and-nerf-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work delves into the task of pose-free novel view synthesis from stereo pairs, a challenging and pioneering task in 3D vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-correspondence-pose-and-nerf-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
