<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 21:07:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Design of Negative Sampling Strategies for Distantly Supervised Skill Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-of-negative-sampling-strategies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a manually annotated evaluation benchmark for skill extraction based on the ESCO taxonomy, on which we validate our models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-of-negative-sampling-strategies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CovidMis20: COVID-19 Misinformation Detection System on Twitter Tweets using Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidmis20-covid-19-misinformation-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online news and information sources are convenient and accessible ways to learn about current issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covidmis20-covid-19-misinformation-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Inter-Group Link Injection Degrades the Fairness of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-inter-group-link-injection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope our findings raise awareness about this issue in our community and lay a foundation for the future development of GNN models that are more robust to such attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-inter-group-link-injection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-of-Day Neural Style Transfer for Architectural Photographs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-of-day-neural-style-transfer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Architectural photography is a genre of photography that focuses on capturing a building or structure in the foreground with dramatic lighting in the background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-of-day-neural-style-transfer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Intent Discovery: Learning from Open World Dialogue System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-intent-discovery-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional intent classification models are based on a pre-defined intent set and only recognize limited in-domain (IND) intent classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-intent-discovery-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaDE: Improving Sparse Representations using a Dual Document Encoder for First-stage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spade-improving-sparse-representations-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse document representations have been widely used to retrieve relevant documents via exact lexical matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spade-improving-sparse-representations-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Meta-level Analysis of Online Anomaly Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-level-analysis-of-online-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The behavior of the detectors is correlated with the characteristics of different datasets (i. e., meta-features), thereby providing a meta-level analysis of their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-level-analysis-of-online-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deep variational free energy approach to dense hydrogen</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-variational-free-energy-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a deep generative model-based variational free energy approach to the equations of state of dense hydrogen.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-variational-free-energy-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethink about the Word-level Quality Estimation for Machine Translation from Human Judgement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethink-about-the-word-level-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the post-editing effort can be used to measure the translation quality to some extent, we find it usually conflicts with the human judgement on whether the word is well or poorly translated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethink-about-the-word-level-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Brain Multigraph Population From a Single Graph Template for Boosting One-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-brain-multigraph-population-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A central challenge in training one-shot learning models is the limited representativeness of the available shots of the data space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-brain-multigraph-population-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Predictive Reproducibility of Federated Graph Neural Networks using Medical Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-predictive-reproducibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this presents the first work investigating the reproducibility of federated GNN models with application to classifying medical imaging and brain connectivity datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-predictive-reproducibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of HodgeRank and Spectral Method: Target Attack Against Rank Aggregation Is the Fixed Point of Adversarial Game</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-hodgerank-and-spectral-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the perspective of the dynamical system, the attack behavior with a target ranking list is a fixed point belonging to the composition of the adversary and the victim.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-hodgerank-and-spectral-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSAQ-ViT V2: Towards Accurate and General Data-Free Quantization for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psaq-vit-v2-towards-accurate-and-general-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose PSAQ-ViT V2, a more accurate and general data-free quantization framework for ViTs, built on top of PSAQ-ViT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psaq-vit-v2-towards-accurate-and-general-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expressive Reasoning Graph Store: A Unified Framework for Managing RDF and Property Graph Databases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-reasoning-graph-store-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Resource Description Framework (RDF) and Property Graph (PG) are the two most commonly used data models for representing, storing, and querying graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expressive-reasoning-graph-store-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Bias with a Synthetic Data Generator: Empirical Evidence and Philosophical Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-bias-with-a-synthetic-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning applications are becoming increasingly pervasive in our society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-bias-with-a-synthetic-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Judge a Language Model by Its Last Layer: Contrastive Learning with Layer-Wise Attention Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-judge-a-language-model-by-its-last</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent pre-trained language models (PLMs) achieved great success on many natural language processing tasks through learning linguistic features and contextualized sentence representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-judge-a-language-model-by-its-last</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-Level Logit Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-level-logit-perturbation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, limited studies have explicitly explored for the perturbation of logit vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-level-logit-perturbation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Discretization using Voronoi Trees for Continuous-Action POMDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-discretization-using-voronoi-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Voronoi tree is a Binary Space Partitioning (BSP) that implicitly maintains the partition of a cell as the Voronoi diagram of two points sampled from the cell.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-discretization-using-voronoi-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised motion descriptor for cardiac phase detection in 4D CMR based on discrete vector field estimations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-motion-descriptor-for-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneously, deep learning-based deformable image registration is able to estimate discrete vector fields which warp one time step of a CMR sequence to the following in a self-supervised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-motion-descriptor-for-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense against Privacy Leakage in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-privacy-leakage-in-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) provides a promising distributed learning paradigm, since it seeks to protect users privacy by not sharing their private training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-privacy-leakage-in-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Solve Multiple-TSP with Time Window and Rejections via Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-solve-multiple-tsp-with-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a manager-worker framework based on deep reinforcement learning to tackle a hard yet nontrivial variant of Travelling Salesman Problem (TSP), \ie~multiple-vehicle TSP with time window and rejections (mTSPTWR), where customers who cannot be served before the deadline are subject to rejections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-solve-multiple-tsp-with-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity Tagging: Extracting Entities in Text Without Mention Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-tagging-extracting-entities-in-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detection and disambiguation of all entities in text is a crucial task for a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-tagging-extracting-entities-in-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVNet: Where SO(3) Equivariance Meets Binarization on Point Cloud Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svnet-where-so-3-equivariance-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precisely, the presence of scalar features makes the major part of the network binarizable, while vector features serve to retain rich structural information and ensure SO(3) equivariance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svnet-where-so-3-equivariance-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointScatter: Point Set Representation for Tubular Structure Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointscatter-point-set-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this, we propose PointScatter, an alternative to the segmentation models for the tubular structure extraction task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointscatter-point-set-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoryDALL-E: Adapting Pretrained Text-to-Image Transformers for Story Continuation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storydall-e-adapting-pretrained-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we first propose the task of story continuation, where the generated visual story is conditioned on a source image, allowing for better generalization to narratives with new characters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storydall-e-adapting-pretrained-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Allocation to Agents with Restrictions: Maximizing Likelihood with Minimum Compromise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-allocation-to-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus is on resource allocation problems where agents may have restrictions that make them incompatible with some resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-allocation-to-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSL: A Large-scale Chinese Scientific Literature Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csl-a-large-scale-chinese-scientific-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CSL can serve as a Chinese corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csl-a-large-scale-chinese-scientific-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Large Language Models for Robot 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-large-language-models-for-robot-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce three paradigms for leveraging language for classifying rooms in indoor environments based on their contained objects: (i) a zero-shot approach, (ii) a feed-forward classifier approach, and (iii) a contrastive classifier approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-large-language-models-for-robot-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartKex: Machine Learning Assisted SSH Keys Extraction From The Heap Dump</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartkex-machine-learning-assisted-ssh-keys</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A commonly used method in digital forensics is to extract data from the main memory of a digital device.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartkex-machine-learning-assisted-ssh-keys</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Some other poor soul's problems": a peer recommendation intervention for health-related social support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-other-poor-soul-s-problems-a-peer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results support the usefulness and demand for peer recommendation and suggest benefits to evaluating larger peer recommendation interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-other-poor-soul-s-problems-a-peer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switchable Online Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchable-online-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of focusing on the accuracy gap at test phase by the existing arts, the core idea of SwitOKD is to adaptively calibrate the gap at training phase, namely distillation gap, via a switching strategy between two modes -- expert mode (pause the teacher while keep the student learning) and learning mode (restart the teacher).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchable-online-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Preserving Adversarial Code Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-preserving-adversarial-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the tremendous success of pre-trained language models (PrLMs) for source code comprehension tasks, current literature studies either ways to further improve the performance (generalization) of PrLMs, or their robustness against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-preserving-adversarial-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Domain Dialog Evaluation using Follow-Ups Likelihood</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-domain-dialog-evaluation-using-follow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic evaluation of open-domain dialogs remains an unsolved problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-domain-dialog-evaluation-using-follow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Distributional Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-distributional-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this fundamental issue, we propose Wasserstein Distributional Learning (WDL), a flexible density-on-scalar regression modeling framework that starts with the Wasserstein distance $W_2$ as a proper metric for the space of density outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-distributional-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CustOmics: A versatile deep-learning based strategy for multi-omics integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customics-a-versatile-deep-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in high-throughput sequencing technologies have enabled the extraction of multiple features that depict patient samples at diverse and complementary molecular levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customics-a-versatile-deep-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CenterFormer: Center-based Transformer for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centerformer-center-based-transformer-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It then uses the feature of the center candidate as the query embedding in the transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centerformer-center-based-transformer-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexical Simplification Benchmarks for English, Portuguese, and Spanish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexical-simplification-benchmarks-for-english</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To showcase the usability of the dataset, we adapt two state-of-the-art lexical simplification systems with differing architectures (neural vs.\ non-neural) to all three languages (English, Spanish, and Brazilian Portuguese) and evaluate their performances on our new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexical-simplification-benchmarks-for-english</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Observability during DRL for Robot Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-observability-during-drl-for-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) has made tremendous advances in both simulated and real-world robot control tasks in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-observability-during-drl-for-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communication-Efficient and Privacy-Preserving Feature-based Federated Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-and-privacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to improve the communication efficiency, we in this paper propose the feature-based federated transfer learning as an innovative approach to reduce the uplink payload by more than five orders of magnitude compared to that of existing approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communication-efficient-and-privacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Feature Statistics Mapping for Generalized Screen Content Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-feature-statistics-mapping-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The underlying mechanism of the proposed approach is based upon the wild assumption that the SCIs, which are not physically acquired, still obey certain statistics that could be understood in a learning fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-feature-statistics-mapping-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical few-shot segmentation for cross-institution male pelvic structures with spatial registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-few-shot-segmentation-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prowess that makes few-shot learning desirable in medical image analysis is the efficient use of the support image data, which are labelled to classify or segment new classes, a task that otherwise requires substantially more training images and expert annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-few-shot-segmentation-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attitude-Guided Loop Closure for Cameras with Negative Plane</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attitude-guided-loop-closure-for-cameras-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we propose a loop closure framework with a new outlier rejection method based on the unit length representation, to improve the accuracy of LF-VIO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attitude-guided-loop-closure-for-cameras-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Next Action by Modeling the Abstract Goal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-next-action-by-modeling-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is through the submission of this paper that our method is currently the new state-of-the-art for action anticipation in EK55 and EGTEA Gaze+ https://competitions. codalab. org/competitions/20071#results Code available at https://github. com/debadityaroy/Abstract_Goal]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-next-action-by-modeling-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenLoco: Generalized Locomotion Controllers for Quadrupedal Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genloco-generalized-locomotion-controllers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a framework for training generalized locomotion (GenLoco) controllers for quadrupedal robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genloco-generalized-locomotion-controllers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model interpretation using improved local regression with variable importance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-interpretation-using-improved-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A fundamental question on the use of ML models concerns the explanation of their predictions for increasing transparency in decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-interpretation-using-improved-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiBiNet++:Improving FiBiNet by Greatly Reducing Model Size for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fibinet-improving-fibinet-by-greatly-reducing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Click-Through Rate(CTR) estimation has become one of the most fundamental tasks in many real-world applications and various deep models have been proposed to resolve this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fibinet-improving-fibinet-by-greatly-reducing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bending the Future: Autoregressive Modeling of Temporal Knowledge Graphs in Curvature-Variable Hyperbolic Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bending-the-future-autoregressive-modeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The chronological hierarchies between knowledge graphs at different timestamps are represented by embedding the knowledge graphs as vectors in a common hyperbolic space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bending-the-future-autoregressive-modeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness in Forecasting of Observations of Linear Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-in-forecasting-of-observations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In machine learning, training data often capture the behaviour of multiple subgroups of some underlying human population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-in-forecasting-of-observations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SANCL: Multimodal Review Helpfulness Prediction with Selective Attention and Natural Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sancl-multimodal-review-helpfulness-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the boom of e-commerce, Multimodal Review Helpfulness Prediction (MRHP), which aims to sort product reviews according to the predicted helpfulness scores has become a research hotspot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sancl-multimodal-review-helpfulness-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Network-based Internet Censorship via Latent Feature Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-network-based-internet-censorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To estimate the probability of censorship events from the inferred latent features, we rely on a densely connected multi-layer neural network model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-network-based-internet-censorship</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
