<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 21:06:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Scaffolding a Student to Instill Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaffolding-a-student-to-instill-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel knowledge distillation (KD) method to selectively instill teacher knowledge into a student model motivated by situations where the student's capacity is significantly smaller than that of the teachers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaffolding-a-student-to-instill-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskPrompter: Spatial-Channel Multi-Task Prompting for Dense Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskprompter-spatial-channel-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each task prompt learns task-specific representation for one task, while all the prompts can jointly contribute to the learning of the shared image token representations, and the interactions between different task prompts model the cross-task relationship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskprompter-spatial-channel-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMPLE: Specialized Model-Sample Matching for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-specialized-model-sample-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, our method is highly efficient and achieves more than 1000 times training speedup compared to the conventional DG methods with fine-tuning a pretrained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-specialized-model-sample-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Edge Inference by Selective Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-edge-inference-by-selective-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training a hybrid learner is difficult since we lack annotations of hard edge-examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-edge-inference-by-selective-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-refined Denoising Network for Robust Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-refined-denoising-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph (KG), which contains rich side information, becomes an essential part to boost the recommendation performance and improve its explainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-refined-denoising-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-Sensitive Self-Training for Optimizing Non-Decomposable Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-sensitive-self-training-for-optimizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the proposed CSST framework, we obtain practical self-training methods (for both vision and NLP tasks) for optimizing different non-decomposable metrics using deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-sensitive-self-training-for-optimizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local-Global Transformer Enhanced Unfolding Network for Pan-sharpening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-transformer-enhanced-unfolding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we customize a Local-Global Transformer (LGT) to simultaneously model local and global dependencies, and further formulate an LGT-based prior module for image denoising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-transformer-enhanced-unfolding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HQP: A Human-Annotated Dataset for Detecting Online Propaganda</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hqp-a-human-annotated-dataset-for-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) To address the cost of labeling, we extend our work to few-shot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hqp-a-human-annotated-dataset-for-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Hybrid Proposal Modulation for Lane Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-hybrid-proposal-modulation-for-lane</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the shape and location constraints, we design a quality-aware classification loss to adaptively supervise each positive proposal so that the discriminative power can be further boosted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-hybrid-proposal-modulation-for-lane</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stable and Scalable Method for Solving Initial Value PDEs with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stable-and-scalable-method-for-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike conventional grid and mesh based methods for solving partial differential equations (PDEs), neural networks have the potential to break the curse of dimensionality, providing approximate solutions to problems where using classical solvers is difficult or impossible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stable-and-scalable-method-for-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGED: A Benchmark dataset for Performance Evaluation of Spiking Gesture Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sged-a-benchmark-dataset-for-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a pseudo dual-flow network based on this dataset, and verify the application potential of this dataset in the affective computing community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sged-a-benchmark-dataset-for-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCpdf: Building a High Quality Corpus for Visually Rich Documents from Web Crawl Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccpdf-building-a-high-quality-corpus-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the field of document understanding has progressed a lot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ccpdf-building-a-high-quality-corpus-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musical Voice Separation as Link Prediction: Modeling a Musical Perception Task as a Multi-Trajectory Tracking Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musical-voice-separation-as-link-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach builds a graph from a musical piece, by creating one node for every note, and separates the melodic trajectories by predicting a link between two notes if they are consecutive in the same voice/stream.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musical-voice-separation-as-link-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Chart Spark: Embedding Semantic Context into Chart with Text-to-Image Generative Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-chart-spark-embedding-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pictorial visualization seamlessly integrates data and semantic context into visual representation, conveying complex information in a manner that is both engaging and informative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-chart-spark-embedding-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Perturbation to Improve Goodness-of-Fit Tests based on Kernelized Stein Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-perturbation-to-improve-goodness-of-fit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kernelized Stein discrepancy (KSD) is a score-based discrepancy widely used in goodness-of-fit tests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-perturbation-to-improve-goodness-of-fit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CED: Catalog Extraction from Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ced-catalog-extraction-from-documents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we build a large manually annotated corpus, which is the first dataset for the Catalog Extraction from Documents (CED) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ced-catalog-extraction-from-documents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA-Adapter V2: Parameter-Efficient Visual Instruction Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-v2-parameter-efficient-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This strategy effectively alleviates the interference between the two tasks of image-text alignment and instruction following and achieves strong multi-modal reasoning with only a small-scale image-text and instruction dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-v2-parameter-efficient-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Enhanced Model for Live Video Comment Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-model-for-live-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Live video commenting is popular on video media platforms, as it can create a chatting atmosphere and provide supplementary information for users while watching videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-model-for-live-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralKG-ind: A Python Library for Inductive Knowledge Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralkg-ind-a-python-library-for-inductive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the dynamic characteristics of knowledge graphs, many inductive knowledge graph representation learning (KGRL) works have been proposed in recent years, focusing on enabling prediction over new entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralkg-ind-a-python-library-for-inductive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A feature selection method based on Shapley values robust to concept shift in regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-selection-method-based-on-shapley-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature selection is one of the most relevant processes in any methodology for creating a statistical learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-selection-method-based-on-shapley-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Redundancy and Biases in Public Document Information Extraction Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-redundancy-and-biases-in-public</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in the Visually-rich Document Understanding (VrDU) field and particularly the Key-Information Extraction (KIE) task are marked with the emergence of efficient Transformer-based approaches such as the LayoutLM models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-redundancy-and-biases-in-public</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Made of Steel? Learning Plausible Materials for Components in the Vehicle Repair Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/made-of-steel-learning-plausible-materials</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to learn domain-specific plausible materials for components in the vehicle repair domain by probing Pretrained Language Models (PLMs) in a cloze task style setting to overcome the lack of annotated datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/made-of-steel-learning-plausible-materials</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are the Best Multilingual Document Embeddings simply Based on Sentence Embeddings?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-best-multilingual-document-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that while a simple sentence average results in a strong baseline for classification tasks, more complex combinations are necessary for semantic tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-best-multilingual-document-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Knowledge Graph Entity Alignment with Graph Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knowledge-graph-entity-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity alignment (EA) which links equivalent entities across different knowledge graphs (KGs) plays a crucial role in knowledge fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knowledge-graph-entity-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Multimodal Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-multimodal-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging (e. g., via interpolation or task arithmetic) fuses multiple models trained on different tasks to generate a multi-task solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-multimodal-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synergy of Machine and Deep Learning Models for Multi-Painter Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-of-machine-and-deep-learning-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing availability of digitized art collections has created the need to manage, analyze and categorize large amounts of data related to abstract concepts, highlighting a demanding problem of computer science and leading to new research perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-of-machine-and-deep-learning-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGAligner : 3D Scene Alignment with Scene Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgaligner-3d-scene-alignment-with-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SGAligner, the first method for aligning pairs of 3D scene graphs that is robust to in-the-wild scenarios (ie, unknown overlap -- if any -- and changes in the environment).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgaligner-3d-scene-alignment-with-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-based Maximally Interfered Retrieval for Domain Incremental 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-maximally-interfered-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate 3D object detection in all weather conditions remains a key challenge to enable the widespread deployment of autonomous vehicles, as most work to date has been performed on clear weather data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-maximally-interfered-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeqTrack: Sequence to Sequence Learning for Visual Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqtrack-sequence-to-sequence-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new sequence-to-sequence learning framework for visual tracking, dubbed SeqTrack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqtrack-sequence-to-sequence-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Attention Model with Occlusion-aware Texture Regression for 3D Hand Reconstruction from a Single RGB Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-attention-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate our probabilistic model's state-of-the-art accuracy in 3D hand and texture reconstruction from a single image in both training schemes, including in the presence of severe occlusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-attention-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN based IoT Device Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnn-based-iot-device-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the use of the Internet of Things is becoming more and more popular, many security vulnerabilities are emerging with the large number of devices being introduced to the market.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnn-based-iot-device-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Analysis of the FRP Rebar Using Computer Vision Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-analysis-of-the-frp-rebar-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a method to analyze the inner structure of the composite FRP rebar, namely the shift of the real center of gravity with a respect to the geometrical center of rebar and changes of cross-sectional characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-analysis-of-the-frp-rebar-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Evaluation of POS Taggers: From Wall Street Journal to Fandom Wiki</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-evaluation-of-pos-taggers-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Wall Street Journal section of the Penn Treebank has been the de-facto standard for evaluating POS taggers for a long time, and accuracies over 97\% have been reported.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-evaluation-of-pos-taggers-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density Invariant Contrast Maximization for Neuromorphic Earth Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-invariant-contrast-maximization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is to ensure that the contrast is only high around the correct motion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-invariant-contrast-maximization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSTM based IoT Device Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-iot-device-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the use of the Internet of Things is becoming more and more popular, many security vulnerabilities are emerging with the large number of devices being introduced to the market.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lstm-based-iot-device-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatLog: Recording and Analyzing ChatGPT Across Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlog-recording-and-analyzing-chatgpt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there are abundant researches about evaluating ChatGPT on natural language understanding and generation tasks, few studies have investigated how ChatGPT's behavior changes over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlog-recording-and-analyzing-chatgpt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseFusion: Fusing Multi-Modal Sparse Representations for Multi-Sensor 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsefusion-fusing-multi-modal-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, given that objects occupy only a small part of a scene, finding dense candidates and generating dense representations is noisy and inefficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsefusion-fusing-multi-modal-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaMini-LM: A Diverse Herd of Distilled Models from Large-Scale Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamini-lm-a-diverse-herd-of-distilled-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we carefully develop a large set of 2. 58M instructions based on both existing and newly-generated instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamini-lm-a-diverse-herd-of-distilled-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're Afraid Language Models Aren't Modeling Ambiguity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-re-afraid-language-models-aren-t-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the task remains extremely challenging, including for the recent GPT-4, whose generated disambiguations are considered correct only 32% of the time in human evaluation, compared to 90% for disambiguations in our dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-re-afraid-language-models-aren-t-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Big Brother: Attacking Search Engines with Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-big-brother-attacking-search-engines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Search engines are vulnerable to attacks against indexing and searching via text encoding manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-big-brother-attacking-search-engines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight, Pre-trained Transformers for Remote Sensing Timeseries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-pre-trained-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Presto can be used for transfer learning or as a feature extractor for simple models, enabling efficient deployment at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-pre-trained-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLT: An R package for Linear Law-based Feature Space Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llt-an-r-package-for-linear-law-based-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The presented R package, called LLT, implements this algorithm in a flexible yet user-friendly way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llt-an-r-package-for-linear-law-based-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explainable Collaborative Filtering with Taste Clusters Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-collaborative-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent decades, there have been significant advancements in latent embedding-based CF methods for improved accuracy, such as matrix factorization, neural collaborative filtering, and LightGCN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-collaborative-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Are State-of-the-Art Evaluators of Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-state-of-the-art-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Token-matching-based metrics, such as BLEU, have demonstrated weak correlations with human practitioners in code generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-state-of-the-art-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Is Not the Main Factor Behind the Gap Between SGD and Adam on Transformers, but Sign Descent Might Be</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-is-not-the-main-factor-behind-the-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This suggests that Adam outperform SGD because it uses a more robust gradient estimate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-is-not-the-main-factor-behind-the-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>string2string: A Modern Python Library for String-to-String Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It includes traditional algorithmic solutions as well as recent advanced neural approaches to tackle various problems in string alignment, distance measurement, lexical and semantic search, and similarity analysis -- along with several helpful visualization tools and metrics to facilitate the interpretation and analysis of these methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Figments and Misalignments: A Framework for Fine-grained Crossmodal Misinformation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figments-and-misalignments-a-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that AMM adds noise to the training and evaluation process while exacerbating the unimodal bias, where text-only or image-only detectors can seemingly outperform their multimodal counterparts on an inherently multimodal task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figments-and-misalignments-a-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mimic-IV-ICD: A new benchmark for eXtreme MultiLabel Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-iv-icd-a-new-benchmark-for-extreme-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical notes are assigned ICD codes - sets of codes for diagnoses and procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-iv-icd-a-new-benchmark-for-extreme-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RegHEC: Hand-Eye Calibration via Simultaneous Multi-view Point Clouds Registration of Arbitrary Object</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reghec-hand-eye-calibration-via-simultaneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RegHEC is a registration-based hand-eye calibration technique with no need for accurate calibration rig but arbitrary available objects, applicable for both eye-in-hand and eye-to-hand cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reghec-hand-eye-calibration-via-simultaneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Object-Centric Generalized Value Functions From Pixels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-centric-generalized-value</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Reinforcement Learning has shown significant progress in extracting useful representations from high-dimensional inputs albeit using hand-crafted auxiliary tasks and pseudo rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-object-centric-generalized-value</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
