<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 21:08:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Diffusion Guidance via Learning Degradation-Aware Models for Blind Super Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-diffusion-guidance-via-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, diffusion-based blind super-resolution (SR) methods have shown great ability to generate high-resolution images with abundant high-frequency detail, but the detail is often achieved at the expense of fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-diffusion-guidance-via-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Tree Search for Comprehensive Exploration in LLM-Based Automatic Heuristic Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-for-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handcrafting heuristics for solving complex planning tasks (e. g., NP-hard combinatorial optimization (CO) problems) is a common practice but requires extensive domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-tree-search-for-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CityDreamer4D: Compositional Generative Model of Unbounded 4D Cities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citydreamer4d-compositional-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main insights are 1) 4D city generation should separate dynamic objects (e. g., vehicles) from static scenes (e. g., buildings and roads), and 2) all objects in the 4D scene should be composed of different types of neural fields for buildings, vehicles, and background stuff.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citydreamer4d-compositional-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperSAM: Crafting a SAM Supernetwork via Structured Pruning and Unstructured Parameter Prioritization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supersam-crafting-a-sam-supernetwork-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Architecture Search (NAS) is a powerful approach of automating the design of efficient neural architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supersam-crafting-a-sam-supernetwork-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Inherent Limits of Pretrained LLMs: The Unexpected Convergence of Instruction Tuning and In-Context Learning Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inherent-limits-of-pretrained-llms-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs), trained on extensive web-scale corpora, have demonstrated remarkable abilities across diverse tasks, especially as they are scaled up.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-inherent-limits-of-pretrained-llms-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual WetlandBirds Dataset: Bird Species Identification and Behavior Recognition in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-wetlandbirds-dataset-bird-species</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current biodiversity loss crisis makes animal monitoring a relevant field of study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-wetlandbirds-dataset-bird-species</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do Generative Models Draw a Software Engineer? A Case Study on Stable Diffusion Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-do-generative-models-draw-a-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, if used without consciousness, artificially generated images could reinforce these biases in the SE domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-do-generative-models-draw-a-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Feature Fusion for Emotion Analysis and Suicide Risk Differentiation in Chinese Psychological Support Hotlines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-feature-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mental health is a critical global public health issue, and psychological support hotlines play a pivotal role in providing mental health assistance and identifying suicide risks at an early stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-feature-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complexity Control Facilitates Reasoning-Based Compositional Generalization in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexity-control-facilitates-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have demonstrated impressive capabilities across various tasks, yet their performance on compositional problems remains a subject of debate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexity-control-facilitates-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score-based 3D molecule generation with neural fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-3d-molecule-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this representation, we propose a new model based on walk-jump sampling for unconditional 3D molecule generation in the continuous space using neural fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-3d-molecule-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonSter: Marry Monodepth to Stereo Unleashes Power</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monster-marry-monodepth-to-stereo-unleashes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The refined monodepth is in turn guides stereo effectively at ill-posed regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monster-marry-monodepth-to-stereo-unleashes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Transformation Learning for Equivariant Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-transformation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current methods depend on transformation labels and thus struggle with interdependency and complex transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-transformation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disjoint Processing Mechanisms of Hierarchical and Linear Grammars in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disjoint-processing-mechanisms-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using these grammars, we first observe that language models show distinct behaviors on hierarchical versus linearly structured inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disjoint-processing-mechanisms-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Densely Connected Parameter-Efficient Tuning for Referring Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densely-connected-parameter-efficient-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While some pioneering studies have undertaken preliminary explorations, they still remain at the level of aligned encoders (e. g., CLIP) and lack exploration of misaligned encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densely-connected-parameter-efficient-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Sampled Softmax with Inverted Multi-Index: Methods, Theory and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sampled-softmax-with-inverted-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The softmax function is a cornerstone of multi-class classification, integral to a wide range of machine learning applications, from large-scale retrieval and ranking models to advanced large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sampled-softmax-with-inverted-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karatsuba Matrix Multiplication and its Efficient Custom Hardware Implementations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/karatsuba-matrix-multiplication-and-its</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the extension of the scalar Karatsuba multiplication algorithm to matrix multiplication, showing how this maintains the reduction in multiplication complexity of the original Karatsuba algorithm while reducing the complexity of the extra additions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/karatsuba-matrix-multiplication-and-its</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToMATO: Verbalizing the Mental States of Role-Playing LLMs for Benchmarking Theory of Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomato-verbalizing-the-mental-states-of-role</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These verbalized thoughts serve as answers to questions designed to assess the mental states of characters within conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomato-verbalizing-the-mental-states-of-role</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANSR-DT: An Adaptive Neuro-Symbolic Learning and Reasoning Framework for Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ansr-dt-an-adaptive-neuro-symbolic-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an Adaptive Neuro-Symbolic Learning Framework for digital twin technology called ``ANSR-DT."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ansr-dt-an-adaptive-neuro-symbolic-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge prompt chaining for semantic modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-prompt-chaining-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we proposed a novel automatic semantic modeling framework: Knowledge Prompt Chaining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-prompt-chaining-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal LLMs Can Reason about Aesthetics in Zero-Shot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-llms-can-reason-about-aesthetics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the first study on how Multimodal LLMs' (MLLMs) reasoning ability shall be elicited to evaluate the aesthetics of artworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-llms-can-reason-about-aesthetics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VECT-GAN: A variationally encoded generative model for overcoming data scarcity in pharmaceutical science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vect-gan-a-variationally-encoded-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data scarcity in pharmaceutical research has led to reliance on labour-intensive trial and error approaches for development rather than data driven methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vect-gan-a-variationally-encoded-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Alignment of FOL Closeness Metrics with Human Judgement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-alignment-of-fol-closeness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using ground-truth FOLs, we carefully designed various perturbations on the ground-truth to assess metric sensitivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-alignment-of-fol-closeness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOTLoc: General Outdoor Text-based Localization Using Scene Graph Retrieval with OpenStreetMap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotloc-general-outdoor-text-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, by utilizing publicly available map data, such as OpenStreetMap, which provides global information on outdoor spaces, we eliminate the need for additional effort to create custom map data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gotloc-general-outdoor-text-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Graph Contrastive Learning with Line Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trapped by the label scarcity in molecular property prediction and drug design, graph contrastive learning (GCL) came forward.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuan: Yielding Unblemished Aesthetics Through A Unified Network for Visual Imperfections Removal in Generated Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-yielding-unblemished-aesthetics-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative AI presents transformative potential across various domains, from creative arts to scientific visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-yielding-unblemished-aesthetics-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwinTExCo: Exemplar-based video colorization using Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swintexco-exemplar-based-video-colorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video colorization represents a compelling domain within the field of Computer Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swintexco-exemplar-based-video-colorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AVS-Mamba: Exploring Temporal and Multi-modal Mamba for Audio-Visual Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avs-mamba-exploring-temporal-and-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To perform multi-modal fusion, we propose the Modality Aggregation Decoder, leveraging the Vision-to-Audio Fusion Block to integrate visual features into audio features across both frame and temporal levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avs-mamba-exploring-temporal-and-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DM-Mamba: Dual-domain Multi-scale Mamba for MRI reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-mamba-dual-domain-multi-scale-mamba-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these, we propose a dual-domain multi-scale Mamba for MRI reconstruction from the following perspectives: (1) We pioneer vision Mamba in k-space learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-mamba-dual-domain-multi-scale-mamba-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Modal AI Copilot for Single-Cell Analysis with Instruction Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-ai-copilot-for-single-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models excel at interpreting complex natural language instructions, enabling them to perform a wide range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-ai-copilot-for-single-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Deep Learning-based Forward Solvers for Brain Tumor Growth Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deep-learning-based-forward-solvers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Glioblastoma, a highly aggressive brain tumor, poses major challenges due to its poor prognosis and high morbidity rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deep-learning-based-forward-solvers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Classification Trees for Continuous Feature Data Using Dynamic Programming with Branch-and-Bound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-classification-trees-for-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computing an optimal classification tree that provably maximizes training performance within a given size limit, is NP-hard, and in practice, most state-of-the-art methods do not scale beyond computing optimal trees of depth three.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-classification-trees-for-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Backdoor Attack to Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-backdoor-attack-to-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This demonstrates the vulnerability of DNNs to energy backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-backdoor-attack-to-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENOM: Text-driven Unrestricted Adversarial Example Generation with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/venom-text-driven-unrestricted-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that VENOM achieves superior ASR and image quality compared to prior methods, marking a significant advancement in adversarial example generation and providing insights into model vulnerabilities for improved defense development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/venom-text-driven-unrestricted-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding subtraction and division of stochastic signals using normalizing flows: NFdeconvolve</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-subtraction-and-division-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the $x=a+b$ example, $a$ can be fluorescence background and $b$ the signal of interest whose statistics are to be learned from the measured $x$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-subtraction-and-division-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Globally Convergent Variational Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-convergent-variational-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This VI method, which may be considered an instance of neural posterior estimation (NPE), minimizes an expectation of the inclusive (forward) KL divergence to fit a variational distribution that is parameterized by a neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-convergent-variational-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced SPS Velocity-adaptive Scheme: Access Fariness in 5G NR V2I Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-sps-velocity-adaptive-scheme-access</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vehicle-to-Infrastructure (V2I) technology enables information exchange between vehicles and road infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-sps-velocity-adaptive-scheme-access</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-ST: A Multimodal Large Language Model for Fine-Grained Spatial-Temporal Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-st-a-multimodal-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose ST-Align dataset with 4. 3M training samples for fine-grained spatial-temporal multimodal understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-st-a-multimodal-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logarithmic Memory Networks (LMNs): Efficient Long-Range Sequence Modeling for Resource-Constrained Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logarithmic-memory-networks-lmns-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-range sequence modeling is a crucial aspect of natural language processing and time series analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logarithmic-memory-networks-lmns-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D$^2$-DPM: Dual Denoising for Quantized Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-2-dpm-dual-denoising-for-quantized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose D2-DPM, a dual denoising mechanism aimed at precisely mitigating the adverse effects of quantization noise on the noise estimation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-2-dpm-dual-denoising-for-quantized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Likes to Sleep: A Computer-Assisted Comparison of Object Naming Data from 30 Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-likes-to-sleep-a-computer-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object naming - the act of identifying an object with a word or a phrase - is a fundamental skill in interpersonal communication, relevant to many disciplines, such as psycholinguistics, cognitive linguistics, or language and vision research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-likes-to-sleep-a-computer-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Label Refinement Matters More than Preference Optimization under Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-label-refinement-matters-more-than</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ILR improves the SFT data by using comparison feedback to decide whether human demonstrations should be replaced by model-generated alternatives, then retrains the model via SFT on the updated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-label-refinement-matters-more-than</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDiffRetro: Retrosynthesis Prediction with Dual Graph Enhanced Molecular Representation and Diffusion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdiffretro-retrosynthesis-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typically, the retrosynthesis prediction involves two phases: Reaction Center Identification and Reactant Generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdiffretro-retrosynthesis-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CuAsmRL: Optimizing GPU SASS Schedules via Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuasmrl-optimizing-gpu-sass-schedules-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, those specialized kernels may still leave performance on the table as CUDA assembly experts show that manual optimization of GPU SASS schedules can lead to better performance, and trial-and-error is largely employed to manually find the best GPU SASS schedules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuasmrl-optimizing-gpu-sass-schedules-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PokerBench: Training Large Language Models to become Professional Poker Players</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pokerbench-training-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PokerBench thus presents a unique benchmark for a quick and reliable evaluation of the poker-playing ability of LLMs as well as a comprehensive benchmark to study the progress of LLMs in complex game-playing scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pokerbench-training-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Analysis of DNN-based White-Box Explainable AI Methods in Network Security</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-dnn-based-white-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[New research focuses on creating artificial intelligence (AI) solutions for network intrusion detection systems (NIDS), drawing its inspiration from the ever-growing number of intrusions on networked systems, increasing its complexity and intelligibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-dnn-based-white-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Equilibrium in Online Learning: Theory and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-equilibrium-in-online-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new perspective on online learning that we refer to as gradient equilibrium: a sequence of iterates achieves gradient equilibrium if the average of gradients of losses along the sequence converges to zero.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-equilibrium-in-online-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OptiChat: Bridging Optimization Models and Practitioners with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optichat-bridging-optimization-models-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization models have been applied to solve a wide variety of decision-making problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optichat-bridging-optimization-models-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tarsier2: Advancing Large Vision-Language Models from Detailed Video Description to Comprehensive Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tarsier2-advancing-large-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Tarsier2, a state-of-the-art large vision-language model (LVLM) designed for generating detailed and accurate video descriptions, while also exhibiting superior general video understanding capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tarsier2-advancing-large-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3UR-LLM: An End-to-End Multimodal Large Language Model for 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ur-llm-an-end-to-end-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) exhibit impressive capabilities in 2D tasks, yet encounter challenges in discerning the spatial positions, interrelations, and causal logic in scenes when transitioning from 2D to 3D representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ur-llm-an-end-to-end-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHEQ-ing the Box: Safe Variable Impedance Learning for Robotic Polishing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheq-ing-the-box-safe-variable-impedance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results highlight the potential of adaptive hybrid RL for real-world, contact-rich tasks trained directly on hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheq-ing-the-box-safe-variable-impedance</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
