<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 21:07:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Learning for Efficient Fine-Tuning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-for-efficient-fine-tuning-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The research investigates the application of meta-learning strategies to enhance the adaptability and performance of LLMs with limited computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-for-efficient-fine-tuning-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Learning Abductive Reasoning using VSA Distributed Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-abductive-reasoning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Abductive Rule Learner with Context-awareness (ARLC), a model that solves abstract reasoning tasks based on Learn-VRF.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-abductive-reasoning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeaKR: Self-aware Knowledge Retrieval for Adaptive Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seakr-self-aware-knowledge-retrieval-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Self-aware Knowledge Retrieval (SeaKR), a novel adaptive RAG model that extracts self-aware uncertainty of LLMs from their internal states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seakr-self-aware-knowledge-retrieval-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Pareto Set for Multi-Objective Continuous Robot Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pareto-set-for-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a control problem with multiple conflicting objectives, there exists a set of Pareto-optimal policies called the Pareto set instead of a single optimal policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pareto-set-for-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEX-TTS: Diffusion-based EXpressive Text-to-Speech with Style Modeling on Time Variability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-tts-diffusion-based-expressive-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expressive Text-to-Speech (TTS) using reference speech has been studied extensively to synthesize natural speech, but there are limitations to obtaining well-represented styles and improving model generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-tts-diffusion-based-expressive-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELLO: Causal Evaluation of Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cello-causal-evaluation-of-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work typically focuses on commonsense causality between events and/or actions, which is insufficient for applications like embodied agents and lacks the explicitly defined causal graphs required for formal causal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cello-causal-evaluation-of-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suri: Multi-constraint Instruction Following for Long-form Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suri-multi-constraint-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing research on instruction following largely focuses on tasks with simple instructions and short responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suri-multi-constraint-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSP: Self-Supervised Prompting for Cross-Lingual Transfer to Low-Resource Languages using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-prompting-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate their effectiveness for NLP tasks in low-resource languages (LRLs), especially in the setting of zero-labelled cross-lingual transfer (0-CLT), where no labelled training data for the target language is available -- however training data from one or more related medium-resource languages (MRLs) is utilized, alongside the available unlabeled test data for a target language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-prompting-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpleFusion: A Simple Fusion Framework for Infrared and Visible Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplefusion-a-simple-fusion-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating visible and infrared images into one high-quality image, also known as visible and infrared image fusion, is a challenging yet critical task for many downstream vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplefusion-a-simple-fusion-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporally Multi-Scale Sparse Self-Attention for Physical Activity Data Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-multi-scale-sparse-self-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wearable sensors enable health researchers to continuously collect data pertaining to the physiological state of individuals in real-world settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-multi-scale-sparse-self-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUWSOD: Holistic Self-training for Unified Weakly Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huwsod-holistic-self-training-for-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most WSOD methods rely on traditional object proposals to generate candidate regions and are confronted with unstable training, which easily gets stuck in a poor local optimum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huwsod-holistic-self-training-for-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Anywhere Pointed: Layout-aware GUI Screen Reading with Tree-of-Lens Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-anywhere-pointed-layout-aware-gui-screen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Tree-of-Lens (ToL) agent, utilizing a novel ToL grounding mechanism, to address the SPR task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-anywhere-pointed-layout-aware-gui-screen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking 3D: Anomaly Detection with 2D-3D Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-3d-anomaly-detection-with-2d-3d-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic anomaly detection based on visual cues holds practical significance in various domains, such as manufacturing and product quality assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-3d-anomaly-detection-with-2d-3d-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Biased Selective Labels to Pseudo-Labels: An Expectation-Maximization Framework for Learning from Biased Decisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-biased-selective-labels-to-pseudo-labels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by causal models of selective labels, we propose Disparate Censorship Expectation-Maximization (DCEM), an algorithm for learning in the presence of disparate censorship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-biased-selective-labels-to-pseudo-labels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dysca: A Dynamic and Scalable Benchmark for Evaluating Perception Ability of LVLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dysca-a-dynamic-and-scalable-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, these benchmarks merely focus on evaluating LVLMs on the realistic style images and clean scenarios, leaving the multi-stylized images and noisy scenarios unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dysca-a-dynamic-and-scalable-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALVe: Semantic Alignment Verification for Floorplan Reconstruction from Sparse Panoramas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salve-semantic-alignment-verification-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once the room poses are computed, room layouts are inferred using HorizonNet, and the floorplan is constructed by stitching the most confident layout boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salve-semantic-alignment-verification-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STBench: Assessing the Ability of Large Language Models in Spatio-Temporal Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stbench-assessing-the-ability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of large language models (LLMs) holds promise for reforming the methodology of spatio-temporal data mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stbench-assessing-the-ability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmPO: Theory-Driven Dataset Construction for Empathetic Response Generation through Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empo-theory-driven-dataset-construction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empathetic response generation is a desirable aspect of conversational agents, crucial for facilitating engaging and emotionally intelligent multi-turn conversations between humans and machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empo-theory-driven-dataset-construction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Pronged Human Evaluation of ChatGPT Self-Correction in Radiology Report Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-pronged-human-evaluation-of-chatgpt-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiology reports are highly technical documents aimed primarily at doctor-doctor communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-pronged-human-evaluation-of-chatgpt-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Weak-to-Strong Generalization with Reliability-Aware Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-weak-to-strong-generalization-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are now rapidly advancing and surpassing human abilities on many natural language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-weak-to-strong-generalization-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the duration of traffic incidents for Sydney greater metropolitan area using machine learning methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-duration-of-traffic-incidents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results demonstrate that XGBoost and LightGBM outperform conventional models with XGBoost achieving the lowest RMSE of 33. 7 for predicting incident duration and highest classification F1 score of 0. 62 for a 30-minute duration threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-duration-of-traffic-incidents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correspondence-Free Non-Rigid Point Set Registration Using Unsupervised Clustering Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correspondence-free-non-rigid-point-set-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel non-rigid point set registration method that is inspired by unsupervised clustering analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correspondence-free-non-rigid-point-set-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabReD: A Benchmark of Tabular Machine Learning in-the-Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabred-a-benchmark-of-tabular-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine existing tabular benchmarks and find two common characteristics of industry-grade tabular data that are underrepresented in the datasets available to the academic community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabred-a-benchmark-of-tabular-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoder based approach for the mitigation of spurious correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-approach-for-the-mitigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) have exhibited remarkable performance across various tasks, yet their susceptibility to spurious correlations poses a significant challenge for out-of-distribution (OOD) generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-approach-for-the-mitigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimensions underlying the representational alignment of deep neural networks with humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensions-underlying-the-representational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying this framework to humans and a DNN model of natural images revealed a low-dimensional DNN embedding of both visual and semantic dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimensions-underlying-the-representational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Remarkable Robustness of LLMs: Stages of Inference?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-remarkable-robustness-of-llms-stages-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that deleting and swapping interventions retain 72-95\% of the original model's prediction accuracy without fine-tuning, whereas models with more layers exhibit more robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-remarkable-robustness-of-llms-stages-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORE4D: A 4D Human-Object-Human Interaction Dataset for Collaborative Object REarrangement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core4d-a-4d-human-object-human-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With 1K human-object-human motion sequences captured in the real world, we enrich CORE4D by contributing an iterative collaboration retargeting strategy to augment motions to a variety of novel objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core4d-a-4d-human-object-human-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Retrieval Augmentation for Personalized Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-retrieval-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the proposed LAPDOG model consists of a story retriever and a dialogue generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-retrieval-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BackMix: Mitigating Shortcut Learning in Echocardiography with Minimal Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backmix-mitigating-shortcut-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks can learn spurious correlations that lead to the correct prediction in a validation set, but generalise poorly because the predictions are right for the wrong reason.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backmix-mitigating-shortcut-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Expressiveness of $K$-hop Message-Passing GNNs by Injecting Contextualized Substructure Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-expressiveness-of-k-hop-message</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there is a line of works aiming to enhance the expressive power of graph neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-expressiveness-of-k-hop-message</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Test for Data Analysis Pipeline by Selective Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-test-for-data-analysis-pipeline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel statistical test designed to assess the statistical significance of data analysis pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-test-for-data-analysis-pipeline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReXTime: A Benchmark Suite for Reasoning-Across-Time in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rextime-a-benchmark-suite-for-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This form of reasoning, requiring advanced understanding of cause-and-effect relationships across video segments, poses significant challenges to even the frontier multimodal large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rextime-a-benchmark-suite-for-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolving Discrepancies in Compute-Optimal Scaling of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-discrepancies-in-compute-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a secondary result, we derive scaling laws for the optimal learning rate and batch size, finding that tuning the AdamW $\beta_2$ parameter is essential at lower batch sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-discrepancies-in-compute-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient World Models with Context-Aware Tokenization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-world-models-with-context-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling up deep Reinforcement Learning (RL) methods presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-world-models-with-context-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Graph Semantic and Structural Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-graph-semantic-and-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, for node-level semantics, we find that contrasting nodes from distinct classes is beneficial to provide a well-performing discrimination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-graph-semantic-and-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retain, Blend, and Exchange: A Quality-aware Spatial-Stereo Fusion Approach for Event Stream Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retain-blend-and-exchange-a-quality-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel dual-stream framework for event stream-based pattern recognition via differentiated fusion, termed EFV++.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retain-blend-and-exchange-a-quality-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural Attention: Rethinking Transformer for Unpaired Medical Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-attention-rethinking-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce UNet Structured Transformer (UNest), a novel architecture incorporating structural inductive biases for unpaired medical image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-attention-rethinking-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Taxonomic Image-based Out-of-distribution Detection With DNA Barcodes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-taxonomic-image-based-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-based species identification could help scaling biodiversity monitoring to a global scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-taxonomic-image-based-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Stochastic Weight Averaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-stochastic-weight-averaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its potential benefits, maintaining a running average of parameters can hinder generalization, as an underlying running model begins to overfit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-stochastic-weight-averaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiveBench: A Challenging, Contamination-Free LLM Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livebench-a-challenging-contamination-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a new benchmark for LLMs designed to be immune to both test set contamination and the pitfalls of LLM judging and human crowdsourcing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/livebench-a-challenging-contamination-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedMLP: Federated Multi-Label Medical Image Classification under Task Heterogeneity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmlp-federated-multi-label-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on two publicly-available medical datasets validate the superiority of FedMLP against the state-of-the-art both federated semi-supervised and noisy label learning approaches under task heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmlp-federated-multi-label-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Aware Vision-and-Language Navigation: Bridging Simulation to Reality with Dynamic Human Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-aware-vision-and-language-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-and-Language Navigation (VLN) aims to develop embodied agents that navigate based on human instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-aware-vision-and-language-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPureData: Automated Filtering of Web Data for LLM Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopuredata-automated-filtering-of-web-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Up-to-date and reliable Large Language Models (LLMs) are consistently sought after.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopuredata-automated-filtering-of-web-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-adaptive Synergetic Two-way Pseudoinverse Learning System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-adaptive-synergetic-two-way</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The whole system is trained using a non-gradient descent learning algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-adaptive-synergetic-two-way</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Missing In Homophily? Disentangling Graph Homophily For Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-missing-in-homophily-disentangling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, a crucial question arises: What is missing in our current understanding of homophily?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-is-missing-in-homophily-disentangling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidential Concept Embedding Models: Towards Reliable Concept Explanations for Skin Disease Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidential-concept-embedding-models-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proposed methods, we can enhance concept explanations' reliability for both supervised and label-efficient settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidential-concept-embedding-models-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional-Reachable Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning with Mutually Responsive Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-reachable-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical reinforcement learning (HRL) addresses complex long-horizon tasks by skillfully decomposing them into subgoals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-reachable-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Prompting Tuning for Personalized Conversations with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompting-tuning-for-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate those issues, we propose \textbf{S}elective \textbf{P}rompt \textbf{T}uning (SPT), which softly prompts LLMs for personalized conversations in a selective way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-prompting-tuning-for-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look into Mixture-of-Experts in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-mixture-of-experts-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mixture-of-experts (MoE) is gaining increasing attention due to its unique properties and remarkable performance, especially for language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-mixture-of-experts-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiTrack: Bidirectional Offline 3D Multi-Object Tracking Using Camera-LiDAR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitrack-bidirectional-offline-3d-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with real-time multi-object tracking (MOT), offline multi-object tracking (OMOT) has the advantages to perform 2D-3D detection fusion, erroneous link correction, and full track optimization but has to deal with the challenges from bounding box misalignment and track evaluation, editing, and refinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitrack-bidirectional-offline-3d-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
