<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:11:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Low-light image enhancement based on sharpening-smoothing image filter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-image-enhancement-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, inverse HSV transform is applied to the enhanced V component and H, S components to obtain the enhanced image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-light-image-enhancement-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixup-Augmented Meta-Learning for Sample-Efficient Fine-Tuning of Protein Simulators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixup-augmented-meta-learning-for-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular dynamics simulations have emerged as a fundamental instrument for studying biomolecules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixup-augmented-meta-learning-for-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biquality Learning: a Framework to Design Algorithms Dealing with Closed-Set Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biquality-learning-a-framework-to-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training machine learning models from data with weak supervision and dataset shifts is still challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biquality-learning-a-framework-to-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxonomic Loss for Morphological Glossing of Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomic-loss-for-morphological-glossing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Morpheme glossing is a critical task in automated language documentation and can benefit other downstream applications greatly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomic-loss-for-morphological-glossing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSFlow: Multi-Scale Flow-based Framework for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msflow-multi-scale-flow-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised anomaly detection (UAD) attracts a lot of research interest and drives widespread applications, where only anomaly-free samples are available for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msflow-multi-scale-flow-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-temporal MLP-graph network for 3D human pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-mlp-graph-network-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph convolutional networks and their variants have shown significant promise in 3D human pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-mlp-graph-network-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyGPT: Detecting Industrial Anomalies using Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygpt-detecting-industrial-anomalies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) such as MiniGPT-4 and LLaVA have demonstrated the capability of understanding images and achieved remarkable performance in various visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygpt-detecting-industrial-anomalies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Robot Learning through Learned Human-Attention Feature Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-robot-learning-through-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to model and emulate the human attention with an approximate prediction model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-robot-learning-through-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Grid Transformer for Document Layout Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-grid-transformer-for-document-layout</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document pre-trained models and grid-based models have proven to be very effective on various tasks in Document AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-grid-transformer-for-document-layout</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Robustness of Object Detection Models in Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-object-detection-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The robustness of object detection models is a major concern when applied to real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-robustness-of-object-detection-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid Membership Latent Distance Model for Unsigned and Signed Integer Weighted Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-membership-latent-distance-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph representation learning (GRL) has become a prominent tool for furthering the understanding of complex networks providing tools for network embedding, link prediction, and node classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-membership-latent-distance-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPTrans: Transferring Visual Knowledge with Pre-trained Models for Multimodal Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliptrans-transferring-visual-knowledge-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneously, there has been an influx of multilingual pre-trained models for NMT and multimodal pre-trained models for vision-language tasks, primarily in English, which have shown exceptional generalisation ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliptrans-transferring-visual-knowledge-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Upsample by Learning to Sample</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-upsample-by-learning-to-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DySample, an ultra-lightweight and effective dynamic upsampler.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-upsample-by-learning-to-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Prior-Free Positive-Unlabeled Learning with Taylor Variational Loss for Hyperspectral Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-prior-free-positive-unlabeled-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positive-unlabeled learning (PU learning) in hyperspectral remote sensing imagery (HSI) is aimed at learning a binary classifier from positive and unlabeled data, which has broad prospects in various earth vision applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-prior-free-positive-unlabeled-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Mobile Face Anti-Spoofing: A Robust Framework for Diverse Attack Types under Screen Flash</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mobile-face-anti-spoofing-a-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an attack type robust face anti-spoofing framework under light flash, called ATR-FAS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mobile-face-anti-spoofing-a-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADFA: Attention-augmented Differentiable top-k Feature Adaptation for Unsupervised Medical Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adfa-attention-augmented-differentiable-top-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then apply differentiable top-k feature adaptation to train the patch descriptor, mapping the extracted feature representations to a new vector space, enabling effective detection of anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adfa-attention-augmented-differentiable-top-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Model Transferability through the Lens of Potential Energy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-model-transferability-through-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results on 10 downstream tasks and 12 self-supervised models demonstrate that our approach can seamlessly integrate into existing ranking techniques and enhance their performances, revealing its effectiveness for the model selection task and its potential for understanding the mechanism in transfer learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-model-transferability-through-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect, Augment, Compose, and Adapt: Four Steps for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-augment-compose-and-adapt-four-steps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) plays a crucial role in object detection when adapting a source-trained detector to a target domain without annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-augment-compose-and-adapt-four-steps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSAM: Visual Explanations from Style Augmentation as Adversarial Attacker and Their Influence in Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wsam-visual-explanations-from-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, style augmentation is capturing attention due to convolutional neural networks (CNN) being strongly biased toward recognizing textures rather than shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wsam-visual-explanations-from-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Neuro-Inspired Adaptability for Continual Learning in Artificial Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-neuro-inspired-adaptability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning aims to empower artificial intelligence (AI) with strong adaptability to the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-neuro-inspired-adaptability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParaGuide: Guided Diffusion Paraphrasers for Plug-and-Play Textual Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraguide-guided-diffusion-paraphrasers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our parameter-efficient approach, ParaGuide, leverages paraphrase-conditioned diffusion models alongside gradient-based guidance from both off-the-shelf classifiers and strong existing style embedders to transform the style of text while preserving semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paraguide-guided-diffusion-paraphrasers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Do Program-of-Thoughts Work for Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-program-of-thoughts-work-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although there are effective methods like program-of-thought prompting for LLMs which uses programming language to tackle complex reasoning tasks, the specific impact of code data on the improvement of reasoning capabilities remains under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-program-of-thoughts-work-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From SMOTE to Mixup for Deep Imbalanced Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-smote-to-mixup-for-deep-imbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditionally, the well-known synthetic minority oversampling technique (SMOTE) for data augmentation, a data mining approach for imbalanced learning, has been used to improve this generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-smote-to-mixup-for-deep-imbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Multi-Task Gaussian Cox Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-multi-task-gaussian-cox</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel extension of multi-task Gaussian Cox processes for modeling multiple heterogeneous correlated tasks jointly, e. g., classification and regression, via multi-output Gaussian processes (MOGP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-multi-task-gaussian-cox</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Reinforcement Learning Training Regimes for Social Robot Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-reinforcement-learning-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method to improve the generalization performance of RL social navigation methods using curriculum learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-reinforcement-learning-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read-only Prompt Optimization for Vision-Language Few-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-only-prompt-optimization-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RPO leverages masked attention to prevent the internal representation shift in the pre-trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-only-prompt-optimization-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEFHRI: A Communication Efficient Federated Learning Framework for Recognizing Industrial Human-Robot Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cefhri-a-communication-efficient-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning plays a vital role in industrial HRI by enhancing the adaptability and autonomy of robots in complex environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cefhri-a-communication-efficient-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reprogramming under constraints: Revisiting efficient and reliable transferability of lottery tickets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reprogramming-under-constraints-revisiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of foundation models with huge pre-training budgets, the downstream tasks have been shifted to the narrative of efficient and fast adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reprogramming-under-constraints-revisiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Loss Functions: Traffic Predictions in Regular and Congestion Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-loss-functions-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While accurate forecasting of regular traffic conditions is crucial, a reliable AI system must also accurately forecast congestion scenarios to maintain safe and efficient transportation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-loss-functions-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble of Counterfactual Explainers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-of-counterfactual-explainers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In eXplainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI), several counterfactual explainers have been proposed, each focusing on some desirable properties of counterfactual instances: minimality, actionability, stability, diversity, plausibility, discriminative power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-of-counterfactual-explainers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Integration of Information Using Top-Down Modulated WTA Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-integration-of-information-using-top</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that WTA circuits are capable of integrating the probabilistic information represented by other WTA networks, and that top down processes can improve a WTA network's inference and learning performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-integration-of-information-using-top</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards quantitative precision for ECG analysis: Leveraging state space models, self-supervision and patient metadata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-quantitative-precision-for-ecg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These components consistently enhance performance beyond the existing state-of-the-art, which is predominantly based on convolutional models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-quantitative-precision-for-ecg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared Lexical Items as Triggers of Code Switching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shared-lexical-items-as-triggers-of-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Why do bilingual speakers code-switch (mix their two languages)?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shared-lexical-items-as-triggers-of-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OEBench: Investigating Open Environment Challenges in Real-World Relational Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oebench-investigating-open-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, while several real-world streaming datasets are available, it is uncertain whether these open environment challenges are prevalent and how existing incremental learning algorithms perform on real datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oebench-investigating-open-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPS: A Practical Partition Index for Filtered Similarity Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caps-a-practical-partition-index-for-filtered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the surging popularity of approximate near-neighbor search (ANNS), driven by advances in neural representation learning, the ability to serve queries accompanied by a set of constraints has become an area of intense interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caps-a-practical-partition-index-for-filtered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Explanation Methods for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-explanation-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many applications classification alone is not enough, we often need to classify but also understand what the model learns (e. g., why was a prediction given, based on what information in the data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-explanation-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing Learning Curves During Language Model Pre-Training: Learning, Forgetting, and Stability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-learning-curves-during</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We quantify the final surprisal, within-run variability, age of acquisition, forgettability, and cross-run variability of learning curves for individual tokens in context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-learning-curves-during</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sub-universal variational circuits for combinatorial optimization problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sub-universal-variational-circuits-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum variational circuits have gained significant attention due to their applications in the quantum approximate optimization algorithm and quantum machine learning research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sub-universal-variational-circuits-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking the Generation of Fact Checking Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-generation-of-fact-checking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results show that in justification production summarization benefits from the claim information, and, in particular, that a claim-driven extractive step improves abstractive summarization performances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-the-generation-of-fact-checking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic solar flare forecasting using historical magnetogram data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-solar-flare-forecasting-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider over 4 solar cycles of daily historical magnetogram data from multiple instruments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-solar-flare-forecasting-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Neural Ranking Models with Traditional IR Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-neural-ranking-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural ranking methods based on large transformer models have recently gained significant attention in the information retrieval community, and have been adopted by major commercial solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-neural-ranking-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliability Gaps Between Groups in COMPAS Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-gaps-between-groups-in-compas</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the inter-rater reliability of risk assessment instruments (RAIs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-gaps-between-groups-in-compas</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Providing Previously Unseen Users Fair Recommendations Using Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/providing-previously-unseen-users-fair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An emerging definition of fairness in machine learning requires that models are oblivious to demographic user information, e. g., a user's gender or age should not influence the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/providing-previously-unseen-users-fair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Feedforward Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-feedforward-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We break the linear link between the layer size and its inference cost by introducing the fast feedforward (FFF) architecture, a logarithmic-time alternative to feedforward networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-feedforward-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Discovery and Effective Evaluation of Visual Perceptual Similarity: A Benchmark and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-discovery-and-effective-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given an image of a certain object, the goal of VSD is to retrieve images of different objects with high perceptual visual similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-discovery-and-effective-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spoken Language Intelligence of Large Language Models for Language Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoken-language-intelligence-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus is centered on evaluating the efficacy of LLMs in the realm of education, specifically in the areas of spoken language learning which encompass phonetics, phonology, and second language acquisition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoken-language-intelligence-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Task Semantic Decomposition Framework with Task-specific Pre-training for Few-Shot NER</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-semantic-decomposition-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of few-shot named entity recognition is to identify named entities with limited labeled instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-semantic-decomposition-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Modification of the Upper Confidence Bound Algorithm by Generalized Weighted Averages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-modification-of-the-upper-confidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In preliminary experiments, we investigated the optimal parameters of a simple generalized UCB1 (G-UCB1), prepared for comparison and GWA-UCB1, in a stochastic MAB problem with two arms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-modification-of-the-upper-confidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRGCN: Heterogeneous Graph-level Anomaly Detection with Hierarchical Relation-augmented Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrgcn-heterogeneous-graph-level-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the problem, we propose HRGCN, an unsupervised deep heterogeneous graph neural network, to model complex heterogeneous relations between different entities in the system for effectively identifying these anomalous behaviour graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrgcn-heterogeneous-graph-level-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISC-MedLLM: Bridging General Large Language Models and Real-World Medical Consultation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disc-medllm-bridging-general-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose DISC-MedLLM, a comprehensive solution that leverages Large Language Models (LLMs) to provide accurate and truthful medical response in end-to-end conversational healthcare services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disc-medllm-bridging-general-large-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
