<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 09:19:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Drift Guided LayerNorm Tuning for Efficient Multimodal Metaphor Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2505-11237</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods for multimodal metaphor identification often struggle to bridge the gap between literal and figurative interpretations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2505-11237</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenoArmory: A Unified Evaluation Framework for Adversarial Attacks on Genomic Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2505-10983</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the first unified adversarial attack benchmark for Genomic Foundation Models (GFMs), named GenoArmory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2505-10983</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning on a Budget: Miniaturizing DeepSeek R1 with SFT-GRPO Alignment for Instruction-Tuned LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-on-a-budget-miniaturizing-deepseek</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a modular, low-cost replication of the DeepSeek-R1 training methodology using Qwen2. 5-0. 5B-Instruct (a compact instruction-tuned LLM) optimized via a two-stage pipeline: Supervised Fine-Tuning (SFT) and Group Relative Policy Optimization (GRPO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-on-a-budget-miniaturizing-deepseek</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Dense Hand Contact Estimation from Imbalanced Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2505-11152</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, there exists class imbalance issue from hand contact datasets where majority of samples are not in contact.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2505-11152</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finetune-RAG: Fine-Tuning Language Models to Resist Hallucination in Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetune-rag-fine-tuning-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) has emerged as a powerful framework to improve factuality in large language models (LLMs) by grounding their outputs in retrieved documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetune-rag-fine-tuning-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Opportunistic Coronary Calcium Screening at Veterans Affairs Hospitals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-opportunistic-coronary-calcium-screening</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions This nongated CT CAC algorithm was developed across a national health care system and shows strong performance in evaluation against paired gated CT scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-opportunistic-coronary-calcium-screening</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTVCrafter: 4D Motion Tokenization for Open-World Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtvcrafter-4d-motion-tokenization-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose MTVCrafter (Motion Tokenization Video Crafter), the first framework that directly models raw 3D motion sequences (i. e., 4D motion) for human image animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtvcrafter-4d-motion-tokenization-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Feasibility Matter? Understanding the Impact of Feasibility on Synthetic Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-feasibility-matter-understanding-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, mixing feasible and infeasible images in training datasets does not significantly impact performance compared to using purely feasible or infeasible datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-feasibility-matter-understanding-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Questions to Clinical Recommendations: Large Language Models Driving Evidence-Based Clinical Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-questions-to-clinical-recommendations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical evidence, derived from rigorous research and data analysis, provides healthcare professionals with reliable scientific foundations for informed decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-questions-to-clinical-recommendations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIG: Privacy Jailbreak Attack on LLMs via Gradient-based Iterative In-Context Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pig-privacy-jailbreak-attack-on-llms-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate PIG and existing jailbreak methods using two privacy-related datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pig-privacy-jailbreak-attack-on-llms-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRSplat: Fast and Robust Gaussian Splatting for Virtual Reality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrsplat-fast-and-robust-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, 3DGS faces key challenges in virtual reality (VR): (1) temporal artifacts, such as popping during head movements, (2) projection-based distortions that result in disturbing and view-inconsistent floaters, and (3) reduced framerates when rendering large numbers of Gaussians, falling below the critical threshold for VR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrsplat-fast-and-robust-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSCI: Addressing CLIP's Inherent Limitations for Compositional Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msci-addressing-clip-s-inherent-limitations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a Multi-Stage Cross-modal Interaction (MSCI) model that effectively explores and utilizes intermediate-layer information from CLIP's visual encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msci-addressing-clip-s-inherent-limitations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADHMR: Aligning Diffusion-based Human Mesh Recovery via Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adhmr-aligning-diffusion-based-human-mesh</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose ADHMR, a framework that Aligns a Diffusion-based HMR model in a preference optimization manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adhmr-aligning-diffusion-based-human-mesh</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCoder-VL: Bridging Vision and Code for Enhanced Multimodal Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-vl-bridging-vision-and-code-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language image-caption datasets, widely used for training Large Multimodal Models, mainly focus on natural scenarios and overlook the intricate details of mathematical figures that are critical for problem-solving, hindering the advancement of current LMMs in multimodal mathematical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-vl-bridging-vision-and-code-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Robustness of Deep Reinforcement Learning for Autonomous Surface Vehicle Control in Field Tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-robustness-of-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advancements in Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) for Autonomous Surface Vehicles (ASVs), their robustness in real-world conditions, particularly under external disturbances, remains insufficiently explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-robustness-of-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond 'Aha!': Toward Systematic Meta-Abilities Alignment in Large Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-aha-toward-systematic-meta-abilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large reasoning models (LRMs) already possess a latent capacity for long chain-of-thought reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-aha-toward-systematic-meta-abilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPentest: Enhancing Vulnerability Management With Autonomous LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopentest-enhancing-vulnerability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent area of increasing research is the use of Large Language Models (LLMs) in penetration testing, which promises to reduce costs and thus allow for higher frequency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopentest-enhancing-vulnerability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSPENet: Contour-Aware and Saliency Priors Embedding Network for Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cspenet-contour-aware-and-saliency-priors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this, we propose a dual-branch priors embedding architecture (DBPEA) that establishes differentiated feature fusion pathways, embedding these two priors at optimal network positions to achieve performance enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cspenet-contour-aware-and-saliency-priors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid Strategy for Aggregated Probabilistic Forecasting and Energy Trading in HEFTCom2024</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-strategy-for-aggregated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obtaining accurate probabilistic energy forecasts and making effective decisions amid diverse uncertainties are routine challenges in future energy systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-strategy-for-aggregated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deconstructing Subset Construction -- Reducing While Determinizing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-subset-construction-reducing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel perspective on the NFA canonization problem, which introduces intermediate minimization steps to reduce the exploration space on-the-fly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-subset-construction-reducing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalizing Large Language Models using Retrieval Augmented Generation and Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-large-language-models-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of large language models (LLMs) has allowed numerous applications, including the generation of queried responses, to be leveraged in chatbots and other conversational assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-large-language-models-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Stage Generative Model for Intracranial Aneurysm Meshes with Morphological Marker Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-generative-model-for-intracranial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing shape generation methods struggle to capture realistic IA features and ignore the relationship between IA pouches and parent vessels, limiting physiological realism and their generation cannot be controlled to have specific morphological measurements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-generative-model-for-intracranial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring entropy production in many-body systems using nonequilibrium MaxEnt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-entropy-production-in-many-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method for inferring entropy production (EP) in high-dimensional stochastic systems, including many-body systems and non-Markovian systems with long memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-entropy-production-in-many-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Nonlinear Dynamics in Physical Modelling Synthesis using Neural Ordinary Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-dynamics-in-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine how modal decomposition can be combined with neural ordinary differential equations for modelling distributed musical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-dynamics-in-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Deep Fusion of Large Language Models and Diffusion Transformers for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-deep-fusion-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper does not describe a new method; instead, it provides a thorough exploration of an important yet understudied design space related to recent advances in text-to-image synthesis -- specifically, the deep fusion of large language models (LLMs) and diffusion transformers (DiTs) for multi-modal generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-deep-fusion-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Radiance Field for Dynamic Scene: From Neural Field to Gaussian Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-radiance-field-for-dynamic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey presents a systematic analysis of over 200 papers focused on dynamic scene representation using radiance field, spanning the spectrum from implicit neural representations to explicit Gaussian primitives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-radiance-field-for-dynamic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Implicit Visual Misunderstandings in Multimodal Large Language Models through Attention Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-implicit-visual-misunderstandings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements have enhanced the capability of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) to comprehend multi-image information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-implicit-visual-misunderstandings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFogHub: Bridging Multi-Regional and Multi-Satellite Data for Global Marine Fog Detection and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfoghub-bridging-multi-regional-and-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning approaches for marine fog detection and forecasting have outperformed traditional methods, demonstrating significant scientific and practical importance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfoghub-bridging-multi-regional-and-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified and Scalable Membership Inference Method for Visual Self-supervised Encoder via Part-aware Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-and-scalable-membership-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this setting, considering that self-supervised model could be trained by completely different self-supervised paradigms, e. g., masked image modeling and contrastive learning, with complex training details, we propose a unified membership inference method called PartCrop.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-and-scalable-membership-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Repetition Problems of LLMs in Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-repetition-problems-of-llms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, RPG first leverages grammar rules to identify repetition problems during code generation, and then strategically decays the likelihood of critical tokens that contribute to repetitions, thereby mitigating them in code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-repetition-problems-of-llms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIPHEI-ViT: Multiplex Immunofluorescence Prediction from H&amp;E Images using ViT Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miphei-vit-multiplex-immunofluorescence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results indicate that our model effectively captures the complex relationships between nuclear morphologies in their tissue context, as visible in H&E images and molecular markers defining specific cell types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miphei-vit-multiplex-immunofluorescence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HWA-UNETR: Hierarchical Window Aggregate UNETR for 3D Multimodal Gastric Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwa-unetr-hierarchical-window-aggregate-unetr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal medical image segmentation faces significant challenges in the context of gastric cancer lesion analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwa-unetr-hierarchical-window-aggregate-unetr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of SMT and MILP for the Nurse Rostering Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-smt-and-milp-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On real-world inspired problems containing a more varied set of shifts and personnel, the SMT solver excels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-smt-and-milp-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuXAI: Explainers for Hybrid Quantum Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quxai-explainers-for-hybrid-quantum-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The gap is the focus of this work, which introduces QuXAI, an framework based upon Q-MEDLEY, an explainer for explaining feature importance in these hybrid systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quxai-explainers-for-hybrid-quantum-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Wireless Localization Model (LWLM): A Foundation Model for Positioning in 6G Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-wireless-localization-model-lwlm-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate and robust localization is a critical enabler for emerging 5G and 6G applications, including autonomous driving, extended reality (XR), and smart manufacturing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-wireless-localization-model-lwlm-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Document Refinement for Long-context Retrieval-augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-document-refinement-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world RAG applications often encounter long-context input scenarios, where redundant information and noise results in higher inference costs and reduced performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-document-refinement-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASS: Multi-Agent Simulation Scaling for Portfolio Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-multi-agent-simulation-scaling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM-based multi-agent has gained significant attention for their potential in simulation and enhancing performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-multi-agent-simulation-scaling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Exploration-Exploitation Strategies of LLMs and Humans: Insights from Standard Multi-armed Bandit Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-exploration-exploitation-strategies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In simple stationary tasks, reasoning-enabled LLMs exhibit similar levels of random and directed exploration compared to humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-exploration-exploitation-strategies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Really Trust Code Copilots? Evaluating Large Language Models from a Code Security Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-you-really-trust-code-copilots-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first propose CoV-Eval, a multi-task benchmark covering various tasks such as code completion, vulnerability repair, vulnerability detection and classification, for comprehensive evaluation of LLM code security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-you-really-trust-code-copilots-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAL: Searching Expandable Architectures for Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-searching-expandable-architectures-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incremental learning is a machine learning paradigm where a model learns from a sequential stream of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-searching-expandable-architectures-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Model Explanations without Ground Truth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-model-explanations-without-ground</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current explanation evaluation frameworks measure quality by comparing against ideal "ground-truth" explanations, or by verifying model sensitivity to important inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-model-explanations-without-ground</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Prompt Optimizers: From Prompt Merits to Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-prompt-optimizers-from-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to limited downward compatibility, verbose, instruction-heavy prompts from advanced LLMs can overwhelm lightweight inference models and degrade response quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-prompt-optimizers-from-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction to Discrete Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-introduction-to-discrete-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we provide a rigorous, yet practical, introduction to discrete variational autoencoders -- specifically, VAEs in which the latent space is made up of latent variables that follow a categorical distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-introduction-to-discrete-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing LLM Text Annotation Skills: A Study on Human Rights Violations in Social Media Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-llm-text-annotation-skills-a-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of increasingly sophisticated natural language processing (NLP) systems, large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable potential for diverse applications, including tasks requiring nuanced textual understanding and contextual reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-llm-text-annotation-skills-a-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PnPXAI: A Universal XAI Framework Providing Automatic Explanations Across Diverse Modalities and Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pnpxai-a-universal-xai-framework-providing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These include limited flexibility to diverse model architectures and data modalities due to hard-coded implementations, a restricted number of supported XAI methods because of the requirements for layer-specific operations of attribution methods, and sub-optimal recommendations of explanations due to the lack of evaluation and optimization phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pnpxai-a-universal-xai-framework-providing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StoryReasoning Dataset: Using Chain-of-Thought for Scene Understanding and Grounded Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyreasoning-dataset-using-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual storytelling systems struggle to maintain character identity across frames and link actions to appropriate subjects, frequently leading to referential hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/storyreasoning-dataset-using-chain-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel Scaling Law for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-scaling-law-for-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply $P$ diverse and learnable transformations to the input, execute forward passes of the model in parallel, and dynamically aggregate the $P$ outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-scaling-law-for-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superposition Yields Robust Neural Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superposition-yields-robust-neural-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that when superposition is weak, meaning only the most frequent features are represented without interference, the scaling of loss with model size depends on the underlying feature frequency; if feature frequencies follow a power law, so does the loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superposition-yields-robust-neural-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Registration Change Detection: A Novel Change Detection Task and Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-registration-change-detection-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel remote sensing change detection task, non-registration change detection, to address the increasing number of emergencies such as natural disasters, anthropogenic accidents, and military strikes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-registration-change-detection-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned Lightweight Smartphone ISP with Unpaired Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-lightweight-smartphone-isp-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Image Signal Processor (ISP) is a fundamental component in modern smartphone cameras responsible for conversion of RAW sensor image data to RGB images with a strong focus on perceptual quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-lightweight-smartphone-isp-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
