<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 21:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Task-specific Scene Structure Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-specific-scene-structure-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the informative structures of scenes is essential for low-level vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-specific-scene-structure-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Models for Prognostics and Health Management of Lithium-Ion Batteries Based on Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-models-for-prognostics-and-health</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-Informed Neural Network (PINN) is an efficient tool to fuse empirical or physical dynamic models with data-driven models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-models-for-prognostics-and-health</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argoverse 2: Next Generation Datasets for Self-Driving Perception and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argoverse-2-next-generation-datasets-for-self-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models are tasked with the prediction of future motion for "scored actors" in each scenario and are provided with track histories that capture object location, heading, velocity, and category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/argoverse-2-next-generation-datasets-for-self-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCRLv2: A Unified Visual Information Preservation Framework for Self-supervised Pre-training in Medical Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcrlv2-a-unified-visual-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in self-supervised learning (SSL) in computer vision are primarily comparative, whose goal is to preserve invariant and discriminative semantics in latent representations by comparing siamese image views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcrlv2-a-unified-visual-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Image Inpainting by Stripe Window Transformer with Joint Attention to CNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-image-inpainting-by-stripe-window</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image inpainting is an important task in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-image-inpainting-by-stripe-window</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P3DC-Shot: Prior-Driven Discrete Data Calibration for Nearest-Neighbor Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p3dc-shot-prior-driven-discrete-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the distribution calibration technique which utilizes the distribution or statistics of the base classes to calibrate the data for few-shot tasks, we propose a novel discrete data calibration operation which is more suitable for NN-based few-shot classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p3dc-shot-prior-driven-discrete-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Undesirable Dependence on Frequency of Gender Bias Metrics Based on Word Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-undesirable-dependence-on-frequency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we study the effect of frequency when measuring female vs. male gender bias with word embedding-based bias quantification methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-undesirable-dependence-on-frequency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing Discrete Self Supervised Speech Representation for Spoken Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-discrete-self-supervised-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following the findings of such an analysis, we propose practical improvements to the discrete unit for the GSLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-discrete-self-supervised-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvNeXt V2: Co-designing and Scaling ConvNets with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This co-design of self-supervised learning techniques and architectural improvement results in a new model family called ConvNeXt V2, which significantly improves the performance of pure ConvNets on various recognition benchmarks, including ImageNet classification, COCO detection, and ADE20K segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credible Remote Sensing Scene Classification Using Evidential Fusion on Aerial-Ground Dual-view Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credible-remote-sensing-scene-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this uncertainty, a novel decision-level fusion strategy is proposed to ensure that the view with lower risk obtains more weight, making the classification more credible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credible-remote-sensing-scene-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Invariance from Generated Variance for Unsupervised Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-invariance-from-generated-variance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work focuses on unsupervised representation learning in person re-identification (ReID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-invariance-from-generated-variance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Driven Universal Model for Organ Segmentation and Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-driven-universal-model-for-organ</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model is developed from an assembly of 14 datasets with 3, 410 CT scans and evaluated on 6, 162 external CT scans from 3 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-driven-universal-model-for-organ</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Probabilistic Models for Scene-Scale 3D Categorical Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-for-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, our work is the first to apply discrete and latent diffusion for 3D categorical data on a scene-scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-for-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRT2: Inductive Linking and Ranking in Knowledge Graphs of Varying Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irt2-inductive-linking-and-ranking-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus is on inductive link prediction models as a basis for practical tools that support knowledge engineers with exploring text collections and discovering and linking new (so-called open-world) entities to the knowledge graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irt2-inductive-linking-and-ranking-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EvidenceCap: Towards trustworthy medical image segmentation via evidential identity cap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidencecap-towards-trustworthy-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation (MIS) is essential for supporting disease diagnosis and treatment effect assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidencecap-towards-trustworthy-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Technique for Human Parsing: A Survey and Outlook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-technique-for-human-parsing-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human parsing aims to partition humans in image or video into multiple pixel-level semantic parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-technique-for-human-parsing-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adaptive Kernel Approach to Federated Learning of Heterogeneous Causal Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-kernel-approach-to-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new causal inference framework to learn causal effects from multiple, decentralized data sources in a federated setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-kernel-approach-to-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation Clustering Algorithm for Dynamic Complete Signed Graphs: An Index-based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-clustering-algorithm-for-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we reduce the complexity of approximating the correlation clustering problem from $O(m\times\left( 2+ \alpha (G) \right)+n)$ to $O(m+n)$ for any given value of $\varepsilon$ for a complete signed graph with $n$ vertices and $m$ positive edges where $\alpha(G)$ is the arboricity of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-clustering-algorithm-for-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detachable Novel Views Synthesis of Dynamic Scenes Using Distribution-Driven Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detachable-novel-views-synthesis-of-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, it employs a neural representation to capture the scene distribution in the static background and a 6D-input NeRF to represent dynamic objects, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detachable-novel-views-synthesis-of-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Readability Using Genetic Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-readability-using-genetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An exhaustive study on a substantial number and diversity of texts confirms that our method was able to optimize the degree of readability in all cases without significantly altering their form or meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-readability-using-genetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Black-Box Adversarial Attack with Meta Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-black-box-adversarial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the scenario of black-box adversarial attack, the target model's parameters are unknown, and the attacker aims to find a successful adversarial perturbation based on query feedback under a query budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-black-box-adversarial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skew Class-balanced Re-weighting for Unbiased Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skew-class-balanced-re-weighting-for-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An unbiased scene graph generation (SGG) algorithm referred to as Skew Class-balanced Re-weighting (SCR) is proposed for considering the unbiased predicate prediction caused by the long-tailed distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skew-class-balanced-re-weighting-for-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature regularization for Non-line-of-sight Imaging from Under-sampled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-regularization-for-non-line-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-line-of-sight (NLOS) imaging aims to reconstruct the three-dimensional hidden scenes from the data measured in the line-of-sight, which uses photon time-of-flight information encoded in light after multiple diffuse reflections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-regularization-for-non-line-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIGPerf: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Deep Learning Training and Inference Workloads on Multi-Instance GPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/migperf-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vision of this paper is to provide a more comprehensive and practical benchmark study for MIG in order to eliminate the need for tedious manual benchmarking and tuning efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/migperf-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTNeuro: A Benchmark for Evaluating Representations of Brain Structure Across Multiple Levels of Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtneuro-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce a new dataset, annotations, and multiple downstream tasks that provide diverse ways to readout information about brain structure and architecture from the same image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtneuro-a-benchmark-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey for In-context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-for-in-context-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing ability of large language models (LLMs), in-context learning (ICL) has become a new paradigm for natural language processing (NLP), where LLMs make predictions only based on contexts augmented with a few training examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-for-in-context-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Graph Neural Networks for Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-graph-neural-networks-for-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of sampling positive and negative links and heuristically computing the features of their enclosing subgraphs, GraphLP utilizes the feature learning ability of deep-learning models to automatically extract the structural patterns of graphs for link prediction under the assumption that real-world graphs are not locally isolated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-graph-neural-networks-for-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Activating Neural Ensembles for Continual Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-activating-neural-ensembles-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability for an agent to continuously learn new skills without catastrophically forgetting existing knowledge is of critical importance for the development of generally intelligent agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-activating-neural-ensembles-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disjoint Masking with Joint Distillation for Efficient Masked Image Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disjoint-masking-with-joint-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Masked image modeling (MIM) has shown great promise for self-supervised learning (SSL) yet been criticized for learning inefficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disjoint-masking-with-joint-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Proactively Forecasting Sentence-Specific Information Popularity within Online News Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-proactively-forecasting-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We model sentence-specific popularity forecasting as a sequence regression task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-proactively-forecasting-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Against Adversarial Attacks on Audio DeepFake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-adversarial-attacks-on-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio DeepFakes are artificially generated utterances created using deep learning methods with the main aim to fool the listeners, most of such audio is highly convincing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defense-against-adversarial-attacks-on-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised 4D LiDAR Moving Object Segmentation in Stationary Settings with Multivariate Occupancy Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-4d-lidar-moving-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the problem of unsupervised moving object segmentation (MOS) in 4D LiDAR data recorded from a stationary sensor, where no ground truth annotations are involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-4d-lidar-moving-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symbolic Visual Reinforcement Learning: A Scalable Framework with Object-Level Abstraction and Differentiable Expression Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-visual-reinforcement-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning efficient and interpretable policies has been a challenging task in reinforcement learning (RL), particularly in the visual RL setting with complex scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symbolic-visual-reinforcement-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Inconsistencies of Conditionals Learned by Masked Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-inconsistencies-of-conditionals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically quantify such inconsistencies in the simple scenario of bigrams for two common styles of masked language models: T5-style and BERT-style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-inconsistencies-of-conditionals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UBIWEAR: An end-to-end, data-driven framework for intelligent physical activity prediction to empower mHealth interventions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ubiwear-an-end-to-end-data-driven-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose UBIWEAR, an end-to-end framework for intelligent physical activity prediction, with the ultimate goal to empower data-driven goal-setting interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ubiwear-an-end-to-end-data-driven-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black-box language model explanation by context length probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-language-model-explanation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present context length probing, a novel explanation technique for causal language models, based on tracking the predictions of a model as a function of the length of available context, and allowing to assign differential importance scores to different contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-language-model-explanation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrix Multiplication: Verifying Strong Uniquely Solvable Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrix-multiplication-verifying-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In subsequent work with Kleinberg and Szegedy, they connected this to the search for combinatorial objects called strong uniquely solvable puzzles (strong USPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrix-multiplication-verifying-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Forgery Classifier On Multi-modality Face Forgery Clues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-forgery-classifier-on-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face forgery detection plays an important role in personal privacy and social security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-forgery-classifier-on-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Control for 6G Industrial Wireless Subnetworks: A Graph Neural Network Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-control-for-6g-industrial-wireless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interference management techniques such as centralized power control can improve spectral efficiency in dense deployments of such subnetworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-control-for-6g-industrial-wireless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node-Element Hypergraph Message Passing for Fluid Dynamics Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-element-hypergraph-message-passing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We implement a message-passing network on such a node-element hypergraph and explore the capability of the network for the modeling of fluid flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/node-element-hypergraph-message-passing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Sensitive Policy with Distributional Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-policy-with-distributional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classical reinforcement learning (RL) techniques are generally concerned with the design of decision-making policies driven by the maximisation of the expected outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-policy-with-distributional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reservoir kernels and Volterra series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reservoir-kernels-and-volterra-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A universal kernel is constructed whose sections approximate any causal and time-invariant filter in the fading memory category with inputs and outputs in a finite-dimensional Euclidean space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reservoir-kernels-and-volterra-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPointLoc: Point-based Indoor Place Recognition using Synthetic RGB-D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpointloc-point-based-indoor-place</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study the main stages of solving the place recognition problem on the HPointLoc dataset, we proposed a new modular approach named as PNTR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hpointloc-point-based-indoor-place</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Change Intervals with Isolation Distributional Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-change-intervals-with-isolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The data-dependent property and finite feature map of IDK enabled iCID to efficiently identify various types of change points in data streams with the tolerance of noise points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-change-intervals-with-isolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monge-Kantorovich Optimal Transport Through Constrictions and Flow-rate Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monge-kantorovich-optimal-transport-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We quantify flow-rate constraints via a bound on a sought probability density of the times that mass-elements cross toll stations and cast the transportation scheduling in a Kantorovich-type of formalism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monge-kantorovich-optimal-transport-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Prediction Intervals for Remaining Useful Lifetime Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-intervals-for-remaining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main objective of Prognostics and Health Management is to estimate the Remaining Useful Lifetime (RUL), namely, the time that a system or a piece of equipment is still in working order before starting to function incorrectly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-intervals-for-remaining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Similarity-Based Predictive Maintenance Framework for Rotating Machinery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-based-predictive-maintenance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For each feature type, three similarity metrics, namely structural similarity measure (SSM), cosine similarity, and Euclidean distance are used to measure the similarity between test signals and reference signals in the feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/similarity-based-predictive-maintenance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Interpretability of Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-interpretability-of-attention-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In trained models with an attention mechanism, the outputs of an intermediate module that encodes the segment of input responsible for the output is often used as a way to peek into the `reasoning` of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-interpretability-of-attention-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT Takes the Bar Exam</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-takes-the-bar-exam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nearly all jurisdictions in the United States require a professional license exam, commonly referred to as "the Bar Exam," as a precondition for law practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-takes-the-bar-exam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Bayesian Variational Autoencoders Know What They Don't Know?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-bayesian-variational-autoencoders-know</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of detecting the Out-of-Distribution (OoD) inputs is of paramount importance for Deep Neural Networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-bayesian-variational-autoencoders-know</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
