<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 09:10:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Feature Circuits: Discovering and Editing Interpretable Causal Graphs in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-feature-circuits-discovering-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce methods for discovering and applying sparse feature circuits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-feature-circuits-discovering-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KazParC: Kazakh Parallel Corpus for Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kazparc-kazakh-parallel-corpus-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce KazParC, a parallel corpus designed for machine translation across Kazakh, English, Russian, and Turkish.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kazparc-kazakh-parallel-corpus-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Map-based Generation of Navigation Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-map-based-generation-of-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new approach to navigation instruction generation by framing the problem as an image captioning task using semantic maps as visual input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-map-based-generation-of-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Situation Awareness for Driver-Centric Driving Style Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/situation-awareness-for-driver-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we found that feature encoders pretrained on our dataset lead to more precise driving behavior modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/situation-awareness-for-driver-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SineNet: Learning Temporal Dynamics in Time-Dependent Partial Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinenet-learning-temporal-dynamics-in-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the U-Net architecture with skip connections is commonly used by prior studies to enable multi-scale processing, our analysis shows that the need for features to evolve across layers results in temporally misaligned features in skip connections, which limits the model's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinenet-learning-temporal-dynamics-in-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total-Decom: Decomposed 3D Scene Reconstruction with Minimal Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/total-decom-decomposed-3d-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene reconstruction from multi-view images is a fundamental problem in computer vision and graphics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/total-decom-decomposed-3d-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burst Super-Resolution with Diffusion Models for Improving Perceptual Quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/burst-super-resolution-with-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our proposed method, on the other hand, burst LR features are used to reconstruct the initial burst SR image that is fed into an intermediate step in the diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/burst-super-resolution-with-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLAP4CLIP: Continual Learning with Probabilistic Finetuning for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clap4clip-continual-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deterministic nature of the existing finetuning methods makes them overlook the many possible interactions across the modalities and deems them unsafe for high-risk CL tasks requiring reliable uncertainty estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clap4clip-continual-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swarm Characteristics Classification Using Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swarm-characteristics-classification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article presents a study on using supervised neural network time series classification (NN TSC) to predict key attributes and tactics of swarming autonomous agents for military contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swarm-characteristics-classification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic Quantization-Aware Approximation for Non-Linear Operations in Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-quantization-aware-approximation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-linear functions are prevalent in Transformers and their lightweight variants, incurring substantial and frequently underestimated hardware costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-quantization-aware-approximation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoAuxNet: Towards Universal 3D Representation Learning for Multi-sensor Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoauxnet-towards-universal-3d-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose geometry-to-voxel auxiliary learning to enable voxel representations to access point-level geometric information, which supports better generalisation of the voxel-based backbone with additional interpretations of multi-sensor point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geoauxnet-towards-universal-3d-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAPMT: AGI Assessment Through Prompt and Metric Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aapmt-agi-assessment-through-prompt-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods are crucial for assessing the quality of images relative to their textual descriptions, and they must accurately mirror human perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aapmt-agi-assessment-through-prompt-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Financial Bots on the Ethereum Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-financial-bots-on-the-ethereum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present a novel approach that utilizes machine learning for the detection of financial bots on the Ethereum platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-financial-bots-on-the-ethereum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Robust Ensemble Algorithm for Ischemic Stroke Lesion Segmentation: Generalizability and Clinical Utility Beyond the ISLES Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-ensemble-algorithm-for-ischemic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address this gap by presenting a novel ensemble algorithm derived from the 2022 Ischemic Stroke Lesion Segmentation (ISLES) challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-robust-ensemble-algorithm-for-ischemic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Clinical NLP Performance through Language Model-Generated Synthetic Clinical Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-clinical-nlp-performance-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models have been showing potential for producing data in mass.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-clinical-nlp-performance-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phonetic Segmentation of the UCLA Phonetics Lab Archive</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phonetic-segmentation-of-the-ucla-phonetics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also discuss the utility of the VoxAngeles corpus for general research and pedagogy in crosslinguistic phonetics, as well as for low-resource and multilingual speech technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phonetic-segmentation-of-the-ucla-phonetics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SG-PGM: Partial Graph Matching Network with Semantic Geometric Fusion for 3D Scene Graph Alignment and Its Downstream Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-pgm-partial-graph-matching-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The alignment between 3D scene graphs is the first step of many downstream tasks such as scene graph aided point cloud registration, mosaicking, overlap checking, and robot navigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-pgm-partial-graph-matching-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataverse: Open-Source ETL (Extract, Transform, Load) Pipeline for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataverse-open-source-etl-extract-transform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges associated with data processing at scale, we propose Dataverse, a unified open-source Extract-Transform-Load (ETL) pipeline for large language models (LLMs) with a user-friendly design at its core.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataverse-open-source-etl-extract-transform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DenseNets Reloaded: Paradigm Shift Beyond ResNets and ViTs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densenets-reloaded-paradigm-shift-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper revives Densely Connected Convolutional Networks (DenseNets) and reveals the underrated effectiveness over predominant ResNet-style architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densenets-reloaded-paradigm-shift-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MineLand: Simulating Large-Scale Multi-Agent Interactions with Limited Multimodal Senses and Physical Needs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineland-simulating-large-scale-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional multi-agent simulators often assume perfect information and limitless capabilities, hindering the ecological validity of social interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineland-simulating-large-scale-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Interactive Human-Machine Learning Interface for Collecting and Learning from Complex Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-interactive-human-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human-Computer Interaction has been shown to lead to improvements in machine learning systems by boosting model performance, accelerating learning and building user confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-interactive-human-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KazSAnDRA: Kazakh Sentiment Analysis Dataset of Reviews and Attitudes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kazsandra-kazakh-sentiment-analysis-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents KazSAnDRA, a dataset developed for Kazakh sentiment analysis that is the first and largest publicly available dataset of its kind.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kazsandra-kazakh-sentiment-analysis-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Cardiac Imaging with Controlled Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-cardiac-imaging-with-controlled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, we conduct all our experiments using a single, consumer-level GPU to highlight the feasibility of our approach within resource-constrained environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-cardiac-imaging-with-controlled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-compatible driving partners through data-regularized self-play reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-compatible-driving-partners-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, incorporating realistic human agents is essential for scalable training and evaluation of autonomous driving systems in simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-compatible-driving-partners-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A diverse Multilingual News Headlines Dataset from around the World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-diverse-multilingual-news-headlines-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Babel Briefings is a novel dataset featuring 4. 7 million news headlines from August 2020 to November 2021, across 30 languages and 54 locations worldwide with English translations of all articles included.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-diverse-multilingual-news-headlines-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniParser: A Unified Framework for Text Spotting, Key Information Extraction and Table Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omniparser-a-unified-framework-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, visually-situated text parsing (VsTP) has experienced notable advancements, driven by the increasing demand for automated document understanding and the emergence of Generative Large Language Models (LLMs) capable of processing document-based questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omniparser-a-unified-framework-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Adversarial Data Collection by Supporting Annotators: Lessons from GAHD, a German Hate Speech Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adversarial-data-collection-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that the resulting dataset is challenging even for state-of-the-art hate speech detection models, and that training on GAHD clearly improves model robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adversarial-data-collection-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTracker: Recoverable Tracking via PN Tree Structured Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtracker-recoverable-tracking-via-pn-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Upon the PN tree memory, we develop corresponding walking rules for determining the state of the target and define a set of control flows to unite the tracker and the detector in different tracking scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtracker-recoverable-tracking-via-pn-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Effective Weakly-Supervised Action Segmentation via Action-Transition-Aware Boundary Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-effective-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly-supervised action segmentation is a task of learning to partition a long video into several action segments, where training videos are only accompanied by transcripts (ordered list of actions).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-effective-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling up ridge regression for brain encoding in a massive individual fMRI dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-ridge-regression-for-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper evaluates different parallelization techniques to reduce the training time of brain encoding with ridge regression on the CNeuroMod Friends dataset, one of the largest deep fMRI resource currently available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-ridge-regression-for-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSMamba: Remote Sensing Image Classification with State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsmamba-remote-sensing-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote sensing image classification forms the foundation of various understanding tasks, serving a crucial function in remote sensing image interpretation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsmamba-remote-sensing-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain-Shift: Unsupervised Pseudo-Healthy Brain Synthesis for Novel Biomarker Extraction in Chronic Subdural Hematoma</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-shift-unsupervised-pseudo-healthy-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deformation fields derived from this process are utilized to extract biomarkers that quantify the shift in the brain due to cSDH.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-shift-unsupervised-pseudo-healthy-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Stock: All we need is just a few fine-tuned models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-stock-all-we-need-is-just-a-few-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an efficient fine-tuning method for large pre-trained models, offering strong in-distribution (ID) and out-of-distribution (OOD) performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-stock-all-we-need-is-just-a-few-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J-CRe3: A Japanese Conversation Dataset for Real-world Reference Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/j-cre3-a-japanese-conversation-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding expressions that refer to the physical world is crucial for such human-assisting systems in the real world, as robots that must perform actions that are expected by users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/j-cre3-a-japanese-conversation-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane-Change in Dense Traffic with Model Predictive Control and Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lane-change-in-dense-traffic-with-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an online smooth-path lane-change control framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lane-change-in-dense-traffic-with-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPXGAT: An Attention based Deep Learning Model for Multiplex Graphs Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpxgat-an-attention-based-deep-learning-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph representation learning has rapidly emerged as a pivotal field of study.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpxgat-an-attention-based-deep-learning-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaijaHate: Evaluating Hate Speech Detection on Nigerian Twitter Using Representative Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naijahate-evaluating-hate-speech-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the global issue of hateful content proliferating in online platforms, hate speech detection (HSD) models are typically developed on datasets collected in the United States, thereby failing to generalize to English dialects from the Majority World.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naijahate-evaluating-hate-speech-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QNCD: Quantization Noise Correction for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qncd-quantization-noise-correction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have revolutionized image synthesis, setting new benchmarks in quality and creativity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qncd-quantization-noise-correction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change-Agent: Towards Interactive Comprehensive Change Interpretation and Analysis from Change Detection and Change Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-agent-towards-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monitoring changes in the Earth's surface is crucial for understanding natural processes and human impacts, necessitating precise and comprehensive interpretation methodologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-agent-towards-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering Misattributed Suicide Causes through Annotation Inconsistency Detection in Death Investigation Notes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-misattributed-suicide-causes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data accuracy is essential for scientific research and policy development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-misattributed-suicide-causes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Multimodal Video Paragraph Captioning Models Robust to Missing Modality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-multimodal-video-paragraph-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video paragraph captioning (VPC) involves generating detailed narratives for long videos, utilizing supportive modalities such as speech and event boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-multimodal-video-paragraph-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT: Exploiting Inter-Class Dynamics for Domain Adaptive Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-exploiting-inter-class-dynamics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Class-Aware Teacher (CAT) to address the class bias issue in the domain adaptation setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-exploiting-inter-class-dynamics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Lookup Tables for Efficient Image Retouching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-lookup-tables-for-efficient-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing enhancement models often optimize for high performance while falling short of reducing hardware inference time and power consumption, especially on edge devices with constrained computing and storage resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-lookup-tables-for-efficient-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Image Attribution for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models in RGB and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-image-attribution-for-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern text-to-image (T2I) diffusion models can generate images with remarkable realism and creativity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-image-attribution-for-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA-GS: Scale-Adaptive Gaussian Splatting for Training-Free Anti-Aliasing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-gs-scale-adaptive-gaussian-splatting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This integration is actually a limiting case of super-sampling, which significantly improves anti-aliasing performance over vanilla Gaussian Splatting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-gs-scale-adaptive-gaussian-splatting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Rank Rescaled Vision Transformer Fine-Tuning: A Residual Design Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-rescaled-vision-transformer-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning for pre-trained Vision Transformers aims to adeptly tailor a model to downstream tasks by learning a minimal set of new adaptation parameters while preserving the frozen majority of pre-trained parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-rank-rescaled-vision-transformer-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation tool for images of cracks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-tool-for-images-of-cracks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithms can be used for augmenting the capability of classical visual inspection of bridge structures, however, the implementation of such an algorithm requires a massive annotated training dataset, which is time-consuming to produce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-tool-for-images-of-cracks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-Adaptive and Geometric-Aware Keypoint Learning for Category-Level 6D Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-adaptive-and-geometric-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) The second design is a Geometric-Aware Feature Aggregation module, which can efficiently integrate the local and global geometric information into keypoint features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-adaptive-and-geometric-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Leaderboard Ranking = Top Coding Proficiency, Always? EvoEval: Evolving Coding Benchmarks via LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-leaderboard-ranking-top-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such limitations inevitably lead us to inquire: Is the leaderboard performance on existing benchmarks reliable and comprehensive enough to measure the program synthesis ability of LLMs?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-leaderboard-ranking-top-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Large Language Models Good at Utility Judgments?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-good-at-utility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) is considered to be a promising approach to alleviate the hallucination issue of large language models (LLMs), and it has received widespread attention from researchers recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-good-at-utility</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
