<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 09:18:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Federated Learning with Multi-Timescale Gradient Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-federated-learning-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key idea is to introduce distinct control variables to (i) correct the client gradient towards the group gradient, i. e., to reduce client model drift caused by local updates based on individual datasets, and (ii) correct the group gradient towards the global gradient, i. e., to reduce group model drift caused by FL over clients within the group.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-federated-learning-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruler: A Model-Agnostic Method to Control Generated Length for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ruler-a-model-agnostic-method-to-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, Ruler equips LLMs with the ability to generate responses of a specified length based on length constraints within the instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ruler-a-model-agnostic-method-to-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on the Honesty of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-the-honesty-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Honesty is a fundamental principle for aligning large language models (LLMs) with human values, requiring these models to recognize what they know and don't know and be able to faithfully express their knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-the-honesty-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When SAM2 Meets Video Camouflaged Object Segmentation: A Comprehensive Evaluation and Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-sam2-meets-video-camouflaged-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a comprehensive study on SAM2's ability in VCOS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-sam2-meets-video-camouflaged-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC: Efficient RRAM-aware NAS and Compilation for DNNs on Resource-Constrained Edge Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rnc-efficient-rram-aware-nas-and-compilation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting network architecture can be optimized for either high accuracy or low latency using a one-shot neural network approach with Pareto optimality achieved through the Non-dominated Sorted Genetic Algorithm II (NSGA-II).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rnc-efficient-rram-aware-nas-and-compilation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Policy Optimization for Constrained Allocation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-policy-optimization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Allocation tasks represent a class of problems where a limited amount of resources must be allocated to a set of entities at each time step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-policy-optimization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv8-ResCBAM: YOLOv8 Based on An Effective Attention Module for Pediatric Wrist Fracture Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov8-rescbam-yolov8-based-on-an-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wrist trauma and even fractures occur frequently in daily life, particularly among children who account for a significant proportion of fracture cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov8-rescbam-yolov8-based-on-an-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Diverse Device Heterogeneous Federated Learning via Task Arithmetic Knowledge Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-diverse-device-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This failure primarily stems from two issues: the dilution of informative logits from more capable devices by those from less capable ones, and the use of a single integrated logits as the distillation target across all devices, which neglects their individual learning capacities and and the unique contributions of each.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-diverse-device-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Visual Object Tracking through Visual Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-object-tracking-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PiVOT proposes a prompt generation network with the pre-trained foundation model CLIP to automatically generate and refine visual prompts, enabling the transfer of foundation model knowledge for tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-visual-object-tracking-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Semantic Ambiguity In Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation Via Probabilistic Prototypical Pixel Contrast</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-semantic-ambiguity-in-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptation aims to reduce the model degradation on the target domain caused by the domain shift between the source and target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-semantic-ambiguity-in-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-video Identity Correlating for Person Re-identification Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-video-identity-correlating-for-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, compared with the previous state-of-the-art~\cite{ISR}, CION with the same ResNet50-IBN achieves higher mAP of 93. 3\% and 74. 3\% on Market1501 and MSMT17, while only utilizing 8\% training samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-video-identity-correlating-for-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off to new Shores: A Dataset &amp; Benchmark for (near-)coastal Flood Inundation Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-to-new-shores-a-dataset-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Altogether, our dataset and benchmark provide a comprehensive platform for evaluating flood forecasts, enabling future solutions for this critical challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-to-new-shores-a-dataset-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCUBench: A Benchmark of Tiny Object Detectors on MCUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcubench-a-benchmark-of-tiny-object-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MCUBench, a benchmark featuring over 100 YOLO-based object detection models evaluated on the VOC dataset across seven different MCUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcubench-a-benchmark-of-tiny-object-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-Driven Temporal Domain Adaptation for Nighttime UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-driven-temporal-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the issue, this work proposes a prompt-driven temporal domain adaptation training framework to fully utilize temporal contexts for challenging nighttime UAV tracking, i. e., TDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-driven-temporal-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LW2G: Learning Whether to Grow for Prompt-based Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lw2g-learning-whether-to-grow-for-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To promote cross-task knowledge facilitation and form an effective and efficient prompt sets pool, we propose a plug-in module in the former stage to \textbf{Learn Whether to Grow (LW2G)} based on the disparities between tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lw2g-learning-whether-to-grow-for-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Convolution Neural Network with Optimized Pooling and Hyperparameter Tuning for Network Intrusion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-convolution-neural-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This demonstrates the effectiveness of EnCNN in real-time network intrusion detection, offering a robust solution for identifying and mitigating security threats, and enhancing overall network resilience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-convolution-neural-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MinerU: An Open-Source Solution for Precise Document Content Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineru-an-open-source-solution-for-precise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document content analysis has been a crucial research area in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineru-an-open-source-solution-for-precise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARLBench: Flexible and Efficient Benchmarking for Hyperparameter Optimization in Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arlbench-flexible-and-efficient-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the extensive and large-scale dataset on hyperparameter landscapes that our selection is based on, ARLBench is an efficient, flexible, and future-oriented foundation for research on AutoRL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arlbench-flexible-and-efficient-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CurricuLLM: Automatic Task Curricula Design for Learning Complex Robot Skills using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curricullm-automatic-task-curricula-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our core idea is that large language models (LLMs), with their extensive training on diverse language data and ability to encapsulate world knowledge, present significant potential for efficiently breaking down tasks and decomposing skills across various robotics environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curricullm-automatic-task-curricula-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AL-GTD: Deep Active Learning for Gaze Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/al-gtd-deep-active-learning-for-gaze-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, our goal is to reduce the reliance on the size of labeled training data for gaze target detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/al-gtd-deep-active-learning-for-gaze-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysGen: Rigid-Body Physics-Grounded Image-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physgen-rigid-body-physics-grounded-image-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PhysGen, a novel image-to-video generation method that converts a single image and an input condition (e. g., force and torque applied to an object in the image) to produce a realistic, physically plausible, and temporally consistent video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physgen-rigid-body-physics-grounded-image-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CycleNet: Enhancing Time Series Forecasting through Modeling Periodic Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclenet-enhancing-time-series-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The stable periodic patterns present in time series data serve as the foundation for conducting long-horizon forecasts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclenet-enhancing-time-series-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MG-Net: Learn to Customize QAOA with Circuit Depth Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-net-learn-to-customize-qaoa-with-circuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this dilemma, here we first analyze the convergence behavior of QAOA, uncovering the origins of this dilemma and elucidating the intricate relationship between the employed mixer Hamiltonian, the specific problem at hand, and the permissible maximum circuit depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-net-learn-to-customize-qaoa-with-circuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Underwater Image Enhancement with Physical-based Denoising Diffusion Implicit Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-enhancement-with-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underwater vision is crucial for autonomous underwater vehicles (AUVs), and enhancing degraded underwater images in real-time on a resource-constrained AUV is a key challenge due to factors like light absorption and scattering, or the sufficient model computational complexity to resolve such factors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/underwater-image-enhancement-with-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-guided topic modeling for interpretable privacy classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-guided-topic-modeling-for-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting and explaining the private information contained in an image in human-understandable terms is a complex and contextual task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-guided-topic-modeling-for-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do We Need Domain-Specific Embedding Models? An Empirical Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-need-domain-specific-embedding-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To account for the possibility that this drop is driven by FinMTEB's higher complexity, we propose four measures to quantify dataset complexity and control for this factor in our analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-we-need-domain-specific-embedding-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Open-Set Domain Generalization Using Evidential Bi-Level Hardest Domain Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-open-set-domain-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe that an adaptive domain scheduler benefits more in OSDG compared with prefixed sequential and random domain schedulers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-open-set-domain-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroPath: A Neural Pathway Transformer for Joining the Dots of Human Connectomes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuropath-a-neural-pathway-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although modern imaging technologies allow us to study connectivity between two distinct brain regions in-vivo, an in-depth understanding of how anatomical structure supports brain function and how spontaneous functional fluctuations emerge remarkable cognition is still elusive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuropath-a-neural-pathway-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkSAM: Fooling Segment Anything Model to Segment Nothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darksam-fooling-segment-anything-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the spatial domain, we disrupt the semantics of both the foreground and background in the image to confuse SAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darksam-fooling-segment-anything-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskLLM: Learnable Semi-Structured Sparsity for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskllm-learnable-semi-structured-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach facilitates end-to-end training on large-scale datasets and offers two notable advantages: 1) High-quality Masks - our method effectively scales to large datasets and learns accurate masks; 2) Transferability - the probabilistic modeling of mask distribution enables the transfer learning of sparsity across domains or tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskllm-learnable-semi-structured-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Modeling of Molecular Dynamics Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-molecular-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce generative modeling of molecular trajectories as a paradigm for learning flexible multi-task surrogate models of MD from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-molecular-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGN: The RNN's New Successor is Effective for Long-Range Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgn-the-rnn-s-new-successor-is-effective-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The other branch employs patches to capture short-term information and aggregate the global representation of the series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgn-the-rnn-s-new-successor-is-effective-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Pretraining for Cardiovascular Magnetic Resonance Cine Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, short-axis cine stacks of 296 subjects (90618 2D slices) were used for unlabeled pretraining with four SSP methods; SimCLR, positional contrastive learning, DINO, and masked image modeling (MIM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Prediction-Powered Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-prediction-powered-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To infer a function value on a specific point $x$, it is essential to assign higher weights to the points closer to $x$, which is called local polynomial / multivariable regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-prediction-powered-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting Regression Models for Conditional Uncertainty Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-regression-models-for-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal Prediction methods have finite-sample distribution-free marginal coverage guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-regression-models-for-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E.T. Bench: Towards Open-Ended Event-Level Video-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-t-bench-towards-open-ended-event-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bench (Event-Level & Time-Sensitive Video Understanding Benchmark), a large-scale and high-quality benchmark for open-ended event-level video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-t-bench-towards-open-ended-event-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harmful Fine-tuning Attacks and Defenses for Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harmful-fine-tuning-attacks-and-defenses-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We in this paper aim to clear some common concerns for the attack setting, and formally establish the research problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harmful-fine-tuning-attacks-and-defenses-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Hierarchy and Temporal Attention Guided Cross Masking for Self-supervised Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-hierarchy-and-temporal-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In self-supervised skeleton-based action recognition, the mask reconstruction paradigm is gaining interest in enhancing model refinement and robustness through effective masking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-hierarchy-and-temporal-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Efficient Deep Blind RAW Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-deep-blind-raw-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we tackle image restoration directly in the RAW domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-deep-blind-raw-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Proportion Detection for Optimized Data Management for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-proportion-detection-for-optimized-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated exceptional performance across a wide range of tasks and domains, with data preparation playing a critical role in achieving these results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-proportion-detection-for-optimized-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AQMLator -- An Auto Quantum Machine Learning E-Platform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aqmlator-an-auto-quantum-machine-learning-e</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A successful Machine Learning (ML) model implementation requires three main components: training dataset, suitable model architecture and training procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aqmlator-an-auto-quantum-machine-learning-e</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype based Masked Audio Model for Self-Supervised Learning of Sound Event Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-masked-audio-model-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant challenge in sound event detection (SED) is the effective utilization of unlabeled data, given the limited availability of labeled data due to high annotation costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-masked-audio-model-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimVG: A Simple Framework for Visual Grounding with Decoupled Multi-modal Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvg-a-simple-framework-for-visual-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual grounding is a common vision task that involves grounding descriptive sentences to the corresponding regions of an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvg-a-simple-framework-for-visual-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-intensity knowledge distillation for robust medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-intensity-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to incorporate joint shape-intensity prior information into the segmentation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-intensity-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Quantum Creep In: Designing Quantum Neural Network Models by Gradually Swapping Out Classical Components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-quantum-creep-in-designing-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To provide a more fine-grained characterisation of the impact of quantum components on the performance of neural networks, we propose a framework where classical neural network layers are gradually replaced by quantum layers that have the same type of input and output while keeping the flow of information between layers unchanged, different from most current research in quantum neural network, which favours an end-to-end quantum model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-quantum-creep-in-designing-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DMC-VB: A Benchmark for Representation Learning for Control with Visual Distractors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmc-vb-a-benchmark-for-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present theDeepMind Control Visual Benchmark (DMC-VB), a dataset collected in the DeepMind Control Suite to evaluate the robustness of offline RL agents for solving continuous control tasks from visual input in the presence of visual distractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dmc-vb-a-benchmark-for-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving logical and functional dependencies in synthetic tabular data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-logical-and-functional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the existing notion of functional dependencies, we introduce the notion of logical dependencies among the attributes in this article.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-logical-and-functional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-bottleneck-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent concept-based interpretable models have succeeded in providing meaningful explanations by pre-defined concept sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-bottleneck-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Wavelet Transformations for Generalizable Deepfake Forgery Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-wavelet-transformations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evolution of digital image manipulation, particularly with the advancement of deep generative models, significantly challenges existing deepfake detection methods, especially when the origin of the deepfake is obscure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-wavelet-transformations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Shortest Plank: Vulnerability-Aware Adversarial Training for Robust Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-shortest-plank-vulnerability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging these insights, we introduce the Vulnerability-aware Adversarial Training (VAT), designed to defend against poisoning attacks in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-shortest-plank-vulnerability</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
