<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 09:11:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Probing the 3D Awareness of Visual Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-3d-awareness-of-visual-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given that such models can classify, delineate, and localize objects in 2D, we ask whether they also represent their 3D structure?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-3d-awareness-of-visual-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Multi-System Multivariate Interconnection and Divergence Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-multi-system-multivariate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying outlier behavior among sensors and subsystems is essential for discovering faults and facilitating diagnostics in large systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-multi-system-multivariate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Quantification of Serial PET/CT Images for Pediatric Hodgkin Lymphoma Patients Using a Longitudinally-Aware Segmentation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-quantification-of-serial-pet-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For baseline segmentation, LAS-Net achieved a mean Dice score of 0. 772.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-quantification-of-serial-pet-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay Attention to Your Neighbours: Training-Free Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-attention-to-your-neighbours-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing approaches often rely on impractical supervised pre-training or access to additional pre-trained networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-attention-to-your-neighbours-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Physical-Digital Facial Attack Detection Via Simulating Spoofing Clues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-physical-digital-facial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SPSC and SDSC augment live samples into simulated attack samples by simulating spoofing clues of physical and digital attacks, respectively, which significantly improve the capability of the model to detect "unseen" attack types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-physical-digital-facial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning representations of learning representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ICLR conference is unique among the top machine learning conferences in that all submitted papers are openly available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaSagnA: Language-based Segmentation Assistant for Complex Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasagna-language-based-segmentation-assistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements have empowered Large Language Models for Vision (vLLMs) to generate detailed perceptual outcomes, including bounding boxes and masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasagna-language-based-segmentation-assistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Reset Policy Optimization for RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-reset-policy-optimization-for-rlhf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the fact that offline preference dataset provides informative states (i. e., data that is preferred by the labelers), our new algorithm, Dataset Reset Policy Optimization (DR-PO), integrates the existing offline preference dataset into the online policy training procedure via dataset reset: it directly resets the policy optimizer to the states in the offline dataset, instead of always starting from the initial state distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-reset-policy-optimization-for-rlhf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training Small Base LMs with Fewer Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-small-base-lms-with-fewer-tokens</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we show that smaller LMs trained utilizing some of the layers of GPT2-medium (355M) and GPT-2-large (770M) can effectively match the val loss of their bigger counterparts when trained from scratch for the same number of training steps on OpenWebText dataset with 9B tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-small-base-lms-with-fewer-tokens</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Visual Question Answering through Question-Driven Image Captions as Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-question-answering-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the impact of incorporating image captioning as an intermediary process within the VQA pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-visual-question-answering-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-free Boost for Open-Vocabulary Object Detection with Confidence Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-boost-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in the region-proposal stage, proposals that contain novel instances showcase lower objectness scores, since they are treated as background proposals during the training phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-boost-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Preference Sampling for Pareto Set Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-preference-sampling-for-pareto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Pareto Set Learning (PSL) has been proposed for learning the entire Pareto set using a neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-preference-sampling-for-pareto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Integration of Semantic and Structural Knowledge in Knowledge Graph Entity Typing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-integration-of-semantic-and-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Knowledge Graph Entity Typing (KGET) task aims to predict missing type annotations for entities in knowledge graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-integration-of-semantic-and-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperbolic Delaunay Geometric Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-delaunay-geometric-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperbolic machine learning is an emerging field aimed at representing data with a hierarchical structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-delaunay-geometric-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations for Face Forgery Detection via Adversarial Removal of Artifacts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-face-forgery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We verify the effectiveness of the proposed explanations from two aspects: (1) Counterfactual Trace Visualization: the enhanced forgery images are useful to reveal artifacts by visually contrasting the original images and two different visualization methods; (2) Transferable Adversarial Attacks: the adversarial forgery images generated by attacking the detection model are able to mislead other detection models, implying the removed artifacts are general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-face-forgery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathological Primitive Segmentation Based on Visual Foundation Model with Zero-Shot Mask Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathological-primitive-segmentation-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Primitive detection and segmentation in digitized tissue samples are essential for objective and automated diagnosis and prognosis of cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathological-primitive-segmentation-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large Scale Survey of Motivation in Software Development and Analysis of its Validity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-survey-of-motivation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, improvement analysis shows that an increase in most motivators predicts an increase in general motivation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-survey-of-motivation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Ambiguity from Perspective of Uncertainty Inference and Affinity Diversification for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-ambiguity-from-perspective-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When activating class objects, we argue that the false activation stems from the bias to the ambiguous regions during the feature extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-ambiguity-from-perspective-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoostTrack: boosting the similarity measure and detection confidence for improved multiple object tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-boosting-the-similarity-measure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To utilize low-detection score bounding boxes in one-stage association, we propose to boost the confidence scores of two groups of detections: the detections we assume to correspond to the existing tracked object, and the detections we assume to correspond to a previously undetected object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosttrack-boosting-the-similarity-measure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Language-Level Performance Disparity in mPLMs via Teacher Language Selection and Cross-lingual Self-Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-language-level-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we introduce ALSACE to leverage the learned knowledge from the well-performing languages to guide under-performing ones within the same mPLM, eliminating the need for additional labeled multilingual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-language-level-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct May Not Be the Best: An Incremental Evolution View of Pose Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-may-not-be-the-best-an-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with this challenge, we propose a fine-grained incremental evolution centered pose generation framework, rather than traditional direct one-to-one in a rush.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-may-not-be-the-best-an-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Multi-Domain Recommendation: an Automatic Domain Feature Extraction and Personalized Integration Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-domain-recommendation-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, by personalized integration of domain features from other domains for each user and the innovation in the training mode, the DFEI framework can yield more accurate conversion identification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-domain-recommendation-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Continuous Sign Language Recognition with Adapted Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continuous-sign-language-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, fully fine-tuning the model easily forgets the generic essential knowledge acquired in the pretraining stage and overfits the downstream data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-continuous-sign-language-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Interactive LLM Serving with Proxy Model-based Sequence Length Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-interactive-llm-serving-with-proxy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been driving a new wave of interactive AI applications across numerous domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-interactive-llm-serving-with-proxy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoPE: Mixture of Prefix Experts for Zero-Shot Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mope-mixture-of-prefix-experts-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot dialogue state tracking (DST) transfers knowledge to unseen domains, reducing the cost of annotating new datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mope-mixture-of-prefix-experts-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Image Modeling as a Framework for Self-Supervised Learning across Eye Movements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-as-a-framework-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make sense of their surroundings, intelligent systems must transform complex sensory inputs to structured codes that are reduced to task-relevant information such as object category.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-as-a-framework-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TBSN: Transformer-Based Blind-Spot Network for Self-Supervised Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbsn-transformer-based-blind-spot-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For channel self-attention, we observe that it may leak the blind-spot information when the channel number is greater than spatial size in the deep layers of multi-scale architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tbsn-transformer-based-blind-spot-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AmpleGCG: Learning a Universal and Transferable Generative Model of Adversarial Suffixes for Jailbreaking Both Open and Closed LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplegcg-learning-a-universal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we utilize those successful suffixes as training data to learn a generative model, named AmpleGCG, which captures the distribution of adversarial suffixes given a harmful query and enables the rapid generation of hundreds of suffixes for any harmful queries in seconds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplegcg-learning-a-universal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SFSORT: Scene Features-based Simple Online Real-Time Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfsort-scene-features-based-simple-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces SFSORT, the world's fastest multi-object tracking system based on experiments conducted on MOT Challenge datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sfsort-scene-features-based-simple-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any2Point: Empowering Any-modality Large Models for Efficient 3D Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any2point-empowering-any-modality-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adapter incorporates prior spatial knowledge from the source modality to guide the local feature aggregation of 3D tokens, compelling the semantic adaption of any-modality transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any2point-empowering-any-modality-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoticIA: A Clickbait Article Summarization Dataset in Spanish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noticia-a-clickbait-article-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present NoticIA, a dataset consisting of 850 Spanish news articles featuring prominent clickbait headlines, each paired with high-quality, single-sentence generative summarizations written by humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noticia-a-clickbait-article-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nostra Domina at EvaLatin 2024: Improving Latin Polarity Detection through Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nostra-domina-at-evalatin-2024-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes submissions from the team Nostra Domina to the EvaLatin 2024 shared task of emotion polarity detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nostra-domina-at-evalatin-2024-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homography Guided Temporal Fusion for Road Line and Marking Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homography-guided-temporal-fusion-for-road-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable segmentation of road lines and markings is critical to autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homography-guided-temporal-fusion-for-road-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroNCAP: Photorealistic Closed-loop Safety Testing for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroncap-photorealistic-closed-loop-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a versatile NeRF-based simulator for testing autonomous driving (AD) software systems, designed with a focus on sensor-realistic closed-loop evaluation and the creation of safety-critical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroncap-photorealistic-closed-loop-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Self-Supervision for Single-View Scene Completion via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-self-supervision-for-single-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to fuse the scene reconstruction from multiple images and distill this knowledge into a more accurate single-view scene reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-self-supervision-for-single-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Concept Drift Detection based on Parallel Activations of Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-concept-drift-detection-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Practical applications of artificial intelligence increasingly often have to deal with the streaming properties of real data, which, considering the time factor, are subject to phenomena such as periodicity and more or less chaotic degeneration - resulting directly in the concept drifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-concept-drift-detection-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Completion in the Dark: Completing Vertebrae Morphology from 3D Ultrasound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-completion-in-the-dark-completing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: Ultrasound (US) imaging, while advantageous for its radiation-free nature, is challenging to interpret due to only partially visible organs and a lack of complete 3D information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-completion-in-the-dark-completing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable All-pole Filters for Time-varying Audio Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-all-pole-filters-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infinite impulse response filters are an essential building block of many time-varying audio systems, such as audio effects and synthesisers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-all-pole-filters-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global versus Local: Evaluating AlexNet Architectures for Tropical Cyclone Intensity Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-versus-local-evaluating-alexnet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first model, trained on the entire dataset, is called the global AlexNet model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-versus-local-evaluating-alexnet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIMAT: Decentralized Iterative Merging-And-Training for Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimat-decentralized-iterative-merging-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This DIMAT paradigm presents a new opportunity for the future decentralized learning, enhancing its adaptability to real-world with sparse and light-weight communication and computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dimat-decentralized-iterative-merging-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMAFF-PSN: A Residual Multi-Scale Attention Feature Fusion Photometric Stereo Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmaff-psn-a-residual-multi-scale-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting accurate normal maps of objects from two-dimensional images in regions of complex structure and spatial material variations is challenging using photometric stereo methods due to the influence of surface reflection properties caused by variations in object geometry and surface materials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmaff-psn-a-residual-multi-scale-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive-Based Deep Embeddings for Label Noise-Resilient Histopathology Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-based-deep-embeddings-for-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep learning have proven highly effective in medical image classification, notably within histopathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-based-deep-embeddings-for-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Vehicle Motion Planning Generalize to Realistic Long-tail Scenarios?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-vehicle-motion-planning-generalize-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assess existing state-of-the-art planners on our benchmark and show that neither rule-based nor learning-based planners can safely navigate the interPlan scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-vehicle-motion-planning-generalize-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-driven pulmonary arteries and veins segmentation reveals demography-associated pulmonary vasculature anatomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-driven-pulmonary-arteries-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we propose a High-abundant Pulmonary Artery-vein Segmentation (HiPaS) framework achieving accurate artery-vein segmentation on both non-contrast CT and CTPA across various spatial resolutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-driven-pulmonary-arteries-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Robust Soft Baby Robot With Rich Interaction Ability for Advanced Machine Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-robust-soft-baby-robot-with-rich</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe one of the reasons for this is the disconnect between traditional robotic design and the properties needed for open-ended, creativity-based AI systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-robust-soft-baby-robot-with-rich</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferable and Principled Efficiency for Open-Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-and-principled-efficiency-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of efficient OVS, we target achieving performance that is comparable to or even better than prior OVS works based on large vision-language foundation models, by utilizing smaller models that incur lower training costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferable-and-principled-efficiency-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLoCO: Learning Long Contexts Offline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lloco-learning-long-contexts-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLoCO, a technique that combines context compression, retrieval, and parameter-efficient finetuning using LoRA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lloco-learning-long-contexts-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comments as Natural Logic Pivots: Improve Code Generation via Comment Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comments-as-natural-logic-pivots-improve-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we suggest that code comments are the natural logic pivot between natural language and code language and propose using comments to boost the code generation ability of code LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comments-as-natural-logic-pivots-improve-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnnoCTR: A Dataset for Detecting and Linking Entities, Tactics, and Techniques in Cyber Threat Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annoctr-a-dataset-for-detecting-and-linking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our few-shot scenario, we find that for identifying the MITRE ATT&CK concepts that are mentioned explicitly or implicitly in a text, concept descriptions from MITRE ATT&CK are an effective source for training data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annoctr-a-dataset-for-detecting-and-linking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DesignQA: A Multimodal Benchmark for Evaluating Large Language Models' Understanding of Engineering Documentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designqa-a-multimodal-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces DesignQA, a novel benchmark aimed at evaluating the proficiency of multimodal large language models (MLLMs) in comprehending and applying engineering requirements in technical documentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designqa-a-multimodal-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
