<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 21:06:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Sparse Visual Prompt for Cross-domain Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-sparse-visual-prompt-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a novel Sparse Visual Domain Prompts (SVDP) approach tailored for addressing domain shift problems in semantic segmentation, which holds minimal discrete trainable parameters (e. g. 10\%) of the prompt and reserves more spatial information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-sparse-visual-prompt-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-centric Artificial Intelligence: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-artificial-intelligence-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) is making a profound impact in almost every domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-centric-artificial-intelligence-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memotion 3: Dataset on sentiment and emotion analysis of codemixed Hindi-English Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memotion-3-dataset-on-sentiment-and-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Memes are the new-age conveyance mechanism for humor on social media sites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memotion-3-dataset-on-sentiment-and-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering mesoscopic descriptions of collective movement with neural stochastic modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-mesoscopic-descriptions-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collective motion is an ubiquitous phenomenon in nature, inspiring engineers, physicists and mathematicians to develop mathematical models and bio-inspired designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-mesoscopic-descriptions-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Update-to-Data Ratio: Minimizing World Model Overfitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-update-to-data-ratio-minimizing-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early stopping based on the validation set performance is a popular approach to find the right balance between under- and overfitting in the context of supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-update-to-data-ratio-minimizing-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Dimensional Approximate Nearest Neighbor Search: with Reliable and Efficient Distance Comparison Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-approximate-nearest-neighbor-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Approximate K nearest neighbor (AKNN) search is a fundamental and challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dimensional-approximate-nearest-neighbor-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scribble-Supervised RGB-T Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribble-supervised-rgb-t-salient-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further polish the expanded labels, we propose a prediction module to alleviate the sharpness of boundary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribble-supervised-rgb-t-salient-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Dehazing via a Multi-Range Temporal Alignment Network with Physical Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-dehazing-via-a-multi-range-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video dehazing aims to recover haze-free frames with high visibility and contrast.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-dehazing-via-a-multi-range-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Length of Stay Prediction Based on Multi-modal Data towards Trustworthy Human-AI Collaboration in Radiomics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hospital-length-of-stay-prediction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To what extent can the patient's length of stay in a hospital be predicted using only an X-ray image?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hospital-length-of-stay-prediction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCE-Calib: Automatic LiDAR-Frame/Event Camera Extrinsic Calibration With A Globally Optimal Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lce-calib-automatic-lidar-frame-event-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an automatic checkerboard-based approach to calibrate extrinsics between a LiDAR and a frame/event camera, where four contributions are presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lce-calib-automatic-lidar-frame-event-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configurable EBEN: Extreme Bandwidth Extension Network to enhance body-conducted speech capture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/configurable-eben-extreme-bandwidth-extension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EBEN leverages a configurable multiband decomposition of the raw captured signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/configurable-eben-extreme-bandwidth-extension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding why shooters shoot -- An AI-powered engine for basketball performance profiling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-why-shooters-shoot-an-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is crucial that the performance profiles can reflect the diverse playstyles, as well as the fast-changing dynamics of the game.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-why-shooters-shoot-an-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust probabilistic inference via a constrained transport metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-probabilistic-inference-via-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach finds applications in a wide variety of robust inference problems, where we intend to perform inference on the parameters associated with the centering distribution in presence of outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-probabilistic-inference-via-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SE-GSL: A General and Effective Graph Structure Learning Framework through Structural Entropy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-gsl-a-general-and-effective-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are de facto solutions to structural data learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/se-gsl-a-general-and-effective-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mCPT at SemEval-2023 Task 3: Multilingual Label-Aware Contrastive Pre-Training of Transformers for Few- and Zero-shot Framing Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcpt-at-semeval-2023-task-3-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the winning system for the zero-shot Spanish framing detection task, which also achieves competitive places in eight additional languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcpt-at-semeval-2023-task-3-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeDoM: Training-Free Energy-Guided Conditional Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freedom-training-free-energy-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a training-Free conditional Diffusion Model (FreeDoM) used for various conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freedom-training-free-energy-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Graph-based Spatial Consistency for Robust Non-rigid Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-graph-based-spatial-consistency-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first design a local spatial consistency measure over the deformation graph of the point cloud, which evaluates the spatial compatibility only between the correspondences in the vicinity of a graph node.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-graph-based-spatial-consistency-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Scene Completion with Cleaner Self</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-scene-completion-with-cleaner-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SSC is a well-known ill-posed problem as the prediction model has to "imagine" what is behind the visible surface, which is usually represented by Truncated Signed Distance Function (TSDF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-scene-completion-with-cleaner-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-path Adaptation from Image to Video Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-path-adaptation-from-image-to-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we efficiently transfer the surpassing representation power of the vision foundation models, such as ViT and Swin, for video understanding with only a few trainable parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-path-adaptation-from-image-to-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Continual Learning Framework with General Parameter-Efficient Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-continual-learning-framework-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The "pre-training $\rightarrow$ downstream adaptation" presents both new opportunities and challenges for Continual Learning (CL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-continual-learning-framework-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distill n' Explain: explaining graph neural networks using simple surrogates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-n-explain-explaining-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose FastDnX, a faster version of DnX that leverages the linear decomposition of our surrogate model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distill-n-explain-explaining-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Recipe for Watermarking Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recipe-for-watermarking-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this regard, watermarking has been a proven solution for copyright protection and content monitoring, but it is underexplored in the DMs literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-recipe-for-watermarking-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effects of Self-supervision and Contrastive Alignment in Deep Multi-view Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effects-of-self-supervision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we present DeepMVC, a unified framework for deep MVC that includes many recent methods as instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effects-of-self-supervision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical-Hyperplane Kernels for Actively Learning Gaussian Process Models of Nonstationary Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-hyperplane-kernels-for-actively</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning methods that are used to produce the surrogate model should therefore address these problems by providing a scheme to keep the number of queries small, e. g. by using active learning and be able to capture the nonlinear and nonstationary properties of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-hyperplane-kernels-for-actively</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Structure Pruning for Compressing CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-structure-pruning-for-compressing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel structure pruning method, termed as dynamic structure pruning, to identify optimal pruning granularities for intra-channel pruning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-structure-pruning-for-compressing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiGeo: Discriminative Geometry-Aware Learning for Generalized Few-Shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digeo-discriminative-geometry-aware-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalized few-shot object detection aims to achieve precise detection on both base classes with abundant annotations and novel classes with limited training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digeo-discriminative-geometry-aware-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLOPER4D: A Scene-Aware Dataset for Global 4D Human Pose Estimation in Urban Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sloper4d-a-scene-aware-dataset-for-global-4d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SLOPER4D, a novel scene-aware dataset collected in large urban environments to facilitate the research of global human pose estimation (GHPE) with human-scene interaction in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sloper4d-a-scene-aware-dataset-for-global-4d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hubs and Hyperspheres: Reducing Hubness and Improving Transductive Few-shot Learning with Hyperspherical Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hubs-and-hyperspheres-reducing-hubness-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distance-based classification is frequently used in transductive few-shot learning (FSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hubs-and-hyperspheres-reducing-hubness-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning for Amalgamation: A Multi-Source Transfer Learning Framework For Sentiment Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-for-amalgamation-a-multi-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transfer learning plays an essential role in Deep Learning, which can remarkably improve the performance of the target domain, whose training data is not sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-for-amalgamation-a-multi-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TypeT5: Seq2seq Type Inference using Static Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/typet5-seq2seq-type-inference-using-static</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been growing interest in automatically predicting missing type annotations in programs written in Python and JavaScript.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/typet5-seq2seq-type-inference-using-static</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting discrete-time bifurcations with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-discrete-time-bifurcations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we train a deep learning classifier to provide an EWS for the five local discrete-time bifurcations of codimension-1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-discrete-time-bifurcations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Clutter in Radar Data -- Label Generation and Detection Using PointNet++</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-clutter-in-radar-data-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because there is no suitable public data set in which clutter is annotated, we design a method to automatically generate the respective labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-clutter-in-radar-data-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FateZero: Fusing Attentions for Zero-shot Text-based Video Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatezero-fusing-attentions-for-zero-shot-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also have a better zero-shot shape-aware editing ability based on the text-to-video model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatezero-fusing-attentions-for-zero-shot-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Intel Neuromorphic DNS Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-intel-neuromorphic-dns-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A critical enabler for progress in neuromorphic computing research is the ability to transparently evaluate different neuromorphic solutions on important tasks and to compare them to state-of-the-art conventional solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-intel-neuromorphic-dns-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExoplANNET: A deep learning algorithm to detect and identify planetary signals in radial velocity data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exoplannet-a-deep-learning-algorithm-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a neural network is proposed to replace the computation of the significance of the signal detected with the radial velocity method and to classify it as of planetary origin or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exoplannet-a-deep-learning-algorithm-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyVBMC: Efficient Bayesian inference in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyvbmc-efficient-bayesian-inference-in-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyVBMC is a Python implementation of the Variational Bayesian Monte Carlo (VBMC) algorithm for posterior and model inference for black-box computational models (Acerbi, 2018, 2020).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyvbmc-efficient-bayesian-inference-in-python</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effectively Modeling Time Series with Simple Discrete State Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effectively-modeling-time-series-with-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For expressivity, we propose a new SSM parameterization based on the companion matrix -- a canonical representation for discrete-time processes -- which enables SpaceTime's SSM layers to learn desirable autoregressive processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effectively-modeling-time-series-with-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving a Better Stability-Plasticity Trade-off via Auxiliary Networks in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-a-better-stability-plasticity-trade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to the natural capabilities of humans to learn new tasks in a sequential fashion, neural networks are known to suffer from catastrophic forgetting, where the model's performances on old tasks drop dramatically after being optimized for a new task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-a-better-stability-plasticity-trade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Logic Specifications for Soft Policy Guidance in POMCP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-logic-specifications-for-soft-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we use inductive logic programming to learn logic specifications from traces of POMCP executions, i. e., sets of belief-action pairs generated by the planner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-logic-specifications-for-soft-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BanglaCoNER: Towards Robust Bangla Complex Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-bangla-complex-named-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named Entity Recognition (NER) is a fundamental task in natural language processing that involves identifying and classifying named entities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-bangla-complex-named-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Distance to Class Centroids and Outlier Discounting for Improved Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-distance-to-class-centroids-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new approach for addressing the challenge of training machine learning models in the presence of noisy labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-distance-to-class-centroids-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Metric Learning for Unsupervised Remote Sensing Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-metric-learning-for-unsupervised-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This loss is motivated by the principle of metric learning where we simultaneously maximize the distance between change pair-wise pixels while minimizing the distance between no-change pair-wise pixels in bi-temporal image domain and their deep feature domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-metric-learning-for-unsupervised-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among Us: Adversarially Robust Collaborative Perception by Consensus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/among-us-adversarially-robust-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This leads to our hypothesize-and-verify framework: perception results with and without collaboration from a random subset of teammates are compared until reaching a consensus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/among-us-adversarially-robust-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataflow graphs as complete causal graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataflow-graphs-as-complete-causal-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Component-based development is one of the core principles behind modern software engineering practices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataflow-graphs-as-complete-causal-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Benchmark: On the Utility of Synthetic Data with Blender for Bare Supervised Learning and Downstream Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-benchmark-on-the-utility-of-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we use the simulation-to-reality adaptation as a downstream task for comparing the transferability between synthetic and real data when used for pre-training, which demonstrates that synthetic data pre-training is also promising to improve real test results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-benchmark-on-the-utility-of-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FindView: Precise Target View Localization Task for Look Around Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findview-precise-target-view-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increase in demands for service robots and automated inspection, agents need to localize in its surrounding environment to achieve more natural communication with humans by shared contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/findview-precise-target-view-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Model Ensemble in Transfer-based Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-model-ensemble-in-transfer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transfer-based adversarial attacks attract tremendous attention as they can identify the weaknesses of deep learning models in a black-box manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-model-ensemble-in-transfer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoLo-CAM: Class Activation Mapping for Object Co-Localization in Weakly-Labeled Unconstrained Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-cam-class-activation-mapping-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although results are promising, objects are assumed to have minimal movement leading to degradation in performance for relatively long-term dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colo-cam-class-activation-mapping-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Post-Processing for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-post-processing-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose using a diffusion model as a post-processing approach, and we introduce Low-light Post-processing Diffusion Model (LPDM) in order to model the conditional distribution between under-exposed and normally-exposed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-post-processing-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Enhancement for Remote Photoplethysmography in a Low-Light Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-enhancement-for-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using collected dataset, we found 1) face detection algorithm cannot detect faces in video captured in low light conditions; 2) A decrease in the amplitude of the pulsatile signal will lead to the noise signal to be in the dominant position; and 3) the chrominance-based method suffers from the limitation in the assumption about skin-tone will not hold, and Green and ICA method receive less influence than POS in dark illuminance environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-enhancement-for-remote</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
