<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 09:16:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ARTS: Semi-Analytical Regressor using Disentangled Skeletal Representations for Human Mesh Recovery from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arts-semi-analytical-regressor-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, to fully utilize these representations, we introduce a semi-analytical regressor to estimate the parameters of the human mesh model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arts-semi-analytical-regressor-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Cross-lingual Emotion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a detailed system description of our entry for the WASSA 2024 Task 2, focused on cross-lingual emotion detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Spectral Bias of Deep Neural Networks by Multi-Grade Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-spectral-bias-of-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) suffer from the spectral bias, wherein DNNs typically exhibit a tendency to prioritize the learning of lower-frequency components of a function, struggling to capture its high-frequency features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-spectral-bias-of-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Habaek: High-performance water segmentation through dataset expansion and inductive bias optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/habaek-high-performance-water-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study highlights the need to enhance structures and include datasets for effective water segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/habaek-high-performance-water-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CompassJudger-1: All-in-one Judge Model Helps Model Evaluation and Evolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compassjudger-1-all-in-one-judge-model-helps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we introduce \textbf{CompassJudger-1}, the first open-source \textbf{all-in-one} judge LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compassjudger-1-all-in-one-judge-model-helps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TALoS: Enhancing Semantic Scene Completion via Test-time Adaptation on the Line of Sight</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talos-enhancing-semantic-scene-completion-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic Scene Completion (SSC) aims to perform geometric completion and semantic segmentation simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talos-enhancing-semantic-scene-completion-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erasing Undesirable Concepts in Diffusion Models with Adversarial Preservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-undesirable-concepts-in-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A practical solution is to selectively removing target concepts from the model, but this may impact the remaining concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erasing-undesirable-concepts-in-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepVigor+: Scalable and Accurate Semi-Analytical Fault Resilience Analysis for Deep Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepvigor-scalable-and-accurate-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantifying the reliability of emerging ML models, including Deep Neural Networks (DNNs), is highly complex due to their enormous size in terms of the number of parameters and computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepvigor-scalable-and-accurate-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Filtering: Adaptive Image-Text Quality Enhancement for MLLM Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-filtering-adaptive-image-text-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A critical factor in training MLLMs is the quality of image-text pairs within multimodal pretraining datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-filtering-adaptive-image-text-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Object Hallucination via Concentric Causal Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-object-hallucination-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the long-term decay in RoPE, LVLMs tend to hallucinate more when relevant visual cues are distant from instruction tokens in the multimodal input sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-object-hallucination-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Deep Feature Reconstruction for Logical and Structural Industrial Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-feature-reconstruction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further enhance DFR into a unified framework, called ULSAD, which is capable of detecting both structural and logical anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-feature-reconstruction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiMTR: Time Series Motion Prediction for Diverse Road Users through Multimodal Feature Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limtr-time-series-motion-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the behavior of road users accurately is crucial to enable the safe operation of autonomous vehicles in urban or densely populated areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limtr-time-series-motion-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The effect of fine-tuning on language model toxicity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-fine-tuning-on-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning language models has become increasingly popular following the proliferation of open models and improvements in cost-effective parameter efficient fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-fine-tuning-on-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-GANTex: 3D Face Reconstruction with StyleGAN3-based Multi-View Images and 3DDFA based Mesh Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-gantex-3d-face-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper tries to tackle this problem by introducing a novel method for texture estimation from a single image by first using StyleGAN and 3D Morphable Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-gantex-3d-face-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient System for Automatic Map Storytelling -- A Case Study on Historical Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-system-for-automatic-map</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the recent advance of GPT-4 in text recognition and map captioning, it still has a limited understanding of maps, as its performance wanes when texts (e. g., titles and legends) in maps are missing or inaccurate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-system-for-automatic-map</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural GaLore: Accelerating GaLore for memory-efficient LLM Training and Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-galore-accelerating-galore-for-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate memory usage, alternative methods like Parameter-Efficient-Fine-Tuning (PEFT) and GaLore approximate weights or optimizer states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-galore-accelerating-galore-for-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMHaze: Intensity-aware Image Dehazing with a Large-scale Multi-intensity Real Haze Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmhaze-intensity-aware-image-dehazing-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LMHaze comprises paired hazy and haze-free images captured in diverse indoor and outdoor environments, spanning multiple scenarios and haze intensities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmhaze-intensity-aware-image-dehazing-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RM-Bench: Benchmarking Reward Models of Language Models with Subtlety and Style</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-bench-benchmarking-reward-models-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this approach fails to assess reward models on subtle but critical content changes and variations in style, resulting in a low correlation with policy model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-bench-benchmarking-reward-models-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RANSAC Back to SOTA: A Two-stage Consensus Filtering for Real-time 3D Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ransac-back-to-sota-a-two-stage-consensus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, one-point RANSAC obtains a consensus set based on length consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ransac-back-to-sota-a-two-stage-consensus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1-bit AI Infra: Part 1.1, Fast and Lossless BitNet b1.58 Inference on CPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1-bit-ai-infra-part-1-1-fast-and-lossless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in 1-bit Large Language Models (LLMs), such as BitNet and BitNet b1. 58, present a promising approach to enhancing the efficiency of LLMs in terms of speed and energy consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1-bit-ai-infra-part-1-1-fast-and-lossless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning and Data Augmentation for Detecting Self-Admitted Technical Debt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-and-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the performance of these approaches remains suboptimal, particularly for specific types of SATD, such as test and requirement debt, primarily due to extremely imbalanced datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-and-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CausalGraph2LLM: Evaluating LLMs for Causal Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalgraph2llm-evaluating-llms-for-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a comprehensive benchmark, \emph{CausalGraph2LLM}, encompassing a variety of causal graph settings to assess the causal graph understanding capability of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causalgraph2llm-evaluating-llms-for-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflection-Bench: probing AI intelligence with reflection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflection-bench-probing-ai-intelligence-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to adapt beliefs or behaviors in response to unexpected outcomes, reflection, is fundamental to intelligent systems' interaction with the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflection-bench-probing-ai-intelligence-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) based LLM Systems from PDFs: An Experience Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an experience report on the development of Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) systems using PDF documents as the primary data source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-retrieval-augmented-generation-rag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compute-Constrained Data Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compute-constrained-data-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data selection can reduce the amount of training data needed to finetune LLMs; however, the efficacy of data selection scales directly with its compute.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compute-constrained-data-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROMPTHEUS: A Human-Centered Pipeline to Streamline SLRs with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptheus-a-human-centered-pipeline-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we developed \textit{PROMPTHEUS}: an AI-driven pipeline solution that automates the SLR process using Large Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptheus-a-human-centered-pipeline-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Griffon-G: Bridging Vision-Language and Vision-Centric Tasks via Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/griffon-g-bridging-vision-language-and-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[None of the LMMs have yet comprehensively unified both types of tasks within a single model, as seen in Large Language Models in the natural language processing field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/griffon-g-bridging-vision-language-and-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arithmetic Transformers Can Length-Generalize in Both Operand Length and Count</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arithmetic-transformers-can-length-generalize</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers often struggle with length generalization, meaning they fail to generalize to sequences longer than those encountered during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arithmetic-transformers-can-length-generalize</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM2.5-StepProver: Advancing Automated Theorem Proving via Expert Iteration on Large-Scale LEAN Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm2-5-stepprover-advancing-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to use large scale LEAN problem datasets Lean-workbook for expert iteration with more than 20, 000 CPU days.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm2-5-stepprover-advancing-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who's Who: Large Language Models Meet Knowledge Conflicts in Practice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-s-who-large-language-models-meet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To analyze how current large language models (LLMs) align with our recommendation, we introduce WhoQA, a public benchmark dataset to examine model's behavior in knowledge conflict situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-s-who-large-language-models-meet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMPLE: Emotion-Aware Multimodal Fusion Prompt Learning for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ample-emotion-aware-multimodal-fusion-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, this paper introduces Emotion-\textbf{A}ware \textbf{M}ultimodal Fusion \textbf{P}rompt \textbf{L}\textbf{E}arning (\textbf{AMPLE}) framework to address the above issue by combining text sentiment analysis with multimodal data and hybrid prompt templates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ample-emotion-aware-multimodal-fusion-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theoretical Insights into Line Graph Transformation on Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-insights-into-line-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Line graph transformation has been widely studied in graph theory, where each node in a line graph corresponds to an edge in the original graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/theoretical-insights-into-line-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPE-Pro: A Structure-Sensitive Deep Learning Model for Protein Representation and Origin Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpe-pro-a-structure-sensitive-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on works in structure prediction, We developed a structure-sensitive supervised deep learning model, Crystal vs Predicted Evaluator for Protein Structure (CPE-Pro), to represent and discriminate the origin of protein structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpe-pro-a-structure-sensitive-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforced Imitative Trajectory Planning for Urban Automated Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-imitative-trajectory-planning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning (RL) faces challenges in trajectory planning for urban automated driving due to the poor convergence of RL and the difficulty in designing reward functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-imitative-trajectory-planning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoTrain: No-code training for state-of-the-art models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotrain-no-code-training-for-state-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AutoTrain Advanced is an open-source library providing best practices for training models on custom datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotrain-no-code-training-for-state-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiOn-XA: Unsupervised Domain Adaptation via LiDAR-Only Cross-Modal Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lion-xa-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose LiOn-XA, an unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) approach that combines LiDAR-Only Cross-Modal (X) learning with Adversarial training for 3D LiDAR point cloud semantic segmentation to bridge the domain gap arising from environmental and sensor setup changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lion-xa-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMART: Self-learning Meta-strategy Agent for Reasoning Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-self-learning-meta-strategy-agent-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This inefficiency raises the question: Can LMs learn to select the optimal strategy in the first attempt, without a need for refinement?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-self-learning-meta-strategy-agent-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Knowledge Editing Really Correct Hallucinations?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-knowledge-editing-really-correct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) suffer from hallucinations, referring to the non-factual information in generated content, despite their superior capacities across tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-knowledge-editing-really-correct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging CORAL-Correlation Consistency Network for Semi-Supervised Left Atrium MRI Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-coral-correlation-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diverging from previous methods focused on each local pixel value, the CORAL-Correlation Consistency Module (CCM) in the CORN leverages second-order statistical information to capture global structural features by minimizing the distribution discrepancy between labeled and unlabeled samples in feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-coral-correlation-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenMU: Your Swiss Army Knife for Music Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmu-your-swiss-army-knife-for-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present OpenMU-Bench, a large-scale benchmark suite for addressing the data scarcity issue in training multimodal language models to understand music.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openmu-your-swiss-army-knife-for-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PALMS: Plane-based Accessible Indoor Localization Using Mobile Smartphones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palms-plane-based-accessible-indoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present PALMS, an innovative indoor global localization and relocalization system for mobile smartphones that utilizes publicly available floor plans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palms-plane-based-accessible-indoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CamI2V: Camera-Controlled Image-to-Video Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cami2v-camera-controlled-image-to-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Epipolar attention is proposed for modeling all cross-frame relationships from a novel perspective of noised condition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cami2v-camera-controlled-image-to-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Pathology Foundation Models: Adaptation Strategies and Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-pathology-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we benchmark four pathology-specific foundation models across 14 datasets and two scenarios-consistency assessment and flexibility assessment-addressing diverse adaptation scenarios and downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-pathology-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Approach to Solving SMAC Task: Generating Decision Tree Code from Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-approach-to-solving-smac-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[StarCraft Multi-Agent Challenge (SMAC) is one of the most commonly used experimental environments in multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL), where the specific task is to control a set number of allied units to defeat enemy forces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-approach-to-solving-smac-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Combating Frequency Simplicity-biased Learning for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-combating-frequency-simplicity-biased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the theoretical justification of models' biased learning behavior on different spatial frequency components, which is based on the dataset frequency properties, we argue that the learning behavior on various frequency components could be manipulated by changing the dataset statistical structure in the Fourier domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-combating-frequency-simplicity-biased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pruning Foundation Models for High Accuracy without Retraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pruning-foundation-models-for-high-accuracy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with this problem, post-training pruning methods are proposed to prune LLMs in one-shot without retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pruning-foundation-models-for-high-accuracy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-InternVL: A Flexible-Transfer Pocket Multimodal Model with 5% Parameters and 90% Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-internvl-a-flexible-transfer-pocket</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have demonstrated impressive performance in vision-language tasks across a broad spectrum of domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-internvl-a-flexible-transfer-pocket</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing and Mitigating the Local Pattern Shortcuts of Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-and-mitigating-the-local-pattern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have advanced significantly due to the attention mechanism, but their quadratic complexity and linear memory demands limit their performance on long-context tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-and-mitigating-the-local-pattern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM2Long: Enhancing SAM 2 for Long Video Segmentation with a Training-Free Memory Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2long-enhancing-sam-2-for-long-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from its heuristic search design, SAM2Long is robust toward occlusions and object reappearances, and can effectively segment and track objects for complex long-term videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2long-enhancing-sam-2-for-long-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Rewiring for Editable Graph Neural Network Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-rewiring-for-editable-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first observe the gradient of cross-entropy loss for the target node and training nodes with significant inconsistency, which indicates that directly fine-tuning the base model using the loss on the target node deteriorates the performance on training nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-rewiring-for-editable-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
