<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 09:17:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FlowReasoner: Reinforcing Query-Level Meta-Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowreasoner-reinforcing-query-level-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a query-level meta-agent named FlowReasoner to automate the design of query-level multi-agent systems, i. e., one system per user query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowreasoner-reinforcing-query-level-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KGMEL: Knowledge Graph-Enhanced Multimodal Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgmel-knowledge-graph-enhanced-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most existing MEL methods overlook the rich structural information available in the form of knowledge-graph (KG) triples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgmel-knowledge-graph-enhanced-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M$^2$AD: Multi-Sensor Multi-System Anomaly Detection through Global Scoring and Calibrated Thresholding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-2-ad-multi-sensor-multi-system-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce M$^2$AD, a framework for unsupervised anomaly detection in multivariate time series data from multiple systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-2-ad-multi-sensor-multi-system-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Effective Can Dropout Be in Multiple Instance Learning ?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-effective-can-dropout-be-in-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the gigapixel resolution of WSI, applications of MIL in WSI typically necessitate a two-stage training scheme: first, extract features from the pre-trained backbone and then perform MIL aggregation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-effective-can-dropout-be-in-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSpec: Relevance and Specificity Grounded Online Filtering for Learning on Video-Text Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/respec-relevance-and-specificity-grounded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Relevance and Specificity-based online filtering framework (ReSpec) that selects data based on four criteria: (i) modality alignment for clean data, (ii) task relevance for target focused data, (iii) specificity for informative and detailed data, and (iv) efficiency for low-latency processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/respec-relevance-and-specificity-grounded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Document Retrieval with G-Retriever</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-document-retrieval-with-g-retriever</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an enhanced approach that replaces the PCST method with an attention-based sub-graph construction technique, enabling more efficient and context-aware retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-document-retrieval-with-g-retriever</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-aware Forgetting Compensation for Exemplar-Free Lifelong Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-forgetting-compensation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve these issues, we propose a novel Distribution-aware Forgetting Compensation (DAFC) model that explores cross-domain shared representation learning and domain-specific distribution integration without using old exemplars or knowledge distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-forgetting-compensation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll the dice &amp; look before you leap: Going beyond the creative limits of next-token prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roll-the-dice-look-before-you-leap-going</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design a suite of minimal algorithmic tasks that are a loose abstraction of open-ended real-world tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roll-the-dice-look-before-you-leap-going</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIV-FlowDiffuser:Transfer-learning-based denoising diffusion models for PIV</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piv-flowdiffuser-transfer-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the special noise step-by-step, we employ a denoising diffusion model~(FlowDiffuser) for PIV analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/piv-flowdiffuser-transfer-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Large Vision-Language Models on Fine-Grained Image Tasks: A Comprehensive Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-vision-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) have demonstrated remarkable multimodal perception capabilities, garnering significant attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-large-vision-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuGaze: Reshaping the future BCI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neugaze-reshaping-the-future-bci</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional brain-computer interfaces (BCIs), reliant on costly electroencephalography or invasive implants, struggle with complex human-computer interactions due to setup complexity and limited precision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neugaze-reshaping-the-future-bci</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-Guided Clothing Warping for Virtual Try-On</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-guided-clothing-warping-for-virtual-try</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their promising performance, these methods often lack precise control over fine details, leading to inconsistencies in shape between clothing and the person's body as well as distortions in exposed limb regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-guided-clothing-warping-for-virtual-try</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyEdit2: An Easy-to-use Steering Framework for Editing Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyedit2-an-easy-to-use-steering-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we provide a demo video at https://zjunlp. github. io/project/EasyEdit2/video for a quick introduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyedit2-an-easy-to-use-steering-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSANET: A Hybrid Self-Cross Attention Network For Remote Sensing Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsanet-a-hybrid-self-cross-attention-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The remote sensing image change detection task is an essential method for large-scale monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsanet-a-hybrid-self-cross-attention-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation with Noisy Labels via Spatially Correlated Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-with-noisy-labels-via-spatially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in many practical scenarios such as medical imaging and remote sensing, obtaining true annotations is not straightforward and usually requires significant human labor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-with-noisy-labels-via-spatially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Summation: Min-Form Credit Assignment Is All Process Reward Model Needs for Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-summation-min-form-credit-assignment-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we identify the main cause of PRM-induced reward hacking: the canonical summation-form credit assignment in reinforcement learning (RL), which defines the value as cumulative gamma-decayed future rewards, easily induces LLMs to hack steps with high rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-summation-min-form-credit-assignment-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni3C: Unifying Precisely 3D-Enhanced Camera and Human Motion Controls for Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3c-unifying-precisely-3d-enhanced-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we present Uni3C, a unified 3D-enhanced framework for precise control of both camera and human motion in video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3c-unifying-precisely-3d-enhanced-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RainbowPlus: Enhancing Adversarial Prompt Generation via Evolutionary Quality-Diversity Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rainbowplus-enhancing-adversarial-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) exhibit remarkable capabilities but are susceptible to adversarial prompts that exploit vulnerabilities to produce unsafe or biased outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rainbowplus-enhancing-adversarial-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Judges as Evaluators: The JETTS Benchmark of LLM-as-Judges as Test-Time Scaling Evaluators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-judges-as-evaluators-the-jetts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling test-time computation, or affording a generator large language model (LLM) extra compute during inference, typically employs the help of external non-generative evaluators (i. e., reward models).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-judges-as-evaluators-the-jetts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRUST-Bench: A Comprehensive Benchmark for C-to-safe-Rust Transpilation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crust-bench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-c</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CRUST-Bench, a dataset of 100 C repositories, each paired with manually-written interfaces in safe Rust as well as test cases that can be used to validate correctness of the transpilation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crust-bench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-c</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRAVE: A Conflicting Reasoning Approach for Explainable Claim Verification Using LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crave-a-conflicting-reasoning-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose CRAVE, a Conflicting Reasoning Approach for explainable claim VErification, that verify the complex claims based on the conflicting rationales reasoned by large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crave-a-conflicting-reasoning-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring $\ell_0$ Sparsification for Inference-free Sparse Retrievers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-ell-0-sparsification-for-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With increasing demands for efficiency, information retrieval has developed a branch of sparse retrieval, further advancing towards inference-free retrieval where the documents are encoded during indexing time and there is no model-inference for queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-ell-0-sparsification-for-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing the Patent Matching Capability of Large Language Models via the Memory Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-patent-matching-capability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose MemGraph, a method that augments the patent matching capabilities of LLMs by incorporating a memory graph derived from their parametric memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-the-patent-matching-capability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DialogueAgents: A Hybrid Agent-Based Speech Synthesis Framework for Multi-Party Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogueagents-a-hybrid-agent-based-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech synthesis is crucial for human-computer interaction, enabling natural and intuitive communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dialogueagents-a-hybrid-agent-based-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAPIP3D: Tracking Any Point in Persistent 3D Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tapip3d-tracking-any-point-in-persistent-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce TAPIP3D, a novel approach for long-term 3D point tracking in monocular RGB and RGB-D videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tapip3d-tracking-any-point-in-persistent-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoWag: A Unified Framework for Shape Preserving Compression of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nowag-a-unified-framework-for-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) exhibit remarkable performance across various natural language processing tasks but suffer from immense computational and memory demands, limiting their deployment in resource-constrained environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nowag-a-unified-framework-for-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seurat: From Moving Points to Depth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seurat-from-moving-points-to-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate depth estimation from monocular videos remains challenging due to ambiguities inherent in single-view geometry, as crucial depth cues like stereopsis are absent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seurat-from-moving-points-to-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO2: The Desktop AgentOS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufo2-the-desktop-agentos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent Computer-Using Agents (CUAs), powered by multimodal large language models (LLMs), offer a promising direction for automating complex desktop workflows through natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufo2-the-desktop-agentos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTIRE 2025 Challenge on Real-World Face Restoration: Methods and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2025-challenge-on-real-world-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides a review of the NTIRE 2025 challenge on real-world face restoration, highlighting the proposed solutions and the resulting outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2025-challenge-on-real-world-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTIRE 2025 Challenge on Image Super-Resolution ($\times$4): Methods and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2025-challenge-on-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the NTIRE 2025 image super-resolution ($\times$4) challenge, one of the associated competitions of the 10th NTIRE Workshop at CVPR 2025.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ntire-2025-challenge-on-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Parameter Interference in Model Merging via Sharpness-Aware Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-parameter-interference-in-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, several research efforts have been made on merging these large models into a single multi-task model, particularly with simple arithmetic on parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-parameter-interference-in-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUDO: Enhancing Text-to-Image Diffusion Models with Self-Supervised Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sudo-enhancing-text-to-image-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Self-sUpervised Direct preference Optimization (SUDO), a novel paradigm that optimizes both fine-grained details at the pixel level and global image quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sudo-enhancing-text-to-image-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Vision LLMs Road-Ready? A Comprehensive Benchmark for Safety-Critical Driving Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-llms-road-ready-a-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on 14 SOTA VLLMs, ranging from 0. 5B to 72B parameters, reveal significant performance gaps, with no model achieving over 40% accuracy, highlighting critical limitations in understanding complex driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-llms-road-ready-a-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaZero-Edu: Making AlphaZero Accessible to Everyone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphazero-edu-making-alphazero-accessible-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed significant progress in reinforcement learning, especially with Zero-like paradigms, which have greatly boosted the generalization and reasoning abilities of large-scale language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphazero-edu-making-alphazero-accessible-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SG-Reg: Generalizable and Efficient Scene Graph Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-reg-generalizable-and-efficient-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It significantly outperforms the hand-crafted baseline in terms of registration success rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sg-reg-generalizable-and-efficient-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk is Not Always Cheap: Promoting Wireless Sensing Models with Text Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talk-is-not-always-cheap-promoting-wireless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wireless signal-based human sensing technologies, such as WiFi, millimeter-wave (mmWave) radar, and Radio Frequency Identification (RFID), enable the detection and interpretation of human presence, posture, and activities, thereby providing critical support for applications in public security, healthcare, and smart environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talk-is-not-always-cheap-promoting-wireless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstruction of angular correlations in the associated top quark and the dark matter mediator production</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruction-of-angular-correlations-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the process of single top quark production within the "simplified model" with a scalar dark matter mediator, a new variable based on angular correlations was presented, for the proper reconstruction of which it is necessary to separate the contributions of two undetectable particles: the neutrino and the mediator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstruction-of-angular-correlations-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Powered Domain Generalization and Domain Adaptation: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-powered-domain-generalization-and-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As machine learning evolves, domain generalization (DG) and domain adaptation (DA) have become crucial for enhancing model robustness across diverse environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-powered-domain-generalization-and-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SphereDiff: Tuning-free Omnidirectional Panoramic Image and Video Generation via Spherical Latent Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spherediff-tuning-free-omnidirectional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend MultiDiffusion to spherical latent space and propose a spherical latent sampling method to enable direct use of pretrained diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spherediff-tuning-free-omnidirectional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-attention for State-based model RWKV-7</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-for-state-based-model-rwkv-7</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CrossWKV, a novel cross-attention mechanism for the state-based RWKV-7 model, designed to enhance the expressive power of text-to-image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-for-state-based-model-rwkv-7</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teach Me How to Denoise: A Universal Framework for Denoising Multi-modal Recommender Systems via Guided Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teach-me-how-to-denoise-a-universal-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, MMRecs struggle with noisy data caused by misalignment among modal content and the gap between modal semantics and recommendation semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teach-me-how-to-denoise-a-universal-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Template-Based Financial Report Generation in Agentic and Decomposed Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-based-financial-report-generation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tailoring structured financial reports from companies' earnings releases is crucial for understanding financial performance and has been widely adopted in real-world analytics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-based-financial-report-generation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unconstrained Monotonic Calibration of Predictions in Deep Ranking Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unconstrained-monotonic-calibration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ranking models primarily focus on modeling the relative order of predictions while often neglecting the significance of the accuracy of their absolute values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unconstrained-monotonic-calibration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Consensus Prompting for Co-Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-consensus-prompting-for-co-salient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our VCP aims to induce the frozen foundation model to perform better on CoSOD tasks by formulating task-specific visual consensus prompts with minimized tunable parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-consensus-prompting-for-co-salient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiGUI-R1: Advancing Multimodal GUI Agents from Reactive Actors to Deliberative Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infigui-r1-advancing-multimodal-gui-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have begun exploring reasoning in GUI tasks with encouraging results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infigui-r1-advancing-multimodal-gui-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explainable Fake Image Detection with Multi-Modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-fake-image-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Progress in image generation raises significant public security concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explainable-fake-image-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know Me, Respond to Me: Benchmarking LLMs for Dynamic User Profiling and Personalized Responses at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-me-respond-to-me-benchmarking-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope that PERSONAMEM, along with the user profile and conversation simulation pipeline, can facilitate future research in the development of truly user-aware chatbots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/know-me-respond-to-me-benchmarking-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCIA: Federated Collaborative Information Aggregation for Privacy-Preserving Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcia-federated-collaborative-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this new paradigm, we introduce the federated collaborative information aggregation (FedCIA) method for privacy-preserving recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcia-federated-collaborative-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DrugGen enhances drug discovery with large language models and reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/druggen-enhances-drug-discovery-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One promising algorithm is DrugGPT, a transformer-based model, that generates small molecules for input protein sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/druggen-enhances-drug-discovery-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Scale-Aware Low-Light Enhancement via Structure-Guided Transformer Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-aware-low-light-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from employing pre-trained models for the extraction of semantics or illumination maps, we choose to extract robust structure priors based on illumination-invariant edge detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-aware-low-light-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
