<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 21:08:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PriorLane: A Prior Knowledge Enhanced Lane Detection Approach Based on Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priorlane-a-prior-knowledge-enhanced-lane</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More importantly, this paper proposes a novel and general framework called PriorLane, which is used to enhance the segmentation performance of the fully vision transformer by introducing the low-cost local prior knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priorlane-a-prior-knowledge-enhanced-lane</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ÚFAL CorPipe at CRAC 2022: Effectivity of Multilingual Models for Coreference Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufal-corpipe-at-crac-2022-effectivity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe the winning submission to the CRAC 2022 Shared Task on Multilingual Coreference Resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufal-corpipe-at-crac-2022-effectivity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4DenoiseNet: Adverse Weather Denoising from Adjacent Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4denoisenet-adverse-weather-denoising-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliable point cloud data is essential for perception tasks \textit{e. g.} in robotics and autonomous driving applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4denoisenet-adverse-weather-denoising-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morphology-Aware Interactive Keypoint Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphology-aware-interactive-keypoint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fully automate this procedure, deep-learning-based methods have been widely proposed and have achieved high performance in detecting keypoints in medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphology-aware-interactive-keypoint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-Guided Multi-Contrast Deep Unfolding Network for MRI Super-resolution Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-guided-multi-contrast-deep-unfolding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretable neural network models are of significant interest since they enhance the trustworthiness required in clinical practice when dealing with medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-guided-multi-contrast-deep-unfolding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Round-trip Translation for Automatic Machine Translation Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-round-trip-translation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the reference-based evaluation paradigm is widely used in many machine translation tasks, it is difficult to be applied to translation with low-resource languages, as those languages suffer from a deficiency of corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-round-trip-translation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Marker-free Extrinsic Camera Calibration using Person Keypoint Detections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-marker-free-extrinsic-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The person keypoint detections from multiple views are received at a central backend where they are synchronized, filtered, and assigned to person hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-marker-free-extrinsic-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Error Analysis for Document-level Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-error-analysis-for-document-level-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document-level information extraction (IE) tasks have recently begun to be revisited in earnest using the end-to-end neural network techniques that have been successful on their sentence-level IE counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-error-analysis-for-document-level-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold-Start Data Selection for Few-shot Language Model Fine-tuning: A Prompt-Based Uncertainty Propagation Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-start-data-selection-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose PATRON, a new method that uses prompt-based uncertainty estimation for data selection for pre-trained language model fine-tuning under cold-start scenarios, i. e., no initial labeled data are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-start-data-selection-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CommunityLM: Probing Partisan Worldviews from Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communitylm-probing-partisan-worldviews-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As political attitudes have diverged ideologically in the United States, political speech has diverged lingusitically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communitylm-probing-partisan-worldviews-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HarDNet-DFUS: An Enhanced Harmonically-Connected Network for Diabetic Foot Ulcer Image Segmentation and Colonoscopy Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardnet-dfus-an-enhanced-harmonically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The codes are available on https://github. com/kytimmylai/DFUC2022 (for Diabetic Foot Ulcers Segmentation) and https://github. com/YuWenLo/HarDNet-DFUS (for Colonoscopy Polyp Segmentation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardnet-dfus-an-enhanced-harmonically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NU-net: An Unpretentious Nested U-net for Breast Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nu-net-an-unpretentious-nested-u-net-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, variable tumor morphology, blurred boundary, and similar intensity distributions bring challenges for accurate segmentation of breast tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nu-net-an-unpretentious-nested-u-net-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M^4I: Multi-modal Models Membership Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-4i-multi-modal-models-membership-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, we propose Multi-modal Models Membership Inference (M^4I) with two attack methods to infer the membership status, named metric-based (MB) M^4I and feature-based (FB) M^4I, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-4i-multi-modal-models-membership-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Langevin Autoencoders for Learning Deep Latent Variable Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-autoencoders-for-learning-deep-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the ALD, we also present a new deep latent variable model named the Langevin autoencoder (LAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-autoencoders-for-learning-deep-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Temporal Densely Connected Recurrent Network for Event-based Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-temporal-densely-connected-recurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By this recurrent architecture, we can explicitly model not only the sequential but also non-sequential geometric consistency across time steps to accumulate information from previous frames to recover the entire human bodies, achieving a stable and accurate human pose estimation from event data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-temporal-densely-connected-recurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Masked Autoencoders for Medical Vision-and-Language Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-masked-autoencoders-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we conduct further analysis to better verify the effectiveness of different components of our approach and various settings of pre-training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-masked-autoencoders-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEQGAN: Learning the Loss Function for PINNs with Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deqgan-learning-the-loss-function-for-pinns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solutions to differential equations are of significant scientific and engineering relevance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deqgan-learning-the-loss-function-for-pinns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-distilled Feature Aggregation for Self-supervised Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distilled-feature-aggregation-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this problem, we propose the Self-Distilled Feature Aggregation (SDFA) module for simultaneously aggregating a pair of low-scale and high-scale features and maintaining their contextual consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distilled-feature-aggregation-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Is Flat: A Seq2Seq Generative Framework for Various Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-is-flat-a-seq2seq-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy the KG structure information loss from the "flat" text, we further improve the input representations of entities and relations, and the inference algorithm in KG-S2S.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-is-flat-a-seq2seq-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Recognition with Deep Nearest Centroids</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-with-deep-nearest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We devise deep nearest centroids (DNC), a conceptually elegant yet surprisingly effective network for large-scale visual recognition, by revisiting Nearest Centroids, one of the most classic and simple classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-with-deep-nearest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answering Count Questions with Structured Answers from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answering-count-questions-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we address the challenging case of answering count queries in web search, such as ``number of songs by John Lennon''.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answering-count-questions-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Edge Displacement Vaserstein Distance on UD Parsing Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-edge-displacement-vaserstein-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We contribute to the discussion on parsing performance in NLP by introducing a measurement that evaluates the differences between the distributions of edge displacement (the directed distance of edges) seen in training and test data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-edge-displacement-vaserstein-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iFlipper: Label Flipping for Individual Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iflipper-label-flipping-for-individual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose an approximate linear programming algorithm and provide theoretical guarantees on how close its result is to the optimal solution in terms of the number of label flips.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iflipper-label-flipping-for-individual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TempoWiC: An Evaluation Benchmark for Detecting Meaning Shift in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tempowic-an-evaluation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we present TempoWiC, a new benchmark especially aimed at accelerating research in social media-based meaning shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tempowic-an-evaluation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Transformations for Cross-lingual Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-transformations-for-cross-lingual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper deals with cross-lingual sentiment analysis in Czech, English and French languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-transformations-for-cross-lingual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIPHY: Probing "Visible" Physical Commonsense Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viphy-probing-visible-physical-commonsense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While such tasks measure the requisite knowledge to ground and reason over a given visual instance, they do not, however, measure the ability of VLMs to retain and generalize such knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viphy-probing-visible-physical-commonsense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Update Projection Approach to Safe Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-update-projection-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to previous safe RL methods, CUP enjoys the benefits of 1) CUP generalizes the surrogate functions to generalized advantage estimator (GAE), leading to strong empirical performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-update-projection-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AssembleRL: Learning to Assemble Furniture from Their Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assemblerl-learning-to-assemble-furniture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of simulation environments has enabled learning-based approaches for assembly planning, which is otherwise a labor-intensive and daunting task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assemblerl-learning-to-assemble-furniture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Solve 3D Vision Tasks Starting from A 2D Vision Transformer?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-solve-3d-vision-tasks-starting-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers (ViTs) have proven to be effective, in solving 2D image understanding tasks by training over large-scale image datasets; and meanwhile as a somehow separate track, in modeling the 3D visual world too such as voxels or point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-solve-3d-vision-tasks-starting-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPACE-3: Unified Dialog Model Pre-training for Task-Oriented Dialog Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/space-3-unified-dialog-model-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To capture the structured dialog semantics, we pre-train the dialog understanding module via a novel tree-induced semi-supervised contrastive learning objective with the help of extra dialog annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/space-3-unified-dialog-model-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Evaluate Performance of Multi-modal Semantic Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-evaluate-performance-of-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we analyze the SeLo performance of RS cross-modal retrieval models in detail, explore the impact of different variables on this task, and provide a complete benchmark for the SeLo task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-evaluate-performance-of-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Find Strong Summary Coherence Measures? A Toolbox and a Comparative Study for Summary Coherence Measure Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-find-strong-summary-coherence-measures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While none of the currently available automatic coherence measures are able to assign reliable coherence scores to system summaries across all evaluation metrics, large-scale language models fine-tuned on self-supervised tasks show promising results, as long as fine-tuning takes into account that they need to generalize across different summary lengths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-find-strong-summary-coherence-measures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImageArg: A Multi-modal Tweet Dataset for Image Persuasiveness Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagearg-a-multi-modal-tweet-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing interest in developing corpora of persuasive texts has promoted applications in automated systems, e. g., debating and essay scoring systems; however, there is little prior work mining image persuasiveness from an argumentative perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagearg-a-multi-modal-tweet-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classical Sequence Match is a Competitive Few-Shot One-Class Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classical-sequence-match-is-a-competitive-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, transformer-based models gradually become the default choice for artificial intelligence pioneers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classical-sequence-match-is-a-competitive-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few Clean Instances Help Denoising Distant Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-clean-instances-help-denoising-distant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing distantly supervised relation extractors usually rely on noisy data for both model training and evaluation, which may lead to garbage-in-garbage-out systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-clean-instances-help-denoising-distant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Inference Prompts for Zero-shot Emotion Classification in Text across Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-inference-prompts-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This raises the question how to prompt a natural language inference model for zero-shot learning emotion classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-inference-prompts-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landmark-free Statistical Shape Modeling via Neural Flow Deformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmark-free-statistical-shape-modeling-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Statistical shape modeling aims at capturing shape variations of an anatomical structure that occur within a given population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmark-free-statistical-shape-modeling-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Visual Prompt: Unifying Distributional Control of Pre-Trained Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-visual-prompt-unifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate how PromptGen can control several generative models (e. g., StyleGAN2, StyleNeRF, diffusion autoencoder, and NVAE) using various off-the-shelf models: (1) with the CLIP model, PromptGen can sample images guided by text, (2) with image classifiers, PromptGen can de-bias generative models across a set of attributes, and (3) with inverse graphics models, PromptGen can sample images of the same identity in different poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-visual-prompt-unifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Lifecycle Management in Evolving Input Distributions for Learning-based Aerospace Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-lifecycle-management-in-evolving-input</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithms within this framework are evaluated based on (1) model performance throughout mission lifetime and (2) cumulative costs associated with labeling and model retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-lifecycle-management-in-evolving-input</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflectance-Oriented Probabilistic Equalization for Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflectance-oriented-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in image enhancement, it remains difficult for existing approaches to adaptively improve the brightness and contrast for both low-light and normal-light images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflectance-oriented-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reflectance-Guided, Contrast-Accumulated Histogram Equalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflectance-guided-contrast-accumulated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing image enhancement methods fall short of expectations because with them it is difficult to improve global and local image contrast simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reflectance-guided-contrast-accumulated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAAP-440 Dataset and Baseline for Neural Architecture Accuracy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naap-440-dataset-and-baseline-for-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regression algorithms are a common tool to predicting a candidate architecture's accuracy, which can dramatically accelerate the search procedure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naap-440-dataset-and-baseline-for-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevNet: Self-supervised Monocular Depth Learning via Density Volume Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/devnet-self-supervised-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised depth learning from monocular images normally relies on the 2D pixel-wise photometric relation between temporally adjacent image frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/devnet-self-supervised-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fragility of Multi-Treebank Parsing Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fragility-of-multi-treebank-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Treebank selection for parsing evaluation and the spurious effects that might arise from a biased choice have not been explored in detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fragility-of-multi-treebank-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCDSN-DC: An Accurate and Lightweight Convolutional Neural Network for Stereo Estimation with Depth Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcdsn-dc-an-accurate-and-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method extends FC-DCNN by improving the feature extractor, adding a network structure for training highly accurate similarity functions and a network structure for filling inconsistent disparity estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcdsn-dc-an-accurate-and-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Comment Generation via Multi-Pass Deliberation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-comment-generation-via-multi-pass</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we treat the comment of the retrieved code as the initial draft and input it with the code and keywords into DECOM to start the iterative deliberation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-comment-generation-via-multi-pass</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSFool: Crafting High-quality Adversarial Time Series through Multi-objective Optimization to Fool Recurrent Neural Network Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsfool-crafting-high-quality-adversarial-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, an efficient and widely applicable approach called TSFool for crafting high-quality adversarial time series for the RNN classifier is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsfool-crafting-high-quality-adversarial-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jointly Contrastive Representation Learning on Road Network and Trajectory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointly-contrastive-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike the existing cross-scale contrastive learning methods on graphs that only contrast a graph and its belonging nodes, the contrast between road segment and trajectory is elaborately tailored via novel positive sampling and adaptive weighting strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jointly-contrastive-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order-Disorder: Imitation Adversarial Attacks for Black-box Neural Ranking Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-disorder-imitation-adversarial-attacks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose an imitation adversarial attack on black-box neural passage ranking models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-disorder-imitation-adversarial-attacks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Combines Paraphrase: Teaching Pre-trained Models to Understand Rare Biomedical Words</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-combines-paraphrase-teaching-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt-based fine-tuning for pre-trained models has proven effective for many natural language processing tasks under few-shot settings in general domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-combines-paraphrase-teaching-pre</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
