<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:10:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>This is Your AI on Peer Pressure: An Observational Study of Inter-Agent Social Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-is-your-ai-on-peer-pressure-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When AI agents converse, do they influence each other like humans do?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-is-your-ai-on-peer-pressure-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MinosEval: Distinguishing Factoid and Non-Factoid for Tailored Open-Ended QA Evaluation with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minoseval-distinguishing-factoid-and-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-ended question answering (QA) is a key task for evaluating the capabilities of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minoseval-distinguishing-factoid-and-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConLID: Supervised Contrastive Learning for Low-Resource Language Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conlid-supervised-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language identification (LID) is a critical step in curating multilingual LLM pretraining corpora from web crawls.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conlid-supervised-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acoustic Waveform Inversion with Image-to-Image Schrödinger Bridges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoustic-waveform-inversion-with-image-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the issue by employing a Schr\"odinger Bridge that interpolates between the distributions of ground truth and smoothed velocity models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acoustic-waveform-inversion-with-image-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimizing Structural Vibrations via Guided Flow Matching Design Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimizing-structural-vibrations-via-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The flow matching model and its training data implicitly define the design space, enabling a broader exploration of potential solutions as no optimization of manually-defined design parameters is required.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimizing-structural-vibrations-via-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sampling 3D Molecular Conformers with Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-3d-molecular-conformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion Transformers (DiTs) have demonstrated strong performance in generative modeling, particularly in image synthesis, making them a compelling choice for molecular conformer generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-3d-molecular-conformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiscRec: Disentangled Semantic-Collaborative Modeling for Generative Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrec-disentangled-semantic-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative recommendation is emerging as a powerful paradigm that directly generates item predictions, moving beyond traditional matching-based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrec-disentangled-semantic-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capturing Polysemanticity with PRISM: A Multi-Concept Feature Description Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-polysemanticity-with-prism-a-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated interpretability research aims to identify concepts encoded in neural network features to enhance human understanding of model behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capturing-polysemanticity-with-prism-a-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Vector Quantization with Distributional Matching: A Theoretical and Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-vector-quantization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training instability arises from the gradient discrepancy introduced by the straight-through estimator, especially in the presence of significant quantization errors, while codebook collapse occurs when only a small subset of code vectors are utilized during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-vector-quantization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Graph Anomaly Detection via Robust Homophily Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-graph-anomaly-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AdaFreq learns a set of adaptive spectral filters that capture different frequency components of the labeled normal nodes with varying homophily in the channel-wise and cross-channel views of node attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-graph-anomaly-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender Inclusivity Fairness Index (GIFI): A Multilevel Framework for Evaluating Gender Diversity in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-inclusivity-fairness-index-gifi-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a comprehensive evaluation of gender fairness in large language models (LLMs), focusing on their ability to handle both binary and non-binary genders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gender-inclusivity-fairness-index-gifi-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show-o2: Improved Native Unified Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o2-improved-native-unified-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on a language model, autoregressive modeling and flow matching are natively applied to the language head and flow head, respectively, to facilitate text token prediction and image/video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o2-improved-native-unified-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SonicVerse: Multi-Task Learning for Music Feature-Informed Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonicverse-multi-task-learning-for-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detailed captions that accurately reflect the characteristics of a music piece can enrich music databases and drive forward research in music AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonicverse-multi-task-learning-for-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Loss Functions in Recommender Systems: A Comparative Study with a Rényi Divergence-Based Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-loss-functions-in-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work conducts comprehensive analyses of these losses, yielding significant insights: 1) Common strengths -- both can be viewed as augmentations of traditional losses with Distributional Robust Optimization (DRO), enhancing robustness to distributional shifts; 2) Respective limitations -- stemming from their use of different distribution distance metrics in DRO optimization, SL exhibits high sensitivity to false negative instances, whereas CCL suffers from low data utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-loss-functions-in-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Caching to Accelerate Your Off-the-Shelf Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-caching-to-accelerate-your-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based image generation models excel at producing high-quality synthetic content, but suffer from slow and computationally expensive inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-caching-to-accelerate-your-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing point cloud analysis via neighbor aggregation correction based on cross-stage structure correlation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-point-cloud-analysis-via-neighbor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud analysis is the cornerstone of many downstream tasks, among which aggregating local structures is the basis for understanding point cloud data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-point-cloud-analysis-via-neighbor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Step Diffusion for Detail-Rich and Temporally Consistent Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-diffusion-for-detail-rich-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After consistency learning, we fix the CFR and C-LoRA modules and train a Detail-LoRA (D-LoRA) to enhance spatial details while aligning with the temporal space defined by C-LoRA to keep temporal coherence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-diffusion-for-detail-rich-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel-level Certified Explanations via Randomized Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-level-certified-explanations-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Post-hoc attribution methods aim to explain deep learning predictions by highlighting influential input pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixel-level-certified-explanations-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COSMMIC: Comment-Sensitive Multimodal Multilingual Indian Corpus for Summarization and Headline Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmmic-comment-sensitive-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite progress in comment-aware multimodal and multilingual summarization for English and Chinese, research in Indian languages remains limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmmic-comment-sensitive-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Chest X-ray Classification in Latent Space with Homomorphically Encrypted Neural Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-chest-x-ray-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We approximate the activation functions with lower-degree polynomials to balance the accuracy and efficiency in compliance with HE requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-chest-x-ray-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeurAgenix: Leveraging LLMs for Solving Complex Combinatorial Optimization Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heuragenix-leveraging-llms-for-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heuristic algorithms play a vital role in solving combinatorial optimization (CO) problems, yet traditional designs depend heavily on manual expertise and struggle to generalize across diverse instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heuragenix-leveraging-llms-for-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classification of Multi-Parametric Body MRI Series Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-multi-parametric-body-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results indicate that in both the internal and external datasets, the DenseNet-121 model attains high accuracy for the task of classifying 8 body MRI series types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-multi-parametric-body-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentGroupChat-V2: Divide-and-Conquer Is What LLM-Based Multi-Agent System Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentgroupchat-v2-divide-and-conquer-is-what</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model based multi-agent systems have demonstrated significant potential in social simulation and complex task resolution domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentgroupchat-v2-divide-and-conquer-is-what</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Bugs in Data Visualization Libraries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-bugs-in-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, a good understanding of the unique characteristics of bugs in DataViz libraries is essential for researchers and developers to detect and fix bugs in DataViz libraries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-bugs-in-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC: Adaptive BayesNet Structure Learning for Computational Scalable Multi-task Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abc-adaptive-bayesnet-structure-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ABC (Adaptive BayesNet structure learning for computational scalable multi-task image Compression), a novel, comprehensive framework that achieves computational scalability across all NIC components through Bayesian network (BayesNet) structure learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abc-adaptive-bayesnet-structure-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Shielded Image Compression: Defending Against Exploitation from Vision-Language Pretrained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-shielded-image-compression-defending</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper further incorporates an adaptive multi-objective optimization strategy to obtain improved encrypting performance and perceptual quality simultaneously within a unified training process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-shielded-image-compression-defending</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPARE: Single-Pass Annotation with Reference-Guided Evaluation for Automatic Process Supervision and Reward Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spare-single-pass-annotation-with-reference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Process or step-wise supervision has played a crucial role in advancing complex multi-step reasoning capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spare-single-pass-annotation-with-reference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Interest Recommendation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-interest-recommendation-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing recommendation methods often struggle to model users' multifaceted preferences due to the diversity and volatility of user behavior, as well as the inherent uncertainty and ambiguity of item attributes in practical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-interest-recommendation-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Ground Metric Learning with Applications to scRNA data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-ground-metric-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The learned global ground metric enables more accurate optimal transport distances, leading to improved performance in embedding, clustering and classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-ground-metric-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan3D 2.1: From Images to High-Fidelity 3D Assets with Production-Ready PBR Material</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-1-from-images-to-high-fidelity-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D AI-generated content (AIGC) is a passionate field that has significantly accelerated the creation of 3D models in gaming, film, and design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-1-from-images-to-high-fidelity-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Vaccinate: Combining Structure Learning and Effective Vaccination for Epidemic and Outbreak Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-vaccinate-combining-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we consider the problem of minimizing the extinction time of an outbreak modeled by an SIS model where the graph on which the disease spreads is unknown and only the infection states of the vertices are observed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-to-vaccinate-combining-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Gradients for Stable Learning at Scale in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-gradients-for-stable-learning-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling deep reinforcement learning networks is challenging and often results in degraded performance, yet the root causes of this failure mode remain poorly understood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-gradients-for-stable-learning-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiscoSG: Towards Discourse-Level Text Scene Graph Parsing through Iterative Graph Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discosg-towards-discourse-level-text-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce a new task, Discourse-level text Scene Graph parsing (DiscoSG), supported by our dataset DiscoSG-DS, which comprises 400 expert-annotated and 8, 430 synthesised multi-sentence caption-graph pairs for images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discosg-towards-discourse-level-text-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Hyperbole and Metaphor Detection with Their Bidirectional Dynamic Interaction and Emotion Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-hyperbole-and-metaphor-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods mostly focus on superficial text features, ignoring the associations of hyperbole and metaphor as well as the effect of implicit emotion on perceiving these rhetorical devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-hyperbole-and-metaphor-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIT-LVM: Structured Regularization for Interaction Terms in Linear Predictors using Latent Variable Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lit-lvm-structured-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some of the simplest, yet most frequently used predictors in statistics and machine learning use weighted linear combinations of features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lit-lvm-structured-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedWSIDD: Federated Whole Slide Image Classification via Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedwsidd-federated-whole-slide-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on multiple WSI classification tasks, including CAMELYON16 and CAMELYON17, demonstrate that FedWSIDD offers flexibility for heterogeneous local models, enhances local WSI classification performance, and preserves patient privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedwsidd-federated-whole-slide-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiMixQA: A Multimodal Benchmark for Question Answering over Tables and Charts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikimixqa-a-multimodal-benchmark-for-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among these, GPT-4-o is the only model exceeding 50% accuracy in this setting, whereas open-source models perform considerably worse, with a maximum accuracy of 27%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikimixqa-a-multimodal-benchmark-for-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Informed Grounding Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-informed-grounding-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose Context-INformed Grounding Supervision (CINGS), a post-training supervision in which the model is trained with relevant context prepended to the response, while computing the loss only over the response tokens and masking out the context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-informed-grounding-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciVer: Evaluating Foundation Models for Multimodal Scientific Claim Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciver-evaluating-foundation-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SciVer, the first benchmark specifically designed to evaluate the ability of foundation models to verify claims within a multimodal scientific context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciver-evaluating-foundation-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximating Language Model Training Data from Weights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximating-language-model-training-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When applied to a model trained with SFT on MSMARCO web documents, our method reduces perplexity from 3. 3 to 2. 3, compared to an expert LLAMA model's perplexity of 2. 0.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximating-language-model-training-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantically-Aware Rewards for Open-Ended R1 Training in Free-Form Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-aware-rewards-for-open-ended-r1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through comprehensive evaluations, including LLM-as-a-judge, human ratings, and qualitative analysis, we show that PrefBERT, trained on multi-sentence and paragraph-length responses, remains reliable across varied long passages and aligns well with the verifiable rewards GRPO needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-aware-rewards-for-open-ended-r1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All is Not Lost: LLM Recovery without Checkpoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-is-not-lost-llm-recovery-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The conventional approaches to recover from failures are to either use checkpointing, where periodically a copy of the entire model is sent to an additional storage, or redundant computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-is-not-lost-llm-recovery-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-World Object Counting in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-object-counting-in-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new task of open-world object counting in videos: given a text description, or an image example, that specifies the target object, the objective is to enumerate all the unique instances of the target objects in the video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-object-counting-in-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-shot Face Sketch Synthesis in the Wild via Generative Diffusion Prior and Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-face-sketch-synthesis-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a one-shot face sketch synthesis method based on diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-face-sketch-synthesis-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAS-Eval: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Security Evaluation of LLM Agents in Real-World Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ras-eval-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid deployment of Large language model (LLM) agents in critical domains like healthcare and finance necessitates robust security frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ras-eval-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapFM: Foundation Model-Driven HD Mapping with Multi-Task Contextual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapfm-foundation-model-driven-hd-mapping-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This multi-task learning approach provides richer contextual supervision, leading to a more comprehensive scene representation and ultimately resulting in higher accuracy and improved quality of the predicted vectorized HD maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapfm-foundation-model-driven-hd-mapping-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoX: Low-Rank Extrapolation Robustifies LLM Safety Against Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lox-low-rank-extrapolation-robustifies-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this insight, we propose a novel training-free method, termed Low-Rank Extrapolation (LoX), to enhance safety robustness by extrapolating the safety subspace of an aligned LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lox-low-rank-extrapolation-robustifies-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conquering the Retina: Bringing Visual in-Context Learning to OCT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conquering-the-retina-bringing-visual-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in medical image analysis have led to the development of highly specialized models tailored to specific clinical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conquering-the-retina-bringing-visual-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaky Thoughts: Large Reasoning Models Are Not Private Thinkers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leaky-thoughts-large-reasoning-models-are-not</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study privacy leakage in the reasoning traces of large reasoning models used as personal agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leaky-thoughts-large-reasoning-models-are-not</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DM-FNet: Unified multimodal medical image fusion via diffusion process-trained encoder-decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-fnet-unified-multimodal-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving high-quality fusion results requires a careful balance of brightness, color, contrast, and detail; this ensures that the fused images effectively display relevant anatomical structures and reflect the functional status of the tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-fnet-unified-multimodal-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
