<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:08:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SGFormer: Single-Layer Graph Transformers with Approximation-Free Linear Complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgformer-single-layer-graph-transformers-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning representations on large graphs is a long-standing challenge due to the inter-dependence nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgformer-single-layer-graph-transformers-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-depth Analysis of Low-rank Matrix Factorisation in a Federated Setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-depth-analysis-of-low-rank-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a linear rate of convergence of the excess loss which depends on $\sigma_{\max} / \sigma_{r}$, where $\sigma_{r}$ is the $r^{\mathrm{th}}$ singular value of the concatenation $\mathbf{S}$ of the matrices $(\mathbf{S}^i)_{i=1}^N$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-depth-analysis-of-low-rank-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Supervised Poison Vulnerability to Strengthen Self-Supervised Defense</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-supervised-poison-vulnerability-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Availability poisons exploit supervised learning (SL) algorithms by introducing class-related shortcut features in images such that models trained on poisoned data are useless for real-world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-supervised-poison-vulnerability-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAPX: An explainable model-agnostic framework for the detection of false information on social media networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapx-an-explainable-model-agnostic-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automated detection of false information has become a fundamental task in combating the spread of "fake news" on online social media networks (OSMN) as it reduces the need for manual discernment by individuals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapx-an-explainable-model-agnostic-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Estimation by Density Aware Evidential Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-estimation-by-density-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evidential deep learning (EDL) has shown remarkable success in uncertainty estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-estimation-by-density-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Transformer for Fusion and Pose Estimation in Deep Visual Inertial Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-transformer-for-fusion-and-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study aims to improve pose estimation accuracy by leveraging the attention mechanisms in transformers, which better utilize historical data compared to the recurrent neural network (RNN) based methods seen in recent methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-transformer-for-fusion-and-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Monolingual and Crosslingual Word-in-Context Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-monolingual-and-crosslingual-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results on the monolingual tasks confirmed that our representations exhibited a competitive performance compared to that of the previous study for the context-aware lexical semantic tasks and outperformed it for STS estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-monolingual-and-crosslingual-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Analysis of Pretrained Audio Representations in Music Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-pretrained-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the years, Music Information Retrieval (MIR) has proposed various models pretrained on large amounts of music data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-pretrained-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anytime Continual Learning for Open Vocabulary Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anytime-continual-learning-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a dynamic weighting between predictions of a partially fine-tuned model and a fixed open vocabulary model that enables continual improvement when training samples are available for a subset of a task's labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anytime-continual-learning-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffFAS: Face Anti-Spoofing via Generative Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difffas-face-anti-spoofing-via-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our analysis, we propose DiffFAS framework, which quantifies quality as prior information input into the network to counter image quality shift, and performs diffusion-based high-fidelity cross-domain and cross-attack types generation to counter image style shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difffas-face-anti-spoofing-via-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAE Explainer: Supplement Learning Variational Autoencoders with Interactive Visualization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vae-explainer-supplement-learning-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variational Autoencoders are widespread in Machine Learning, but are typically explained with dense math notation or static code examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vae-explainer-supplement-learning-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba-YOLO-World: Marrying YOLO-World with Mamba for Open-Vocabulary Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-yolo-world-marrying-yolo-world-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary detection (OVD) aims to detect objects beyond a predefined set of categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-yolo-world-marrying-yolo-world-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINNfluence: Influence Functions for Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinnfluence-influence-functions-for-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) have emerged as a flexible and promising application of deep learning to partial differential equations in the physical sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinnfluence-influence-functions-for-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenMapping: Unleashing the Potential of Inverse Perspective Mapping for Robust Online HD Map Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genmapping-unleashing-the-potential-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework is established with a triadic synergy architecture, including principal and dual auxiliary branches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genmapping-unleashing-the-potential-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo: Band-sequence Modeling for High-Quality Audio Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apollo-band-sequence-modeling-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio restoration has become increasingly significant in modern society, not only due to the demand for high-quality auditory experiences enabled by advanced playback devices, but also because the growing capabilities of generative audio models necessitate high-fidelity audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apollo-band-sequence-modeling-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VistaFormer: Scalable Vision Transformers for Satellite Image Time Series Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vistaformer-scalable-vision-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VistaFormer, a lightweight Transformer-based model architecture for the semantic segmentation of remote-sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vistaformer-scalable-vision-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect Fake with Fake: Leveraging Synthetic Data-driven Representation for Synthetic Image Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-fake-with-fake-leveraging-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Are general-purpose visual representations acquired solely from synthetic data useful for detecting fake images?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-fake-with-fake-leveraging-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents in Software Engineering: Survey, Landscape, and Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-in-software-engineering-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved remarkable success and have been widely used in various downstream tasks, especially in the tasks of the software engineering (SE) field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-in-software-engineering-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PiEEG-16 to Measure 16 EEG Channels with Raspberry Pi for Brain-Computer Interfaces and EEG devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pieeg-16-to-measure-16-eeg-channels-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces a cost-effective gateway into the fascinating world of neuroscience: the PIEEG-16, a versatile shield for RaspberryPi designed to measure 16 channels of various biosignals, including EEG (electroencephalography), EMG (electromyography), and ECG (electrocardiography) without any data transfer over the network (Wi-Fi, Bluetooth) and processing and feature ectraction directly on the Raspberry in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pieeg-16-to-measure-16-eeg-channels-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign Language Sense Disambiguation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sign-language-sense-disambiguation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project explores methods to enhance sign language translation of German sign language, specifically focusing on disambiguation of homonyms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sign-language-sense-disambiguation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Short Codes for Fading Channels with No or Receiver-Only Channel State Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-short-codes-for-fading-channels-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian codes that achieve capacity for AWGN channels may be unsuitable for these no-CSI and CSIR-only cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-short-codes-for-fading-channels-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Space Score-based Diffusion Model for Probabilistic Multivariate Time Series Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-score-based-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose the Latent Space Score-Based Diffusion Model (LSSDM) for probabilistic multivariate time series imputation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-space-score-based-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measure-Theoretic Time-Delay Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measure-theoretic-time-delay-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The celebrated Takens' embedding theorem provides a theoretical foundation for reconstructing the full state of a dynamical system from partial observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measure-theoretic-time-delay-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing the boundaries of event subsampling in event-based video classification using CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-boundaries-of-event-subsampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event cameras offer low-power visual sensing capabilities ideal for edge-device applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-boundaries-of-event-subsampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Neural Operators with Diffusion Models Improves Spectral Representation in Turbulence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-neural-operators-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We integrate neural operators with diffusion models to address the spectral limitations of neural operators in surrogate modeling of turbulent flows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-neural-operators-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomimetic Frontend for Differentiable Audio Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomimetic-frontend-for-differentiable-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While models in audio and speech processing are becoming deeper and more end-to-end, they as a consequence need expensive training on large data, and are often brittle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomimetic-frontend-for-differentiable-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CasDyF-Net: Image Dehazing via Cascaded Dynamic Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casdyf-net-image-dehazing-via-cascaded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by dynamic filtering, we propose using cascaded dynamic filters to create a multi-branch network by dynamically generating filter kernels based on feature map distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casdyf-net-image-dehazing-via-cascaded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Context Leads but Parametric Memory Follows in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-context-leads-but-parametric-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable progress in leveraging diverse knowledge sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-context-leads-but-parametric-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Program Inversion with Differentiable Planning: A Framework for Unified Robot Program Parameter and Trajectory Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-program-inversion-with-differentiable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents SPI-DP, a novel first-order optimizer capable of optimizing robot programs with respect to both high-level task objectives and motion-level constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-program-inversion-with-differentiable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Rare Word Accuracy in Direct Speech Translation with a Retrieval-and-Demonstration Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-rare-word-accuracy-in-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To leverage these valuable resources, we propose a retrieval-and-demonstration approach to enhance rare word translation accuracy in direct ST models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-rare-word-accuracy-in-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Graph Representation Learning via Structural Similarity Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-representation-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose a specially designed graph that leverages graph kernel algorithms to represent the similarity between molecules quantitatively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-graph-representation-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CF-PRNet: Coarse-to-Fine Prototype Refining Network for Point Cloud Completion and Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cf-prnet-coarse-to-fine-prototype-refining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In modern agriculture, precise monitoring of plants and fruits is crucial for tasks such as high-throughput phenotyping and automated harvesting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cf-prnet-coarse-to-fine-prototype-refining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-Optimization of Robot Design and Control: Enhancing Performance and Understanding Design Complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-optimization-of-robot-design-and-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This might limit how well the design is adapted to a task, as the suitability of the design is given by how well the robot performs in the task, which requires both a design and a controller.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-optimization-of-robot-design-and-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B4: Towards Optimal Assessment of Plausible Code Solutions with Plausible Tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/b4-towards-optimal-assessment-of-plausible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed approximated optimal strategy B4 significantly surpasses existing heuristics in selecting code solutions generated by large language models (LLMs) with LLM-generated tests, achieving a relative performance improvement by up to 50% over the strongest heuristic and 246% over the random selection in the most challenging scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/b4-towards-optimal-assessment-of-plausible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://arxiv.org/pdf/2409.07491</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-pdf-2409-07491</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces a cost-effective gateway into the fascinating world of neuroscience: the PIEEG-16, a versatile shield for RaspberryPi designed to measure 16 channels of various biosignals, including EEG (electroencephalography), EMG (electromyography), and ECG (electrocardiography) without any data transfer over the network (Wi-Fi, Bluetooth) and processing and feature ectraction directly on the Raspberry in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/https-arxiv-org-pdf-2409-07491</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkinFormer: Learning Statistical Texture Representation with Transformer for Skin Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinformer-learning-statistical-texture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a trans\textbf{Former} network (\textbf{SkinFormer}) that efficiently extracts and fuses statistical texture representation for \textbf{Skin} lesion segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skinformer-learning-statistical-texture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTR-VT: Handwritten Text Recognition with Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htr-vt-handwritten-text-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce a data-efficient ViT method that uses only the encoder of the standard transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htr-vt-handwritten-text-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Efficient Child-Adult Speaker Diarization with Simulated Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-child-adult-speaker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then train a Whisper Encoder-based model, achieving strong zero-shot performance on child-adult speaker diarization using real datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-child-adult-speaker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder for Low-altitude Aircraft with Binary Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathfinder-for-low-altitude-aircraft-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A prior global topological map (e. g., the OpenStreetMap, OSM) can boost the performance of autonomous mapping by a ground mobile robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathfinder-for-low-altitude-aircraft-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining Datasets in Words: Statistical Models with Natural Language Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-datasets-in-words-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make sense of massive data, we often fit simplified models and then interpret the parameters; for example, we cluster the text embeddings and then interpret the mean parameters of each cluster.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-datasets-in-words-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynSUM -- Synthetic Benchmark with Structured and Unstructured Medical Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synsum-synthetic-benchmark-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SynSUM dataset is primarily designed to facilitate research on clinical information extraction in the presence of tabular background variables, which can be linked through domain knowledge to concepts of interest to be extracted from the text - the symptoms, in the case of SynSUM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synsum-synthetic-benchmark-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking reCAPTCHAv2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-recaptchav2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work examines the efficacy of employing advanced machine learning methods to solve captchas from Google's reCAPTCHAv2 system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-recaptchav2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Dynamic Factor Models and Neural Controlled Differential Equations for Nowcasting GDP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-dynamic-factor-models-and-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, DFMs face two main challenges: i) the lack of capturing economic uncertainties such as sudden recessions or booms, and ii) the limitation of capturing irregular dynamics from mixed-frequency data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-dynamic-factor-models-and-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring SSL Discrete Speech Features for Zipformer-based Contextual ASR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-ssl-discrete-speech-features-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) based discrete speech representations are highly compact and domain adaptable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-ssl-discrete-speech-features-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODAQ: Open Dataset of Audio Quality - Benchmark on GitHub</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odaq-open-dataset-of-audio-quality-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ODAQ is a dataset addressing the scarcity of openly available collections of audio signals accompanied by corresponding subjective scores of perceived quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odaq-open-dataset-of-audio-quality-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabKANet: Tabular Data Modelling with Kolmogorov-Arnold Network and Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabkanet-tabular-data-modelling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tabular data is the most common type of data in real-life scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabkanet-tabular-data-modelling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WirelessAgent: Large Language Model Agents for Intelligent Wireless Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wirelessagent-large-language-model-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wireless networks are increasingly facing challenges due to their expanding scale and complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wirelessagent-large-language-model-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation for DoA Estimation in Multipath Channels with Interferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-for-doa-estimation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of estimating the direction-of-arrival (DoA) of a desired source located in a known region of interest in the presence of interfering sources and multipath.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-for-doa-estimation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Text-guided Object Inpainting with Semantic Pre-inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-text-guided-object-inpainting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to decompose the typical single-stage object inpainting into two cascaded processes: 1) semantic pre-inpainting that infers the semantic features of desired objects in a multi-modal feature space; 2) high-fieldity object generation in diffusion latent space that pivots on such inpainted semantic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-text-guided-object-inpainting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Few-Shot Image Classification through Learnable Multi-Scale Embedding and Attention Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-image-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conducted comprehensive evaluations on the MiniImageNet and FC100 datasets, specifically in the 5-way 1-shot and 5-way 5-shot scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-few-shot-image-classification</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
