<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 09:18:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>One-shot Federated Learning via Synthetic Distiller-Distillate Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-learning-via-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, they may encounter scalability issues with complex datasets due to inherent two-step information loss: first, during local training (from data to model), and second, when transferring knowledge to the server model (from model to inversed data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-learning-via-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DrIFT: Autonomous Drone Dataset with Integrated Real and Synthetic Data, Flexible Views, and Transformed Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drift-autonomous-drone-dataset-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, drone detection accuracy is significantly affected by domain shifts due to environmental changes, varied points of view, and background shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drift-autonomous-drone-dataset-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Flexible 3D Perception: Object-Centric Occupancy Completion Augments 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-flexible-3d-perception-object-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing that foreground objects only occupy a small portion of the scene, we introduce object-centric occupancy as a supplement to object bboxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-flexible-3d-perception-object-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-aware retinal layer segmentation in OCT through probabilistic signed distance functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-retinal-layer-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these shortcomings, our methodology refines the segmentation by predicting a signed distance function (SDF) that effectively parameterizes the retinal layer shape via level set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-retinal-layer-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Dual-Space Embedding for Entity Alignment via Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-dual-space-embedding-for-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity alignment aims to match identical entities across different knowledge graphs (KGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-dual-space-embedding-for-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Transfer for Dual-Aspect Cross Domain Cognitive Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-transfer-for-dual-aspect-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PromptCD is designed to adapt seamlessly across diverse CDCD scenarios, introducing PromptCD-S for student-aspect CDCD and PromptCD-E for exercise-aspect CDCD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-transfer-for-dual-aspect-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLa: HoloLens Object Labeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hola-hololens-object-labeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of medical Augmented Reality (AR) applications, object tracking is a key challenge and requires a significant amount of annotation masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hola-hololens-object-labeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCEAN: Open-World Contrastive Authorship Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ocean-open-world-contrastive-authorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an era where cyberattacks increasingly target the software supply chain, the ability to accurately attribute code authorship in binary files is critical to improving cybersecurity measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ocean-open-world-contrastive-authorship</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two stages domain invariant representation learners solve the large co-variate shift in unsupervised domain adaptation with two dimensional data domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stages-domain-invariant-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform two stages domain invariant representation learning to bridge the gap between source and target with semantic intermediate data (unsupervised).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stages-domain-invariant-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinVT: Empower Your Image-level Large Language Model to Understand Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linvt-empower-your-image-level-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have been widely used in various tasks, motivating us to develop an LLM-based assistant for videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linvt-empower-your-image-level-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEYOLO: Dual-Feature-Enhancement YOLO for Cross-Modality Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deyolo-dual-feature-enhancement-yolo-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fuse the two modalities to maximize the advantages of cross-modality, we design a dual-enhancement-based cross-modality object detection network DEYOLO, in which semantic-spatial cross modality and novel bi-directional decoupled focus modules are designed to achieve the detection-centered mutual enhancement of RGB-infrared (RGB-IR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deyolo-dual-feature-enhancement-yolo-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanoDreamer: 3D Panorama Synthesis from a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panodreamer-3d-panorama-synthesis-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present PanoDreamer, a novel method for producing a coherent 360$^\circ$ 3D scene from a single input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panodreamer-3d-panorama-synthesis-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurgBox: Agent-Driven Operating Room Sandbox with Surgery Copilot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgbox-agent-driven-operating-room-sandbox</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these cognitive challenges in surgical training and operation, we propose SurgBox, an agent-driven sandbox framework to systematically enhance the cognitive capabilities of surgeons in immersive surgical simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgbox-agent-driven-operating-room-sandbox</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLP-ADBench: NLP Anomaly Detection Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlp-adbench-nlp-anomaly-detection-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work fills a crucial gap in the field and establishes a foundation for advancing NLP anomaly detection, particularly in the context of improving the safety and reliability of web-based systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlp-adbench-nlp-anomaly-detection-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing the contents of semantic representations from text, behavior, and brain data using the psychNorms metabase</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-contents-of-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We carry out the first systematic evaluation of the similarities and differences between semantic representations derived from text, behavior, and brain data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-the-contents-of-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse autoencoders reveal selective remapping of visual concepts during adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-autoencoders-reveal-selective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adapting foundation models for specific purposes has become a standard approach to build machine learning systems for downstream applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-autoencoders-reveal-selective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCraft: A Benchmark for Multi-Modal Multi-Agent Systems in Minecraft</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teamcraft-a-benchmark-for-multi-modal-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collaboration is a cornerstone of society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teamcraft-a-benchmark-for-multi-modal-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMO: Reframing Dialogue Interaction with Fine-grained Element Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demo-reframing-dialogue-interaction-with-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have made dialogue one of the central modes of human-machine interaction, leading to the accumulation of vast amounts of conversation logs and increasing demand for dialogue generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demo-reframing-dialogue-interaction-with-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixedGaussianAvatar: Realistically and Geometrically Accurate Head Avatar via Mixed 2D-3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixedgaussianavatar-realistically-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attach the 2D Gaussians to the triangular mesh of the FLAME model and connect additional 3D Gaussians to those 2D Gaussians where the rendering quality of 2DGS is inadequate, creating a mixed 2D-3D Gaussian representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixedgaussianavatar-realistically-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConQRet: Benchmarking Fine-Grained Evaluation of Retrieval Augmented Argumentation with LLM Judges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conqret-benchmarking-fine-grained-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To validate the proposed techniques, we introduce ConQRet, a new benchmark featuring long and complex human-authored arguments on debated topics, grounded in real-world websites, allowing an exhaustive evaluation across retrieval effectiveness, argument quality, and groundedness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conqret-benchmarking-fine-grained-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIAS: A Body-based Interpretable Active Speaker Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-a-body-based-interpretable-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that BIAS is state-of-the-art in challenging conditions where body-based features are of utmost importance (Columbia, open-settings, and WASD), and yields competitive results in AVA-ActiveSpeaker, where face is more influential than body for ASD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-a-body-based-interpretable-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Blessing: Class-Wise Embedding guided Instance-Dependent Partial Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-blessing-class-wise-embedding-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In partial label learning (PLL), every sample is associated with a candidate label set comprising the ground-truth label and several noisy labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-blessing-class-wise-embedding-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stag-1: Towards Realistic 4D Driving Simulation with Video Generation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stag-1-towards-realistic-4d-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose a Spatial-Temporal simulAtion for drivinG (Stag-1) model to reconstruct real-world scenes and design a controllable generative network to achieve 4D simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stag-1-towards-realistic-4d-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact: Exploring Space-Time Perceptive Clues for Weakly Supervised Satellite Image Time Series Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-exploring-space-time-perceptive-clues</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkably, the segmentation network trained on Exact-generated masks achieves 95% of its fully supervised performance, showing the bright promise of weakly supervised paradigm in crop mapping scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-exploring-space-time-perceptive-clues</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaserGuider: A Laser Based Physical Backdoor Attack against Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laserguider-a-laser-based-physical-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the laser-based backdoor triggers, we present a physical backdoor attack, called LaserGuider, which possesses remote control ability and achieves high temporal stealthiness, flexibility, and mobility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/laserguider-a-laser-based-physical-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Machine Translation with Unstructured Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-machine-translation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In machine translation (MT), previous work typically retrieves in-context examples from paired MT corpora, or domain-specific knowledge from knowledge graphs, to enhance models' MT ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-machine-translation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaussianFormer-2: Probabilistic Gaussian Superposition for Efficient 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-gaussian-superposition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose a probabilistic Gaussian superposition model which interprets each Gaussian as a probability distribution of its neighborhood being occupied and conforms to probabilistic multiplication to derive the overall geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-gaussian-superposition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Hash for Recommendation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-hash-for-recommendation-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we present a comprehensive review of current HashRec algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-hash-for-recommendation-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the Limits of Segment Anything Model: Analyzing Challenges in Segmenting Tree-Like and Low-Contrast Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-limits-of-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM) has shown impressive performance in interactive and zero-shot segmentation across diverse domains, suggesting that they have learned a general concept of "objects" from their large-scale training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-limits-of-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LossVal: Efficient Data Valuation for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossval-efficient-data-valuation-for-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessing the importance of individual training samples is a key challenge in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lossval-efficient-data-valuation-for-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divot: Diffusion Powers Video Tokenizer for Comprehension and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divot-diffusion-powers-video-tokenizer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We posit that if a video diffusion model can effectively de-noise video clips by taking the features of a video tokenizer as the condition, then the tokenizer has successfully captured robust spatial and temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divot-diffusion-powers-video-tokenizer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRAM: Generalization in Deep RL with a Robust Adaptation Module</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gram-generalization-in-deep-rl-with-a-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reliable deployment of deep reinforcement learning in real-world settings requires the ability to generalize across a variety of conditions, including both in-distribution scenarios seen during training as well as novel out-of-distribution scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gram-generalization-in-deep-rl-with-a-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISR: Measuring Instrumental Self-Reasoning in Frontier Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misr-measuring-instrumental-self-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a suite of tasks to evaluate the instrumental self-reasoning ability of large language model (LLM) agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/misr-measuring-instrumental-self-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Branch Subpixel-Guided Network for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-branch-subpixel-guided-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) has been widely applied into hyperspectral image (HSI) classification owing to its promising feature learning and representation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-branch-subpixel-guided-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynFinTabs: A Dataset of Synthetic Financial Tables for Information and Table Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synfintabs-a-dataset-of-synthetic-financial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the effectiveness of our dataset in training models to extract information from table images, we create FinTabQA, a layout large language model trained on an extractive question-answering task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synfintabs-a-dataset-of-synthetic-financial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socially-Informed Reconstruction for Pedestrian Trajectory Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socially-informed-reconstruction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pedestrian trajectory prediction remains a challenge for autonomous systems, particularly due to the intricate dynamics of social interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socially-informed-reconstruction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEIM: DETR with Improved Matching for Fast Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deim-detr-with-improved-matching-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce DEIM, an innovative and efficient training framework designed to accelerate convergence in real-time object detection with Transformer-based architectures (DETR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deim-detr-with-improved-matching-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Similarity and Dissimilarity Guided Symmetric Non-Negative Matrix Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-similarity-and-dissimilarity-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we construct the similarity matrix as a weighted $k$-NN graph with learnable weight that reflects the reliability of each $k$-th NN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-similarity-and-dissimilarity-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult Glioma Segmentation in Sub-Saharan Africa using Transfer Learning on Stratified Finetuning Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adult-glioma-segmentation-in-sub-saharan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gliomas, a kind of brain tumor characterized by high mortality, present substantial diagnostic challenges in low- and middle-income countries, particularly in Sub-Saharan Africa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adult-glioma-segmentation-in-sub-saharan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does your model understand genes? A benchmark of gene properties for biological and text models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-your-model-understand-genes-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that text-based models and protein language models generally outperform expression-based models in genomic properties and regulatory functions tasks, whereas expression-based models demonstrate superior performance in localization tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-your-model-understand-genes-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDUAL: A Dual-Strategy with Adaptive Loss and Dynamic Aggregation for Mitigating Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddual-a-dual-strategy-with-adaptive-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our findings, we then introduce an innovative dual-strategy approach designed to effectively resolve these issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddual-a-dual-strategy-with-adaptive-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZipAR: Accelerating Autoregressive Image Generation through Spatial Locality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipar-accelerating-autoregressive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ZipAR, a training-free, plug-and-play parallel decoding framework for accelerating auto-regressive (AR) visual generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipar-accelerating-autoregressive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask of truth: model sensitivity to unexpected regions of medical images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-of-truth-model-sensitivity-to-unexpected</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that all models trained on the PadChest dataset, irrespective of the masking strategy, are able to obtain an Area Under the Curve (AUC) above random.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-of-truth-model-sensitivity-to-unexpected</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligned Music Notation and Lyrics Transcription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligned-music-notation-and-lyrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces and formalizes, for the first time, the Aligned Music Notation and Lyrics Transcription (AMNLT) challenge, which addresses the complete transcription of vocal scores by jointly considering music symbols, lyrics, and their synchronization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligned-music-notation-and-lyrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIND: Effective Incorrect Assignment Detection through a Multi-Modal Structure-Enhanced Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-effective-incorrect-assignment-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of academic publications has exacerbated the issue of author name ambiguity in online digital libraries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mind-effective-incorrect-assignment-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinity: Scaling Bitwise AutoRegressive Modeling for High-Resolution Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinity-scaling-bitwise-autoregressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Infinity, a Bitwise Visual AutoRegressive Modeling capable of generating high-resolution, photorealistic images following language instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinity-scaling-bitwise-autoregressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft Tensor Product Representations for Fully Continuous, Compositional Visual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-tensor-product-representations-for-fully</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fully align compositional representations with continuous vector spaces, we extend Smolensky's Tensor Product Representation (TPR) and propose a new type of inherently *continuous* compositional representation, *Soft TPR*, along with a theoretically-principled architecture, *Soft TPR Autoencoder*, designed specifically for learning Soft TPRs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-tensor-product-representations-for-fully</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bench-CoE: a Framework for Collaboration of Experts from Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bench-coe-a-framework-for-collaboration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are key technologies driving intelligent systems to handle multiple tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bench-coe-a-framework-for-collaboration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanEdit: A High-Quality Human-Rewarded Dataset for Instruction-based Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanedit-a-high-quality-human-rewarded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HumanEdit bridges this gap by employing human annotators to construct data pairs and administrators to provide feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanedit-a-high-quality-human-rewarded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Adapter: The Devil is in the Masks for Open-Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-adapter-the-devil-is-in-the-masks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mask-Adapter integrates seamlessly into open-vocabulary segmentation methods based on mask pooling in a plug-and-play manner, delivering more accurate classification results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-adapter-the-devil-is-in-the-masks-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
