<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:07:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Superposed Decoding: Multiple Generations from a Single Autoregressive Inference Pass</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superposed-decoding-multiple-generations-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve this by feeding a superposition of the $k$ most recent token embeddings from the drafts as input to the next decoding step of the language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superposed-decoding-multiple-generations-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frustratingly Easy Test-Time Adaptation of Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frustratingly-easy-test-time-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to its simplicity and comparatively negligible computation, ZERO can serve as a strong baseline for future work in this field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frustratingly-easy-test-time-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yuan 2.0-M32: Mixture of Experts with Attention Router</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-2-0-m32-mixture-of-experts-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yuan 2. 0-M32, with a similar base architecture as Yuan-2. 0 2B, uses a mixture-of-experts architecture with 32 experts of which 2 experts are active.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yuan-2-0-m32-mixture-of-experts-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Skeleton-based Motion Encoder Models for Clinical Applications: Estimating Parkinson's Disease Severity in Walking Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-skeleton-based-motion-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we establish a benchmark for the analysis of skeleton-based motion encoder models in clinical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-skeleton-based-motion-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tool Learning with Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tool-learning-with-large-language-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this survey, we focus on reviewing existing literature from the two primary aspects (1) why tool learning is beneficial and (2) how tool learning is implemented, enabling a comprehensive understanding of tool learning with LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tool-learning-with-large-language-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual Contributions as Intrinsic Exploration Scaffolds for Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-contributions-as-intrinsic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL), effective exploration is critical, especially in sparse reward environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/individual-contributions-as-intrinsic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CompetEvo: Towards Morphological Evolution from Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/competevo-towards-morphological-evolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training an agent to adapt to specific tasks through co-optimization of morphology and control has widely attracted attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/competevo-towards-morphological-evolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review and Implementation of Object Detection Models and Optimizations for Real-time Medical Mask Detection during the COVID-19 Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-and-implementation-of-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional Neural Networks (CNN) are commonly used for the problem of object detection thanks to their increased accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-and-implementation-of-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeSplat: Generalizable 3D Gaussian Splatting Towards Free-View Synthesis of Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freesplat-generalizable-3d-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing generalizable 3D Gaussian Splatting methods are largely confined to narrow-range interpolation between stereo images due to their heavy backbones, thus lacking the ability to accurately localize 3D Gaussian and support free-view synthesis across wide view range.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freesplat-generalizable-3d-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSDL: Data Set Description Language for Bridging Modalities and Tasks in AI Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsdl-data-set-description-language-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of artificial intelligence, the diversity of data modalities and annotation formats often renders data unusable directly, requiring understanding and format conversion before it can be used by researchers or developers with different needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsdl-data-set-description-language-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAIntbench: A Holistic and Precise Benchmark for Bias Evaluation in Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faintbench-a-holistic-and-precise-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development and reduced barriers to entry for Text-to-Image (T2I) models have raised concerns about the biases in their outputs, but existing research lacks a holistic definition and evaluation framework of biases, limiting the enhancement of debiasing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faintbench-a-holistic-and-precise-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deform3DGS: Flexible Deformation for Fast Surgical Scene Reconstruction with Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deform3dgs-flexible-deformation-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tissue deformation poses a key challenge for accurate surgical scene reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deform3dgs-flexible-deformation-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Series Representation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-representation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Central to this concept is the self-supervised pretraining of Time Series Representation Models (TSRMs), which once learned can be easily tailored and fine-tuned for specific tasks, such as forecasting and imputation, in an automated and resource-efficient manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-series-representation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Trust Recommender System Fairness Evaluation? The Role of Fairness and Relevance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-trust-recommender-system-fairness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that most of these measures: i) correlate weakly with one another and even contradict each other at times; ii) are less sensitive to rank position changes than relevance- and fairness-only measures, meaning that they are less granular than traditional RS measures; and iii) tend to compress scores at the low end of their range, meaning that they are not very expressive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-trust-recommender-system-fairness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipette: Automatic Fine-grained Large Language Model Training Configurator for Real-World Clusters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pipette-automatic-fine-grained-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, they often fail to consider the memory requirement per GPU, often recommending solutions that could not be executed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pipette-automatic-fine-grained-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforced Model Predictive Control via Trust-Region Quasi-Newton Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-model-predictive-control-via-trust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances propose to use reinforcement learning applied to a parameterized model predictive controller to recover the optimal control performance even if an imperfect model or short prediction horizons are used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-model-predictive-control-via-trust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgoNCE++: Do Egocentric Video-Language Models Really Understand Hand-Object Interactions?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egonce-do-egocentric-video-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the occurrence of diverse EgoHOIs in the real world, we propose an open-vocabulary benchmark named EgoHOIBench to reveal the diminished performance of current egocentric video-language models (EgoVLM) on fined-grained concepts, indicating that these models still lack a full spectrum of egocentric understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egonce-do-egocentric-video-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning with Bilevel Optimization in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensuring safety in MARL, particularly when deploying it in real-world applications such as autonomous driving, emerges as a critical challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Analytic Exemplar-Free Continual Learning with Large Models for Imbalanced Autonomous Driving Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-analytic-exemplar-free-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of these scenarios can be formulated as an online continual learning (OCL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-analytic-exemplar-free-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Dynamic Topics in Chain-Free Fashion by Evolution-Tracking Contrastive Learning and Unassociated Word Exclusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-dynamic-topics-in-chain-free-fashion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing models suffer from repetitive topic and unassociated topic issues, failing to reveal the evolution and hindering further applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-dynamic-topics-in-chain-free-fashion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAVIN: Multi-Action Video Generation with Diffusion Models via Transition Video Infilling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mavin-multi-action-video-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core challenge lies in generating smooth and natural transitions between these segments given the inherent complexity and variability of action transitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mavin-multi-action-video-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal and Extensible Language-Vision Models for Organ Segmentation and Tumor Detection from Abdominal Computed Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-extensible-language-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these AI models often struggle with flexibility for partially annotated datasets and extensibility for new classes due to limitations in the one-hot encoding, architectural design, and learning scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-and-extensible-language-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Cycloid Trajectory of EM Iterations in Mixed Linear Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-cycloid-trajectory-of-em</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the trajectory of iterations and the convergence rates of the Expectation-Maximization (EM) algorithm for two-component Mixed Linear Regression (2MLR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-cycloid-trajectory-of-em</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are Visually-Grounded Language Models Bad at Image Classification?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-are-visually-grounded-language-models-bad</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image classification is one of the most fundamental capabilities of machine vision intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-are-visually-grounded-language-models-bad</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashST: A Simple and Universal Prompt-Tuning Framework for Traffic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashst-a-simple-and-universal-prompt-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we incorporate a distribution mapping mechanism to align the data distributions of pre-training and downstream data, facilitating effective knowledge transfer in spatio-temporal forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashst-a-simple-and-universal-prompt-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Guiding Exploration for Combinatorial Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-guiding-exploration-for-combinatorial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present our research as the first to apply LLMs to a broad range of CPs and demonstrate that SGE outperforms existing prompting strategies by over 27. 84% in CP optimization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-guiding-exploration-for-combinatorial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OV-DQUO: Open-Vocabulary DETR with Denoising Text Query Training and Open-World Unknown Objects Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-dquo-open-vocabulary-detr-with-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-Vocabulary Detection (OVD) aims to detect objects from novel categories beyond the base categories on which the detector is trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-dquo-open-vocabulary-detr-with-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruct-ReID++: Towards Universal Purpose Instruction-Guided Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct-reid-towards-universal-purpose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the task-specific evaluation setting, gallery sets are categorized according to specific ReID tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruct-reid-towards-universal-purpose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting Pre-Trained Vision Models for Novel Instance Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-pre-trained-vision-models-for-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Novel Instance Detection and Segmentation (NIDS) aims at detecting and segmenting novel object instances given a few examples of each instance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-pre-trained-vision-models-for-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MC-GTA: Metric-Constrained Model-Based Clustering using Goodness-of-fit Tests with Autocorrelations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-gta-metric-constrained-model-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A wide range of (multivariate) temporal (1D) and spatial (2D) data analysis tasks, such as grouping vehicle sensor trajectories, can be formulated as clustering with given metric constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-gta-metric-constrained-model-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OwLore: Outlier-weighed Layerwise Sampled Low-Rank Projection for Memory-Efficient LLM Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owlore-outlier-weighed-layerwise-sampled-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Outlier-weighed Layerwise Sampled Low-Rank Projection (OwLore), a new memory-efficient fine-tuning approach, inspired by the layerwise outlier distribution of LLMs, which dynamically samples pre-trained layers to fine-tune instead of adding additional adaptors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owlore-outlier-weighed-layerwise-sampled-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metaheuristics and Large Language Models Join Forces: Towards an Integrated Optimization Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaheuristics-and-large-language-models-join</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the rise of Large Language Models (LLMs) a couple of years ago, researchers in metaheuristics (MHs) have wondered how to use their power in a beneficial way within their algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaheuristics-and-large-language-models-join</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Futures: A Natural Language Driven Career Prediction System for Computer Science and Software Engineering Students</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-futures-a-natural-language-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, the research helps individual CS and SWE students find suitable jobs that match their skills, interests, and skill-related activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-futures-a-natural-language-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Algorithms for Optimizing Emergency Exit Placement in Indoor Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-algorithms-for-optimizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of finding the optimal placement of emergency exits in an indoor environment to facilitate the rapid and orderly evacuation of crowds is addressed in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-algorithms-for-optimizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Based Link Anomaly Detection in Continuous-Time Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-link-anomaly-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly detection in continuous-time dynamic graphs is an emerging field yet under-explored in the context of learning-based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-link-anomaly-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning Based Handwriting Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-based-handwriting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SSL-HV: Self-Supervised Learning approaches applied to the task of Handwriting Verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-based-handwriting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Logical Reasoning via Symbolic Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-logical-reasoning-via-symbolic-chain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Technically, building upon an LLM, SymbCoT 1) first translates the natural language context into the symbolic format, and then 2) derives a step-by-step plan to solve the problem with symbolic logical rules, 3) followed by a verifier to check the translation and reasoning chain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-logical-reasoning-via-symbolic-chain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Circuits in Pretrained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-circuits-in-pretrained-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve into the computation graph of the language model to uncover the knowledge circuits that are instrumental in articulating specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-circuits-in-pretrained-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SarcNet: A Novel AI-based Framework to Automatically Analyze and Score Sarcomere Organizations in Fluorescently Tagged hiPSC-CMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarcnet-a-novel-ai-based-framework-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present a novel deep learning-based framework that leverages cell images and integrates cell features to automatically evaluate the sarcomere structure of hiPSC-CMs from the onset of differentiation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarcnet-a-novel-ai-based-framework-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Reinforcement Learning in Black-Box Environments via Adaptive Shielding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-reinforcement-learning-in-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empowering safe exploration of reinforcement learning (RL) agents during training is a critical impediment towards deploying RL agents in many real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-reinforcement-learning-in-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTAG: Tabletop Games for Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytag-tabletop-games-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern Tabletop Games present various interesting challenges for Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytag-tabletop-games-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Low-rank Compression Framework for Click-through Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-low-rank-compression-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a unified low-rank decomposition framework for compressing CTR prediction models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-low-rank-compression-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Shift Estimation-and-Correction for Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-shift-estimation-and-correction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a novel COlor MOdulation (COMO) module to modulate the separately corrected colors in the over- and under-exposed regions to produce the enhanced image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-shift-estimation-and-correction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMPareto: Boosting Multimodal Learning with Innocent Unimodal Assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmpareto-boosting-multimodal-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in this paper, we identify the previously ignored gradient conflict between multimodal and unimodal learning objectives, potentially misleading the unimodal encoder optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmpareto-boosting-multimodal-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Source-Free Domain Adaptation with MLLM-driven Curriculum Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-source-free-domain-adaptation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source-Free Domain Adaptation (SFDA) aims to adapt a pre-trained source model to a target domain using only unlabeled target data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-source-free-domain-adaptation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-FedUL: A Training-Free Federated Unlearning with Provable Skew Resilience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-fedul-a-training-free-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) has recently emerged as a compelling machine learning paradigm, prioritizing the protection of privacy for training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-fedul-a-training-free-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Rejection Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rejection-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in powerful pre-trained diffusion models encourage the development of methods to improve the sampling performance under well-trained diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rejection-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Generation via Cross-Modal In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-generation-via-cross-modal-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, they often result in misaligned image generation for prompt sequences featuring multiple objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-generation-via-cross-modal-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-aware multi-modality learning for eye disease screening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-multi-modality-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel multi-modality evidential fusion pipeline for eye disease screening.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-multi-modality-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViG: Linear-complexity Visual Sequence Learning with Gated Linear Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vig-linear-complexity-visual-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, linear complexity sequence modeling networks have achieved modeling capabilities similar to Vision Transformers on a variety of computer vision tasks, while using fewer FLOPs and less memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vig-linear-complexity-visual-sequence</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
