<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 21:07:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Stable Artist: Steering Semantics in Diffusion Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stable-artist-steering-semantics-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large, text-conditioned generative diffusion models have recently gained a lot of attention for their impressive performance in generating high-fidelity images from text alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stable-artist-steering-semantics-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MegaCRN: Meta-Graph Convolutional Recurrent Network for Spatio-Temporal Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megacrn-meta-graph-convolutional-recurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatio-temporal modeling as a canonical task of multivariate time series forecasting has been a significant research topic in AI community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megacrn-meta-graph-convolutional-recurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Finetuning of Transformers for Source Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-finetuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained Transformers achieve state-of-the-art performance in various code-processing tasks but may be too large to be deployed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-finetuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning and Tree Search Methods for the Unit Commitment Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-and-tree-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When generator outages are considered, guided tree search saves over 2\% in operating costs as compared with methods using conventional $N-x$ reserve criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-and-tree-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware-efficient learning of quantum many-body states</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-efficient-learning-of-quantum-many</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient characterization of highly entangled multi-particle systems is an outstanding challenge in quantum science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-efficient-learning-of-quantum-many</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Dimensional Self Attention based Approach for Remaining Useful Life Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-self-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigated the mainstream RUL prediction models and summarized the basic steps of RUL prediction modeling in this scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-self-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instrumental Variables in Causal Inference and Machine Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instrumental-variables-in-causal-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper serves as the first effort to systematically and comprehensively introduce and discuss the IV methods and their applications in both causal inference and machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instrumental-variables-in-causal-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning over Different Types of Knowledge Graphs: Static, Temporal and Multi-Modal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-over-different-types-of-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The early works in this domain mainly focus on static KGR and tend to directly apply general knowledge graph embedding models to the reasoning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-over-different-types-of-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPop7: A Pure-Python Library for Population-Based Black-Box Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypop7-a-pure-python-library-for-population</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a pure-Python open-source library, called PyPop7, for black-box optimization (BBO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypop7-a-pure-python-library-for-population</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis of Thai Capital Market Linkages: Part II. Bivariate Copula vs. Granger Causality, a Centrality Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-thai-capital-market-linkages-part-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analytically thorough understanding of financial-market dynamics is fundamental to the promotion of capital-market innovation, efficiency, and resilience; innovative, efficient, and resilient capital market, in turn, is fundamental to the sustainable economic development of the nation and the robust financial stability of its economy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysis-of-thai-capital-market-linkages-part-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph algorithms for predicting subcellular localization at the pathway level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-algorithms-for-predicting-subcellular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein subcellular localization is an important factor in normal cellular processes and disease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-algorithms-for-predicting-subcellular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolving Semantic Confusions for Improved Zero-Shot Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-semantic-confusions-for-improved-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot detection (ZSD) is a challenging task where we aim to recognize and localize objects simultaneously, even when our model has not been trained with visual samples of a few target ("unseen") classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-semantic-confusions-for-improved-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NMS Strikes Back</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nms-strikes-back</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our detector that trains Deformable-DETR with traditional IoU-based label assignment achieved 50. 2 COCO mAP within 12 epochs (1x schedule) with ResNet50 backbone, outperforming all existing traditional or transformer-based detectors in this setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nms-strikes-back</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Prediction by Efficient Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-prediction-by-efficient-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video prediction is a challenging computer vision task that has a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-prediction-by-efficient-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALSO: Automotive Lidar Self-supervision by Occupancy estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/also-automotive-lidar-self-supervision-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea is to train the model on a pretext task which is the reconstruction of the surface on which the 3D points are sampled, and to use the underlying latent vectors as input to the perception head.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/also-automotive-lidar-self-supervision-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REAP: A Large-Scale Realistic Adversarial Patch Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reap-a-large-scale-realistic-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the REAP (REalistic Adversarial Patch) benchmark, a digital benchmark that allows the user to evaluate patch attacks on real images, and under real-world conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reap-a-large-scale-realistic-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked autoencoders is an effective solution to transformer data-hungry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-is-an-effective-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This results in ViT not performing as well as CNNs on small datasets like medicine and science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-is-an-effective-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOTCOLD Block: Fooling Thermal Infrared Detectors with a Novel Wearable Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hotcold-block-fooling-thermal-infrared</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial attacks on thermal infrared imaging expose the risk of related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hotcold-block-fooling-thermal-infrared</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor-based Sequential Learning via Hankel Matrix Representation for Next Item Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-sequential-learning-via-hankel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attentive transformer models have recently been shown to solve the next item recommendation task very efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-sequential-learning-via-hankel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ProtoPNet Really Explainable? Evaluating and Improving the Interpretability of Prototypes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-protopnet-really-explainable-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ProtoPNet and its follow-up variants (ProtoPNets) have attracted broad research interest for their intrinsic interpretability from prototypes and comparable accuracy to non-interpretable counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-protopnet-really-explainable-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoDem: Accelerating Visual Model-Based Reinforcement Learning with Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modem-accelerating-visual-model-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify key ingredients for leveraging demonstrations in model learning -- policy pretraining, targeted exploration, and oversampling of demonstration data -- which forms the three phases of our model-based RL framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modem-accelerating-visual-model-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRoUDA: Meta Self-training for Robust Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srouda-meta-self-training-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new meta self-training pipeline, named SRoUDA, for improving adversarial robustness of UDA models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srouda-meta-self-training-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPN: A Word Vector Level Data Augmentation Algorithm in Deep Learning for Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rpn-a-word-vector-level-data-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In subsequent experiments, we found that adding RPN to the training or fine-tuning model resulted in a stable boost on all 8 natural language processing tasks, including TweetEval, CoLA, and SST-2 datasets, and more significant improvements than other data augmentation algorithms. The RPN algorithm applies to all sentence-level tasks for language understanding and is used in any deep learning model with a word embedding layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rpn-a-word-vector-level-data-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborating Heterogeneous Natural Language Processing Tasks via Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborating-heterogeneous-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we further broaden the application scope of FL in NLP by proposing an Assign-Then-Contrast (denoted as ATC) framework, which enables clients with heterogeneous NLP tasks to construct an FL course and learn useful knowledge from each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborating-heterogeneous-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Cross-Encoders for Zero-Shot Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-defense-of-cross-encoders-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the number of parameters and early query-document interactions of cross-encoders play a significant role in the generalization ability of retrieval models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-defense-of-cross-encoders-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untargeted Attack against Federated Recommendation Systems via Poisonous Item Embeddings and the Defense</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/untargeted-attack-against-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on two public datasets show that ClusterAttack can effectively degrade the performance of FedRec systems while circumventing many defense methods, and UNION can improve the resistance of the system against various untargeted attacks, including our ClusterAttack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/untargeted-attack-against-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-Level Debiased Natural Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-level-debiased-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also verify that DCT can reduce biased latent features from the model's representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-level-debiased-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mul-GAD: a semi-supervised graph anomaly detection framework via aggregating multi-view information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mul-gad-a-semi-supervised-graph-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a more comprehensive conclusion, we further investigate the effect of the objective function and the number of fused views on detection performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mul-gad-a-semi-supervised-graph-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transductive Linear Probing: A Novel Framework for Few-Shot Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transductive-linear-probing-a-novel-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More recently, inspired by the development of graph self-supervised learning, transferring pretrained node embeddings for few-shot node classification could be a promising alternative to meta-learning but remains unexposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transductive-linear-probing-a-novel-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Feature Models for Learning Interacting Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-feature-models-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particle dynamics and multi-agent systems provide accurate dynamical models for studying and forecasting the behavior of complex interacting systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-feature-models-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orthogonal SVD Covariance Conditioning and Latent Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-svd-covariance-conditioning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on visual recognition demonstrate that our methods can simultaneously improve covariance conditioning and generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orthogonal-svd-covariance-conditioning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Neural Volumetric Field for Point Cloud Geometry Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-neural-volumetric-field-for-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The neural field representation of the point cloud includes the network parameters and all the latent codes, which are generated by using back-propagation over the network parameters and its input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-neural-volumetric-field-for-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DISCO: Adversarial Defense with Local Implicit Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-adversarial-defense-with-local-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of adversarial defenses for image classification, where the goal is to robustify a classifier against adversarial examples, is considered.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-adversarial-defense-with-local-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ezDPS: An Efficient and Zero-Knowledge Machine Learning Inference Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ezdps-an-efficient-and-zero-knowledge-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning as a service (MLaaS) permits resource-limited clients to access powerful data analytics services ubiquitously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ezdps-an-efficient-and-zero-knowledge-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Associations Between Natural Language Processing (NLP) Enriched Social Determinants of Health and Suicide Death among US Veterans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/associations-between-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All SDOH, measured by structured data and NLP, were significantly associated with increased risk of suicide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/associations-between-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastClass: A Time-Efficient Approach to Weakly-Supervised Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastclass-a-time-efficient-approach-to-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly-supervised text classification aims to train a classifier using only class descriptions and unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastclass-a-time-efficient-approach-to-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuS2: Fast Learning of Neural Implicit Surfaces for Multi-view Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neus2-fast-learning-of-neural-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To accelerate the training process, we integrate multi-resolution hash encodings into a neural surface representation and implement our whole algorithm in CUDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neus2-fast-learning-of-neural-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Scale Balanced 6-DoF Grasp Detection in Cluttered Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-balanced-6-dof-grasp-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, a Scale Balanced Learning (SBL) loss and an Object Balanced Sampling (OBS) strategy are designed, where SBL enlarges the gradients of the samples whose scales are in low frequency by apriori weights while OBS captures more points on small-scale objects with the help of an auxiliary segmentation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-scale-balanced-6-dof-grasp-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted Adversarial Attacks on Deep Reinforcement Learning Policies via Model Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-adversarial-attacks-on-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this metric to craft optimal adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-adversarial-attacks-on-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Knowledge Graph Service for Developing Domain Language Models in AI Software</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-knowledge-graph-service-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By enhancing the task-specific training procedure with domain knowledge graphs, we propose KnowledgeDA, a unified and low-code domain language model development service.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-knowledge-graph-service-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An approach to robust ICP initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-approach-to-robust-icp-initialization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this note, we propose an approach for initializing the Iterative Closest Point (ICP) algorithm that allows us to apply ICP to unlabelled point clouds that are related by rigid transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-approach-to-robust-icp-initialization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A soft nearest-neighbor framework for continual semi-supervised learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-soft-nearest-neighbor-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advances, the performance of state-of-the-art continual learning approaches hinges on the unrealistic scenario of fully labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-soft-nearest-neighbor-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Whac-A-Mole Dilemma: Shortcuts Come in Multiples Where Mitigating One Amplifies Others</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-whac-a-mole-dilemma-shortcuts-come-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Key to advancing the reliability of vision systems is understanding whether existing methods can overcome multiple shortcuts or struggle in a Whac-A-Mole game, i. e., where mitigating one shortcut amplifies reliance on others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-whac-a-mole-dilemma-shortcuts-come-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention-based Multi-Scale Feature Learning Network for Multimodal Medical Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-multi-scale-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a novel fixed fusion strategy termed Softmax-based weighted strategy based on the Softmax weights and matrix nuclear norm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-multi-scale-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation for Large-Scale Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we construct a pretext task, \textit{i. e.,} point cloud colorization, with a self-supervised learning to transfer the learned prior knowledge from a large amount of unlabeled point cloud to a weakly supervised network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-semantic-segmentation-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Grid-based Sensor Floor Platform for Robot Localization using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-grid-based-sensor-floor-platform-for-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sensor Floor consists of 345 nodes installed across the floor of our logistic research hall with dual-band RF and Inertial Measurement Unit (IMU) sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-grid-based-sensor-floor-platform-for-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-Free Structured Diffusion Guidance for Compositional Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-structured-diffusion-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we improve the compositional skills of T2I models, specifically more accurate attribute binding and better image compositions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-structured-diffusion-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expeditious Saliency-guided Mix-up through Random Gradient Thresholding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expeditious-saliency-guided-mix-up-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mix-up training approaches have proven to be effective in improving the generalization ability of Deep Neural Networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expeditious-saliency-guided-mix-up-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networked Restless Bandits with Positive Externalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/networked-restless-bandits-with-positive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Restless multi-armed bandits are often used to model budget-constrained resource allocation tasks where receipt of the resource is associated with an increased probability of a favorable state transition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/networked-restless-bandits-with-positive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Robust Kernel Statistics for Testing Distributional Treatment Effects Even Under One Sided Overlap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-kernel-statistics-for-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we focus on the problem of testing for causal effects that manifest in a difference in distribution for treatment and control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-kernel-statistics-for-testing</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
