<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 21:06:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging POMDPs and Bayesian decision making for robust maintenance planning under model uncertainty: An application to railway systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-pomdps-and-bayesian-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a framework to estimate POMDP transition and observation model parameters directly from available data, via Markov Chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) sampling of a Hidden Markov Model (HMM) conditioned on actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-pomdps-and-bayesian-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Visual Computing with Camera RAW Snapshots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-visual-computing-with-camera-raw</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional cameras capture image irradiance on a sensor and convert it to RGB images using an image signal processor (ISP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-visual-computing-with-camera-raw</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localizing Scan Targets from Human Pose for Autonomous Lung Ultrasound Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-scan-targets-from-human-pose-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultrasound is progressing toward becoming an affordable and versatile solution to medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localizing-scan-targets-from-human-pose-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Gold Standard: Grounding Summarization Evaluation with Robust Human Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-gold-standard-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[4) We evaluate existing automatic metrics using the collected human annotations across evaluation protocols and demonstrate how our benchmark leads to more statistically stable and significant results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-gold-standard-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Object Localization: Observing the Background to Discover Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-object-localization-observing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This way, the salient objects emerge as a by-product without any strong assumption on what an object should be.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-object-localization-observing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexiViT: One Model for All Patch Sizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexivit-one-model-for-all-patch-sizes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers convert images to sequences by slicing them into patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexivit-one-model-for-all-patch-sizes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QueryPose: Sparse Multi-Person Pose Regression via Spatial-Aware Part-Level Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/querypose-sparse-multi-person-pose-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing end-to-end methods rely on dense representations to preserve the spatial detail and structure for precise keypoint localization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/querypose-sparse-multi-person-pose-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-stage Contextual Transformer-based Convolutional Neural Network for Airway Extraction from CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-contextual-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, the total airway mask and CT images are provided to the subnetwork, and the intrapulmonary airway mask and corresponding CT scans to the subnetwork in the second stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-contextual-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASTER: Multi-task Pre-trained Bottlenecked Masked Autoencoders are Better Dense Retrievers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/master-multi-task-pre-trained-bottlenecked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense retrieval aims to map queries and passages into low-dimensional vector space for efficient similarity measuring, showing promising effectiveness in various large-scale retrieval tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/master-multi-task-pre-trained-bottlenecked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Put Attention to Temporal Saliency Patterns of Multi-Horizon Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-attention-to-temporal-saliency-patterns</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the mentioned observation, in this paper, we propose a novel architecture, Temporal Saliency Detection (TSD), on top of the attention mechanism and apply it to multi-horizon time series prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-attention-to-temporal-saliency-patterns</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreCDo: A Large Corpus for French Cross-Domain Dialect Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frecdo-a-large-corpus-for-french-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel corpus for French dialect identification comprising 413, 522 French text samples collected from public news websites in Belgium, Canada, France and Switzerland.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frecdo-a-large-corpus-for-french-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable ML for Imbalanced Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-ml-for-imbalanced-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a set of techniques that can be used by both deep learning model users to identify, visualize and understand class prototypes, sub-concepts and outlier instances; and by imbalanced learning algorithm developers to detect features and class exemplars that are key to model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-ml-for-imbalanced-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUIDD: Deep-Unfolded Interleaved Detection and Decoding for MIMO Wireless Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duidd-deep-unfolded-interleaved-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the efficacy of DUIDD using NVIDIA's Sionna link-level simulator in a 5G-near multi-user MIMO-OFDM wireless system with a novel low-complexity soft-input soft-output data detector, an optimized low-density parity-check decoder, and channel vectors from a commercial ray-tracer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duidd-deep-unfolded-interleaved-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliced Optimal Partial Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-optimal-partial-transport</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimal transport (OT) has become exceedingly popular in machine learning, data science, and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sliced-optimal-partial-transport</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAMP: Doubly Aligned Multilingual Parser for Task-Oriented Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damp-doubly-aligned-multilingual-parser-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern virtual assistants use internal semantic parsing engines to convert user utterances to actionable commands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damp-doubly-aligned-multilingual-parser-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting Distribution Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-distribution-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A distribution inference attack aims to infer statistical properties of data used to train machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-distribution-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Training of Query-Based Object Detection via Selective Query Recollection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-training-of-query-based-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates a phenomenon where query-based object detectors mispredict at the last decoding stage while predicting correctly at an intermediate stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-training-of-query-based-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-like Adaptive Modeling Multi-Agent Learning System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-like-adaptive-modeling-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a self-supervised multi-agent system, termed a memory-like adaptive modeling multi-agent learning system (MAMMALS), that realizes online learning towards behavioral pattern clustering tasks for time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-like-adaptive-modeling-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF-Art: Text-Driven Neural Radiance Fields Stylization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-art-text-driven-neural-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a powerful representation of 3D scenes, the neural radiance field (NeRF) enables high-quality novel view synthesis from multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-art-text-driven-neural-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Vision Transformers for MobileNet Size and Speed</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-vision-transformers-for-mobilenet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the success of Vision Transformers (ViTs) in computer vision tasks, recent arts try to optimize the performance and complexity of ViTs to enable efficient deployment on mobile devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-vision-transformers-for-mobilenet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RWEN-TTS: Relation-aware Word Encoding Network for Natural Text-to-Speech Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rwen-tts-relation-aware-word-encoding-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of deep learning, a huge number of text-to-speech (TTS) models which produce human-like speech have emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rwen-tts-relation-aware-word-encoding-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Generalization by Learning and Removing Domain-specific Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-by-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the images output by the encoder-decoder network, another classifier is designed to learn the domain-invariant features to conduct image classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-by-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Establishing a stronger baseline for lightweight contrastive models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-a-stronger-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common practice to address this problem is to introduce a pretrained contrastive teacher model and train the lightweight networks with distillation signals generated by the teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/establishing-a-stronger-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PulseImpute: A Novel Benchmark Task for Pulsative Physiological Signal Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulseimpute-a-novel-benchmark-task-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The promise of Mobile Health (mHealth) is the ability to use wearable sensors to monitor participant physiology at high frequencies during daily life to enable temporally-precise health interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulseimpute-a-novel-benchmark-task-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Negative Style Transfer in Hybrid Dialogue System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-negative-style-transfer-in-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the functionality of dialogue systems evolves, hybrid dialogue systems that accomplish user-specific goals and participate in open-topic chitchat with users are attracting growing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-negative-style-transfer-in-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGO: Recurrent Graph Optimizer For Multiple Rotation Averaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rago-recurrent-graph-optimizer-for-multiple-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our graph optimizer iteratively refines the global camera rotations by minimizing each node's single rotation objective function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rago-recurrent-graph-optimizer-for-multiple-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Learning for Cross-Lingual Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-cross-lingual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a cross-lingual sentiment analysis of news articles using zero-shot and few-shot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-cross-lingual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTMDet: An Empirical Study of Designing Real-Time Object Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmdet-an-empirical-study-of-designing-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to design an efficient real-time object detector that exceeds the YOLO series and is easily extensible for many object recognition tasks such as instance segmentation and rotated object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmdet-an-empirical-study-of-designing-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust, but Verify: Cross-Modality Fusion for HD Map Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-cross-modality-fusion-for-hd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-definition (HD) map change detection is the task of determining when sensor data and map data are no longer in agreement with one another due to real-world changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-cross-modality-fusion-for-hd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Detection of Contextualized Embedding Bias with Application to Ideology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-detection-of-contextualized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a fully unsupervised method to detect bias in contextualized embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-detection-of-contextualized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MABSplit: Faster Forest Training Using Multi-Armed Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mabsplit-faster-forest-training-using-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an algorithm that accelerates the training of random forests and other popular tree-based learning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mabsplit-faster-forest-training-using-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lorentz Group Equivariant Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorentz-group-equivariant-autoencoders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been significant work recently in developing machine learning models in high energy physics (HEP), for tasks such as classification, simulation, and anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorentz-group-equivariant-autoencoders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Coarse-Grained Potentials of Protein Thermodynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-coarse-grained-potentials-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The coarse-grained models are capable of accelerating the dynamics by more than three orders of magnitude while preserving the thermodynamics of the systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-coarse-grained-potentials-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DHumanGAN: Towards Photo-Realistic 3D-Aware Human Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dhumangan-towards-photo-realistic-3d-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present 3DHumanGAN, a 3D-aware generative adversarial network (GAN) that synthesizes images of full-body humans with consistent appearances under different view-angles and body-poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dhumangan-towards-photo-realistic-3d-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directional Direct Feedback Alignment: Estimating Backpropagation Paths for Efficient Learning on Neural Processors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directional-direct-feedback-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is therefore a demand for alternative algorithms to BP that could improve the latency, memory requirements, and energy footprint of neural networks on hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directional-direct-feedback-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding continuous operator learning through Physics-based boundary constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-continuous-operator-learning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical experiments based on multiple PDEs with a wide variety of applications indicate that the proposed approach ensures satisfaction of BCs, and leads to more accurate solutions over the entire domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-continuous-operator-learning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convergent Data-driven Regularizations for CT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergent-data-driven-regularizations-for-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reconstruction of images from their corresponding noisy Radon transform is a typical example of an ill-posed linear inverse problem as arising in the application of computerized tomography (CT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergent-data-driven-regularizations-for-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducible scaling laws for contrastive language-image learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducible-scaling-laws-for-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we investigate scaling laws for contrastive language-image pre-training (CLIP) with the public LAION dataset and the open-source OpenCLIP repository.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducible-scaling-laws-for-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Probabilistic Models beat GANs on Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-beat-gans-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of Deep Learning applications critically depends on the quality and scale of the underlying training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-beat-gans-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Ethics on Blockchain: Topic Analysis on Twitter Data for Blockchain Security</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-ethics-on-blockchain-topic-analysis-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that the tweets discussed profound topics of ethical concern, including security, equity, emotional sentiments, and the desire for solutions to MEV.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-ethics-on-blockchain-topic-analysis-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Artifacts in Real-World Video Super-Resolution Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-artifacts-in-real-world-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aggregate a new hidden state that contains fewer artifacts from the hidden state pool, we devise a Selective Cross Attention (SCA) module, in which the attention between input features and each hidden state is calculated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-artifacts-in-real-world-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shared Coupling-bridge for Weakly Supervised Local Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shared-coupling-bridge-for-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse local feature extraction is usually believed to be of important significance in typical vision tasks such as simultaneous localization and mapping, image matching and 3D reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shared-coupling-bridge-for-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECON: Explicit Clothed humans Obtained from Normals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/econ-explicit-clothed-humans-obtained-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of artist-curated scans, and deep implicit functions (IF), is enabling the creation of detailed, clothed, 3D humans from images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/econ-explicit-clothed-humans-obtained-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Visual Object Representations to Human Requirements: A Case Study with a Recycling Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-visual-object-representations-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robots are well-suited to alleviate the burden of repetitive and tedious manipulation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-visual-object-representations-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedSkip: Combatting Statistical Heterogeneity with Federated Skip Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedskip-combatting-statistical-heterogeneity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in addition to previous explorations for improvement in federated averaging, our analysis shows that another critical bottleneck is the poorer optima of client models in more heterogeneous conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedskip-combatting-statistical-heterogeneity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TencentPretrain: A Scalable and Flexible Toolkit for Pre-training Models of Different Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencentpretrain-a-scalable-and-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed pre-training models of different modalities are showing a rising trend of homogeneity in their model structures, which brings the opportunity to implement different pre-training models within a uniform framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tencentpretrain-a-scalable-and-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAMixer: Object-aware Mixing Layer for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oamixer-object-aware-mixing-layer-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the object labels, OAMixer computes a reweighting mask with a learnable scale parameter that intensifies the interaction of patches containing similar objects and applies the mask to the patch mixing layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oamixer-object-aware-mixing-layer-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DA Wand: Distortion-Aware Selection using Neural Mesh Parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-wand-distortion-aware-selection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a neural technique for learning to select a local sub-region around a point which can be used for mesh parameterization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-wand-distortion-aware-selection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Statistical Model for Predicting Generalization in Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-model-for-predicting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a set is hardly available in few-shot learning scenarios, a highly disregarded shortcoming in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-statistical-model-for-predicting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Mini-Batch Training with Varying Length Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-mini-batch-training-with-varying-length</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method of normalizing the lengths of the time series in a dataset by exploiting the dynamic matching ability of Dynamic Time Warping (DTW).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-mini-batch-training-with-varying-length</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
