<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 09:16:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CloudS2Mask: A novel deep learning approach for improved cloud and cloud shadow masking in Sentinel-2 imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clouds2mask-a-novel-deep-learning-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precise and efficient cloud and cloud shadow masking methods are required for the automated use of this data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clouds2mask-a-novel-deep-learning-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Feature Augmentation for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-feature-augmentation-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods focus on learning invariance across domains to enhance model robustness, and data augmentation has been widely used to learn invariant predictors, with most methods performing augmentation in the input space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-feature-augmentation-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-based Hopfield Boosting for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-hopfield-boosting-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is critical when deploying machine learning models in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-hopfield-boosting-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Distillation Improves DNA Sequence Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-improves-dna-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised pretraining (SSP) has been recognized as a method to enhance prediction accuracy in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-improves-dna-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-level Hypergraph Contrastive Learning with Adaptive Temperature Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-hypergraph-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these works have the following limitations in modeling the high-order relationships over unlabeled data: (i) They primarily focus on maximizing the agreements among individual node embeddings while neglecting the capture of group-wise collective behaviors within hypergraphs; (ii) Most of them disregard the importance of the temperature index in discriminating contrastive pairs during contrast optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-hypergraph-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Transformers with Dynamically Composable Multi-Head Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transformers-with-dynamically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of DCMHA is a $\it{Compose}$ function that transforms the attention score and weight matrices in an input-dependent way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transformers-with-dynamically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StraightPCF: Straight Point Cloud Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/straightpcf-straight-point-cloud-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud filtering is a fundamental 3D vision task, which aims to remove noise while recovering the underlying clean surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/straightpcf-straight-point-cloud-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan-DiT: A Powerful Multi-Resolution Diffusion Transformer with Fine-Grained Chinese Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan-dit-a-powerful-multi-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For fine-grained language understanding, we train a Multimodal Large Language Model to refine the captions of the images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan-dit-a-powerful-multi-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDPN6D: Residual-based Dense Point-wise Network for 6Dof Object Pose Estimation Based on RGB-D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdpn6d-residual-based-dense-point-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel method for calculating the 6DoF pose of an object using a single RGB-D image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdpn6d-residual-based-dense-point-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Vision-Language Pre-training by Cluster Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pre-training-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple strategy for masking image patches during visual-language contrastive learning that improves the quality of the learned representations and the training speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pre-training-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Collaboration Networks for Geospatial Vehicle Detection in Dense, Occluded, and Large-Scale Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-collaboration-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we first construct two multimodal dense and occlusion vehicle detection datasets for large-scale events, utilizing RGB and height map modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-collaboration-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Fairness Through Channel Pruning for Dermatological Disease Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-fairness-through-channel-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerous studies have revealed that deep learning-based medical image classification models may exhibit bias towards specific demographic attributes, such as race, gender, and age.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-fairness-through-channel-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EndoDAC: Efficient Adapting Foundation Model for Self-Supervised Depth Estimation from Any Endoscopic Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endodac-efficient-adapting-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Endoscopic Depth Any Camera (EndoDAC) which is an efficient self-supervised depth estimation framework that adapts foundation models to endoscopic scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endodac-efficient-adapting-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientTrain++: Generalized Curriculum Learning for Efficient Visual Backbone Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-generalized-curriculum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These patterns, when observed through frequency and spatial domains, incorporate lower-frequency components, and the natural image contents without distortion or data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-generalized-curriculum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEDNet: Twin Encoder Decoder Neural Network for 2D Camera and LiDAR Road Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tednet-twin-encoder-decoder-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust road surface estimation is required for autonomous ground vehicles to navigate safely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tednet-twin-encoder-decoder-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating LLMs at Evaluating Temporal Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-llms-at-evaluating-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) highlights the urgent need for evolving evaluation methodologies that keep pace with improvements in language comprehension and information processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-llms-at-evaluating-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-aware synthesis of pathological lung CT scans using CycleGAN for enhanced semi-supervised lung segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-synthesis-of-pathological-lung-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lung surrounding is derived based on ground truth lung masks available in the healthy domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-synthesis-of-pathological-lung-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Time to Waste: Squeeze Time into Channel for Mobile Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-time-to-waste-squeeze-time-into-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to squeeze the time axis of a video sequence into the channel dimension and present a lightweight video recognition network, term as \textit{SqueezeTime}, for mobile video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-time-to-waste-squeeze-time-into-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Knowledge Graph Embedding with Universal Orthogonal Parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-knowledge-graph-embedding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in knowledge graph embedding (KGE) rely on Euclidean/hyperbolic orthogonal relation transformations to model intrinsic logical patterns and topological structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-knowledge-graph-embedding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS MARCO Web Search: a Large-scale Information-rich Web Dataset with Millions of Real Click Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-marco-web-search-a-large-scale-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent breakthroughs in large models have highlighted the critical significance of data scale, labels and modals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-marco-web-search-a-large-scale-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepHYDRA: Resource-Efficient Time-Series Anomaly Detection in Dynamically-Configured Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deephydra-resource-efficient-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A downside of such methods is that they require a static input size, or lose data through cropping, sampling, or other dimensionality reduction methods, making deployment on systems with variability on monitored data channels, such as computing clusters difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deephydra-resource-efficient-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARDEN, Can You Repeat That? Defending against Jailbreaks via Repetition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parden-can-you-repeat-that-defending-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A promising approach is to use the LLM itself as the safeguard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parden-can-you-repeat-that-defending-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synergistic Integration of Coordinate Network and Tensorial Feature for Improving Neural Radiance Fields from Sparse Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergistic-integration-of-coordinate-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it has limitations in capturing low-frequency details and tends to overuse parameters for low-frequency features due to its bias toward fine details, despite its multi-resolution concept.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergistic-integration-of-coordinate-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on the Robustness of Massively Multilingual Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Massively multilingual neural machine translation (MMNMT) has been proven to enhance the translation quality of low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLHF Workflow: From Reward Modeling to Online RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlhf-workflow-from-reward-modeling-to-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the workflow of Online Iterative Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) in this technical report, which is widely reported to outperform its offline counterpart by a large margin in the recent large language model (LLM) literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlhf-workflow-from-reward-modeling-to-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESTAD: REconstruction and Similarity based Transformer for time series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restad-reconstruction-and-similarity-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This layer fits a non-parametric density in the latent representation, such that a high RBF output indicates similarity with predominantly normal training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restad-reconstruction-and-similarity-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEPTH: Discourse Education through Pre-Training Hierarchically</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-discourse-education-through-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language Models (LMs) often struggle with linguistic understanding at the discourse level, even though discourse patterns such as coherence, cohesion, and narrative flow are prevalent in their pre-training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-discourse-education-through-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LlamaTurk: Adapting Open-Source Generative Large Language Models for Low-Resource Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamaturk-adapting-open-source-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite advancements in English-dominant generative large language models, further development is needed for low-resource languages to enhance global accessibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamaturk-adapting-open-source-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeVA: Offline MLLM as Training-Free Video Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeva-offline-mllm-as-training-free-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study provides an essential, yet must-know baseline, and reveals several surprising findings: 1) FreeVA, leveraging only offline image-based MLLM without additional training, excels in zero-shot video question-answering (e. g., MSVD-QA, ActivityNet-QA, and MSRVTT-QA), even surpassing state-of-the-art methods that involve video instruction tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeva-offline-mllm-as-training-free-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Platonic Representation Hypothesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-platonic-representation-hypothesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that representations in AI models, particularly deep networks, are converging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-platonic-representation-hypothesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Exploration via Reflected Replica Exchange Stochastic Gradient Langevin Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-exploration-via-reflected-replica</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Replica exchange stochastic gradient Langevin dynamics (reSGLD) is an effective sampler for non-convex learning in large-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-exploration-via-reflected-replica</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Object Pose Estimation: A Comprehensive Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-object-pose-estimation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object pose estimation is a fundamental computer vision problem with broad applications in augmented reality and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-object-pose-estimation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaOut: Do We Really Need Mamba for Vision?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaout-do-we-really-need-mamba-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For vision tasks, as image classification does not align with either characteristic, we hypothesize that Mamba is not necessary for this task; Detection and segmentation tasks are also not autoregressive, yet they adhere to the long-sequence characteristic, so we believe it is still worthwhile to explore Mamba's potential for these tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaout-do-we-really-need-mamba-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptLink: Leveraging Large Language Models for Cross-Source Biomedical Concept Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptlink-leveraging-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, PromptLink is a generic framework without reliance on additional prior knowledge, context, or training data, making it well-suited for concept linking across various types of data sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptlink-leveraging-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binning as a Pretext Task: Improving Self-Supervised Learning in Tabular Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binning-as-a-pretext-task-improving-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability of deep networks to learn superior representations hinges on leveraging the proper inductive biases, considering the inherent properties of datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binning-as-a-pretext-task-improving-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OverlapMamba: Novel Shift State Space Model for LiDAR-based Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overlapmamba-novel-shift-state-space-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a novel way, we employ a stochastic reconstruction approach to build shift state space models, compressing the visual representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overlapmamba-novel-shift-state-space-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacBehaviour: An R package for behavioural experimentation on large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macbehaviour-an-r-package-for-behavioural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In summary, "MacBehaviour" is an R package for machine behaviour studies which offers a user-friendly interface and comprehensive features to simplify and standardize the experimental process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macbehaviour-an-r-package-for-behavioural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling of Time-varying Wireless Communication Channel with Fading and Shadowing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-of-time-varying-wireless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new approach that combines a deep learning neural network with a mixture density network model to derive the conditional probability density function (PDF) of receiving power given a communication distance in general wireless communication systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-of-time-varying-wireless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Localized Adaptive Risk Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localized-adaptive-risk-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adaptive Risk Control (ARC) is an online calibration strategy based on set prediction that offers worst-case deterministic long-term risk control, as well as statistical marginal coverage guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/localized-adaptive-risk-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyLLM: Few-shot Anomaly Edge Detection for Dynamic Graphs using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyllm-few-shot-anomaly-edge-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the evolving of time, the types of anomaly edges are emerging and the labeled anomaly samples are few for each type.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyllm-few-shot-anomaly-edge-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeRFlow: Piecewise Rectified Flow as Universal Plug-and-Play Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perflow-piecewise-rectified-flow-as-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Piecewise Rectified Flow (PeRFlow), a flow-based method for accelerating diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perflow-piecewise-rectified-flow-as-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sakuga-42M Dataset: Scaling Up Cartoon Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sakuga-42m-dataset-scaling-up-cartoon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we harness the success of the scaling paradigm to benefit cartoon research?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sakuga-42m-dataset-scaling-up-cartoon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Sequence Parallelism Approach for Long Context Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-sequence-parallelism-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequence parallelism (SP), which divides the sequence dimension of input tensors across multiple computational devices, is becoming key to unlocking the long-context capabilities of generative AI models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-sequence-parallelism-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANTONMT: Investigating Back-Translation and Model-Switch Mechanisms for Cantonese-English Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cantonmt-investigating-back-translation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this, a new parallel corpus has been created by combining different available corpora online with preprocessing and cleaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cantonmt-investigating-back-translation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Retrieval-Augmented Generation: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consequently enhanced an extensive survey and proposed an analysis framework for benchmarks of RAG systems, RAGR (Retrieval, Generation, Additional Requirement), designed to systematically analyze RAG benchmarks by focusing on measurable outputs and established truths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Analysis of Static Word Embeddings for Turkish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-analysis-of-static-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are basically two types of word embedding models which are non-contextual (static) models and contextual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-analysis-of-static-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-VOILA: Gaze-Facilitated Information Querying in Daily Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-voila-gaze-facilitated-information-querying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern information querying systems are progressively incorporating multimodal inputs like vision and audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-voila-gaze-facilitated-information-querying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RATLIP: Generative Adversarial CLIP Text-to-Image Synthesis Based on Recurrent Affine Transformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ratlip-generative-adversarial-clip-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, both our generator and discriminator utilize the powerful pre-trained model, Clip, which has been extensively employed for establishing associations between text and images through the learning of multimodal representations in latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ratlip-generative-adversarial-clip-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Decision Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-decision-mamba</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce two novel methods, Decision Mamba (DM) and Hierarchical Decision Mamba (HDM), aimed at enhancing the performance of the Transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-decision-mamba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDFormer:When Degradation Prediction Embraces Diffusion Model for Blind Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdformer-when-degradation-prediction-embraces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing Blind image Super-Resolution (BSR) methods focus on estimating either kernel or degradation information, but have long overlooked the essential content details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdformer-when-degradation-prediction-embraces</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
