<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:14:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xmodel-VLM: A Simple Baseline for Multimodal Vision Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmodel-vlm-a-simple-baseline-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Xmodel-VLM, a cutting-edge multimodal vision language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmodel-vlm-a-simple-baseline-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RobustMVS: Single Domain Generalized Deep Multi-view Stereo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustmvs-single-domain-generalized-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate the generalization results, we build a novel MVS domain generalization benchmark including synthetic and real-world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustmvs-single-domain-generalized-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReconBoost: Boosting Can Achieve Modality Reconcilement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconboost-boosting-can-achieve-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores a novel multi-modal alternating learning paradigm pursuing a reconciliation between the exploitation of uni-modal features and the exploration of cross-modal interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconboost-boosting-can-achieve-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeX++: Learning Time-Series Explanations with Information Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timex-learning-time-series-explanations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The design of the objective function builds upon the principle of information bottleneck (IB), and modifies the IB objective function to avoid trivial solutions and distributional shift issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timex-learning-time-series-explanations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaze-DETR: Using Expert Gaze to Reduce False Positives in Vulvovaginal Candidiasis Screening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-detr-using-expert-gaze-to-reduce-false</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate detection of vulvovaginal candidiasis is critical for women's health, yet its sparse distribution and visually ambiguous characteristics pose significant challenges for accurate identification by pathologists and neural networks alike.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-detr-using-expert-gaze-to-reduce-false</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICAL: Implicit Character-Aided Learning for Enhanced Handwritten Mathematical Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ical-implicit-character-aided-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant progress has been made in the field of handwritten mathematical expression recognition, while existing encoder-decoder methods are usually difficult to model global information in \LaTeX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ical-implicit-character-aided-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenGait: A Comprehensive Benchmark Study for Gait Recognition towards Better Practicality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengait-a-comprehensive-benchmark-study-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we first develop OpenGait, a flexible and efficient gait recognition platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengait-a-comprehensive-benchmark-study-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lens functions for exploring UMAP Projections with Domain Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lens-functions-for-exploring-umap-projections</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of the lens functions is demonstrated in two use cases and their computational cost is analysed in a synthetic benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lens-functions-for-exploring-umap-projections</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMFusion: Multi-modality Diffusion Model for Lymph Node Metastasis Diagnosis in Esophageal Cancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmfusion-multi-modality-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, efficient and effective interactions between multi-modal representations need to be further explored, lacking insightful exploration of prognostic correlation in multi-modality features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmfusion-multi-modality-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Space Learning for Cross-Color Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-space-learning-for-cross-color-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The primary color profile of the same identity is assumed to remain consistent in typical Person Re-identification (Person ReID) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-space-learning-for-cross-color-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeCoDEx: Confounder Detector Guidance for Improved Diffusion-based Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decodex-confounder-detector-guidance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning classifiers are prone to latching onto dominant confounders present in a dataset rather than on the causal markers associated with the target class, leading to poor generalization and biased predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decodex-confounder-detector-guidance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CloudS2Mask: A novel deep learning approach for improved cloud and cloud shadow masking in Sentinel-2 imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clouds2mask-a-novel-deep-learning-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precise and efficient cloud and cloud shadow masking methods are required for the automated use of this data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clouds2mask-a-novel-deep-learning-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSHazeDiff: A Unified Fourier-aware Diffusion Model for Remote Sensing Image Dehazing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rshazediff-a-unified-fourier-aware-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since remote sensing images contain extensive small-scale texture structures, it is important to effectively restore image details from hazy images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rshazediff-a-unified-fourier-aware-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-based Hopfield Boosting for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-hopfield-boosting-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is critical when deploying machine learning models in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-hopfield-boosting-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Debiased Inference via Automatic Differentiation and Probabilistic Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-debiased-inference-via-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an algorithm that simplifies the construction of efficient estimators, making them accessible to a broader audience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-debiased-inference-via-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysing Cross-Speaker Convergence in Face-to-Face Dialogue through the Lens of Automatically Detected Shared Linguistic Constructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-cross-speaker-convergence-in-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversation requires a substantial amount of coordination between dialogue participants, from managing turn taking to negotiating mutual understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analysing-cross-speaker-convergence-in-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Feature Augmentation for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-feature-augmentation-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods focus on learning invariance across domains to enhance model robustness, and data augmentation has been widely used to learn invariant predictors, with most methods performing augmentation in the input space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-feature-augmentation-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promoting AI Equity in Science: Generalized Domain Prompt Learning for Accessible VLM Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promoting-ai-equity-in-science-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework paves the way for sustainable and inclusive VLM research, transcending the barriers between academia and industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promoting-ai-equity-in-science-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the Pope Catholic? Yes, the Pope is Catholic. Generative Evaluation of Intent Resolution in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-pope-catholic-yes-the-pope-is-catholic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans often express their communicative intents indirectly or non-literally, which requires their interlocutors -- human or AI -- to understand beyond the literal meaning of words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-the-pope-catholic-yes-the-pope-is-catholic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Fairness Through Channel Pruning for Dermatological Disease Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-fairness-through-channel-pruning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerous studies have revealed that deep learning-based medical image classification models may exhibit bias towards specific demographic attributes, such as race, gender, and age.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-fairness-through-channel-pruning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jacobian Regularizer-based Neural Granger Causality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jacobian-regularizer-based-neural-granger</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advancement of neural networks, diverse methods for neural Granger causality have emerged, which demonstrate proficiency in handling complex data, and nonlinear relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jacobian-regularizer-based-neural-granger</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Transformers with Dynamically Composable Multi-Head Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transformers-with-dynamically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of DCMHA is a $\it{Compose}$ function that transforms the attention score and weight matrices in an input-dependent way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transformers-with-dynamically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Prior Information Generation with CLIP for Few-Shot Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-prior-information-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot segmentation remains challenging due to the limitations of its labeling information for unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-prior-information-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Distributed Approach to Autonomous Intersection Management via Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-distributed-approach-to-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous intersection management (AIM) poses significant challenges due to the intricate nature of real-world traffic scenarios and the need for a highly expensive centralised server in charge of simultaneously controlling all the vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-distributed-approach-to-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-aware synthesis of pathological lung CT scans using CycleGAN for enhanced semi-supervised lung segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-synthesis-of-pathological-lung-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lung surrounding is derived based on ground truth lung masks available in the healthy domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-synthesis-of-pathological-lung-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating LLMs at Evaluating Temporal Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-llms-at-evaluating-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) highlights the urgent need for evolving evaluation methodologies that keep pace with improvements in language comprehension and information processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-llms-at-evaluating-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADA-Track: End-to-End Multi-Camera 3D Multi-Object Tracking with Alternating Detection and Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-track-end-to-end-multi-camera-3d-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a learnable data association module based on edge-augmented cross-attention, leveraging appearance and geometric features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ada-track-end-to-end-multi-camera-3d-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RS-Reg: Probabilistic and Robust Certified Regression Through Randomized Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rs-reg-probabilistic-and-robust-certified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Randomized smoothing has shown promising certified robustness against adversaries in classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rs-reg-probabilistic-and-robust-certified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEDNet: Twin Encoder Decoder Neural Network for 2D Camera and LiDAR Road Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tednet-twin-encoder-decoder-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust road surface estimation is required for autonomous ground vehicles to navigate safely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tednet-twin-encoder-decoder-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treatment Effect Estimation for User Interest Exploration on Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treatment-effect-estimation-for-user-interest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The empirical results validate the effectiveness of UpliftRec in discovering users' hidden interests while achieving superior recommendation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treatment-effect-estimation-for-user-interest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted Augmentation for Low-Resource Event Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-augmentation-for-low-resource-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing the challenge of low-resource information extraction remains an ongoing issue due to the inherent information scarcity within limited training examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-augmentation-for-low-resource-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientTrain++: Generalized Curriculum Learning for Efficient Visual Backbone Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-generalized-curriculum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These patterns, when observed through frequency and spatial domains, incorporate lower-frequency components, and the natural image contents without distortion or data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficienttrain-generalized-curriculum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Knowledge Graph Embedding with Universal Orthogonal Parameterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-knowledge-graph-embedding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in knowledge graph embedding (KGE) rely on Euclidean/hyperbolic orthogonal relation transformations to model intrinsic logical patterns and topological structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-knowledge-graph-embedding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Time to Waste: Squeeze Time into Channel for Mobile Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-time-to-waste-squeeze-time-into-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to squeeze the time axis of a video sequence into the channel dimension and present a lightweight video recognition network, term as \textit{SqueezeTime}, for mobile video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-time-to-waste-squeeze-time-into-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Distillation Improves DNA Sequence Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-improves-dna-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised pretraining (SSP) has been recognized as a method to enhance prediction accuracy in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-improves-dna-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-level Hypergraph Contrastive Learning with Adaptive Temperature Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-hypergraph-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these works have the following limitations in modeling the high-order relationships over unlabeled data: (i) They primarily focus on maximizing the agreements among individual node embeddings while neglecting the capture of group-wise collective behaviors within hypergraphs; (ii) Most of them disregard the importance of the temperature index in discriminating contrastive pairs during contrast optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-hypergraph-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EndoDAC: Efficient Adapting Foundation Model for Self-Supervised Depth Estimation from Any Endoscopic Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endodac-efficient-adapting-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Endoscopic Depth Any Camera (EndoDAC) which is an efficient self-supervised depth estimation framework that adapts foundation models to endoscopic scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endodac-efficient-adapting-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Vision-Language Pre-training by Cluster Masking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pre-training-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple strategy for masking image patches during visual-language contrastive learning that improves the quality of the learned representations and the training speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-vision-language-pre-training-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Output-decomposed Learning of Mealy Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/output-decomposed-learning-of-mealy-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an active automata learning algorithm which learns a decomposition of a finite state machine, based on projecting onto individual outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/output-decomposed-learning-of-mealy-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Collaboration Networks for Geospatial Vehicle Detection in Dense, Occluded, and Large-Scale Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-collaboration-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we first construct two multimodal dense and occlusion vehicle detection datasets for large-scale events, utilizing RGB and height map modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-collaboration-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan-DiT: A Powerful Multi-Resolution Diffusion Transformer with Fine-Grained Chinese Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan-dit-a-powerful-multi-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For fine-grained language understanding, we train a Multimodal Large Language Model to refine the captions of the images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan-dit-a-powerful-multi-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RDPN6D: Residual-based Dense Point-wise Network for 6Dof Object Pose Estimation Based on RGB-D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdpn6d-residual-based-dense-point-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel method for calculating the 6DoF pose of an object using a single RGB-D image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rdpn6d-residual-based-dense-point-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StraightPCF: Straight Point Cloud Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/straightpcf-straight-point-cloud-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud filtering is a fundamental 3D vision task, which aims to remove noise while recovering the underlying clean surfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/straightpcf-straight-point-cloud-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boostlet.js: Image processing plugins for the web via JavaScript injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boostlet-js-image-processing-plugins-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can web-based image processing and visualization tools easily integrate into existing websites without significant time and effort?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boostlet-js-image-processing-plugins-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Selection Bias in Machine Learning for Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-selection-bias-in-machine-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose two independent networks (T-Net) and a multitasking network (MT-Net) for addressing SSB, where one network/task identifies the target subpopulation which is representative of the study population and the second makes predictions for the identified subpopulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-selection-bias-in-machine-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Investigation of Distilling Large Language Models into Cross-Encoders for Passage Re-ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-investigation-of-distilling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-encoders distilled from large language models are more effective re-rankers than cross-encoders fine-tuned using manually labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-investigation-of-distilling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many-Shot Regurgitation (MSR) Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-shot-regurgitation-msr-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings reveal a striking difference in the distribution of verbatim matches between $D_{\rm pre}$ and $D_{\rm post}$, with the frequency of verbatim reproduction being significantly higher when LLMs (e. g. GPT models and LLaMAs) are prompted with text from datasets they were likely trained on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-shot-regurgitation-msr-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Decision Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-decision-mamba</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce two novel methods, Decision Mamba (DM) and Hierarchical Decision Mamba (HDM), aimed at enhancing the performance of the Transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-decision-mamba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Analysis of Static Word Embeddings for Turkish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-analysis-of-static-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are basically two types of word embedding models which are non-contextual (static) models and contextual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-analysis-of-static-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Expansion and enhanced Compression for Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-expansion-and-enhanced-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this context, we propose a new algorithm that enhances the compression of previous class knowledge by cutting and mixing patches of previous class samples with the new images during compression using our Rehearsal-CutMix method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-expansion-and-enhanced-compression</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
