<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:12:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Structural-Based Uncertainty in Deep Learning Across Anatomical Scales: Analysis in White Matter Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-based-uncertainty-in-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results from a multi-centric MRI dataset of 172 patients demonstrate that our proposed measures more effectively capture model errors at the lesion and patient scales compared to measures that average voxel-scale uncertainty values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-based-uncertainty-in-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SentAlign: Accurate and Scalable Sentence Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentalign-accurate-and-scalable-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SentAlign, an accurate sentence alignment tool designed to handle very large parallel document pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentalign-accurate-and-scalable-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Is Multilinguality a Curse? Language Modeling for 250 High- and Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-is-multilinguality-a-curse-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, concrete evidence for the effects of multilinguality on language modeling performance in individual languages remains scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-is-multilinguality-a-curse-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Similarity is Not Enough to Explain Language Model Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-similarity-is-not-enough-to-explain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models achieve high performance on many but not all downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-similarity-is-not-enough-to-explain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WildlifeDatasets: An open-source toolkit for animal re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildlifedatasets-an-open-source-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present WildlifeDatasets (https://github. com/WildlifeDatasets/wildlife-datasets) - an open-source toolkit intended primarily for ecologists and computer-vision / machine-learning researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildlifedatasets-an-open-source-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Ocean of Biases: Political Bias Attribution in Language Models via Causal Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-ocean-of-biases-political-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) has sparked intense debate regarding their ability to perceive and interpret complex socio-political landscapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-ocean-of-biases-political-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Meme-ing: Measuring Linguistic Variation in Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-meme-ing-measuring-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much work in the space of NLP has used computational methods to explore sociolinguistic variation in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-meme-ing-measuring-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Knowledge Editing in Language Models via Relation Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-knowledge-editing-in-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Editing (KE) for modifying factual knowledge in Large Language Models (LLMs) has been receiving increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-knowledge-editing-in-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toulouse Hyperspectral Data Set: a benchmark data set to assess semi-supervised spectral representation learning and pixel-wise classification techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toulouse-hyperspectral-data-set-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Airborne hyperspectral images can be used to map the land cover in large urban areas, thanks to their very high spatial and spectral resolutions on a wide spectral domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toulouse-hyperspectral-data-set-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-shot Visual Question Answering via Large Language Models with Reasoning Question Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-visual-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This results in a set of candidate answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-visual-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Domain-based Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-based-dataset-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents FreD, a novel parameterization method for dataset distillation, which utilizes the frequency domain to distill a small-sized synthetic dataset from a large-sized original dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-based-dataset-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable and Effective Generative Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-and-effective-generative-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper represents an important milestone in generative retrieval research by showing, for the first time, that generative retrieval models can be trained to perform effectively on large-scale standard retrieval benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-and-effective-generative-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Transformer Learning with Proximity Data Generation for Text-Based Person Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-transformer-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a proximity data generation (PDG) module to automatically produce more diverse data for cross-modal training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-transformer-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Generalizable SER: Soft Labeling and Data Augmentation for Modeling Temporal Emotion Shifts in Large-Scale Multilingual Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalizable-ser-soft-labeling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing emotions in spoken communication is crucial for advanced human-machine interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-generalizable-ser-soft-labeling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Potential of Large Language Models in Computational Argumentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-large-language-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated strong abilities in understanding context and generating natural language, it is worthwhile to evaluate the performance of LLMs on various computational argumentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-large-language-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safer-Instruct: Aligning Language Models with Automated Preference Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safer-instruct-aligning-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) is a vital strategy for enhancing model safety in language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safer-instruct-aligning-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConeQuest: A Benchmark for Cone Segmentation on Mars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conequest-a-benchmark-for-cone-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying pitted cones globally on Mars would be of great importance, but expert geologists are unable to sort through the massive orbital image archives to identify all examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conequest-a-benchmark-for-cone-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4K-Resolution Photo Exposure Correction at 125 FPS with ~8K Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4k-resolution-photo-exposure-correction-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The illumination of improperly exposed photographs has been widely corrected using deep convolutional neural networks or Transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4k-resolution-photo-exposure-correction-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate Helps Supervise Unreliable Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debate-helps-supervise-unreliable-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparing debate to a baseline we call consultancy, where a single expert argues for only one answer which is correct half of the time, we find that debate performs significantly better, with 84% judge accuracy compared to consultancy's 74%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debate-helps-supervise-unreliable-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvNet vs Transformer, Supervised vs CLIP: Beyond ImageNet Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnet-vs-transformer-supervised-vs-clip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern computer vision offers a great variety of models to practitioners, and selecting a model from multiple options for specific applications can be challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnet-vs-transformer-supervised-vs-clip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factcheck-GPT: End-to-End Fine-Grained Document-Level Fact-Checking and Correction of LLM Output</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcheck-gpt-end-to-end-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increased use of large language models (LLMs) across a variety of real-world applications calls for mechanisms to verify the factual accuracy of their outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factcheck-gpt-end-to-end-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target-oriented Domain Adaptation for Infrared Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-oriented-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DASRGAN operates on the synergy of two key components: 1) Texture-Oriented Adaptation (TOA) to refine texture details meticulously, and 2) Noise-Oriented Adaptation (NOA), dedicated to minimizing noise transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-oriented-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It Takes Two to Negotiate: Modeling Social Exchange in Online Multiplayer Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/it-takes-two-to-negotiate-modeling-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We annotated a dataset of over 10, 000 chat messages for different negotiation strategies and empirically examined their importance in predicting long- and short-term game outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/it-takes-two-to-negotiate-modeling-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning with Model Predictive Control for Highway Ramp Metering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-with-model-predictive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the backdrop of an increasingly pressing need for effective urban and highway transportation systems, this work explores the synergy between model-based and learning-based strategies to enhance traffic flow management by use of an innovative approach to the problem of highway ramp metering control that embeds Reinforcement Learning techniques within the Model Predictive Control framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-with-model-predictive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token Prediction as Implicit Classification to Identify LLM-Generated Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-prediction-as-implicit-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach for identifying the possible large language models (LLMs) involved in text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-prediction-as-implicit-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Toeplitz Neural Network with Constant-time Inference Complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-toeplitz-neural-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, State Space Models (SSMs) achieve lower performance than TNNs in language modeling but offer the advantage of constant inference complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-toeplitz-neural-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Generation and Evaluation Capabilities of Large Language Models for Instruction Controllable Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-generation-and-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study reveals that instruction controllable text summarization remains a challenging task for LLMs, since (1) all LLMs evaluated still make factual and other types of errors in their summaries; (2) all LLM-based evaluation methods cannot achieve a strong alignment with human annotators when judging the quality of candidate summaries; (3) different LLMs show large performance gaps in summary generation and evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-generation-and-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Complex Disease Trajectories using Deep Generative Models with Semi-Supervised Latent Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-disease-trajectories-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a deep generative time series approach using latent temporal processes for modeling and holistically analyzing complex disease trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-disease-trajectories-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stopping Methods for Technology Assisted Reviews based on Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stopping-methods-for-technology-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Technology Assisted Review (TAR), which aims to reduce the effort required to screen collections of documents for relevance, is used to develop systematic reviews of medical evidence and identify documents that must be disclosed in response to legal proceedings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stopping-methods-for-technology-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MC^2: A Multilingual Corpus of Minority Languages in China</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-2-a-multilingual-corpus-of-minority</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing LLMs exhibit limited abilities in understanding low-resource languages, including the minority languages in China, due to a lack of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-2-a-multilingual-corpus-of-minority</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Large Language Models Temporally Grounded?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-temporally-grounded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we provide LLMs with textual narratives and probe them with respect to their common-sense knowledge of the structure and duration of events, their ability to order events along a timeline, and self-consistency within their temporal model (e. g., temporal relations such as after and before are mutually exclusive for any pair of events).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-temporally-grounded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Efficient and Incremental Spectral Clustering via Parametric Spectral Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-and-incremental-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The findings of this research contribute to the advancement of clustering techniques and open new avenues for efficient and effective data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-and-incremental-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated title and abstract screening for scoping reviews using the GPT-4 Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-title-and-abstract-screening-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scoping reviews, a type of literature review, require intensive human effort to screen large numbers of scholarly sources for their relevance to the review objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-title-and-abstract-screening-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Variational Auto-Encoder Architectures, Configurations, and Datasets for Generative Music Explainable AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-variational-auto-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper contributes a systematic examination of the impact that different combinations of Variational Auto-Encoder models (MeasureVAE and AdversarialVAE), configurations of latent space in the AI model (from 4 to 256 latent dimensions), and training datasets (Irish folk, Turkish folk, Classical, and pop) have on music generation performance when 2 or 4 meaningful musical attributes are imposed on the generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-variational-auto-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen-Audio: Advancing Universal Audio Understanding via Unified Large-Scale Audio-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-audio-advancing-universal-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, instruction-following audio-language models have received broad attention for audio interaction with humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-audio-advancing-universal-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Open-Ended Visual Recognition with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-ended-visual-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Localizing and recognizing objects in the open-ended physical world poses a long-standing challenge within the domain of machine perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-ended-visual-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture of Coupled HMMs for Robust Modeling of Multivariate Healthcare Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-coupled-hmms-for-robust-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on challenging real-world epidemiological and semi-synthetic data demonstrate the advantages of the M-CHMM: improved data fit, capacity to efficiently handle missing and noisy measurements, improved prediction accuracy, and ability to identify interpretable subsets in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-coupled-hmms-for-robust-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Language Instruction Tuning: A Review and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-instruction-tuning-a-review</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction tuning is an essential supervised training phase for Large Language Models (LLMs), with the goal of enhancing LLMs' capacity to generalize instruction execution and adapt to user preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-instruction-tuning-a-review</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Abstractive Summarization of Diverse Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-abstractive-summarization-of-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first formally define fairness in abstractive summarization as not underrepresenting perspectives of any groups of people and propose four reference-free automatic metrics measuring the differences between target and source perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-abstractive-summarization-of-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Semi-supervised Hierarchical Stacked Encoder for Legal Judgement Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semi-supervised-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the judgment of a legal case from its unannotated case facts is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semi-supervised-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models are Better Bug Detector Through Code-Pair Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-better-bug-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our task in real-world dataset of bug detection and two most powerful LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-better-bug-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cattle Identification Using Muzzle Images and Deep Learning Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cattle-identification-using-muzzle-images-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional animal identification methods such as ear-tagging, ear notching, and branding have been effective but pose risks to the animal and have scalability issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cattle-identification-using-muzzle-images-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Adversarial Node Placement in Decentralized Federated Learning Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-adversarial-node-placement-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses this gap by analyzing the performance of decentralized FL for various adversarial placement strategies when adversaries can jointly coordinate their placement within a network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-adversarial-node-placement-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-efficient Stochastic methods for Memory-based Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-stochastic-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training Memory-based transformers can require a large amount of memory and can be quite inefficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-stochastic-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Using Distribution-Based Compositionality Assessment to Evaluate Compositional Generalisation in Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-using-distribution-based-compositionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a fully-automated procedure to create natural language compositionality benchmarks, making it simple and inexpensive to apply it further to other datasets and languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-using-distribution-based-compositionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEC-DePenD: Non-Autoregressive Grammatical Error Correction with Decoupled Permutation and Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gec-depend-non-autoregressive-grammatical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grammatical error correction (GEC) is an important NLP task that is currently usually solved with autoregressive sequence-to-sequence models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gec-depend-non-autoregressive-grammatical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deformation-based morphometry framework for disentangling Alzheimer's disease from normal aging using learned normal aging templates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deformation-based-morphometry-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a deformation-based morphometry framework to estimate normal aging and AD-specific atrophy patterns of subjects from morphological MRI scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deformation-based-morphometry-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiPar: A Lightweight Parallel Learning Model for Practical In-Vehicle Network Intrusion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipar-a-lightweight-parallel-learning-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through experiments, we prove that LiPar has great detection performance, running efficiency, and lightweight model size, which can be well adapted to the in-vehicle environment practically and protect the in-vehicle CAN bus security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipar-a-lightweight-parallel-learning-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Training for Semantic Segmentation with Output Contrastive Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-training-for-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning-based segmentation models have achieved impressive performance on public benchmarks, generalizing well to unseen environments remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-training-for-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eval-GCSC: A New Metric for Evaluating ChatGPT's Performance in Chinese Spelling Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eval-gcsc-a-new-metric-for-evaluating-chatgpt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in the Chinese Spelling Correction (CSC) task, we observe a discrepancy: while ChatGPT performs well under human evaluation, it scores poorly according to traditional metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eval-gcsc-a-new-metric-for-evaluating-chatgpt</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
