<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 21:06:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MDAESF: Cine MRI Reconstruction Based on Motion-Guided Deformable Alignment and Efficient Spatiotemporal Self-Attention Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdaesf-cine-mri-reconstruction-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cine MRI can jointly obtain the continuous influence of the anatomical structure and physiological and pathological mechanisms of organs in the two dimensions of time domain and space domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdaesf-cine-mri-reconstruction-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMMDet: Road-Side Multitype and Multigroup Sensor Detection System for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmmdet-road-side-multitype-and-multigroup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we implement muti-type sensor detection and multi-group sensors fusion in this environment, including camera-radar and camera-lidar detection based on result-level fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmmdet-road-side-multitype-and-multigroup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invertible Kernel PCA with Random Fourier Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invertible-kernel-pca-with-random-fourier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kernel principal component analysis (kPCA) is a widely studied method to construct a low-dimensional data representation after a nonlinear transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invertible-kernel-pca-with-random-fourier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Image-in-Audio Deep Steganography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-image-in-audio-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of steganography has experienced a surge of interest due to the recent advancements in AI-powered techniques, particularly in the context of multimodal setups that enable the concealment of signals within signals of a different nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-image-in-audio-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMR: A Large-Scale Multi-Reference Dataset for Reference-based Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmr-a-large-scale-multi-reference-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we construct a large-scale, multi-reference super-resolution dataset, named LMR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmr-a-large-scale-multi-reference-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Legibility of Visual Text Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-legibility-of-visual-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address this gap by learning models that predict the legibility of a perturbed string, and rank candidate perturbations based on their legibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-legibility-of-visual-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceXHuBERT: Text-less Speech-driven E(X)pressive 3D Facial Animation Synthesis Using Self-Supervised Speech Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facexhubert-text-less-speech-driven-e-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents FaceXHuBERT, a text-less speech-driven 3D facial animation generation method that allows to capture personalized and subtle cues in speech (e. g. identity, emotion and hesitation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facexhubert-text-less-speech-driven-e-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provable Data Subset Selection For Efficient Neural Network Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-data-subset-selection-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the first algorithm to construct coresets for \emph{RBFNNs}, i. e., small weighted subsets that approximate the loss of the input data on any radial basis function network and thus approximate any function defined by an \emph{RBFNN} on the larger input data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-data-subset-selection-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PC-JeDi: Diffusion for Particle Cloud Generation in High Energy Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-jedi-diffusion-for-particle-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new method to efficiently generate jets in High Energy Physics called PC-JeDi.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pc-jedi-diffusion-for-particle-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the relevance of traditional genres: a network analysis of fiction readers' preferences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-relevance-of-traditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis reveals that the network communities correspond to existing combinations of traditional genres, but that the exact communities differ depending on whether we consider books that people read or books that people enjoy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-relevance-of-traditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Certified Training and Robustness Verification of Neural ODEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-certified-training-and-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Ordinary Differential Equations (NODEs) are a novel neural architecture, built around initial value problems with learned dynamics which are solved during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-certified-training-and-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Federated Learning for Collaborative Intelligence in Massive IoT Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-federated-learning-for-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implementing existing federated learning in massive Internet of Things (IoT) networks faces critical challenges such as imbalanced and statistically heterogeneous data and device diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-federated-learning-for-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TANGOS: Regularizing Tabular Neural Networks through Gradient Orthogonalization and Specialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangos-regularizing-tabular-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Tabular Neural Gradient Orthogonalization and Specialization (TANGOS), a novel framework for regularization in the tabular setting built on latent unit attributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tangos-regularizing-tabular-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionDepth: Diffusion Denoising Approach for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondepth-diffusion-denoising-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose DiffusionDepth, a new approach that reformulates monocular depth estimation as a denoising diffusion process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondepth-diffusion-denoising-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAM: An Integrated Activation-Coupled Model of Sentence Processing and Eye Movements in Reading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seam-an-integrated-activation-coupled-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first-ever integration of a complete process model of eye-movement control with linguistic dependency completion processes in sentence comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seam-an-integrated-activation-coupled-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decision-BADGE: Decision-based Adversarial Batch Attack with Directional Gradient Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decision-badge-decision-based-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of Decision-BADGE and the accuracy loss function performs better than both score-based image-dependent attack and white-box universal attack methods in terms of attack time efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decision-badge-decision-based-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Recommendation Systems with User Personality Inferred from Product Reviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-systems-with-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on our two newly contributed personality datasets -- Amazon-beauty and Amazon-music -- validate our hypothesis, showing performance boosts of 3--28%. Our analysis uncovers that varying personality types contribute differently to recommendation performance: open and extroverted personalities are most helpful in music recommendation, while a conscientious personality is most helpful in beauty product recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-systems-with-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Regret Bounds for Online Kernel Selection under Bandit Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-regret-bounds-for-online-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply the two algorithms to online kernel selection with time constraint and prove new regret bounds matching or improving the previous $O(\sqrt{T\ln{K}} +\Vert f\Vert^2_{\mathcal{H}_i}\max\{\sqrt{T},\frac{T}{\sqrt{\mathcal{R}}}\})$ expected bound where $\mathcal{R}$ is the time budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-regret-bounds-for-online-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-distribution Detection with Implicit Outlier Transformation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It leads to a min-max learning scheme -- searching to synthesize OOD data that leads to worst judgments and learning from such OOD data for uniform performance in OOD detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaitEditer: Attribute Editing for Gait Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitediter-attribute-editing-for-gait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gait pattern is a promising biometric for applications, as it can be captured from a distance without requiring individual cooperation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaitediter-attribute-editing-for-gait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Stochastic Gradient Riemannian Langevin Dynamics in Non-Diagonal Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-stochastic-gradient-riemannian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For best performance the methods should use a Riemannian metric that improves posterior exploration by accounting for the local curvature, but the existing methods resort to simple diagonal metrics to remain computationally efficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-stochastic-gradient-riemannian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVOLIN Benchmark: Evaluation of Line Detection and Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolin-benchmark-evaluation-of-line-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is missing a complete benchmark where one can evaluate lines from a sequential stream of images in all its stages: Line detection, Line Association and Pose error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolin-benchmark-evaluation-of-line-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Splines for Non-Linear Approximations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-splines-for-non-linear-approximations-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum Computing offers a new paradigm for efficient computing and many AI applications could benefit from its potential boost in performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-splines-for-non-linear-approximations-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perspective Projection-Based 3D CT Reconstruction from Biplanar X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perspective-projection-based-3d-ct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X-ray computed tomography (CT) is one of the most common imaging techniques used to diagnose various diseases in the medical field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perspective-projection-based-3d-ct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cones: Concept Neurons in Diffusion Models for Customized Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cones-concept-neurons-in-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concatenating multiple clusters of concept neurons can vividly generate all related concepts in a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cones-concept-neurons-in-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spawrious: A Benchmark for Fine Control of Spurious Correlation Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spawrious-a-benchmark-for-fine-control-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of spurious correlations (SCs) arises when a classifier relies on non-predictive features that happen to be correlated with the labels in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spawrious-a-benchmark-for-fine-control-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Rotation Averaging: Uncertainties and Robust Losses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-rotation-averaging-uncertainties</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit the rotation averaging problem applied in global Structure-from-Motion pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-rotation-averaging-uncertainties</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic 3d regression with projected huber distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-3d-regression-with-projected</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show that the mode of the predicted distribution outperform our regression baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-3d-regression-with-projected</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mimic before Reconstruct: Enhancing Masked Autoencoders with Feature Mimicking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-before-reconstruct-enhancing-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this, previous methods simply replace the pixel reconstruction targets of 75% masked tokens by encoded features from pre-trained image-image (DINO) or image-language (CLIP) contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-before-reconstruct-enhancing-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RiDDLE: Reversible and Diversified De-identification with Latent Encryptor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riddle-reversible-and-diversified-de</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents RiDDLE, short for Reversible and Diversified De-identification with Latent Encryptor, to protect the identity information of people from being misused.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/riddle-reversible-and-diversified-de</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Image Modeling with Local Multi-Scale Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-with-local-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lower layers are not explicitly guided and the interaction among their patches is only used for calculating new activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-image-modeling-with-local-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BaDLAD: A Large Multi-Domain Bengali Document Layout Analysis Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badlad-a-large-multi-domain-bengali-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While strides have been made in deep learning based Bengali Optical Character Recognition (OCR) in the past decade, the absence of large Document Layout Analysis (DLA) datasets has hindered the application of OCR in document transcription, e. g., transcribing historical documents and newspapers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badlad-a-large-multi-domain-bengali-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Model Adaptation for Cross-Condition Robustness in Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-model-adaptation-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate normal-to-adverse condition model adaptation for semantic segmentation, whereby image-level correspondences are available in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-model-adaptation-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3AE: Multimodal Representation Learning for Brain Tumor Segmentation with Missing Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3ae-multimodal-representation-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first stage, a multimodal masked autoencoder (M3AE) is proposed, where both random modalities (i. e., modality dropout) and random patches of the remaining modalities are masked for a reconstruction task, for self-supervised learning of robust multimodal representations against missing modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3ae-multimodal-representation-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Message Passing Perspective on Learning Dynamics of Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-message-passing-perspective-on-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, contrastive learning achieves impressive results on self-supervised visual representation learning, but there still lacks a rigorous understanding of its learning dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-message-passing-perspective-on-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Auditing Large Language Models via Discrete Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-auditing-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Auditing large language models for unexpected behaviors is critical to preempt catastrophic deployments, yet remains challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-auditing-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RACCER: Towards Reachable and Certain Counterfactual Explanations for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raccer-towards-reachable-and-certain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose RACCER, the first RL-specific approach to generating counterfactual explanations for the behaviour of RL agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raccer-towards-reachable-and-certain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preference-Aware Delivery Planning for Last-Mile Logistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-aware-delivery-planning-for-last</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, despite many decades of solid research on solving these VRP instances, we still see significant gaps between optimized routes and the routes that are actually preferred by the practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-aware-delivery-planning-for-last</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-adaptive Depth-wise Heterogenous Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-adaptive-depth-wise-heterogenous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is a promising paradigm that allows multiple clients to collaboratively train a model without sharing the local data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-adaptive-depth-wise-heterogenous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiM: Distilling Dataset into Generative Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dim-distilling-dataset-into-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, we are the first to achieve higher accuracy on complex architectures than simple ones, such as 75. 1\% with ResNet-18 and 72. 6\% with ConvNet-3 on ten images per class of CIFAR-10.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dim-distilling-dataset-into-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Enhancement From Degradation: A Diffusion Model For Fundus Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-enhancement-from-degradation-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel diffusion model based framework, named Learning Enhancement from Degradation (LED), for enhancing fundus images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-enhancement-from-degradation-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual ChatGPT: Talking, Drawing and Editing with Visual Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-chatgpt-talking-drawing-and-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, We build a system called \textbf{Visual ChatGPT}, incorporating different Visual Foundation Models, to enable the user to interact with ChatGPT by 1) sending and receiving not only languages but also images 2) providing complex visual questions or visual editing instructions that require the collaboration of multiple AI models with multi-steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-chatgpt-talking-drawing-and-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Avatar: Expressive Human Avatars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-avatar-expressive-human-avatars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method models bodies, hands, facial expressions and appearance in a holistic fashion and can be learned from either full 3D scans or RGB-D data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-avatar-expressive-human-avatars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Fidelity Synthetic Face Generation for Rosacea Skin Condition from Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-synthetic-face-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, for the first time, a small dataset of Rosacea with 300 full-face images is utilized to further investigate the possibility of generating synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-synthetic-face-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastFill: Efficient Compatible Model Update</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastfill-efficient-compatible-model-update</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of retrieving the most similar data from a gallery set to a given query data is performed through a similarity comparison on features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastfill-efficient-compatible-model-update</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector Quantized Time Series Generation with a Bidirectional Prior Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantized-time-series-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series generation (TSG) studies have mainly focused on the use of Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) combined with recurrent neural network (RNN) variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantized-time-series-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-Effective Hyperparameter Optimization for Large Language Model Generation Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-hyperparameter-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) like GPT-3 have sparked significant interest in their generative capabilities, leading to the development of various commercial applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-effective-hyperparameter-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Hypothesis Tests Detect Clinically Relevant Subgroup Shifts in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hypothesis-tests-detect-clinically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate subgroup shift detection in the framework of statistical hypothesis testing and show that recent state-of-the-art statistical tests can be effectively applied to subgroup shift detection on medical imaging data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hypothesis-tests-detect-clinically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Densely Connected $G$-invariant Deep Neural Networks with Signed Permutation Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densely-connected-g-invariant-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce and investigate, for finite groups $G$, $G$-invariant deep neural network ($G$-DNN) architectures with ReLU activation that are densely connected -- i. e., include all possible skip connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/densely-connected-g-invariant-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-EBM: Towards Understanding the Manifolds of Energy-Based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-ebm-towards-understanding-the-manifolds-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its simplicity, M-EBM significantly improves unconditional EBMs in training stability and speed on a host of benchmark datasets, such as CIFAR10, CIFAR100, CelebA-HQ, and ImageNet 32x32.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-ebm-towards-understanding-the-manifolds-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
