<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:12:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Few-Shot Learning for Ischemic Stroke Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-few-shot-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precise ischemic lesion segmentation plays an essential role in improving diagnosis and treatment planning for ischemic stroke, one of the prevalent diseases with the highest mortality rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-few-shot-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preference Transformer: Modeling Human Preferences using Transformers for RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-transformer-modeling-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Preference Transformer, a neural architecture that models human preferences using transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-transformer-modeling-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matching-based Term Semantics Pre-training for Spoken Patient Query Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-based-term-semantics-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical Slot Filling (MSF) task aims to convert medical queries into structured information, playing an essential role in diagnosis dialogue systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matching-based-term-semantics-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting IPv4 Services Across All Ports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-ipv4-services-across-all-ports</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Internet-wide scanning is commonly used to understand the topology and security of the Internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-ipv4-services-across-all-ports</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter Tuning and Model Evaluation in Causal Effect Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-and-model-evaluation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find hyperparameter tuning and model evaluation are much more important than causal estimators and ML methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-and-model-evaluation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Variety Identification with True Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-variety-identification-with-true</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research has shown that this is a problematic assumption, particularly in the case of very similar languages (e. g., Croatian and Serbian) and national language varieties (e. g., Brazilian and European Portuguese), where texts may contain no distinctive marker of the particular language or variety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-variety-identification-with-true</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why (and When) does Local SGD Generalize Better than SGD?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-and-when-does-local-sgd-generalize-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local SGD is a communication-efficient variant of SGD for large-scale training, where multiple GPUs perform SGD independently and average the model parameters periodically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-and-when-does-local-sgd-generalize-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Metric Maze: A Taxonomy of Evaluation Metrics for Anomaly Detection in Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-metric-maze-a-taxonomy-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of time series anomaly detection is constantly advancing, with several methods available, making it a challenge to determine the most appropriate method for a specific domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-metric-maze-a-taxonomy-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CTRLStruct: Dialogue Structure Learning for Open-Domain Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctrlstruct-dialogue-structure-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then we perform clustering to utterance-level representations and form topic-level clusters that can be considered as vertices in dialogue structure graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ctrlstruct-dialogue-structure-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning Guided Multi-Objective Exam Paper Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-guided-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the repetitive and complex work of instructors, exam paper generation (EPG) technique has become a salient topic in the intelligent education field, which targets at generating high-quality exam paper automatically according to instructor-specified assessment criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-guided-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FeatAug-DETR: Enriching One-to-Many Matching for DETRs with Feature Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feataug-detr-enriching-one-to-many-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first method is One-to-many Matching via Data Augmentation (denoted as DataAug-DETR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feataug-detr-enriching-one-to-many-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning-Based Software Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-based-software-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Reasoning-Based Software Testing (RBST), a new way of thinking at the testing problem as a causal reasoning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-based-software-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Meta-Learning via Few-shot Pseudo-supervised Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-meta-learning-via-few-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised meta-learning aims to learn generalizable knowledge across a distribution of tasks constructed from unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-meta-learning-via-few-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESceme: Vision-and-Language Navigation with Episodic Scene Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esceme-vision-and-language-navigation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The episodic scene memory allows the agent to envision a bigger picture of the next prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esceme-vision-and-language-navigation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Labels Are All You Need for Coarse Seagrass Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-labels-are-all-you-need-for-coarse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms previous approaches that require patch-level labels on the multi-species 'DeepSeagrass' dataset by 6. 8% (absolute) for the class-weighted F1 score, and by 12. 1% (absolute) F1 score for seagrass presence/absence on the 'Global Wetlands' dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-labels-are-all-you-need-for-coarse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoLab: Geometry-based Tractography Parcellation of Superficial White Matter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolab-geometry-based-tractography</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Superficial white matter (SWM) has been less studied than long-range connections despite being of interest to clinical research, andfew tractography parcellation methods have been adapted to SWM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolab-geometry-based-tractography</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Source Soft Pseudo-Label Learning with Domain Similarity-based Weighting for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-soft-pseudo-label-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a method of domain adaptive training for semantic segmentation using multiple source datasets that are not necessarily relevant to the target dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-soft-pseudo-label-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Language Acquisition with Theory of Mind</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-language-acquisition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find some evidence that increasing task difficulty in the training process results in more fluent and precise utterances in evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-language-acquisition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict-Based Cross-View Consistency for Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conflict-based-cross-view-consistency-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new conflict-based cross-view consistency (CCVC) method based on a two-branch co-training framework for semi-supervised semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conflict-based-cross-view-consistency-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Orthogonal Planes for Indoor Panoramic Room Layout Estimation with Cross-Scale Distortion Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-orthogonal-planes-for-indoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the Manhattan World assumption, most existing indoor layout estimation schemes focus on recovering layouts from vertically compressed 1D sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-orthogonal-planes-for-indoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropout Reduces Underfitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-reduces-underfitting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we explore a symmetric technique for regularizing overfitting models - late dropout, where dropout is not used in the early iterations and is only activated later in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-reduces-underfitting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image as Set of Points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-as-set-of-points</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Context clusters (CoCs) view an image as a set of unorganized points and extract features via simplified clustering algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-as-set-of-points</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferring Models Trained on Natural Images to 3D MRI via Position Encoded Slice Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferring-models-trained-on-natural-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transfer learning has remarkably improved computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferring-models-trained-on-natural-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token Contrast for Weakly-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-contrast-for-weakly-supervised-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, to further differentiate the low-confidence regions in CAM, we devised a Class Token Contrast module (CTC) inspired by the fact that class tokens in ViT can capture high-level semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-contrast-for-weakly-supervised-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Contrastive Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we propose a Heterogeneous Graph Contrastive Learning (HGCL), which is able to incorporate heterogeneous relational semantics into the user-item interaction modeling with contrastive learning-enhanced knowledge transfer across different views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of High-Dimensional Bayesian Optimization Algorithms on BBOB</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-high-dimensional-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Optimization (BO) is a class of black-box, surrogate-based heuristics that can efficiently optimize problems that are expensive to evaluate, and hence admit only small evaluation budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-high-dimensional-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Effect of Data Augmentation in Adversarial Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-effect-of-data-augmentation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this observation, we revisit existing self-AT methods and discover an inherent dilemma that affects self-AT robustness: either strong or weak data augmentations are harmful to self-AT, and a medium strength is insufficient to bridge the gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-effect-of-data-augmentation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Hamiltonian Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-hamiltonian-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Quantum Hamiltonian Descent (QHD), which is derived from the path integral of dynamical systems referring to the continuous-time limit of classical gradient descent algorithms, as a truly quantum counterpart of classical gradient methods where the contribution from classically-prohibited trajectories can significantly boost QHD's performance for non-convex optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-hamiltonian-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auxiliary Functions as Koopman Observables: Data-Driven Polynomial Optimization for Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-functions-as-koopman-observables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a flexible data-driven method for dynamical system analysis that does not require explicit model discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-functions-as-koopman-observables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuscleMap: Towards Video-based Activated Muscle Group Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musclemap-towards-video-based-activated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle the new task of video-based Activated Muscle Group Estimation (AMGE) aiming at identifying currently activated muscular regions of humans performing a specific activity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musclemap-towards-video-based-activated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Visual Similarity Learning in 3D Medical Image Self-supervised Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-visual-similarity-learning-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel visual similarity learning paradigm, Geometric Visual Similarity Learning, which embeds the prior of topological invariance into the measurement of the inter-image similarity for consistent representation of semantic regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-visual-similarity-learning-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Motion Diffusion as a Generative Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-as-a-generative-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using an off-the-shelf state-of-the-art (SOTA) motion diffusion model as a prior, we evaluate our approach for the three mentioned cases and show that we consistently outperform SOTA models that were designed and trained for those tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-as-a-generative-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUNT: Few-shot Tabular Learning with Self-generated Tasks from Unlabeled Tables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stunt-few-shot-tabular-learning-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning with few labeled tabular samples is often an essential requirement for industrial machine learning applications as varieties of tabular data suffer from high annotation costs or have difficulties in collecting new samples for novel tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stunt-few-shot-tabular-learning-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WiCE: Real-World Entailment for Claims in Wikipedia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wice-real-world-entailment-for-claims-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our annotations are over sub-sentence units of the hypothesis, decomposed automatically by GPT-3, each of which is labeled with a subset of evidence sentences from the source document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wice-real-world-entailment-for-claims-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transmission-Guided Bayesian Generative Model for Smoke Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transmission-guided-bayesian-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To effectively model the two types of uncertainty, we introduce a Bayesian generative model to simultaneously estimate the posterior distribution of model parameters and its predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transmission-guided-bayesian-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete-time Competing-Risks Regression with or without Penalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-time-competing-risks-regression-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we showcase the utility of our procedure by estimating a survival model for the length of stay of patients hospitalized in the intensive care unit, considering three competing events: discharge to home, transfer to another medical facility, and in-hospital death.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-time-competing-risks-regression-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specformer: Spectral Graph Neural Networks Meet Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specformer-spectral-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we introduce Specformer, which effectively encodes the set of all eigenvalues and performs self-attention in the spectral domain, leading to a learnable set-to-set spectral filter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specformer-spectral-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLANet: Multi-Level Attention Network with Sub-instruction for Continuous Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlanet-multi-level-attention-network-with-sub</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a better performance in continuous VLN, we design a multi-level instruction understanding procedure and propose a novel model, Multi-Level Attention Network (MLANet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlanet-multi-level-attention-network-with-sub</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVA: Disentangling Adversarial Variational Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dava-disentangling-adversarial-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare DAVA to models with optimal hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dava-disentangling-adversarial-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Head Multi-Loss Model Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-multi-loss-model-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Delivering meaningful uncertainty estimates is essential for a successful deployment of machine learning models in the clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-head-multi-loss-model-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardinality Estimation over Knowledge Graphs with Embeddings and Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardinality-estimation-over-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cardinality Estimation over Knowledge Graphs (KG) is crucial for query optimization, yet remains a challenging task due to the semi-structured nature and complex correlations of typical Knowledge Graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardinality-estimation-over-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAP-IQ: Unified Approximation of any-order Shapley Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-iq-unified-approximation-of-any-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SHAP-IQ is based on a novel representation and, in contrast to existing methods, we provide theoretical guarantees for its approximation quality, as well as estimates for the variance of the point estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-iq-unified-approximation-of-any-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Arbitrary-Modal Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delivering-arbitrary-modal-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make this possible, we present the arbitrary cross-modal segmentation model CMNeXt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delivering-arbitrary-modal-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation from Heterogeneous Models for Top-K Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-from-heterogeneous-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work aims to transfer the ensemble knowledge of heterogeneous teachers to a lightweight student model using knowledge distillation (KD), to reduce the huge inference costs while retaining high accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-from-heterogeneous-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LANDMARK: Language-guided Representation Enhancement Framework for Scene Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmark-language-guided-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, representation-level unbiased strategies endow LANDMARK the advantage of compatibility with other methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmark-language-guided-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay Less But Get More: A Dual-Attention-based Channel Estimation Network for Massive MIMO Systems with Low-Density Pilots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-less-but-get-more-a-dual-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, with the proposed transfer learning approach, the DACEN-based method with ultra-low-density pilots ($\rho_L^\prime=2/52$) achieves higher estimation accuracy than the existing methods with low-density pilots, thereby demonstrating the effectiveness and the superiority of the proposed method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-less-but-get-more-a-dual-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can BERT Refrain from Forgetting on Sequential Tasks? A Probing Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bert-refrain-from-forgetting-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained language models help to achieve state of the art on a variety of natural language processing (NLP) tasks, nevertheless, they still suffer from forgetting when incrementally learning a sequence of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bert-refrain-from-forgetting-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In all LikelihoodS: How to Reliably Select Pseudo-Labeled Data for Self-Training in Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-all-likelihoods-how-to-reliably-select</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a practical proof of concept, we spotlight the application of three of our robust extensions on simulated and real-world data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-all-likelihoods-how-to-reliably-select</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Circuit Repair Against Formal Specifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-circuit-repair-against-formal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a separated hierarchical Transformer for multimodal representation learning of the formal specification and the circuit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-circuit-repair-against-formal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Network Acceleration with Tiny Sets: Hypothesis, Theory, and Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-network-acceleration-with-tiny-sets-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For 22% latency reduction, it surpasses previous methods by on average 7 percentage points on ImageNet-1k.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-network-acceleration-with-tiny-sets-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
