<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 21:08:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-temporal collaborative multiple-stream transformer network for liver lesion classification on multiple-sequence magnetic resonance imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-collaborative-multiple-stream</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate identification of focal liver lesions is essential for determining the appropriate therapeutic approach in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-collaborative-multiple-stream</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Study of Machine Unlearning Techniques for Computer Vision and NLP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-of-machine-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine unlearning is an emerging field in machine learning that focuses on efficiently removing the influence of specific data from a trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-of-machine-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Performance of TAAF for image classification models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-performance-of-taaf-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the results of testing a custom activation function, The Analog Activation Function (TAAF), on both the MNIST and CIFAR-10 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-performance-of-taaf-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redistribute Ensemble Training for Mitigating Memorization in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistribute-ensemble-training-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel method for diffusion models from the perspective of visual modality, which is more generic and fundamental for mitigating memorization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistribute-ensemble-training-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Classic GNNs for Graph-level Tasks: Simple Architectures Meet Excellence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-classic-gnns-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Message-passing Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are often criticized for their limited expressiveness, issues like over-smoothing and over-squashing, and challenges in capturing long-range dependencies, while Graph Transformers (GTs) are considered superior due to their global attention mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-classic-gnns-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eidetic Learning: an Efficient and Provable Solution to Catastrophic Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eidetic-learning-an-efficient-and-provable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show with a variety of network architectures and sets of tasks that EideticNets are immune to forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eidetic-learning-an-efficient-and-provable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stochastic Parrot on LLM's Shoulder: A Summative Assessment of Physical Concept Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stochastic-parrot-on-llm-s-shoulder-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a systematic way, we investigate a widely asked question: Do LLMs really understand what they say?, which relates to the more familiar term Stochastic Parrot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stochastic-parrot-on-llm-s-shoulder-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyGFM: Graph Foundation Model for Zero/Few-shot Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygfm-graph-foundation-model-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose AnomalyGFM, a GAD-oriented graph foundation model that supports zero-shot inference and few-shot prompt tuning for GAD in diverse graph datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalygfm-graph-foundation-model-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-Theta Attention: Sparsifying Transformers by Compensated Thresholding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-theta-attention-sparsifying-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The attention mechanism is essential for the impressive capabilities of transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-theta-attention-sparsifying-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Aware Human-machine Collaboration in Camouflaged Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-human-machine-collaboration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Camouflaged Object Detection (COD), the task of identifying objects concealed within their environments, has seen rapid growth due to its wide range of practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-human-machine-collaboration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViLa-MIL: Dual-scale Vision-Language Multiple Instance Learning for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vila-mil-dual-scale-vision-language-multiple-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a dual-scale visual descriptive text prompt based on the frozen large language model (LLM) to boost the performance of VLM effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vila-mil-dual-scale-vision-language-multiple-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composite Sketch+Text Queries for Retrieving Objects with Elusive Names and Complex Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-sketch-text-queries-for-retrieving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, as a solution to this problem, we propose a pretrained multimodal transformer-based baseline, STNET (Sketch+Text Network), that uses a hand-drawn sketch to localize relevant objects in the natural scene image, and encodes the text and image to perform image retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-sketch-text-queries-for-retrieving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Latent Progression: Individual-based Spatiotemporal Disease Progression on 3D Brain MRIs via Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-latent-progression-individual-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key contributions in BrLP are fourfold: (i) it operates in a small latent space, mitigating the computational challenges posed by high-dimensional imaging data; (ii) it explicitly integrates subject metadata to enhance the individualization of predictions; (iii) it incorporates prior knowledge of disease dynamics through an auxiliary model, facilitating the integration of longitudinal data; and (iv) it introduces the Latent Average Stabilization (LAS) algorithm, which (a) enforces spatiotemporal consistency in the predicted progression at inference time and (b) allows us to derive a measure of the uncertainty for the prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-latent-progression-individual-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Universal Design Neural Network for the Color Vision Deficiencies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-universal-design-neural-network-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generate CUD images for color deficiencies, we follow a four-step process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-universal-design-neural-network-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss Landscape Analysis for Reliable Quantized ML Models for Scientific Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-landscape-analysis-for-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method to perform empirical analysis of the loss landscape of machine learning (ML) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-landscape-analysis-for-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light-A-Video: Training-free Video Relighting via Progressive Light Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-a-video-training-free-video-relighting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, leveraging the physical principle of light transport independence, we apply linear blending between the source video's appearance and the relighted appearance, using a Progressive Light Fusion (PLF) strategy to ensure smooth temporal transitions in illumination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-a-video-training-free-video-relighting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform Kernel Prober</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-kernel-prober</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a class of pseudometrics called Uniform Kernel Prober (UKP) for comparing features or representations learned by different statistical models such as neural networks when the downstream prediction tasks involve kernel ridge regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-kernel-prober</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New tools for comparing classical and neural ODE models for tumor growth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-tools-for-comparing-classical-and-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new computational tool TumorGrowth. jl for modeling tumor growth is introduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-tools-for-comparing-classical-and-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grammar Control in Dialogue Response Generation for Language Learning Chatbots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammar-control-in-dialogue-response</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they are hard to control for linguistic forms that correspond to learners' current needs, such as grammar.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammar-control-in-dialogue-response</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget What You Know about LLMs Evaluations - LLMs are Like a Chameleon</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-what-you-know-about-llms-evaluations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) often appear to excel on public benchmarks, but these high scores may mask an overreliance on dataset-specific surface cues rather than true language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-what-you-know-about-llms-evaluations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Instrumental Variable Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-instrumental-variable-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our empirical results show that the DIV method performs well for a broad range of simulated data, exhibiting advantages over existing IV approaches in terms of the identifiability and estimation error of the mean or quantile treatment effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-instrumental-variable-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Vision-Centric 3D Occupancy World Model for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-vision-centric-3d-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the high annotation cost for 3D outdoor scenes, we propose a semi-supervised vision-centric 3D occupancy world model, PreWorld, to leverage the potential of 2D labels through a novel two-stage training paradigm: the self-supervised pre-training stage and the fully-supervised fine-tuning stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-vision-centric-3d-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Robust Framework for Multimodal Hate Detection: A Study on Video vs. Image-based Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-robust-framework-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a systematic analysis of fusion-based approaches for multimodal hate detection, focusing on their performance across video and image-based content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-robust-framework-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneity in Sectoral Production and the Macro Effect of Sectoral Shocks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-in-sectoral-production-and-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effect of a negative sectoral shock on GDP depends on how important the shocked sector is as a direct and indirect supplier and how easily sectors can substitute inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-in-sectoral-production-and-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinRL-DeepSeek: LLM-Infused Risk-Sensitive Reinforcement Learning for Trading Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrl-deepseek-llm-infused-risk-sensitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel risk-sensitive trading agent combining reinforcement learning and large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrl-deepseek-llm-infused-risk-sensitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Capability Discovery via Model Self-Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-capability-discovery-via-model-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Automated Capability Discovery (ACD), a framework that designates one foundation model as a scientist to systematically propose open-ended tasks probing the abilities of a subject model (potentially itself).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-capability-discovery-via-model-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EIQP: Execution-time-certified and Infeasibility-detecting QP Solver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiqp-execution-time-certified-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solving real-time quadratic programming (QP) is a ubiquitous task in control engineering, such as in model predictive control and control barrier function-based QP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiqp-execution-time-certified-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph RAG-Tool Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-rag-tool-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this limitation by introducing Graph RAG-Tool Fusion, a novel plug-and-play approach that combines the strengths of vector-based retrieval with efficient graph traversal to capture all relevant tools (nodes) along with any nested dependencies (edges) within the predefined tool knowledge graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-rag-tool-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPO-Shift: Shifting the Distribution of Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpo-shift-shifting-the-distribution-of-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Direct Preference Optimization (DPO) and its variants have become increasingly popular for aligning language models with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpo-shift-shifting-the-distribution-of-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RusCode: Russian Cultural Code Benchmark for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ruscode-russian-cultural-code-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of cultural awareness can reduce the generation quality and lead to undesirable consequences such as unintentional insult, and the spread of prejudice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ruscode-russian-cultural-code-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASP-2: Rethinking Sequence Parallelism for Linear Attention and Its Hybrid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasp-2-rethinking-sequence-parallelism-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce LASP-2, a new SP method to enhance both communication and computation parallelism when training linear attention transformer models with very-long input sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasp-2-rethinking-sequence-parallelism-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JamendoMaxCaps: A Large Scale Music-caption Dataset with Imputed Metadata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamendomaxcaps-a-large-scale-music-caption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce JamendoMaxCaps, a large-scale music-caption dataset featuring over 200, 000 freely licensed instrumental tracks from the renowned Jamendo platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamendomaxcaps-a-large-scale-music-caption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Elliptic Curve Based Solution to the Perspective-Three-Point Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-elliptic-curve-based-solution-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Perspective-Three-Point Problem (P3P) is solved by first focusing on determining the directions of the lines through pairs of control points, relative to the camera, rather than the distances from the camera to the control points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-elliptic-curve-based-solution-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auditing Prompt Caching in Language Model APIs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-prompt-caching-in-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We detect global cache sharing across users in seven API providers, including OpenAI, resulting in potential privacy leakage about users' prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auditing-prompt-caching-in-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolution of cooperation in a bimodal mixture of conditional cooperators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-cooperation-in-a-bimodal-mixture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explore the effects of hard and soft conditional cooperators, we examine their interactions in two scenarios: structural mixture (SM) and probabilistic mixture (PM), where the two behavioral modes are fixed and probabilistically adopted, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolution-of-cooperation-in-a-bimodal-mixture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Benchmark for Vietnamese Sentence Paraphrases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-benchmark-for-vietnamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ViSP, a high-quality Vietnamese dataset for sentence paraphrasing, consisting of 1. 2M original-paraphrase pairs collected from various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-benchmark-for-vietnamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial-Label Learning with Conformal Candidate Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-label-learning-with-conformal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To work around the missing labeled validation set, which is typically required for conformal prediction, we propose a strategy that alternates between training a PLL classifier to label the validation set, leveraging these predicted class labels for calibration, and pruning candidate labels that are not part of the resulting conformal sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-label-learning-with-conformal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Efficient RLHF Pipeline: A Unified View from Contextual Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-rlhf-pipeline-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) is a widely used approach for aligning Large Language Models (LLMs) with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-rlhf-pipeline-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Physics and Data-Driven Approaches: An Explainable and Uncertainty-Aware Hybrid Model for Wind Turbine Power Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-physics-and-data-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a hybrid semi-parametric model that combines the strengths of both approaches, applied to a dataset from a wind farm with four turbines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-physics-and-data-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchMAX: A Comprehensive Multilingual Evaluation Suite for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmax-a-comprehensive-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous multilingual benchmarks focus primarily on simple understanding tasks, but for large language models(LLMs), we emphasize proficiency in instruction following, reasoning, long context understanding, code generation, and so on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmax-a-comprehensive-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Language Model Makes an Effective Long Text Extractor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-language-model-makes-an-effective-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the task of extracting longer entity spans (e. g., awards) from extended texts (e. g., homepages) is barely explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-language-model-makes-an-effective-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target-Augmented Shared Fusion-based Multimodal Sarcasm Explanation Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-augmented-shared-fusion-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TURBO assumes the target of the sarcasm and guides the multimodal shared fusion mechanism in learning intricacies of the intended irony for explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-augmented-shared-fusion-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Language Models to Follow Instructions and Hallucinate Less via Effective Data Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-to-follow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By considering data quality and avoiding unfamiliar data, we can utilize the selected data to effectively align LLMs to follow instructions and hallucinate less.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-to-follow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Goedel-Prover: A Frontier Model for Open-Source Automated Theorem Proving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goedel-prover-a-frontier-model-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the miniF2F benchmark, it achieves a 57. 6% success rate (Pass@32), exceeding the previous best open-source model by 7. 6%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goedel-prover-a-frontier-model-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devil is in the Prompts: De-Identification Traces Enhance Memorization Risks in Synthetic Chest X-Ray Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-prompts-de-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic chest X-ray generation is one of the most common applications in medical image analysis with the MIMIC-CXR dataset serving as the primary data repository for this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-is-in-the-prompts-de-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Sparse Mixture Of Experts Text Embedding Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-sparse-mixture-of-experts-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer-based text embedding models have improved their performance on benchmarks like MIRACL and BEIR by increasing their parameter counts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-sparse-mixture-of-experts-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination, Monofacts, and Miscalibration: An Empirical Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-monofacts-and-miscalibration-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent theoretical work by [Kalai and Vempala 2024] proves that a particular notion of hallucination rate in LLMs must be lower bounded by the training data monofact rate (related to the classical Good-Turing missing mass estimator) minus model miscalibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-monofacts-and-miscalibration-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeI/O: Condensing Reasoning Patterns via Code Input-Output Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codei-o-condensing-reasoning-patterns-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning is a fundamental capability of Large Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codei-o-condensing-reasoning-patterns-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SketchFlex: Facilitating Spatial-Semantic Coherence in Text-to-Image Generation with Region-Based Sketches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketchflex-facilitating-spatial-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image models can generate visually appealing images from text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketchflex-facilitating-spatial-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CreAgent: Towards Long-Term Evaluation of Recommender System under Platform-Creator Information Asymmetry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creagent-towards-long-term-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous studies have attempted to model creator behavior, they often overlook the role of information asymmetry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creagent-towards-long-term-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
