<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 21:06:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Edge2Node: Reducing Edge Prediction to Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge2node-reducing-edge-prediction-to-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A common approach for edge prediction is to first obtain the embeddings of two nodes, and then a predefined scoring function is used to predict the existence of an edge between the two nodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edge2node-reducing-edge-prediction-to-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabRepo: A Large Scale Repository of Tabular Model Evaluations and its AutoML Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabrepo-a-large-scale-repository-of-tabular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TabRepo contains the predictions and metrics of 1206 models evaluated on 200 regression and classification datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabrepo-a-large-scale-repository-of-tabular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CogVLM: Visual Expert for Pretrained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogvlm-visual-expert-for-pretrained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CogVLM, a powerful open-source visual language foundation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogvlm-visual-expert-for-pretrained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OVIR-3D: Open-Vocabulary 3D Instance Retrieval Without Training on 3D Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovir-3d-open-vocabulary-3d-instance-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents OVIR-3D, a straightforward yet effective method for open-vocabulary 3D object instance retrieval without using any 3D data for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ovir-3d-open-vocabulary-3d-instance-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QualEval: Qualitative Evaluation for Model Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qualeval-qualitative-evaluation-for-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the shortcomings of quantitative metrics by proposing QualEval, which augments quantitative scalar metrics with automated qualitative evaluation as a vehicle for model improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qualeval-qualitative-evaluation-for-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FocusTune: Tuning Visual Localization through Focus-Guided Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focustune-tuning-visual-localization-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose FocusTune, a focus-guided sampling technique to improve the performance of visual localization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focustune-tuning-visual-localization-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LitSumm: Large language models for literature summarisation of non-coding RNAs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litsumm-large-language-models-for-literature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Availability: Code used to produce these summaries can be found here: https://github. com/RNAcentral/litscan-summarization and the dataset of contexts and summaries can be found here: https://huggingface. co/datasets/RNAcentral/litsumm-v1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litsumm-large-language-models-for-literature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating treatment effects from single-arm trials via latent-variable modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-treatment-effects-from-single-arm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to previous methods, our results show improved performance both for direct treatment effect estimation as well as for effect estimation via patient matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-treatment-effects-from-single-arm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A survey and classification of face alignment methods based on face models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-and-classification-of-face-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face alignment is the process of fitting the landmarks in a face model to the respective ground truth positions in an input image containing a face.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-and-classification-of-face-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persistent homology for high-dimensional data based on spectral methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistent-homology-for-high-dimensional-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a remedy, we find that spectral distances on the $k$-nearest-neighbor graph of the data, such as diffusion distance and effective resistance, allow persistent homology to detect the correct topology even in the presence of high-dimensional noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistent-homology-for-high-dimensional-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convergence Analysis of Sequential Federated Learning on Heterogeneous Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-analysis-of-sequential-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are two categories of methods in Federated Learning (FL) for joint training across multiple clients: i) parallel FL (PFL), where clients train models in a parallel manner; and ii) sequential FL (SFL), where clients train models in a sequential manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-analysis-of-sequential-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini Minds: Exploring Bebeshka and Zlata Baby Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-minds-exploring-bebeshka-and-zlata-baby</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe the University of Lyon 2 submission to the Strict-Small track of the BabyLM competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-minds-exploring-bebeshka-and-zlata-baby</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validity problems in clinical machine learning by indirect data labeling using consensus definitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/validity-problems-in-clinical-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate a validity problem of machine learning in the vital application area of disease diagnosis in medicine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/validity-problems-in-clinical-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pursuit of Human Labeling: A New Perspective on Unsupervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-pursuit-of-human-labeling-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its simplicity, HUME outperforms a supervised linear classifier on top of self-supervised representations on the STL-10 dataset by a large margin and achieves comparable performance on the CIFAR-10 dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-pursuit-of-human-labeling-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling Downstream Gender Bias from Large Language Models: A Study on AI Educational Writing Assistance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-downstream-gender-bias-from-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate that there is no significant difference in gender bias between the resulting peer reviews of groups with and without LLM suggestions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-downstream-gender-bias-from-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Weighting for Kernel Density Ratios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-weighting-for-kernel-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kernel density estimation (KDE) is integral to a range of generative and discriminative tasks in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-weighting-for-kernel-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FATE: Feature-Agnostic Transformer-based Encoder for learning generalized embedding spaces in flow cytometry data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fate-feature-agnostic-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This limitation becomes particularly relevant in scenarios where the attributes captured during data acquisition vary across different samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fate-feature-agnostic-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhoGPT: Generative Pre-training for Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phogpt-generative-pre-training-for-vietnamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We open-source a state-of-the-art 7. 5B-parameter generative model series named PhoGPT for Vietnamese, which includes the base pre-trained monolingual model PhoGPT-7B5 and its instruction-following variant, PhoGPT-7B5-Instruct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phogpt-generative-pre-training-for-vietnamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLEN: Generative Retrieval via Lexical Index Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glen-generative-retrieval-via-lexical-index</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For training, GLEN effectively exploits a dynamic lexical identifier using a two-phase index learning strategy, enabling it to learn meaningful lexical identifiers and relevance signals between queries and documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glen-generative-retrieval-via-lexical-index</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Neural Fields for Learning Atlases of 4D Fetal MRI Time-series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-neural-fields-for-learning-atlases-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply our method to learning subject-specific atlases and motion stabilization of dynamic BOLD MRI time-series of fetuses in utero.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-neural-fields-for-learning-atlases-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architectural Sweet Spots for Modeling Human Label Variation by the Example of Argument Quality: It's Best to Relate Perspectives!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-sweet-spots-for-modeling-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To best represent the interplay of individual and shared perspectives, we consider a continuum of approaches ranging from models that fully aggregate perspectives into a majority label to "share nothing"-architectures in which each annotator is considered in isolation from all other annotators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/architectural-sweet-spots-for-modeling-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models are Super Mario: Absorbing Abilities from Homologous Models as a Free Lunch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-super-mario-absorbing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this observation, we further sparsify delta parameters of multiple SFT homologous models with DARE and subsequently merge them into a single model by parameter averaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-super-mario-absorbing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A universal framework for accurate and efficient geometric deep learning of molecular systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-framework-for-accurate-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular sciences address a wide range of problems involving molecules of different types and sizes and their complexes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-universal-framework-for-accurate-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BanLemma: A Word Formation Dependent Rule and Dictionary Based Bangla Lemmatizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banlemma-a-word-formation-dependent-rule-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lemmatization holds significance in both natural language processing (NLP) and linguistics, as it effectively decreases data density and aids in comprehending contextual meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/banlemma-a-word-formation-dependent-rule-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonparametric modeling of the composite effect of multiple nutrients on blood glucose dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-modeling-of-the-composite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By differentiating treatment components, incorporating their dosages, and sharing statistical information across patients via a hierarchical multi-output Gaussian process, our method improves prediction accuracy over existing approaches, and allows us to interpret the different effects of carbohydrates and fat on the overall glucose response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonparametric-modeling-of-the-composite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Evaluation Metrics of Open-Vocabulary Segmentaion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-evaluation-metrics-of-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We benchmarked the proposed evaluation metrics on 12 open-vocabulary methods of three segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-evaluation-metrics-of-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-Labeling for Domain-Agnostic Bangla Automatic Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-for-domain-agnostic-bangla</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate the efficacy of the model trained on psuedo-label data for the designed test-set along with publicly-available Bangla datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-for-domain-agnostic-bangla</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLaMM: Pixel Grounding Large Multimodal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glamm-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Grounding LMM (GLaMM), the first model that can generate natural language responses seamlessly intertwined with corresponding object segmentation masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glamm-pixel-grounding-large-multimodal-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weight-Sharing Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weight-sharing-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weight-sharing is ubiquitous in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weight-sharing-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiSPANS: A Multi-range Spatial-Temporal Transformer Network for Traffic Forecast via Structural Entropy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multispans-a-multi-range-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we propose a relative structural entropy-based position encoding and a multi-head attention masking scheme based on multi-layer encoding trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multispans-a-multi-range-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient, Self-Supervised Human Pose Estimation with Inductive Prior Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-self-supervised-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We (1) analyze the relationship between reconstruction quality and pose estimation accuracy, (2) develop a model pipeline that outperforms the baseline which inspired our work, using less than one-third the amount of training data, and (3) offer a new metric suitable for self-supervised settings that measures the consistency of predicted body part length proportions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-self-supervised-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kinematic-aware Prompting for Generalizable Articulated Object Manipulation with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinematic-aware-prompting-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalizable articulated object manipulation is essential for home-assistant robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kinematic-aware-prompting-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holistic Analysis of Hallucination in GPT-4V(ision): Bias and Interference Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-analysis-of-hallucination-in-gpt-4v</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce a new benchmark, namely, the Bias and Interference Challenges in Visual Language Models (Bingo).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holistic-analysis-of-hallucination-in-gpt-4v</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Self-Rationalizers with Multi-Reward Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-self-rationalizers-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results on five difficult question-answering datasets StrategyQA, QuaRel, OpenBookQA, NumerSense and QASC show that not only does MaRio improve task accuracy, but it also improves the self-rationalization quality of small LMs across the aforementioned axes better than a supervised fine-tuning (SFT) baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-self-rationalizers-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Linear Subspace Identification: A Machine Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-linear-subspace-identification-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning (ML) and linear System Identification (SI) have been historically developed independently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-linear-subspace-identification-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Multi-modal Unsupervised Representation Learning for Skeleton-based Action Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-multi-modal-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this manner, our framework is able to learn the unified representations of uni-modal or multi-modal skeleton input, which is flexible to different kinds of modality input for robust action understanding in practical cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-multi-modal-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human as Points: Explicit Point-based 3D Human Reconstruction from Single-view RGB Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-as-points-explicit-point-based-3d-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latest trends in the research field of single-view human reconstruction devote to learning deep implicit functions constrained by explicit body shape priors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-as-points-explicit-point-based-3d-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCPR: A Multi-Scale Attention-Based LiDAR-Camera Fusion Network for Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcpr-a-multi-scale-attention-based-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most existing multimodal place recognition methods only use limited field-of-view camera images, which leads to an imbalance between features from different modalities and limits the effectiveness of sensor fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lcpr-a-multi-scale-attention-based-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructed Language Models with Retrievers Are Powerful Entity Linkers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructed-language-models-with-retrievers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative approaches powered by large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated emergent abilities in tasks that require complex reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructed-language-models-with-retrievers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical considerations for variable screening in the Super Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-considerations-for-variable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the performance of a Super Learner using the lasso for dimension reduction has not been fully explored in cases where the lasso is known to perform poorly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-considerations-for-variable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Image Semantic Communication Model for Artificial Intelligent Internet of Things</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-semantic-communication-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, at the transmitter side, a high-precision image semantic segmentation algorithm is proposed to extract the semantic information of the image to achieve significant compression of the image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-image-semantic-communication-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APGL4SR: A Generic Framework with Adaptive and Personalized Global Collaborative Information in Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apgl4sr-a-generic-framework-with-adaptive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a graph-driven framework, named Adaptive and Personalized Graph Learning for Sequential Recommendation (APGL4SR), that incorporates adaptive and personalized global collaborative information into sequential recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apgl4sr-a-generic-framework-with-adaptive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truly Scale-Equivariant Deep Nets with Fourier Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truly-scale-equivariant-deep-nets-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In computer vision, models must be able to adapt to changes in image resolution to effectively carry out tasks such as image segmentation; This is known as scale-equivariance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truly-scale-equivariant-deep-nets-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Foundation Model for Music Informatics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-model-for-music-informatics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates foundation models tailored for music informatics, a domain currently challenged by the scarcity of labeled data and generalization issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-foundation-model-for-music-informatics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTP-ViT: Efficient Vision Transformers via Graph-based Token Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gtp-vit-efficient-vision-transformers-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers (ViTs) have revolutionized the field of computer vision, yet their deployments on resource-constrained devices remain challenging due to high computational demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gtp-vit-efficient-vision-transformers-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot Bilingual App Reviews Mining with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-bilingual-app-reviews-mining-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[App reviews from app stores are crucial for improving software requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-bilingual-app-reviews-mining-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1D-Convolutional transformer for Parkinson disease diagnosis from gait</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1d-convolutional-transformer-for-parkinson</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental results show that our approach is effective for detecting the different stages of Parkinson's disease from gait data, with a final accuracy of 88%, outperforming other state-of-the-art AI methods on the Physionet gait dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1d-convolutional-transformer-for-parkinson</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Stage Generative Model with CycleGAN and Joint Diffusion for MRI-based Brain Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-generative-model-with-cyclegan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, current supervised learning methods require extensively annotated images and the state-of-the-art generative models used in unsupervised methods often have limitations in covering the whole data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-generative-model-with-cyclegan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructPix2NeRF: Instructed 3D Portrait Editing from a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructpix2nerf-instructed-3d-portrait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the help of our proposed token position randomization strategy, we could even achieve multi-semantic editing through one single pass with the portrait identity well-preserved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructpix2nerf-instructed-3d-portrait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Self-Supervised Cross-View Training For Sentence Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-self-supervised-cross-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a framework called Self-supervised Cross-View Training (SCT) to narrow the performance gap between large and small PLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-self-supervised-cross-view</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
