<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:09:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Context Autoregressive Video Modeling with Next-Frame Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-autoregressive-video-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing RoPE lacks effective temporal decay for remote context and fails to extrapolate well to long video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-context-autoregressive-video-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correcting Deviations from Normality: A Reformulated Diffusion Model for Multi-Class Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correcting-deviations-from-normality-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This leads to potential degradation of normal regions during reconstruction, hampering the effectiveness of anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correcting-deviations-from-normality-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention IoU: Examining Biases in CelebA using Attention Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-iou-examining-biases-in-celeba</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer vision models have been shown to exhibit and amplify biases across a wide array of datasets and tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-iou-examining-biases-in-celeba</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Spoofing Detection using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-spoofing-detection-using-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spoof detection is critical for enhancing the security of image recognition systems, and this research compares the models effectiveness through accuracy, precision, recall, and F1 score metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-spoofing-detection-using-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoGS: Unified Near and Far Object Reconstruction via Homogeneous Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hogs-unified-near-and-far-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Novel view synthesis has demonstrated impressive progress recently, with 3D Gaussian splatting (3DGS) offering efficient training time and photorealistic real-time rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hogs-unified-near-and-far-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoLLM: A Large Language Model for Composed Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collm-a-large-language-model-for-composed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that CoLLM achieves state-of-the-art performance across multiple CIR benchmarks and settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collm-a-large-language-model-for-composed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RGL: A Graph-Centric, Modular Framework for Efficient Retrieval-Augmented Generation on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgl-a-graph-centric-modular-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in graph learning have paved the way for innovative retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) systems that leverage the inherent relational structures in graph data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rgl-a-graph-centric-modular-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Hidden Potential of CLIP in Generalizable Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-hidden-potential-of-clip-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper tackles the challenge of detecting partially manipulated facial deepfakes, which involve subtle alterations to specific facial features while retaining the overall context, posing a greater detection difficulty than fully synthetic faces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-hidden-potential-of-clip-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Coarse-to-Fine Selection for High-IPC Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-coarse-to-fine-selection-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works on dataset distillation demonstrate that combining distilled and real data can mitigate the effectiveness decay.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-coarse-to-fine-selection-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond outlier removal: Integrated ensemble matching for accurate image keypoint correspondence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-outlier-removal-integrated-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel two-tier matching approach for robust feature correspondence and geometric transformation estimation in computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-outlier-removal-integrated-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware-Rasterized Ray-Based Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-rasterized-ray-based-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel, hardware rasterized rendering approach for ray-based 3D Gaussian Splatting (RayGS), obtaining both fast and high-quality results for novel view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardware-rasterized-ray-based-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeanStereo: A Leaner Backbone based Stereo Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leanstereo-a-leaner-backbone-based-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To recover the performance lost because of a leaner backbone, we propose to use learned attention weights based cost volume combined with LogL1 loss for stereo matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leanstereo-a-leaner-backbone-based-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Stereo Networks for Performant and Efficient Leaner Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-stereo-networks-for-performant-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, our student network while performing better than the performance oriented methods like PSMNet [1], CFNet [2], and LEAStereo [3]) on benchmark SceneFlow dataset, is 8x, 5x, and 8x faster respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-stereo-networks-for-performant-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoMP: Continual Multimodal Pre-training for Vision Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comp-continual-multimodal-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Vision Foundation Models (VFMs) provide strong visual representations for a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comp-continual-multimodal-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DINO in the Room: Leveraging 2D Foundation Models for 3D Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dino-in-the-room-leveraging-2d-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision foundation models (VFMs) trained on large-scale image datasets provide high-quality features that have significantly advanced 2D visual recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dino-in-the-room-leveraging-2d-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PP-FormulaNet: Bridging Accuracy and Efficiency in Advanced Formula Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-formulanet-bridging-accuracy-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present PP-FormulaNet, a state-of-the-art formula recognition model that excels in both accuracy and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-formulanet-bridging-accuracy-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRiNS: A Python Library for Simulating Gene Regulatory Network Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grins-a-python-library-for-simulating-gene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergent dynamics of complex gene regulatory networks govern various cellular processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grins-a-python-library-for-simulating-gene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MC-LLaVA: Multi-Concept Personalized Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-llava-multi-concept-personalized-vision-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the costs related to joint training, we propose a personalized textual prompt that uses visual token information to initialize concept tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-llava-multi-concept-personalized-vision-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniPCGC: Towards Practical Point Cloud Geometry Compression via an Efficient Unified Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipcgc-towards-practical-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, through the dynamic combination of UELC and VRCM, we achieve lossy compression, lossless compression, variable rate and complexity within a unified framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipcgc-towards-practical-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrapped Model Predictive Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapped-model-predictive-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Bootstrapped Model Predictive Control (BMPC), a novel algorithm that performs policy learning in a bootstrapped manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrapped-model-predictive-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Image Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-image-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current generative models, such as autoregressive and diffusion approaches, decompose high-dimensional data distribution learning into a series of simpler subtasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-image-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xKV: Cross-Layer SVD for KV-Cache Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xkv-cross-layer-svd-for-kv-cache-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) with long context windows enable powerful applications but come at the cost of high memory consumption to store the Key and Value states (KV-Cache).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xkv-cross-layer-svd-for-kv-cache-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkAlign: Scalable Schema Linking for Real-World Large-Scale Multi-Database Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linkalign-scalable-schema-linking-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce LinkAlign, a novel framework that can effectively adapt existing baselines to real-world environments by systematically addressing schema linking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linkalign-scalable-schema-linking-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpleRL-Zoo: Investigating and Taming Zero Reinforcement Learning for Open Base Models in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplerl-zoo-investigating-and-taming-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeepSeek-R1 has shown that long chain-of-thought (CoT) reasoning can naturally emerge through a simple reinforcement learning (RL) framework with rule-based rewards, where the training may directly start from the base models-a paradigm referred to as zero RL training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplerl-zoo-investigating-and-taming-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-R1: Evolving Human-Free Alignment in Large Vision-Language Models via Vision-Guided Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-r1-evolving-human-free-alignment-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) typically follow a two-stage training paradigm-pretraining and supervised fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-r1-evolving-human-free-alignment-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Machine Learning Interatomic Potentials with Global Charge Redistribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-machine-learning-interatomic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach enables more accurate and efficient simulations of systems with long-range interactions and charge heterogeneity, expanding the applicability of MLIPs in computational materials science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-machine-learning-interatomic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PathoHR: Breast Cancer Survival Prediction on High-Resolution Pathological Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathohr-breast-cancer-survival-prediction-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Breast cancer survival prediction in computational pathology presents a remarkable challenge due to tumor heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pathohr-breast-cancer-survival-prediction-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimMotionEdit: Text-Based Human Motion Editing with Motion Similarity Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simmotionedit-text-based-human-motion-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-based 3D human motion editing is a critical yet challenging task in computer vision and graphics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simmotionedit-text-based-human-motion-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperNOs: Automated and Parallel Library for Neural Operators Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypernos-automated-and-parallel-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces HyperNOs, a PyTorch library designed to streamline and automate the process of exploring neural operators, with a special focus on hyperparameter optimization for comprehensive and exhaustive exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypernos-automated-and-parallel-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysTwin: Physics-Informed Reconstruction and Simulation of Deformable Objects from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phystwin-physics-informed-reconstruction-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating a physical digital twin of a real-world object has immense potential in robotics, content creation, and XR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phystwin-physics-informed-reconstruction-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConSol: Sequential Probability Ratio Testing to Find Consistent LLM Reasoning Paths Efficiently</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consol-sequential-probability-ratio-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) integrating explicit reasoning, such as OpenAI's o3-mini, DeepSeek-R1, and QWQ-32B, enable smaller models to solve complex tasks by generating intermediate reasoning steps prior to providing answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consol-sequential-probability-ratio-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring a Principled Framework for Deep Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-a-principled-framework-for-deep-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subspace clustering is a classical unsupervised learning task, built on a basic assumption that high-dimensional data can be approximated by a union of subspaces (UoS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-a-principled-framework-for-deep-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dereflection Any Image with Diffusion Priors and Diversified Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dereflection-any-image-with-diffusion-priors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reflection removal of a single image remains a highly challenging task due to the complex entanglement between target scenes and unwanted reflections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dereflection-any-image-with-diffusion-priors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Is Not Enough: Leveraging Behavior for Neural Network Weight Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-is-not-enough-leveraging-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows such models to be applied to a wide variety of downstream tasks, and they demonstrate strong predictive performance and low reconstruction error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-is-not-enough-leveraging-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center-guided Classifier for Semantic Segmentation of Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-guided-classifier-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[i. e., larger intraclass variance, which makes semantic segmentation for remote sensing images more challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-guided-classifier-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastCuRL: Curriculum Reinforcement Learning with Progressive Context Extension for Efficient Training R1-like Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastcurl-curriculum-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose \textbf{\textsc{FastCuRL}}, a simple yet efficient \textbf{Cu}rriculum \textbf{R}einforcement \textbf{L}earning approach with context window extending strategy to accelerate the reinforcement learning training efficiency for R1-like reasoning models while enhancing their performance in tackling complex reasoning tasks with long chain-of-thought rationales, particularly with a 1. 5B parameter language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastcurl-curriculum-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAW-Adapter: Adapting Pre-trained Visual Model to Camera RAW Images and A Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-adapter-adapting-pre-trained-visual-model-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, most existing visual perception methods that utilize RAW data directly integrate image signal processing (ISP) stages with subsequent network modules, often overlooking potential synergies at the model level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raw-adapter-adapting-pre-trained-visual-model-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communities in the Kuramoto Model: Dynamics and Detection via Path Signatures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communities-in-the-kuramoto-model-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Path signatures provide a reparametrization-invariant characterization of dynamical data and, in particular, can be used to compute the lead matrix which reveals lead-lag phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communities-in-the-kuramoto-model-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FFaceNeRF: Few-shot Face Editing in Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffacenerf-few-shot-face-editing-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To utilize masks with a desired layout, an extensive training dataset is required, which is challenging to gather.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffacenerf-few-shot-face-editing-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-Bench: A Benchmark for AI Agents' Ability to Exploit Real-World Web Application Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cve-bench-a-benchmark-for-ai-agents-ability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) agents are increasingly capable of autonomously conducting cyberattacks, posing significant threats to existing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cve-bench-a-benchmark-for-ai-agents-ability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Versatile Controls for Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-versatile-controls-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite substantial progress in text-to-video generation, achieving precise and flexible control over fine-grained spatiotemporal attributes remains a significant unresolved challenge in video generation research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-versatile-controls-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splat-LOAM: Gaussian Splatting LiDAR Odometry and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splat-loam-gaussian-splatting-lidar-odometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDARs provide accurate geometric measurements, making them valuable for ego-motion estimation and reconstruction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splat-loam-gaussian-splatting-lidar-odometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variance Control via Weight Rescaling in LLM Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-control-via-weight-rescaling-in-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The outcome of Large Language Model (LLM) pre-training strongly depends on weight initialization and variance control strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-control-via-weight-rescaling-in-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Overthinking: A Survey on Efficient Reasoning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-overthinking-a-survey-on-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-overthinking-a-survey-on-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni-3DAR: Unified 3D Generation and Understanding via Autoregression on Compressed Spatial Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-3dar-unified-3d-generation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first is a two-level subtree compression strategy, which reduces the octree token sequence by up to 8x.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-3dar-unified-3d-generation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning LLMs by RAG Principles: Towards LLM-native Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-llms-by-rag-principles-towards-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Memory, additional information beyond the training of large language models (LLMs), is crucial to various real-world applications, such as personal assistant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-llms-by-rag-principles-towards-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Reliability of Self-explanation and its Relationship with Classification in Language Model-driven Financial Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-reliability-of-self-explanation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models (LMs) have exhibited exceptional versatility in reasoning and in-depth financial analysis through their proprietary information processing capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-reliability-of-self-explanation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deconstructing Long Chain-of-Thought: A Structured Reasoning Optimization Framework for Long CoT Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-long-chain-of-thought-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable reasoning capabilities through long chain-of-thought (CoT) reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-long-chain-of-thought-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Lighter and Robust Evaluation for Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-lighter-and-robust-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a study which demonstrates the interest of open-weight models for evaluating RAG hallucination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-lighter-and-robust-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal-MAP: Unreal-Engine-Based General Platform for Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unreal-map-unreal-engine-based-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Unreal Multi-Agent Playground (Unreal-MAP), an MARL general platform based on the Unreal-Engine (UE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unreal-map-unreal-engine-based-general</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
