<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 21:05:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>On Masked Pre-training and the Marginal Likelihood</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-masked-pre-training-and-the-marginal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Masked pre-training removes random input dimensions and learns a model that can predict the missing values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-masked-pre-training-and-the-marginal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Risks of Recourse in Binary Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-risks-of-recourse-in-binary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic recourse provides explanations that help users overturn an unfavorable decision by a machine learning system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-risks-of-recourse-in-binary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Language of Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-hidden-language-of-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applied over the state-of-the-art Stable Diffusion model, this decomposition reveals non-trivial and surprising structures in the representations of concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-hidden-language-of-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Grimm -- Open-ended Visual Storytelling via Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-grimm-open-ended-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative models have recently exhibited exceptional capabilities in various scenarios, for example, image generation based on text description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intelligent-grimm-open-ended-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Switching Dynamical Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-switching-dynamical-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamical systems with complex behaviours, e. g. immune system cells interacting with a pathogen, are commonly modelled by splitting the behaviour into different regimes, or modes, each with simpler dynamics, and then learning the switching behaviour from one mode to another.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-switching-dynamical-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting Pre-trained Language Models to Vision-Language Tasks via Dynamic Visual Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-pre-trained-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we also experiment DVP with the recently popular adapter approach to keep the most parameters of PLMs intact when adapting to VL tasks, helping PLMs achieve a quick shift between single- and multi-modal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-pre-trained-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Context Learning User Simulators for Task-Oriented Dialog Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-user-simulators-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel application of large language models in user simulation for task-oriented dialog systems, specifically focusing on an in-context learning approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-context-learning-user-simulators-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Multi-indicator And Multi-organ Medical Image Segmentation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-multi-indicator-and-multi-organ</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, MIMO offers detailed information on the segmentation of each organ in each sample, thereby aiding developers in analyzing and improving the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-multi-indicator-and-multi-organ</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Quality of Revisions in Argumentative Writing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-quality-of-revisions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to revise in response to feedback is critical to students' writing success.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-quality-of-revisions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Offline Reinforcement Learning with Real-Time Budget Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-offline-reinforcement-learning-with-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aiming at promoting the safe real-world deployment of Reinforcement Learning (RL), research on safe RL has made significant progress in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-offline-reinforcement-learning-with-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated Convolution with Learnable Spacings: beyond bilinear interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-convolution-with-learnable-spacings-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dilated Convolution with Learnable Spacings (DCLS) is a recently proposed variation of the dilated convolution in which the spacings between the non-zero elements in the kernel, or equivalently their positions, are learnable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-convolution-with-learnable-spacings-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Potential of 3D Point Cloud Modeling with A Calibrated Local Geometry-driven Distance Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleash-the-potential-of-3d-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By associating each reference point with two given point clouds through computing its directional distances to them, the difference in directional distances of an identical reference point characterizes the geometric difference between a typical local region of the two point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleash-the-potential-of-3d-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TorchRL: A data-driven decision-making library for PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchrl-a-data-driven-decision-making-library</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Striking a balance between integration and modularity is crucial for a machine learning library to be versatile and user-friendly, especially in handling decision and control tasks that involve large development teams and complex, real-world data, and environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torchrl-a-data-driven-decision-making-library</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Vision Transformer with Bidirectional Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-vision-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a Fully Adaptive Self-Attention (FASA) mechanism for vision transformer to model the local and global information as well as the bidirectional interaction between them in context-aware ways.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-vision-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end Knowledge Retrieval with Multi-modal Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-knowledge-retrieval-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate knowledge retrieval with multi-modal queries, i. e. queries containing information split across image and text inputs, a challenging task that differs from previous work on cross-modal retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-knowledge-retrieval-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Event Argument Extraction: Can EAE Models Learn Better When Being Aware of Event Co-occurrences?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-event-argument-extraction-can-eae</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under this framework, we experiment with 3 different training-inference schemes on 4 datasets (ACE05, RAMS, WikiEvents and MLEE) and discover that via training the model to extract all events in parallel, it can better distinguish the semantic boundary of each event and its ability to extract single event gets substantially improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-event-argument-extraction-can-eae</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big data approach towards sarcasm detection in Russian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-big-data-approach-towards-sarcasm-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a set of deterministic algorithms for Russian inflection and automated text synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-big-data-approach-towards-sarcasm-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Unlikelihood Learning Improves Generative Aspect Sentiment Quad Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-unlikelihood-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose marginalized unlikelihood learning to suppress the uncertainty-aware mistake tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-unlikelihood-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label- and slide-free tissue histology using 3D epi-mode quantitative phase imaging and virtual H&amp;E staining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-and-slide-free-tissue-histology-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histological staining of tissue biopsies, especially hematoxylin and eosin (H&E) staining, serves as the benchmark for disease diagnosis and comprehensive clinical assessment of tissue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-and-slide-free-tissue-histology-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Robust Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-self-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-training is an important technique for solving semi-supervised learning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-robust-self-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wuerstchen: Efficient Pretraining of Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuerstchen-efficient-pretraining-of-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Wuerstchen, a novel technique for text-to-image synthesis that unites competitive performance with unprecedented cost-effectiveness and ease of training on constrained hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuerstchen-efficient-pretraining-of-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Pre-trained Model Reversible: From Parameter to Memory Efficient Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-your-pre-trained-model-reversible-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) of pre-trained language models (PLMs) has emerged as a highly successful approach, with training only a small number of parameters without sacrificing performance and becoming the de-facto learning paradigm with the increasing size of PLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/make-your-pre-trained-model-reversible-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing the Internals of Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-internals-of-neural-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern Neural Radiance Fields (NeRFs) learn a mapping from position to volumetric density via proposal network samplers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-the-internals-of-neural-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning for Abdominal Multi-Organ and Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-abdominal-multi-organ</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to dynamically extend a model to new data and classes is critical for multiple organ and tumor segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-for-abdominal-multi-organ</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroGF: A Neural Representation for Fast Geodesic Distance and Path Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurogf-a-neural-representation-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, traditional algorithms for computing geodesic distances and paths on 3D mesh models are often inefficient and slow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurogf-a-neural-representation-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAM-Net: Global Flood Detection from SAR Imagery Using Differential Attention Metric-Based Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-net-global-flood-detection-from-sar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection of flooded areas using high-resolution synthetic aperture radar (SAR) imagery is a critical task with applications in crisis and disaster management, as well as environmental resource planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-net-global-flood-detection-from-sar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intriguing Properties of Text-guided Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intriguing-properties-of-text-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) We find samples in the latent space (which are not outliers) that lead to distorted images independent of the text prompt, suggesting that parts of the latent space are not well-structured.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intriguing-properties-of-text-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affinity-based Attention in Self-supervised Transformers Predicts Dynamics of Object Grouping in Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affinity-based-attention-in-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that our models of affinity spread that were built on feature maps from the self-supervised Transformers showed significant improvement over baseline and CNN based models on predicting reaction time patterns of humans, despite not being trained on the task or with any other object labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affinity-based-attention-in-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSAM: Decoupling Segment Anything Model for Generalizable Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desam-decoupling-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In fully automatic mode, the presence of inevitable poor prompts (such as points outside the mask or boxes significantly larger than the mask) can significantly mislead mask generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desam-decoupling-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving and Benchmarking Offline Reinforcement Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-and-benchmarking-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Offline Reinforcement Learning (RL) has achieved remarkable progress with the emergence of various algorithms and datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-and-benchmarking-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero and Few-shot Semantic Parsing with Ambiguous Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-and-few-shot-semantic-parsing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attempt to address this shortcoming by introducing AmP, a framework, dataset, and challenge for parsing with linguistic ambiguity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-and-few-shot-semantic-parsing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many Answers Should I Give? An Empirical Study of Multi-Answer Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-many-answers-should-i-give-an-empirical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further analyze how well different paradigms of current multi-answer MRC models deal with different types of multi-answer instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-many-answers-should-i-give-an-empirical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiSync: A Bilingual Editor for Synchronized Monolingual Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bisync-a-bilingual-editor-for-synchronized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our globalized world, a growing number of situations arise where people are required to communicate in one or several foreign languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bisync-a-bilingual-editor-for-synchronized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Measures, Partition Lattices and Kernel Tests for High-Order Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-measures-partition-lattices-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models that rely solely on pairwise relationships often fail to capture the complete statistical structure of the complex multivariate data found in diverse domains, such as socio-economic, ecological, or biomedical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-measures-partition-lattices-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReFACT: Updating Text-to-Image Models by Editing the Text Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refact-updating-text-to-image-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image models are trained on extensive amounts of data, leading them to implicitly encode factual knowledge within their parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refact-updating-text-to-image-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Anisotropy and Outliers in Multilingual Language Models for Cross-Lingual Semantic Sentence Similarity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-anisotropy-and-outliers-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate outlier dimensions and their relationship to anisotropy in multiple pre-trained multilingual language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-anisotropy-and-outliers-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vocos: Closing the gap between time-domain and Fourier-based neural vocoders for high-quality audio synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocos-closing-the-gap-between-time-domain-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in neural vocoding are predominantly driven by Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) operating in the time-domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vocos-closing-the-gap-between-time-domain-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Failure Pattern Identification of Predictive Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-failure-pattern-identification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recommendation algorithm is conceptualized as a stochastic sampler that, in each round, queries the annotators a subset of samples for their true labels and obtains the feedback information on whether the samples are misclassified.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-failure-pattern-identification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriSig: Assessing the statistical significance of triclusters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trisig-assessing-the-statistical-significance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work aims at proposing a statistical frame to assess the probability of patterns in tensor data to deviate from null expectations, extending well-established principles for assessing the statistical significance of patterns in matrix data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trisig-assessing-the-statistical-significance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SnapFusion: Text-to-Image Diffusion Model on Mobile Devices within Two Seconds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snapfusion-text-to-image-diffusion-model-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve so by introducing efficient network architecture and improving step distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snapfusion-text-to-image-diffusion-model-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenPI-C: A Better Benchmark and Stronger Baseline for Open-Vocabulary State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openpi-c-a-better-benchmark-and-stronger</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary state tracking is a more practical version of state tracking that aims to track state changes of entities throughout a process without restricting the state space and entity space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openpi-c-a-better-benchmark-and-stronger</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWQ: Activation-aware Weight Quantization for LLM Compression and Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/awq-activation-aware-weight-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown excellent performance on various tasks, but the astronomical model size raises the hardware barrier for serving (memory size) and slows down token generation (memory bandwidth).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/awq-activation-aware-weight-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation Graph Generation via Generative Pre-training over Synthetic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-graph-generation-via-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The generation of explanation graphs is a significant task that aims to produce explanation graphs in response to user input, revealing the internal reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-graph-generation-via-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unfair Utilities and First Steps Towards Improving Them</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfair-utilities-and-first-steps-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many fairness criteria constrain the policy or choice of predictors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unfair-utilities-and-first-steps-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders with Multi-Window Attention Are Better Audio Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-with-multi-window</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several recent works have adapted Masked Autoencoders (MAEs) for learning general-purpose audio representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-with-multi-window</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRES: Generalized Referring Expression Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gres-generalized-referring-expression-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing classic RES datasets and methods commonly support single-target expressions only, i. e., one expression refers to one target object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gres-generalized-referring-expression-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object pop-up: Can we infer 3D objects and their poses from human interactions alone?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-pop-up-can-we-infer-3d-objects-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The intimate entanglement between objects affordances and human poses is of large interest, among others, for behavioural sciences, cognitive psychology, and Computer Vision communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-pop-up-can-we-infer-3d-objects-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layout and Task Aware Instruction Prompt for Zero-shot Document Image Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layout-and-task-aware-instruction-prompt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pre-training-fine-tuning paradigm based on layout-aware multimodal pre-trained models has achieved significant progress on document image question answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layout-and-task-aware-instruction-prompt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDNeRF: Semantics-Driven Face Reconstruction, Prompt Editing and Relighting with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdnerf-semantics-driven-face-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to create high-quality 3D faces from a single image has become increasingly important with wide applications in video conferencing, AR/VR, and advanced video editing in movie industries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fdnerf-semantics-driven-face-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FACT: Federated Adversarial Cross Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-federated-adversarial-cross-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Federated Adversarial Cross Training (FACT), which uses the implicit domain differences between source clients to identify domain shifts in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-federated-adversarial-cross-training</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
