<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 09:17:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Uniform Convergence of Lipschitz Functions with Dependent Gaussian Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-convergence-of-lipschitz-functions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many practical learning problems, training samples are not i. i. d., and there is an intrinsic dependency among samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniform-convergence-of-lipschitz-functions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Time Series Forecasting via Multi-Level Text Alignment with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-time-series-forecasting-via-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adaptation of large language models (LLMs) to time series forecasting poses unique challenges, as time series data is continuous in nature, while LLMs operate on discrete tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-time-series-forecasting-via-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRI: Reducing Cross-Task Interference in Multi-Task Low-Rank Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lori-reducing-cross-task-interference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose LoRA with Reduced Interference (LoRI), a simple yet effective approach that freezes the projection matrices $A$ as random projections and sparsifies the matrices $B$ using task-specific masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lori-reducing-cross-task-interference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating quantum feature map design via large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-quantum-feature-map-design-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum feature maps are a key component of quantum machine learning, encoding classical data into quantum states to exploit the expressive power of high-dimensional Hilbert spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-quantum-feature-map-design-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhaseGen: A Diffusion-Based Approach for Complex-Valued MRI Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phasegen-a-diffusion-based-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce $\textit{PhaseGen}$, a novel complex-valued diffusion model for generating synthetic MRI raw data conditioned on magnitude images, commonly used in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phasegen-a-diffusion-based-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Adversarial Robustness to Bias Elicitation in Large Language Models: Scalable Automated Assessment with LLM-as-a-Judge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-adversarial-robustness-to-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings reveal critical trade-offs between model size and safety, aiding the development of fairer and more robust future language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-adversarial-robustness-to-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaleidoscope: In-language Exams for Massively Multilingual Vision Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaleidoscope-in-language-exams-for-massively</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of vision-language models (VLMs) has mainly relied on English-language benchmarks, leaving significant gaps in both multilingual and multicultural coverage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaleidoscope-in-language-exams-for-massively</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDT: Decoupled Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddt-decoupled-diffusion-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For ImageNet $256\times256$, Our DDT-XL/2 achieves a new state-of-the-art performance of {1. 31 FID}~(nearly $4\times$ faster training convergence compared to previous diffusion transformers).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddt-decoupled-diffusion-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColorizeDiffusion v2: Enhancing Reference-based Sketch Colorization Through Separating Utilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colorizediffusion-v2-enhancing-reference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we conduct an in-depth analysis of the \textbf{carrier}, defined as the latent representation facilitating information transfer from reference to sketch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colorizediffusion-v2-enhancing-reference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting GT2-FLS for Uncertainty Quantification: A Blueprint Calibration Strategy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-gt2-fls-for-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uncertainty Quantification (UQ) is crucial for deploying reliable Deep Learning (DL) models in high-stakes applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-gt2-fls-for-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Diffusion U-Net Representations Contain Positional Embeddings and Anomalies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-u-net-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in synthesizing realistic images, spurring interest in using their representations for various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-u-net-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modality Sensing in mmWave Beamforming for Connected Vehicles Using Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-sensing-in-mmwave-beamforming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Beamforming techniques are considered as essential parts to compensate severe path losses in millimeter-wave (mmWave) communications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modality-sensing-in-mmwave-beamforming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaze-Guided Learning: Avoiding Shortcut Bias in Visual Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-guided-learning-avoiding-shortcut-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we introduce Gaze-CIFAR-10, a human gaze time-series dataset, along with a dual-sequence gaze encoder that models the precise sequential localization of human attention on distinct local attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-guided-learning-avoiding-shortcut-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Nested U-Net Approach: Enhancing Biomarker Segmentation with Attention Mechanisms and Multiscale Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-nested-u-net-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying biomarkers in medical images is vital for a wide range of biotech applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-nested-u-net-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRMedSeg: Unlocking High-resolution Medical Image segmentation via Memory-efficient Attention Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrmedseg-unlocking-high-resolution-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose a memory-efficient framework for high-resolution medical image segmentation, called HRMedSeg.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hrmedseg-unlocking-high-resolution-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniEcon Nexus: Global Microeconomic Simulation Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omniecon-nexus-global-microeconomic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Risk Analysis: Assesses market volatility and systemic risk using network analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omniecon-nexus-global-microeconomic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Data Are Unlearned Equally</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-data-are-unlearned-equally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine unlearning is concerned with the task of removing knowledge learned from particular data points from a trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-data-are-unlearned-equally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caption Anything in Video: Fine-grained Object-centric Captioning via Spatiotemporal Multimodal Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-in-video-fine-grained-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present CAT-V (Caption AnyThing in Video), a training-free framework for fine-grained object-centric video captioning that enables detailed descriptions of user-selected objects through time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caption-anything-in-video-fine-grained-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabRep: a Simple and Effective Continuous Representation for Training Tabular Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabrep-a-simple-and-effective-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultimately, TabRep provides a simple yet effective approach for training tabular diffusion models under a continuous data manifold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabrep-a-simple-and-effective-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoxSeg: Quality-Aware and Peer-Assisted Learning for Box-supervised Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boxseg-quality-aware-and-peer-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Box-supervised instance segmentation methods aim to achieve instance segmentation with only box annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boxseg-quality-aware-and-peer-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoTranh-Abyss-Core-Micro: The Supreme AI for Real-Time Financial Forecasting – Conquer Markets Now</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votranh-abyss-core-micro-the-supreme-ai-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the future of microeconomics!]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votranh-abyss-core-micro-the-supreme-ai-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reinforcement Learning Method for Environments with Stochastic Variables: Post-Decision Proximal Policy Optimization with Dual Critic Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating this post-decision state in the value function approximation leads to more informed and efficient learning in high-dimensional and stochastic environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAD-Net: a full spectral self-attention detail enhancement network for single image dehazing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-net-a-full-spectral-self-attention-detail</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing dehazing methods using vanilla convolution only extract features in the temporal domain and lack the ability to capture multi-directional information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sad-net-a-full-spectral-self-attention-detail</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stereo-LiDAR Fusion by Semi-Global Matching With Discrete Disparity-Matching Cost and Semidensification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-lidar-fusion-by-semi-global-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a real-time, non-learning depth estimation method that fuses Light Detection and Ranging (LiDAR) data with stereo camera input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-lidar-fusion-by-semi-global-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climplicit: Climatic Implicit Embeddings for Global Ecological Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climplicit-climatic-implicit-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning on climatic data holds potential for macroecological applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climplicit-climatic-implicit-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight and Direct Document Relevance Optimization for Generative Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-direct-document-relevance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative information retrieval (GenIR) is a promising neural retrieval paradigm that formulates document retrieval as a document identifier (docid) generation task, allowing for end-to-end optimization toward a unified global retrieval objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-and-direct-document-relevance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFormerv2: Geometry Self-Attention for RGBD Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dformerv2-geometry-self-attention-for-rgbd</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Taking into account that depth can be regarded as a geometry supplement for RGB images, a straightforward question arises: Do we really need to explicitly encode depth information with neural networks as done for RGB images?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dformerv2-geometry-self-attention-for-rgbd</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM2MOT: A Novel Paradigm of Multi-Object Tracking by Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2mot-a-novel-paradigm-of-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To extend this to multi-object tracking (MOT), we propose SAM2MOT, introducing a novel Tracking by Segmentation paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2mot-a-novel-paradigm-of-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Cox Proportional Hazards Model with Symbolic Non-Linear Log-Risk Functions for Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-cox-proportional-hazards-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Generalized Cox Proportional Hazards (GCPH) model, a novel method for survival analysis that leverages KAN to enable a non-linear mapping from covariates to survival outcomes in a fully symbolic manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-cox-proportional-hazards-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhance Then Search: An Augmentation-Search Strategy with Foundation Models for Cross-Domain Few-Shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-then-search-an-augmentation-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models pretrained on extensive datasets, such as GroundingDINO and LAE-DINO, have performed remarkably in the cross-domain few-shot object detection (CD-FSOD) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-then-search-an-augmentation-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hessian of Perplexity for Large Language Models by PyTorch autograd (Open Source)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hessian-of-perplexity-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computing the full Hessian matrix -- the matrix of second-order derivatives for an entire Large Language Model (LLM) is infeasible due to its sheer size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hessian-of-perplexity-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection-Friendly Nonuniformity Correction: A Union Framework for Infrared UAVTarget Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-friendly-nonuniformity-correction-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better balance correction and detection, we introduce a detection-guided self-supervised loss to reduce feature discrepancies between the two tasks, thereby enhancing detection robustness to varying nonuniformity levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-friendly-nonuniformity-correction-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexChunk: Enabling 100M×100M Out-of-Core SpMV (~1.8 min, ~1.7 GB RAM) with Near-Linear Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexchunk-enabling-100mx100m-out-of-core-spmv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Handling large-scale sparse matrices is a fundamental task in many scientific and engineering domains, yet standard in-memory approaches often hit the limitations of available RAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexchunk-enabling-100mx100m-out-of-core-spmv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSL: Not All Tokens Are What You Need for Tuning LLM as a Recommender</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msl-not-all-tokens-are-what-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs), known for their comprehension capabilities and extensive knowledge, have been increasingly applied to recommendation systems (RS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msl-not-all-tokens-are-what-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifting Factor Graphs with Some Unknown Factors for New Individuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifting-factor-graphs-with-some-unknown-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating such background knowledge, LIFAGU is able to further reduce the ambiguity of possible transfers of known potentials to unknown potentials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifting-factor-graphs-with-some-unknown-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Open-Vocabulary Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-open-vocabulary-action-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on scaling open-vocabulary action detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-open-vocabulary-action-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI Enhanced Financial Risk Management Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-enhanced-financial-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces RiskData, a dataset specifically curated for finetuning embedding models in risk management, and RiskEmbed, a finetuned embedding model designed to improve retrieval accuracy in financial question-answering systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-enhanced-financial-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TGraphX: Tensor-Aware Graph Neural Network for Multi-Dimensional Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tgraphx-tensor-aware-graph-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TGraphX presents a novel paradigm in deep learning by unifying convolutional neural networks (CNNs) with graph neural networks (GNNs) to enhance visual reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tgraphx-tensor-aware-graph-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation and Refinement of Reasoning in Small Language Models for Document Re-ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-and-refinement-of-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel approach for training small language models for reasoning-intensive document ranking that combines knowledge distillation with reinforcement learning optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-and-refinement-of-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Symbol Error Probability-based Beamforming in MIMO Gaussian Wiretap Channels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-symbol-error-probability-based-beamforming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates beamforming schemes designed to minimize the symbol error probability (SEP) for an authorized user while guaranteeing that the likelihood of an eavesdropper correctly recovering symbols remains below a predefined threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-symbol-error-probability-based-beamforming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Based Conformal Tube MPC for Safe Control in Interactive Multi-Agent Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-conformal-tube-mpc-for-safe</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety assurance in multi-agent systems with coupled dynamics is a fundamental yet challenging problem, especially when agents exhibit uncertain and state-dependent behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-conformal-tube-mpc-for-safe</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepResearcher: Scaling Deep Research via Reinforcement Learning in Real-world Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepresearcher-scaling-deep-research-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce DeepResearcher, the first comprehensive framework for end-to-end training of LLM-based deep research agents through scaling reinforcement learning (RL) in real-world environments with authentic web search interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepresearcher-scaling-deep-research-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-DAN: towards an efficient prediction strategy for page-level handwritten text recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-dan-towards-an-efficient-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in text recognition led to a paradigm shift for page-level recognition, from multi-step segmentation-based approaches to end-to-end attention-based ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-dan-towards-an-efficient-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Neural Network Based Arrhythmia Classification on Low-cost and Low-compute Micro-controller</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-neural-network-based-arrhythmia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The electrocardiogram (ECG) monitoring device is an expensive albeit essential device for the treatment and diagnosis of cardiovascular diseases (CVD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-neural-network-based-arrhythmia</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steerable Anatomical Shape Synthesis with Implicit Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steerable-anatomical-shape-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative modeling of anatomical structures plays a crucial role in virtual imaging trials, which allow researchers to perform studies without the costs and constraints inherent to in vivo and phantom studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steerable-anatomical-shape-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Augmented Fine Tuning for Mitigating Hallucinations in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-augmented-fine-tuning-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) often produce inaccurate or misleading content-hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-augmented-fine-tuning-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARLANG-1M: A Benchmark for Vision-Language Modeling in SAR Image Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarlang-1m-a-benchmark-for-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic Aperture Radar (SAR) is a crucial remote sensing technology, enabling all-weather, day-and-night observation with strong surface penetration for precise and continuous environmental monitoring and analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sarlang-1m-a-benchmark-for-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoSSVH: Exploring Automated Frame Sampling for Efficient Self-Supervised Video Hashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autossvh-exploring-automated-frame-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose a new framework, termed AutoSSVH, that employs adversarial frame sampling with hash-based contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autossvh-exploring-automated-frame-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitHEP -- The Limits of Low-Precision ML in HEP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bithep-the-limits-of-low-precision-ml-in-hep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing complexity of modern neural network architectures demands fast and memory-efficient implementations to mitigate computational bottlenecks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bithep-the-limits-of-low-precision-ml-in-hep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba as a Bridge: Where Vision Foundation Models Meet Vision Language Models for Domain-Generalized Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-as-a-bridge-where-vision-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing DGSS methods often rely exclusively on either VFMs or VLMs, overlooking their complementary strengths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-as-a-bridge-where-vision-foundation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
