<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:08:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SwinTExCo: Exemplar-based video colorization using Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swintexco-exemplar-based-video-colorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video colorization represents a compelling domain within the field of Computer Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swintexco-exemplar-based-video-colorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DM-Mamba: Dual-domain Multi-scale Mamba for MRI reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-mamba-dual-domain-multi-scale-mamba-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these, we propose a dual-domain multi-scale Mamba for MRI reconstruction from the following perspectives: (1) We pioneer vision Mamba in k-space learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dm-mamba-dual-domain-multi-scale-mamba-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHEQ-ing the Box: Safe Variable Impedance Learning for Robotic Polishing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheq-ing-the-box-safe-variable-impedance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results highlight the potential of adaptive hybrid RL for real-world, contact-rich tasks trained directly on hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheq-ing-the-box-safe-variable-impedance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3UR-LLM: An End-to-End Multimodal Large Language Model for 3D Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ur-llm-an-end-to-end-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) exhibit impressive capabilities in 2D tasks, yet encounter challenges in discerning the spatial positions, interrelations, and causal logic in scenes when transitioning from 2D to 3D representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ur-llm-an-end-to-end-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go-with-the-Flow: Motion-Controllable Video Diffusion Models Using Real-Time Warped Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go-with-the-flow-motion-controllable-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficiency of our algorithm enables us to fine-tune modern video diffusion base models using warped noise with minimal overhead, and provide a one-stop solution for a wide range of user-friendly motion control: local object motion control, global camera movement control, and motion transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/go-with-the-flow-motion-controllable-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D$^2$-DPM: Dual Denoising for Quantized Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-2-dpm-dual-denoising-for-quantized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose D2-DPM, a dual denoising mechanism aimed at precisely mitigating the adverse effects of quantization noise on the noise estimation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-2-dpm-dual-denoising-for-quantized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Label Refinement Matters More than Preference Optimization under Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-label-refinement-matters-more-than</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ILR improves the SFT data by using comparison feedback to decide whether human demonstrations should be replaced by model-generated alternatives, then retrains the model via SFT on the updated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-label-refinement-matters-more-than</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDiffRetro: Retrosynthesis Prediction with Dual Graph Enhanced Molecular Representation and Diffusion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdiffretro-retrosynthesis-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typically, the retrosynthesis prediction involves two phases: Reaction Center Identification and Reactant Generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gdiffretro-retrosynthesis-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PokerBench: Training Large Language Models to become Professional Poker Players</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pokerbench-training-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PokerBench thus presents a unique benchmark for a quick and reliable evaluation of the poker-playing ability of LLMs as well as a comprehensive benchmark to study the progress of LLMs in complex game-playing scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pokerbench-training-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Graph Representations and Graph Neural Networks for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-graph-representations-and-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate Time Series Classification (MTSC) enables the analysis if complex temporal data, and thus serves as a cornerstone in various real-world applications, ranging from healthcare to finance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-graph-representations-and-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Backdoor Attack to Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-backdoor-attack-to-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This demonstrates the vulnerability of DNNs to energy backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-backdoor-attack-to-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Globally Convergent Variational Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-convergent-variational-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This VI method, which may be considered an instance of neural posterior estimation (NPE), minimizes an expectation of the inclusive (forward) KL divergence to fit a variational distribution that is parameterized by a neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globally-convergent-variational-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Motion and Temporal Cues for Unsupervised Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-motion-and-temporal-cues-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address the challenges in unsupervised video object segmentation (UVOS) by proposing an efficient algorithm, termed MTNet, which concurrently exploits motion and temporal cues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-motion-and-temporal-cues-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding subtraction and division of stochastic signals using normalizing flows: NFdeconvolve</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-subtraction-and-division-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the $x=a+b$ example, $a$ can be fluorescence background and $b$ the signal of interest whose statistics are to be learned from the measured $x$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avoiding-subtraction-and-division-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Classification Trees for Continuous Feature Data Using Dynamic Programming with Branch-and-Bound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-classification-trees-for-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computing an optimal classification tree that provably maximizes training performance within a given size limit, is NP-hard, and in practice, most state-of-the-art methods do not scale beyond computing optimal trees of depth three.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-classification-trees-for-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced SPS Velocity-adaptive Scheme: Access Fariness in 5G NR V2I Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-sps-velocity-adaptive-scheme-access</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vehicle-to-Infrastructure (V2I) technology enables information exchange between vehicles and road infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-sps-velocity-adaptive-scheme-access</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FramePainter: Endowing Interactive Image Editing with Video Diffusion Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framepainter-endowing-interactive-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We highlight the effectiveness and efficiency of FramePainter across various of editing signals: it domainantly outperforms previous state-of-the-art methods with far less training data, achieving highly seamless and coherent editing of images, \eg, automatically adjust the reflection of the cup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framepainter-endowing-interactive-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adaptive Orthogonal Convolution Scheme for Efficient and Flexible CNN Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-orthogonal-convolution-scheme-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Orthogonal convolutional layers are the workhorse of multiple areas in machine learning, such as adversarial robustness, normalizing flows, GANs, and Lipschitzconstrained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-orthogonal-convolution-scheme-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Instruct Few-Shot Jailbreaking: Decompose the Attack into Pattern and Behavior Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-instruct-few-shot-jailbreaking-decompose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we take a deeper insight into the mechanism of special token injection and propose Self-Instruct Few-Shot Jailbreaking (Self-Instruct-FSJ) facilitated with the demo-level greedy search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-instruct-few-shot-jailbreaking-decompose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Automated Interpretability with Output-Centric Feature Descriptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-automated-interpretability-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated interpretability pipelines generate natural language descriptions for the concepts represented by features in large language models (LLMs), such as plants or the first word in a sentence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-automated-interpretability-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VENOM: Text-driven Unrestricted Adversarial Example Generation with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/venom-text-driven-unrestricted-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that VENOM achieves superior ASR and image quality compared to prior methods, marking a significant advancement in adversarial example generation and providing insights into model vulnerabilities for improved defense development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/venom-text-driven-unrestricted-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFGraphFR: An attempt at a federated recommendation system based on user text characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufgraphfr-an-attempt-at-a-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Federated learning, the federated recommendation system has gradually become a new recommendation service architecture that can protect users' privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufgraphfr-an-attempt-at-a-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Equilibrium in Online Learning: Theory and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-equilibrium-in-online-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new perspective on online learning that we refer to as gradient equilibrium: a sequence of iterates achieves gradient equilibrium if the average of gradients of losses along the sequence converges to zero.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-equilibrium-in-online-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Deep Active Learning for Medical Imaging: Replay-Base Architecture for Context Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-deep-active-learning-for-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show that RBACA outperforms a baseline framework without CAL, and a state-of-the-art CAL method across various memory sizes and annotation budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-deep-active-learning-for-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-situ graph reasoning and knowledge expansion using Graph-PReFLexOR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-situ-graph-reasoning-and-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pursuit of automated scientific discovery has fueled progress from symbolic logic to modern AI, forging new frontiers in reasoning and pattern recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-situ-graph-reasoning-and-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Inverted Image Pyramid Networks for Visual Perception and Multimodal Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-inverted-image-pyramid-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For multimodal understanding, our PIIP-LLaVA achieves 73. 0% accuracy on TextVQA and 74. 5% on MMBench with only 2. 8M training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-inverted-image-pyramid-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Statistical Capacity of Deep Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-statistical-capacity-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results shed light on the limited capacity of common deep generative models to handle heavy tails.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-statistical-capacity-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenCSG Chinese Corpus: A Series of High-quality Chinese Datasets for LLM Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencsg-chinese-corpus-a-series-of-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities, but their success heavily relies on the quality of pretraining corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencsg-chinese-corpus-a-series-of-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Likes to Sleep: A Computer-Assisted Comparison of Object Naming Data from 30 Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-likes-to-sleep-a-computer-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object naming - the act of identifying an object with a word or a phrase - is a fundamental skill in interpersonal communication, relevant to many disciplines, such as psycholinguistics, cognitive linguistics, or language and vision research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-likes-to-sleep-a-computer-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logarithmic Memory Networks (LMNs): Efficient Long-Range Sequence Modeling for Resource-Constrained Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logarithmic-memory-networks-lmns-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-range sequence modeling is a crucial aspect of natural language processing and time series analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logarithmic-memory-networks-lmns-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-ST: A Multimodal Large Language Model for Fine-Grained Spatial-Temporal Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-st-a-multimodal-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose ST-Align dataset with 4. 3M training samples for fine-grained spatial-temporal multimodal understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-st-a-multimodal-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmoNeXt: an Adapted ConvNeXt for Facial Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emonext-an-adapted-convnext-for-facial-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial expressions play a crucial role in human communication serving as a powerful and impactful means to express a wide range of emotions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emonext-an-adapted-convnext-for-facial-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Driven Water Segmentation with deep learning models for Enhanced Flood Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-water-segmentation-with-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The UNet, ResNet, and DeepLab v3 architectures are tested to determine their effectiveness in various environmental conditions and geographical locations, and the strengths and limitations of each model are also discussed here, providing insights into their applicability in different scenarios by predicting image segmentation masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-driven-water-segmentation-with-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Robustness of Multilingual LLMs on Real-World Noisy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-robustness-of-multilingual-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, mT5 (13B), was the most robust on average overall, across the 3 tasks, and in 4 of the 6 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-robustness-of-multilingual-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Image Generation Fidelity via Progressive Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-generation-fidelity-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that deeper layers are always responsible for high - level content control, while shallow layers handle low - level content control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-image-generation-fidelity-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifelong Learning of Large Language Model based Agents: A Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-learning-of-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey is the first to systematically summarize the potential techniques for incorporating lifelong learning into LLM-based agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelong-learning-of-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Modal Deep Learning Framework for Pan-Cancer Prognosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-deep-learning-framework-for-pan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the multi-modality of patient data and joint training, UMPSNet outperforms all SOTA approaches, and moreover, it demonstrates the effectiveness and generalization ability of the proposed learning paradigm of a single model for multiple cancer types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-modal-deep-learning-framework-for-pan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A User's Guide to $\texttt{KSig}$: GPU-Accelerated Computation of the Signature Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-s-guide-to-texttt-ksig-gpu-accelerated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The signature kernel is a positive definite kernel for sequential and temporal data that has become increasingly popular in machine learning applications due to powerful theoretical guarantees, strong empirical performance, and recently introduced various scalable variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-user-s-guide-to-texttt-ksig-gpu-accelerated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesis and Analysis of Data as Probability Measures with Entropy-Regularized Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-and-analysis-of-data-as-probability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The synthesis problem consists of computing the barycenter, with respect to these costs, of $m$ reference measures given a set of coefficients belonging to the $m$-dimensional simplex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-and-analysis-of-data-as-probability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Text-To-Image Generation via Multilingual Prompting in Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-text-to-image-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as demand for more complex and flexible image descriptions grows, enhancing comprehension of input text within the ICL paradigm remains a critical yet underexplored area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-text-to-image-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pairwise Comparisons without Stochastic Transitivity: Model, Theory and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-comparisons-without-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most statistical models for pairwise comparisons, including the Bradley-Terry (BT) and Thurstone models and many extensions, make a relatively strong assumption of stochastic transitivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-comparisons-without-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skip Mamba Diffusion for Monocular 3D Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-mamba-diffusion-for-monocular-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a unique neural model, leveraging advances from the state space and diffusion generative modeling to achieve remarkable 3D semantic scene completion performance with monocular image input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skip-mamba-diffusion-for-monocular-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Potential of Text in High-Dimensional Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-potential-of-text-in-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series forecasting has traditionally focused on univariate and multivariate numerical data, often overlooking the benefits of incorporating multimodal information, particularly textual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-potential-of-text-in-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathReader : Text-to-Speech for Mathematical Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathreader-text-to-speech-for-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MathReader reduced the WER from 0. 510 to 0. 281 compared to Microsoft Edge, and from 0. 617 to 0. 281 compared to Adobe Acrobat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathreader-text-to-speech-for-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadAlign: Advancing Radiology Report Generation with Vision-Language Concept Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radalign-advancing-radiology-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated chest radiographs interpretation requires both accurate disease classification and detailed radiology report generation, presenting a significant challenge in the clinical workflow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radalign-advancing-radiology-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D3MES: Diffusion Transformer with multihead equivariant self-attention for 3D molecule generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d3mes-diffusion-transformer-with-multihead</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding and predicting the diverse conformational states of molecules is crucial for advancing fields such as chemistry, material science, and drug development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d3mes-diffusion-transformer-with-multihead</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confident Pseudo-labeled Diffusion Augmentation for Canine Cardiomegaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confident-pseudo-labeled-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Canine cardiomegaly, marked by an enlarged heart, poses serious health risks if undetected, requiring accurate diagnostic methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confident-pseudo-labeled-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning First, Then Fusing: A Novel Weakly Supervised Multimodal Violence Detection Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-first-then-fusing-a-novel-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised violence detection refers to the technique of training models to identify violent segments in videos using only video-level labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-first-then-fusing-a-novel-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging ASIC AI Chips for Homomorphic Encryption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-asic-ai-chips-for-homomorphic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cloud-based services are making the outsourcing of sensitive client data increasingly common.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-asic-ai-chips-for-homomorphic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative analysis of optical character recognition methods for Sámi texts from the National Library of Norway</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-optical-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optical Character Recognition (OCR) is crucial to the National Library of Norway's (NLN) digitisation process as it converts scanned documents into machine-readable text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-optical-character</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
