<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 09:12:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LongBoX: Evaluating Transformers on Long-Sequence Clinical Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longbox-evaluating-transformers-on-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessing these models on long sequences is crucial since prior work in the general domain has demonstrated performance degradation of LLMs on longer texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longbox-evaluating-transformers-on-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JaxMARL: Multi-Agent RL Environments in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxmarl-multi-agent-rl-environments-in-jax</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This not only enables GPU acceleration, but also provides a more flexible MARL environment, unlocking the potential for self-play, meta-learning, and other future applications in MARL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jaxmarl-multi-agent-rl-environments-in-jax</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to Basics: A Simple Recipe for Improving Out-of-Domain Retrieval in Dense Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-to-basics-a-simple-recipe-for-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prevailing research practice today often relies on training dense retrievers on existing large datasets such as MSMARCO and then experimenting with ways to improve zero-shot generalization capabilities to unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/back-to-basics-a-simple-recipe-for-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARES: An Automated Evaluation Framework for Retrieval-Augmented Generation Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-an-automated-evaluation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) systems traditionally relies on hand annotations for input queries, passages to retrieve, and responses to generate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ares-an-automated-evaluation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-bayesian-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also show that a single SBNN can be used to represent a variety of spatial processes often used in practice, such as Gaussian processes and lognormal processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-bayesian-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradual Source Domain Expansion for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-source-domain-expansion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) tries to overcome the need for a large labeled dataset by transferring knowledge from a source dataset, with lots of labeled data, to a target dataset, that has no labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradual-source-domain-expansion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INTERVENOR: Prompt the Coding Ability of Large Language Models with the Interactive Chain of Repairing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervenor-prompt-the-coding-ability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Code Learner is asked to generate and repair code according to the instructions from the Code Teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intervenor-prompt-the-coding-ability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-Map-Guided Adaptive Domain Generalization for Cross Modality MRI Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-map-guided-adaptive-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-modal MRI segmentation is of great value for computer-aided medical diagnosis, enabling flexible data acquisition and model generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-map-guided-adaptive-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Anomaly Detection for Chest X-Ray Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-for-chest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chest X-Ray (CXR) examination is a common method for assessing thoracic diseases in clinical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-anomaly-detection-for-chest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS-Former: Memory-Supported Transformer for Weakly Supervised Change Detection with Patch-Level Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-former-memory-supported-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to capture the semantic variations associated with the changed and unchanged regions from the patch-level annotations to obtain promising change results is the critical challenge for the weakly supervised change detection task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms-former-memory-supported-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDMPP: A Device-Model Agnostic Framework for Latency Prediction of Tensor Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdmpp-a-device-model-agnostic-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the large space of DNN models and devices that impede direct profiling of all combinations, recent efforts focus on building a predictor to model the performance of DNN models on different devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdmpp-a-device-model-agnostic-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zenkai -- Framework For Exploring Beyond Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenkai-framework-for-exploring-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zenkai aims to make it easier to get around these limitations and help researchers more easily explore new frontiers in deep learning that do not strictly adhere to the backpropagation framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zenkai-framework-for-exploring-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Do People Tell Stories Online? Story Detection Across Online Communities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-do-people-tell-stories-online-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People share stories online for a myriad of purposes, whether as a means of self-disclosure, processing difficult personal experiences, providing needed information or entertainment, or persuading others to share their beliefs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-do-people-tell-stories-online-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Attention-Based Denoising Framework for Personality Detection in Social Media Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-denoising-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In social media networks, users produce a large amount of text content anytime, providing researchers with a valuable approach to digging for personality-related information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-attention-based-denoising-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Constitutes a Faithful Summary? Preserving Author Perspectives in News Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-constitutes-a-faithful-summary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we take a first step towards designing summarization systems that are faithful to the author's opinions and perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-constitutes-a-faithful-summary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLT: Can Large Language Models Handle Basic Legal Text?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blt-can-large-language-models-handle-basic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the best publicly available LLMs like GPT-4 and PaLM 2 currently perform poorly at basic text handling required of lawyers or paralegals, such as looking up the text at a line of a witness deposition or at a subsection of a contract.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blt-can-large-language-models-handle-basic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Symbolic Integration Brings Causal and Reliable Reasoning Proofs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-integration-brings-causal-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though prompting LLMs with various reasoning structures produces reasoning proofs along with answers, these proofs are not ensured to be causal and reliable due to the inherent defects of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-integration-brings-causal-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PWISeg: Point-based Weakly-supervised Instance Segmentation for Surgical Instruments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwiseg-point-based-weakly-supervised-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel yet effective weakly-supervised surgical instrument instance segmentation approach, named Point-based Weakly-supervised Instance Segmentation (PWISeg).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pwiseg-point-based-weakly-supervised-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Differentiable Logics for Learning Systems: A Research Preview</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-differentiable-logics-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive research on formal verification of machine learning (ML) systems indicates that learning from data alone often fails to capture underlying background knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-differentiable-logics-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center Focusing Network for Real-Time LiDAR Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-focusing-network-for-real-time-lidar-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR panoptic segmentation facilitates an autonomous vehicle to comprehensively understand the surrounding objects and scenes and is required to run in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/center-focusing-network-for-real-time-lidar-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQLNet: Scale-Modulated Query and Localization Network for Few-Shot Class-Agnostic Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlnet-scale-modulated-query-and-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the localization stage, the Scale-aware Multi-head Localization (SAML) module utilizes the query tensor to predict the confidence, location, and size of each potential object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sqlnet-scale-modulated-query-and-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAIA: Delving into Gradient-based Attribution Abnormality for Out-of-distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaia-delving-into-gradient-based-attribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This perspective is motivated by our observation that gradient-based attribution methods encounter challenges in assigning feature importance to OOD data, thereby yielding divergent explanation patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaia-delving-into-gradient-based-attribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedFusion: Manifold Driven Federated Learning for Multi-satellite and Multi-modality Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfusion-manifold-driven-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-satellite, multi-modality in-orbit fusion is a challenging task as it explores the fusion representation of complex high-dimensional data under limited computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfusion-manifold-driven-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reevaluation of Event Extraction: Past, Present, and Future Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reevaluation-of-event-extraction-past</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first identify and discuss these evaluation challenges, including the unfair comparisons resulting from different assumptions about data or different data preprocessing steps, the incompleteness of the current evaluation framework leading to potential dataset bias or data split bias, and low reproducibility of prior studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reevaluation-of-event-extraction-past</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Your Work with Confidence: Confidence Bands for Tuning Curves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-your-work-with-confidence-confidence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The choice of hyperparameters greatly impacts performance in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-your-work-with-confidence-confidence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAM-E: Mammographic synthetic image generation with diffusion models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mam-e-mammographic-synthetic-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we propose using stable diffusion models for the inpainting of synthetic lesions on healthy mammograms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mam-e-mammographic-synthetic-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning with Whom? Large Language Models Have Gender and Racial Biases in Subjective NLP Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-with-whom-large-language-models-have</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that for both tasks, model predictions are closer to the labels from White and female participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-with-whom-large-language-models-have</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inherently Interpretable Time Series Classification via Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherently-interpretable-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional Time Series Classification (TSC) methods are often black boxes that obscure inherent interpretation of their decision-making processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inherently-interpretable-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Evaluation and Insights into the Use of Deep Neural Networks to Detect and Quantify Lymphoma Lesions in PET/CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-and-insights-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study performs comprehensive evaluation of four neural network architectures (UNet, SegResNet, DynUNet, and SwinUNETR) for lymphoma lesion segmentation from PET/CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-evaluation-and-insights-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pachinko: Patching Interpretable QA Models through Natural Language Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pachinko-patching-interpretable-qa-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first one, we present users with incorrect answers and corresponding rationales of various formats and ask them to provide natural language feedback to revise the rationale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pachinko-patching-interpretable-qa-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Far Can We Extract Diverse Perspectives from Large Language Models? Criteria-Based Diversity Prompting!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-extract-diverse-perspectives</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate this problem as diversity extraction in LLMs and propose a criteria-based prompting technique to ground diverse opinions and measure perspective diversity from the generated criteria words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-far-can-we-extract-diverse-perspectives</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepEMD: A Transformer-based Fast Estimation of the Earth Mover's Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepemd-a-transformer-based-fast-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an attention-based model to compute an accurate approximation of the EMD that can be used as a training loss for generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepemd-a-transformer-based-fast-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RENI++ A Rotation-Equivariant, Scale-Invariant, Natural Illumination Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reni-a-rotation-equivariant-scale-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training our model on a curated dataset of 1. 6K HDR environment maps of natural scenes, we compare it against traditional representations, demonstrate its applicability for an inverse rendering task and show environment map completion from partial observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reni-a-rotation-equivariant-scale-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-based soundscape analysis: Jointly identifying sound sources and predicting annoyance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-based-soundscape-analysis-jointly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(4) Generalization tests show that the proposed model's ARP in the presence of model-unknown sound sources is consistent with expert expectations and can explain previous findings from the literature on sound-scape augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-based-soundscape-analysis-jointly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toulouse Hyperspectral Data Set: a benchmark data set to assess semi-supervised spectral representation learning and pixel-wise classification techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toulouse-hyperspectral-data-set-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Airborne hyperspectral images can be used to map the land cover in large urban areas, thanks to their very high spatial and spectral resolutions on a wide spectral domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toulouse-hyperspectral-data-set-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Text Summarization: Unraveling Challenges, Approaches, and Prospects -- A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-summarization-unraveling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generic text summarization approaches often fail to address the specific intent and needs of individual users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-text-summarization-unraveling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Ocean of Biases: Political Bias Attribution in Language Models via Causal Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-ocean-of-biases-political-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) has sparked intense debate regarding their ability to perceive and interpret complex socio-political landscapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-ocean-of-biases-political-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Low Rank Approach to Minimize Sensor-to-Actuator Communication in Finite Horizon Output Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-low-rank-approach-to-minimize-sensor-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we are interested in designing a controller that can be implemented with a minimum number of sensor-to-actuator messages, while satisfying safety constraints over a finite horizon.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-low-rank-approach-to-minimize-sensor-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Transformer Learning with Proximity Data Generation for Text-Based Person Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-transformer-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a proximity data generation (PDG) module to automatically produce more diverse data for cross-modal training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-transformer-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Meme-ing: Measuring Linguistic Variation in Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-meme-ing-measuring-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much work in the space of NLP has used computational methods to explore sociolinguistic variation in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-meme-ing-measuring-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frequency Domain-based Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-based-dataset-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents FreD, a novel parameterization method for dataset distillation, which utilizes the frequency domain to distill a small-sized synthetic dataset from a large-sized original dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frequency-domain-based-dataset-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable and Effective Generative Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-and-effective-generative-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper represents an important milestone in generative retrieval research by showing, for the first time, that generative retrieval models can be trained to perform effectively on large-scale standard retrieval benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-and-effective-generative-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-shot Visual Question Answering via Large Language Models with Reasoning Question Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-visual-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This results in a set of candidate answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-visual-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-ICL: In-Context Learning without Human Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-icl-in-context-learning-without-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of Large Language Models (LLMs), human-computer interaction has evolved towards natural language, offering unprecedented flexibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-icl-in-context-learning-without-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NormNet: Scale Normalization for 6D Pose Estimation in Stacked Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normnet-scale-normalization-for-6d-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing Object Pose Estimation (OPE) methods for stacked scenarios are not robust to changes in object scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normnet-scale-normalization-for-6d-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal NER: A Gold-Standard Multilingual Named Entity Recognition Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-ner-a-gold-standard-multilingual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Universal NER (UNER), an open, community-driven project to develop gold-standard NER benchmarks in many languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-ner-a-gold-standard-multilingual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Knowledge Editing in Language Models via Relation Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-knowledge-editing-in-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Editing (KE) for modifying factual knowledge in Large Language Models (LLMs) has been receiving increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-knowledge-editing-in-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Similarity is Not Enough to Explain Language Model Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-similarity-is-not-enough-to-explain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models achieve high performance on many but not all downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-similarity-is-not-enough-to-explain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical evaluation of Uncertainty Quantification in Retrieval-Augmented Language Models for Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-evaluation-of-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research investigates how uncertainty scores vary when scientific knowledge is incorporated as pretraining and retrieval data and explores the relationship between uncertainty scores and the accuracy of model-generated outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-evaluation-of-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safer-Instruct: Aligning Language Models with Automated Preference Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safer-instruct-aligning-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) is a vital strategy for enhancing model safety in language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safer-instruct-aligning-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
