<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 21:06:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution to MultiEarth 2023 Challenge on Multimodal SAR-to-EO Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-to-multiearth-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Multimodal Learning for Earth and Environment Workshop (MultiEarth 2023) aims to harness the substantial amount of remote sensing data gathered over extensive periods for the monitoring and analysis of Earth's ecosystems'health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-to-multiearth-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftGPT: Learn Goal-oriented Soft Object Manipulation Skills by Generative Pre-trained Heterogeneous Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softgpt-learn-goal-oriented-soft-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Soft object manipulation tasks in domestic scenes pose a significant challenge for existing robotic skill learning techniques due to their complex dynamics and variable shape characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softgpt-learn-goal-oriented-soft-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Knowledge Switching for Pancreas Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-knowledge-switching-for-pancreas</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pancreas segmentation is challenging due to the small proportion and highly changeable anatomical structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-knowledge-switching-for-pancreas</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squeeze, Recover and Relabel: Dataset Condensation at ImageNet Scale From A New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-recover-and-relabel-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new dataset condensation framework termed Squeeze, Recover and Relabel (SRe$^2$L) that decouples the bilevel optimization of model and synthetic data during training, to handle varying scales of datasets, model architectures and image resolutions for effective dataset condensation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-recover-and-relabel-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyKoopman: A Python Package for Data-Driven Approximation of the Koopman Operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pykoopman-a-python-package-for-data-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyKoopman is a Python package for the data-driven approximation of the Koopman operator associated with a dynamical system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pykoopman-a-python-package-for-data-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFCCGAN: A Novel MFCC-Based Speech Synthesizer Using Adversarial Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfccgan-a-novel-mfcc-based-speech-synthesizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluated the model based on a popular intrusive objective speech intelligibility measure (STOI) and quality (NISQA score).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfccgan-a-novel-mfcc-based-speech-synthesizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evading Forensic Classifiers with Attribute-Conditioned Adversarial Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-forensic-classifiers-with-attribute-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these forensic models can detect whether a face image is synthetic or real with high accuracy, they are also vulnerable to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-forensic-classifiers-with-attribute-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitted Value Iteration Methods for Bicausal Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitted-value-iteration-methods-for-bicausal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a fitted value iteration (FVI) method to compute bicausal optimal transport (OT) where couplings have an adapted structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitted-value-iteration-methods-for-bicausal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xSIM++: An Improved Proxy to Bitext Mining Performance for Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsim-an-improved-proxy-to-bitext-mining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In comparison to xSIM, we show that xSIM++ is better correlated with the downstream BLEU scores of translation systems trained on mined bitexts, providing a reliable proxy of bitext mining performance without needing to run expensive bitext mining pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsim-an-improved-proxy-to-bitext-mining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hierarchical Approach to exploiting Multiple Datasets from TalkBank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-approach-to-exploiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TalkBank is an online database that facilitates the sharing of linguistics research data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hierarchical-approach-to-exploiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumbar spine segmentation in MR images: a dataset and a public benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumbar-spine-segmentation-in-mr-images-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a large publicly available multi-center lumbar spine magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) dataset with reference segmentations of vertebrae, intervertebral discs (IVDs), and spinal canal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumbar-spine-segmentation-in-mr-images-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient ResNets: Residual Network Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-resnets-residual-network-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our ResNet achieves a test accuracy of 96. 04% on CIFAR-10 which is much higher than ResNet18 (which has greater than 11 million trainable parameters) when equipped with a number of training strategies and suitable ResNet hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-resnets-residual-network-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking and Analyzing 3D-aware Image Synthesis with a Modularized Codebase</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analyzing-3d-aware-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid advance of 3D-aware image synthesis, existing studies usually adopt a mixture of techniques and tricks, leaving it unclear how each part contributes to the final performance in terms of generality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-analyzing-3d-aware-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Dense-Point Representation for Contour-Aware Graph Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-dense-point-representation-for-contour</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel methodology that combines graph and dense segmentation techniques by jointly learning both point and pixel contour representations, thereby leveraging the benefits of each approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-dense-point-representation-for-contour</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polygon Detection for Room Layout Estimation using Heterogeneous Graphs and Wireframes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polygon-detection-for-room-layout-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a neural network based semantic plane detection method utilizing polygon representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polygon-detection-for-room-layout-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StarVQA+: Co-training Space-Time Attention for Video Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starvqa-co-training-space-time-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attention based Transformer has achieved great success in many computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starvqa-co-training-space-time-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Node-based Core Resilience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-node-based-core-resilience</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first show that a previously proposed measure, Core Strength, does not correctly capture the core resilience of a node upon edge removals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-node-based-core-resilience</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSMT: Real-time Stylized Motion Transition for Characters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsmt-real-time-stylized-motion-transition-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Styled online in-between motion generation has important application scenarios in computer animation and games.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rsmt-real-time-stylized-motion-transition-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambigram Generation by A Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambigram-generation-by-a-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, the pair of 'A' and 'V' shows a high ambigramability (that is, it is easy to generate their ambigrams), and the pair of 'D' and 'K' shows a lower ambigramability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambigram-generation-by-a-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Multiframe Blind Deconvolution via Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-multiframe-blind-deconvolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this method, the image restoration problem is solved with a gradient descent method that is unrolled and accelerated aided by a few small neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-multiframe-blind-deconvolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-VAAL: Multimodal Variational Adversarial Active Learning for Downstream Medical Image Analysis Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-vaal-multimodal-variational-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acquiring properly annotated data is expensive in the medical field as it requires experts, time-consuming protocols, and rigorous validation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-vaal-multimodal-variational-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Implicit Image Function for Efficient Arbitrary-Scale Image Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-implicit-image-function-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a Coarse-to-Fine Multilayer Perceptron (C2F-MLP) to perform decoding with dynamic coordinate slicing, where the number of coordinates in each slice varies as the scale factor varies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-implicit-image-function-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisoGender: A dataset for benchmarking gender bias in image-text pronoun resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visogender-a-dataset-for-benchmarking-gender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VisoGender, a novel dataset for benchmarking gender bias in vision-language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visogender-a-dataset-for-benchmarking-gender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Attackability in Natural Language Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-attackability-in-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial attack research in natural language processing (NLP) has made significant progress in designing powerful attack methods and defence approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-attackability-in-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroCLIP: Neuromorphic Data Understanding by CLIP and SNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroclip-neuromorphic-data-understanding-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle "unseen" recognition for the neuromorphic data, in this paper, we propose NeuroCLIP, which transfers the CLIP's 2D pre-trained knowledge to event spikes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuroclip-neuromorphic-data-understanding-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmark data to study the influence of pre-training on explanation performance in MR image classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-data-to-study-the-influence-of-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a benchmark dataset that allows for quantifying explanation performance in a realistic magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmark-data-to-study-the-influence-of-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdCraft: An Advanced Reinforcement Learning Benchmark Environment for Search Engine Marketing Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adcraft-an-advanced-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce AdCraft, a novel benchmark environment for the Reinforcement Learning (RL) community distinguished by its stochastic and non-stationary properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adcraft-an-advanced-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EquiformerV2: Improved Equivariant Transformer for Scaling to Higher-Degree Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equiformerv2-improved-equivariant-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equivariant Transformers such as Equiformer have demonstrated the efficacy of applying Transformers to the domain of 3D atomistic systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equiformerv2-improved-equivariant-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic Weights and How to Find Them: Where to Prune in Dynamic Sparse Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-weights-and-how-to-find-them-where</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key components of this framework are the pruning and growing criteria, which are repeatedly applied during the training process to adjust the network's sparse connectivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-weights-and-how-to-find-them-where</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Black Box: Analyzing Attention Weights and Hidden States in Pre-trained Language Models for Non-language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-analyzing-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Investigating deep learning language models has always been a significant research area due to the ``black box" nature of most advanced models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-analyzing-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMFlow: An Extensible Toolkit for Finetuning and Inference of Large Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmflow-an-extensible-toolkit-for-finetuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the number of available models and specialized tasks keeps growing, the job of general finetuning becomes highly nontrivial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmflow-an-extensible-toolkit-for-finetuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Relation Between (De)Motivating Topics and Public Stance toward COVID-19 Vaccine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-relation-between-de-motivating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While social media plays a vital role in communication nowadays, misinformation and trolls can easily take over the conversation and steer public opinion on these platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualizing-relation-between-de-motivating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prognostic Biomarker Identification for Pancreatic Cancer by Analyzing Multiple mRNA Microarray and microRNA Expression Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognostic-biomarker-identification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After identifying target genes of DEMs, we selected two DEGs (ECT2 and NRP2) which were also identified among DEMs target genes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prognostic-biomarker-identification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Deep Ensembles: A Large-Scale Evaluation of Bayesian Deep Learning under Distribution Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-deep-ensembles-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian deep learning (BDL) is a promising approach to achieve well-calibrated predictions on distribution-shifted data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-deep-ensembles-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass-Producing Failures of Multimodal Systems with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-producing-failures-of-multimodal-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because CLIP is the backbone for most state-of-the-art multimodal systems, these inputs produce failures in Midjourney 5. 1, DALL-E, VideoFusion, and others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-producing-failures-of-multimodal-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing the Rank Degeneration in Sequential Recommendation via Singular Spectrum Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-the-rank-degeneration-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also establish a correlation between the ranks of sequence and item embeddings and the rank of the user-item preference prediction matrix, which can affect recommendation diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-the-rank-degeneration-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a speed-up alternative method for this fundamental task with comparable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GADBench: Revisiting and Benchmarking Supervised Graph Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gadbench-revisiting-and-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a long history of traditional Graph Anomaly Detection (GAD) algorithms and recently popular Graph Neural Networks (GNNs), it is still not clear (1) how they perform under a standard comprehensive setting, (2) whether GNNs outperform traditional algorithms such as tree ensembles, and (3) their efficiency on large-scale graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gadbench-revisiting-and-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Hierarchical Reasoning Chains by Linking Discourse Units and Key Phrases for Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-hierarchical-reasoning-chains-by-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine reading comprehension (MRC) poses new challenges over logical reasoning, which aims to understand the implicit logical relations entailed in the given contexts and perform inference over them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-hierarchical-reasoning-chains-by-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Mitigating Spurious Correlations in the Wild: A Benchmark &amp; a more Realistic Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-mitigating-spurious-correlations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks often exploit non-predictive features that are spuriously correlated with class labels, leading to poor performance on groups of examples without such features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-mitigating-spurious-correlations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Interactions Reveal Linguistic Structure in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-interactions-reveal-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study feature interactions in the context of feature attribution methods for post-hoc interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-interactions-reveal-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional End-to-End Learning of Retriever-Reader Paradigm for Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-end-to-end-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity Linking (EL) is a fundamental task for Information Extraction and Knowledge Graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-end-to-end-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving and Generating NPR Sunday Puzzles with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-and-generating-npr-sunday-puzzles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the ability of large language models to solve and generate puzzles from the NPR Sunday Puzzle game show using PUZZLEQA, a dataset comprising 15 years of on-air puzzles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-and-generating-npr-sunday-puzzles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3HAN: A Deep Neural Network for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3han-a-deep-neural-network-for-fake-news</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid spread of fake news is a serious problem calling for AI solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3han-a-deep-neural-network-for-fake-news</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PriorBand: Practical Hyperparameter Optimization in the Age of Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priorband-practical-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameters of Deep Learning (DL) pipelines are crucial for their downstream performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/priorband-practical-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Heterophily Aware Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-heterophily-aware-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, urban graphs usually can be observed to possess a unique spatial heterophily property; that is, the dissimilarity of neighbors at different spatial distances can exhibit great diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-heterophily-aware-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding human mobility patterns in Chicago: an analysis of taxi data using clustering techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-human-mobility-patterns-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This analysis will provide a sense of which neighborhoods individuals are using taxis to travel between, suggesting regions to focus new public transit development efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-human-mobility-patterns-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying lottery tickets under label noise: accuracy, calibration, and complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-lottery-tickets-under-label-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pruning deep neural networks is a widely used strategy to alleviate the computational burden in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-lottery-tickets-under-label-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Molecular Discovery with Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-molecular-discovery-with-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language is expected to be a key medium for various human-machine interactions in the era of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-molecular-discovery-with-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polytope: An Algorithm for Efficient Feature Extraction on Hypercubes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polytope-an-algorithm-for-efficient-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel technique, based on computational geometry concepts, which instead carefully pre-selects the precise bytes of data which the user needs in order to then only read those from the datacube.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polytope-an-algorithm-for-efficient-feature</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
