<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:08:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GaussTR: Foundation Model-Aligned Gaussian Transformer for Self-Supervised 3D Spatial Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gausstr-foundation-model-aligned-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce GaussTR, a novel Gaussian Transformer that leverages alignment with foundation models to advance self-supervised 3D spatial understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gausstr-foundation-model-aligned-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tilted Quantile Gradient Updates for Quantile-Constrained Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tilted-quantile-gradient-updates-for-quantile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safe reinforcement learning (RL) is a popular and versatile paradigm to learn reward-maximizing policies with safety guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tilted-quantile-gradient-updates-for-quantile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiLingPoT: Enhancing Mathematical Reasoning with Multilingual Program Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingpot-enhancing-mathematical-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since different programming languages excel in different areas, it is natural to use the most suitable language for solving specific problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingpot-enhancing-mathematical-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Track the Answer: Extending TextVQA from Image to Video with Spatio-Temporal Clues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-the-answer-extending-textvqa-from-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video text-based visual question answering (Video TextVQA) is a practical task that aims to answer questions by jointly reasoning textual and visual information in a given video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/track-the-answer-extending-textvqa-from-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniEval: An Omnidirectional and Automatic RAG Evaluation Benchmark in Financial Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnieval-an-omnidirectional-and-automatic-rag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a typical and practical application of Large Language Models (LLMs), Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) techniques have gained extensive attention, particularly in vertical domains where LLMs may lack domain-specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnieval-an-omnidirectional-and-automatic-rag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic interior-point methods for smooth conic optimization with applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-interior-point-methods-for-smooth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conic optimization plays a crucial role in many machine learning (ML) problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-interior-point-methods-for-smooth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Process-Supervised Reward Models for Clinical Note Generation: A Scalable Approach Guided by Domain Expertise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/process-supervised-reward-models-for-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Process-supervised reward models (PRMs), which verify large language model (LLM) outputs step-by-step, have achieved significant success in mathematical and coding problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/process-supervised-reward-models-for-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAUGE: Taming SAM for Uncertainty-Aligned Multi-Granularity Edge Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sauge-taming-sam-for-uncertainty-aligned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Edge labels are typically at various granularity levels owing to the varying preferences of annotators, thus handling the subjectivity of per-pixel labels has been a focal point for edge detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sauge-taming-sam-for-uncertainty-aligned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locate n' Rotate: Two-stage Openable Part Detection with Foundation Model Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-n-rotate-two-stage-openable-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Transformer-based Openable Part Detection (OPD) framework named Multi-feature Openable Part Detection (MOPD) that incorporates perceptual grouping and geometric priors, outperforming previous methods in performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locate-n-rotate-two-stage-openable-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attentive Eraser: Unleashing Diffusion Model's Object Removal Potential via Self-Attention Redirection Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-eraser-unleashing-diffusion-model-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these problems, we propose Attentive Eraser, a tuning-free method to empower pre-trained diffusion models for stable and effective object removal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-eraser-unleashing-diffusion-model-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSGram: Dynamic Weighting Sub-Metrics for Grammatical Error Correction in the Era of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsgram-dynamic-weighting-sub-metrics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the performance of Grammatical Error Correction (GEC) models has become increasingly challenging, as large language model (LLM)-based GEC systems often produce corrections that diverge from provided gold references.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsgram-dynamic-weighting-sub-metrics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOIDS: High-dimensional Bayesian Optimization via Incumbent-guided Direction Lines and Subspace Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boids-high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When it comes to expensive black-box optimization problems, Bayesian Optimization (BO) is a well-known and powerful solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boids-high-dimensional-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lifting Scheme-Based Implicit Disentanglement of Emotion-Related Facial Dynamics in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifting-scheme-based-implicit-disentanglement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several DFER methods have highlighted the significance of dynamic information, but utilize explicit manners to extract dynamic features with overly strong prior knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifting-scheme-based-implicit-disentanglement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Location-Caption Alignment via Complementary Masking for Weakly-Supervised Dense Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-location-caption-alignment-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods rely on explicit alignment constraints between event locations and captions, which involve complex event proposal procedures during both training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-location-caption-alignment-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-based Local Learning using Stochastic Magnetic Tunnel Junctions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-based-local-learning-using-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain-inspired learning in physical hardware has enormous potential to learn fast at minimal energy expenditure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-based-local-learning-using-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Logits Tree: Pursuing Granularity Reconcilement in Fine-Grained Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-logits-tree-pursuing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the challenge of Granularity Competition in fine-grained classification tasks, which arises due to the semantic gap between multi-granularity labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-logits-tree-pursuing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning of Patch-Based Smooth-Plus-Sparse Models for Image Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-of-patch-based-smooth-plus-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate the optimization as a bilevel problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-of-patch-based-smooth-plus-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptDet: A Lightweight 3D Object Detection Framework with LiDAR Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptdet-a-lightweight-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, multi-modal fusion and knowledge distillation methods for 3D object detection have been proposed to solve this problem, which are time-consuming during the training phase and not friendly to memory cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptdet-a-lightweight-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASAP: Advancing Semantic Alignment Promotes Multi-Modal Manipulation Detecting and Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asap-advancing-semantic-alignment-promotes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ASAP, a new framework for detecting and grounding multi-modal media manipulation (DGM4). Upon thorough examination, we observe that accurate fine-grained cross-modal semantic alignment between the image and text is vital for accurately manipulation detection and grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asap-advancing-semantic-alignment-promotes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining Dimensions for Improving Clustering-based Cross-lingual Topic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-dimensions-for-improving-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This component effectively neutralizes the negative impact of LDDs, enabling the model to accurately identify topics across languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-dimensions-for-improving-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Bias in Deep Neural Networks Using Image Transforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-bias-in-deep-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this, we propose a method to identify dataset bias without the need to crop background information from the images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-bias-in-deep-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoMPaSS: Enhancing Spatial Understanding in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compass-enhancing-spatial-understanding-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image diffusion models excel at generating photorealistic images, but commonly struggle to render accurate spatial relationships described in text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compass-enhancing-spatial-understanding-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural Pruning via Spatial-aware Information Redundancy for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-pruning-via-spatial-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within this framework, we introduce a spatial-aware redundancy metric based on feature maps, thus endowing the pruning process with location sensitivity to better adapt to pruning segmentation networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-pruning-via-spatial-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Data Quantity: Key Factors Driving Performance in Multilingual Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-data-quantity-key-factors-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings identify token similarity and country similarity as pivotal factors, alongside pre-train data and model size, in enhancing model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-data-quantity-key-factors-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArtAug: Enhancing Text-to-Image Generation through Synthesis-Understanding Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artaug-enhancing-text-to-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enables the synthesis model to directly produce aesthetically pleasing images without any extra computational cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artaug-enhancing-text-to-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equity in the Use of ChatGPT for the Classroom: A Comparison of the Accuracy and Precision of ChatGPT 3.5 vs. ChatGPT4 with Respect to Statistics and Data Science Exams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equity-in-the-use-of-chatgpt-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most popular of these platforms is ChatGPT, and it has a paid version (ChatGPT4) and a free version (ChatGPT3. 5).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equity-in-the-use-of-chatgpt-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemStereo: Semantic-Constrained Stereo Matching Network for Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semstereo-semantic-constrained-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the connections between the two tasks and propose a new network that imposes semantic constraints on the stereo matching task, both implicitly and explicitly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semstereo-semantic-constrained-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invisible Watermarks: Attacks and Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invisible-watermarks-attacks-and-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we examine the application of both image-space and latent-space watermarking methods on a single image, where we propose a custom watermark remover network which preserves one of the watermarking modalities while completely removing the other during decoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invisible-watermarks-attacks-and-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EventFull: Complete and Consistent Event Relation Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventfull-complete-and-consistent-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event relation detection is a fundamental NLP task, leveraged in many downstream applications, whose modeling requires datasets annotated with event relations of various types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventfull-complete-and-consistent-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PerSphere: A Comprehensive Framework for Multi-Faceted Perspective Retrieval and Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persphere-a-comprehensive-framework-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As online platforms and recommendation algorithms evolve, people are increasingly trapped in echo chambers, leading to biased understandings of various issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persphere-a-comprehensive-framework-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-in-the-Loop Generation of Adversarial Texts: A Case Study on Tibetan Script</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-generation-of-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How do we generate adversarial texts for less-studied languages?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-in-the-loop-generation-of-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Queries, Representation &amp; Detection: The Next 100 Model Fingerprinting Schemes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/queries-representation-detection-the-next-100</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To foster the creation of new fingerprinting schemes and benchmarks, we open-source our fingerprinting toolbox.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/queries-representation-detection-the-next-100</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Your LLMs Capable of Stable Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-your-llms-capable-of-stable-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of Large Language Models (LLMs) has demonstrated remarkable progress in complex reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-your-llms-capable-of-stable-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised UAV 3D Trajectories Estimation with Sparse Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-uav-3d-trajectories-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compact UAV systems, while advancing delivery and surveillance, pose significant security challenges due to their small size, which hinders detection by traditional methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-uav-3d-trajectories-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SnakModel: Lessons Learned from Training an Open Danish Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snakmodel-lessons-learned-from-training-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SnakModel, a Danish large language model (LLM) based on Llama2-7B, which we continuously pre-train on 13. 6B Danish words, and further tune on 3. 7M Danish instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snakmodel-lessons-learned-from-training-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithmic Fidelity of Large Language Models in Generating Synthetic German Public Opinions: A Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithmic-fidelity-of-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent research, large language models (LLMs) have been increasingly used to investigate public opinions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithmic-fidelity-of-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versatile Ordering Network: An Attention-based Neural Network for Ordering Across Scales and Quality Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-ordering-network-an-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the optimization problems related to ordering are often difficult to solve (e. g., TSP is NP-complete), and developing specialized optimization algorithms is costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-ordering-network-an-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VidTok: A Versatile and Open-Source Video Tokenizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidtok-a-versatile-and-open-source-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Encoding video content into compact latent tokens has become a fundamental step in video generation and understanding, driven by the need to address the inherent redundancy in pixel-level representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidtok-a-versatile-and-open-source-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCTrans: Radar-Camera Transformer via Radar Densifier and Sequential Decoder for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rctrans-radar-camera-transformer-via-radar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In radar-camera 3D object detection, the radar point clouds are sparse and noisy, which causes difficulties in fusing camera and radar modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rctrans-radar-camera-transformer-via-radar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subspace Implicit Neural Representations for Real-Time Cardiac Cine MR Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-implicit-neural-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional cardiac cine MRI methods rely on retrospective gating, which limits temporal resolution and the ability to capture continuous cardiac dynamics, particularly in patients with arrhythmias and beat-to-beat variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subspace-implicit-neural-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster Vision Mamba is Rebuilt in Minutes via Merged Token Re-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-vision-mamba-is-rebuilt-in-minutes-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Re-training the token-reduced model enhances the performance of Mamba, by effectively rebuilding the key knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-vision-mamba-is-rebuilt-in-minutes-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatDiT: A Training-Free Baseline for Task-Agnostic Free-Form Chatting with Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatdit-a-training-free-baseline-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this foundation, we present ChatDiT, a zero-shot, general-purpose, and interactive visual generation framework that leverages pretrained diffusion transformers in their original form, requiring no additional tuning, adapters, or modifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatdit-a-training-free-baseline-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DuSSS: Dual Semantic Similarity-Supervised Vision-Language Model for Semi-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dusss-dual-semantic-similarity-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language Model (VLM) has great potential to enhance pseudo labels by introducing text prompt guided multimodal supervision information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dusss-dual-semantic-similarity-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Errors in the Tobacco3482 Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-errors-in-the-tobacco3482-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tobacco3482 is a widely used document classification benchmark dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-errors-in-the-tobacco3482-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Event Sensory Data for Error Pattern Prediction in Vehicles: A Language Model Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-event-sensory-data-for-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we draw an analogy between processing natural languages and processing multivariate event streams from vehicles in order to predict $\textit{when}$ and $\textit{what}$ error pattern is most likely to occur in the future for a given car.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-event-sensory-data-for-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveTester: A Unified Platform for Simulation-Based Autonomous Driving Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivetester-a-unified-platform-for-simulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, one of the key challenges in ADS testing is the complexity of preparing and configuring simulation environments, particularly in terms of compatibility and stability between the simulator and the ADS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivetester-a-unified-platform-for-simulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CREST: An Efficient Conjointly-trained Spike-driven Framework for Event-based Object Detection Exploiting Spatiotemporal Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crest-an-efficient-conjointly-trained-spike</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-based cameras feature high temporal resolution, wide dynamic range, and low power consumption, which is ideal for high-speed and low-light object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crest-an-efficient-conjointly-trained-spike</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR-Bench: Automated Heterogeneous Information Retrieval Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-bench-automated-heterogeneous-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The testing data in AIR-Bench is generated with respect to diverse tasks, domains and languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-bench-automated-heterogeneous-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Limitations of Large Language Models in Clinical Fact Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-limitations-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Verifying factual claims is critical for using large language models (LLMs) in healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-limitations-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Zero-Shot Multilingual Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-zero-shot-multilingual-aspect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect-based sentiment analysis (ABSA), a sequence labeling task, has attracted increasing attention in multilingual contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-zero-shot-multilingual-aspect</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
