<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient Verification of Quantized Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-verification-of-quantized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantization replaces floating point arithmetic with integer arithmetic in deep neural network models, providing more efficient on-device inference with less power and memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-verification-of-quantized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repaint123: Fast and High-quality One Image to 3D Generation with Progressive Controllable 2D Repainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repaint123-fast-and-high-quality-one-image-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea is to combine the powerful image generation capability of the 2D diffusion model and the texture alignment ability of the repainting strategy for generating high-quality multi-view images with consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repaint123-fast-and-high-quality-one-image-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splatter Image: Ultra-Fast Single-View 3D Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splatter-image-ultra-fast-single-view-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Splatter Image, an ultra-fast approach for monocular 3D object reconstruction which operates at 38 FPS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/splatter-image-ultra-fast-single-view-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning with Extremely Noisy Clients via Negative Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-extremely-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model trained on noisy labels serves as a `bad teacher' in knowledge distillation, aiming to decrease the risk of providing incorrect information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-extremely-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the potential of channel interactions for image restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration aims to reconstruct a clear image from a degraded observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-potential-of-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partially factorized variational inference for high-dimensional mixed models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-factorized-variational-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also provide generic results, which are of independent interest, relating the accuracy of variational inference to the convergence rate of the corresponding coordinate ascent variational inference (CAVI) algorithm for Gaussian targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partially-factorized-variational-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-augmented Multilingual Knowledge Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-multilingual-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge represented in Large Language Models (LLMs) is quite often incorrect and can also become obsolete over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-multilingual-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkyScript: A Large and Semantically Diverse Vision-Language Dataset for Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyscript-a-large-and-semantically-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote sensing imagery, despite its broad applications in helping achieve Sustainable Development Goals and tackle climate change, has not yet benefited from the recent advancements of versatile, task-agnostic vision language models (VLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyscript-a-large-and-semantically-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALMANACS: A Simulatability Benchmark for Language Model Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/almanacs-a-simulatability-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ALMANACS scenarios span twelve safety-relevant topics such as ethical reasoning and advanced AI behaviors; they have idiosyncratic premises to invoke model-specific behavior; and they have a train-test distributional shift to encourage faithful explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/almanacs-a-simulatability-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEER-ZSL: Semantic Encoder-Enhanced Representations for Generalized Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seer-zsl-semantic-encoder-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach generates discriminative classes, effectively classifying both seen and unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seer-zsl-semantic-encoder-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-efficient Spiking Neural Network Equalization for IM/DD Systems with Optimized Neural Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-efficient-spiking-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an energy-efficient equalizer for IM/DD systems based on spiking neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-efficient-spiking-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LRS: Enhancing Adversarial Transferability through Lipschitz Regularized Surrogate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrs-enhancing-adversarial-transferability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The transferability of adversarial examples is of central importance to transfer-based black-box adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lrs-enhancing-adversarial-transferability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assaying on the Robustness of Zero-Shot Machine-Generated Text Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assaying-on-the-robustness-of-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an effort to address these issues, we delve into the realm of zero-shot machine-generated text detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assaying-on-the-robustness-of-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Mindset: An MBTI Exploration of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-mindset-an-mbti-exploration-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel approach for integrating Myers-Briggs Type Indicator (MBTI) personality traits into large language models (LLMs), addressing the challenges of personality consistency in personalized AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-mindset-an-mbti-exploration-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MinePlanner: A Benchmark for Long-Horizon Planning in Large Minecraft Worlds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineplanner-a-benchmark-for-long-horizon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new benchmark for planning tasks based on the Minecraft game.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mineplanner-a-benchmark-for-long-horizon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Shape-Radiance Ambiguity in Radiance Fields with a Closed-Form Color Estimation Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-shape-radiance-ambiguity-in-radiance-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key is a rendering method that is only based on the density field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-shape-radiance-ambiguity-in-radiance-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdvST: Revisiting Data Augmentations for Single Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advst-revisiting-data-augmentations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we propose Adversarial learning with Semantics Transformations (AdvST) that augments the source domain data with semantics transformations and learns a robust model with the augmented data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advst-revisiting-data-augmentations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSL: Understanding and Improving Softmax Loss for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsl-understanding-and-improving-softmax-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Loss functions steer the optimization direction of recommendation models and are critical to model performance, but have received relatively little attention in recent recommendation research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsl-understanding-and-improving-softmax-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Distillation: Regularizing Continued Pre-training for Low-Resource Automatic Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-distillation-regularizing-continued</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, first, we perform vanilla continued pre-training on an initial SSL pre-trained model on the target domain ASR dataset and call it the teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-distillation-regularizing-continued</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at the Few-Shot Adaptation of Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-few-shot-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient transfer learning (ETL) is receiving increasing attention to adapt large pre-trained language-vision models on downstream tasks with a few labeled samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-few-shot-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Prompt Tuning:Unveiling Unseen Classes for Zero-Shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-prompt-tuning-unveiling-unseen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, CLIP has found practical utility in the domain of pixel-level zero-shot segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-prompt-tuning-unveiling-unseen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TagCLIP: A Local-to-Global Framework to Enhance Open-Vocabulary Multi-Label Classification of CLIP Without Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tagclip-a-local-to-global-framework-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, we dissect the preservation of patch-wise spatial information in CLIP and proposed a local-to-global framework to obtain image tags.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tagclip-a-local-to-global-framework-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning English-centric LLMs Into Polyglots: How Much Multilinguality Is Needed?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-english-centric-llms-into-polyglots</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vast majority of today's large language models are English-centric, having been pretrained predominantly on English text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-english-centric-llms-into-polyglots</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameterized Projected Bellman Operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameterized-projected-bellman-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formulate an optimization problem to learn PBO for generic sequential decision-making problems, and we theoretically analyze its properties in two representative classes of RL problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameterized-projected-bellman-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-Optimal Resilient Aggregation Rules for Distributed Learning Using 1-Center and 1-Mean Clustering with Outliers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-resilient-aggregation-rules-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis show that constant approximations to the 1-center and 1-mean clustering problems with outliers provide near-optimal resilient aggregators for metric-based criteria, which have been proven to be crucial in the homogeneous and heterogeneous cases respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-resilient-aggregation-rules-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatFDA: Medical Records Risk Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatfda-medical-records-risk-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In healthcare, the emphasis on patient safety and the minimization of medical errors cannot be overstated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatfda-medical-records-risk-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realistic Rainy Weather Simulation for LiDARs in CARLA Simulator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-rainy-weather-simulation-for-lidars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a simulator-based physical modeling approach to augment LiDAR data in rainy weather in order to improve the perception performance of LiDAR in this scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-rainy-weather-simulation-for-lidars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FusDom: Combining In-Domain and Out-of-Domain Knowledge for Continuous Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusdom-combining-in-domain-and-out-of-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continued pre-training (CP) offers multiple advantages, like target domain adaptation and the potential to exploit the continuous stream of unlabeled data available online.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusdom-combining-in-domain-and-out-of-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiFAR: A Fraud Detection Dataset for Learning to Defer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fifar-a-fraud-detection-dataset-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Financial fraud detection is a high-stakes setting where algorithms and human experts often work in tandem; however, there are no publicly available datasets for L2D concerning this important application of human-AI teaming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fifar-a-fraud-detection-dataset-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Response Enhanced Semi-Supervised Dialogue Query Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-enhanced-semi-supervised-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the observation that the search query is typically related to the topic of dialogue response, we train a response-augmented query producer (RA) to provide rich and effective training signals for QP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-enhanced-semi-supervised-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Machine Learning Algorithms by Union-Free Generic Depth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-machine-learning-algorithms-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a framework for descriptively analyzing sets of partial orders based on the concept of depth functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-machine-learning-algorithms-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeLL: A Lifelong Learning Dataset to Support the Co-Evolution of Data and Language Models of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codell-a-lifelong-learning-dataset-to-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by recent work on lifelong learning applications for language models (LMs) of code, we introduce CodeLL, a lifelong learning dataset focused on code changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codell-a-lifelong-learning-dataset-to-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models With Learned Adaptive Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-learned-adaptive-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have gained traction as powerful algorithms for synthesizing high-quality images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-learned-adaptive-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dual-way Enhanced Framework from Text Matching Point of View for Multimodal Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-way-enhanced-framework-from-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Entity Linking (MEL) aims at linking ambiguous mentions with multimodal information to entity in Knowledge Graph (KG) such as Wikipedia, which plays a key role in many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-way-enhanced-framework-from-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Model Meets New Normals: Test-time Adaptation for Unsupervised Time-series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-model-meets-new-normals-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time-series anomaly detection deals with the problem of detecting anomalous timesteps by learning normality from the sequence of observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-model-meets-new-normals-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Geometric Fracture Assembly via Co-creation Space among Assemblers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-geometric-fracture-assembly-via-co</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, there is a need to develop a scalable framework for geometric fracture assembly without relying on semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-geometric-fracture-assembly-via-co</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object-Aware Domain Generalization for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-aware-domain-generalization-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these problems, we propose an object-aware domain generalization (OA-DG) method for single-domain generalization in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-aware-domain-generalization-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibrating Wireless Ray Tracing for Digital Twinning using Local Phase Error Estimates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrating-wireless-ray-tracing-for-digital</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel channel response-based scheme that, unlike the state of the art, estimates and compensates for the phase errors in the RT-generated channel responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibrating-wireless-ray-tracing-for-digital</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHManip: A Dataset for Long-Horizon Language-Grounded Manipulation Tasks in Cluttered Tabletop Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhmanip-a-dataset-for-long-horizon-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instructing a robot to complete an everyday task within our homes has been a long-standing challenge for robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhmanip-a-dataset-for-long-horizon-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Error Detection with Contrastive Confidence Adaption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-error-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graphs (KGs) often contain various errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-error-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XLand-MiniGrid: Scalable Meta-Reinforcement Learning Environments in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xland-minigrid-scalable-meta-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present XLand-MiniGrid, a suite of tools and grid-world environments for meta-reinforcement learning research inspired by the diversity and depth of XLand and the simplicity and minimalism of MiniGrid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xland-minigrid-scalable-meta-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-DINOiser: Teaching CLIP a few DINO tricks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-dinoiser-teaching-clip-a-few-dino-tricks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to locally improve dense MaskCLIP features, computed with a simple modification of CLIP's last pooling layer, by integrating localization priors extracted from self-supervised features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-dinoiser-teaching-clip-a-few-dino-tricks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celestial Machine Learning: Discovering the Planarity, Heliocentricity, and Orbital Equation of Mars with AI Feynman</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/celestial-machine-learning-discovering-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can a machine or algorithm discover or learn the elliptical orbit of Mars from astronomical sightings alone?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/celestial-machine-learning-discovering-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll With the Punches: Expansion and Shrinkage of Soft Label Selection for Semi-supervised Fine-Grained Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roll-with-the-punches-expansion-and-shrinkage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While semi-supervised learning (SSL) has yielded promising results, the more realistic SSL scenario remains to be explored, in which the unlabeled data exhibits extremely high recognition difficulty, e. g., fine-grained visual classification in the context of SSL (SS-FGVC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/roll-with-the-punches-expansion-and-shrinkage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I-CEE: Tailoring Explanations of Image Classifications Models to User Expertise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-cee-tailoring-explanations-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Informed by existing work, I-CEE explains the decisions of image classification models by providing the user with an informative subset of training data (i. e., example images), corresponding local explanations, and model decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-cee-tailoring-explanations-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact ASP Counting with Compact Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-asp-counting-with-compact-encodings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been growing interest in problems beyond satisfiability, such as model counting, in the context of ASP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-asp-counting-with-compact-encodings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Frequency-Aware Network for Laparoscopic Image Desmoking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-frequency-aware-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laparoscopic surgery offers minimally invasive procedures with better patient outcomes, but smoke presence challenges visibility and safety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-frequency-aware-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M-BEV: Masked BEV Perception for Robust Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-bev-masked-bev-perception-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It mimics various missing cases by randomly masking features of different camera views, then leverages the original features of these views as self-supervision, and reconstructs the masked ones with the distinct spatio-temporal context across views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-bev-masked-bev-perception-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-LFM: Lifting Foundation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-lfm-lifting-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lifting of 3D structure and camera from 2D landmarks is at the cornerstone of the entire discipline of computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-lfm-lifting-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PICNN: A Pathway towards Interpretable Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picnn-a-pathway-towards-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results have demonstrated that our method PICNN (the combination of standard CNNs with our proposed pathway) exhibits greater interpretability than standard CNNs while achieving higher or comparable discrimination power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picnn-a-pathway-towards-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
