<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 21:07:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MAE-DFER: Efficient Masked Autoencoder for Self-supervised Dynamic Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mae-dfer-efficient-masked-autoencoder-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by recent unprecedented success of masked autoencoders (e. g., VideoMAE), this paper proposes MAE-DFER, a novel self-supervised method which leverages large-scale self-supervised pre-training on abundant unlabeled data to advance the development of DFER.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mae-dfer-efficient-masked-autoencoder-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Prediction using Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoji-prediction-using-transformer-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We fine-tuned BERT on a large corpus of text containing both text and emojis to predict the most appropriate emoji for a given text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoji-prediction-using-transformer-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Shielding under Delayed Observation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-shielding-under-delayed-observation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose synthesis algorithms to compute \emph{delay-resilient shields} that guarantee safety under worst-case assumptions on the delays of the input signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-shielding-under-delayed-observation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongNet: Scaling Transformers to 1,000,000,000 Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longnet-scaling-transformers-to-1000000000</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling sequence length has become a critical demand in the era of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longnet-scaling-transformers-to-1000000000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Contrastive Topic Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-topic-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on it, we propose the graph contrastive topic model (GCTM), which conducts graph contrastive learning (GCL) using informative positive and negative samples that are generated by the graph-based sampling strategy leveraging in-depth correlation and irrelevance among documents and words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-topic-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flacuna: Unleashing the Problem Solving Power of Vicuna using FLAN Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flacuna-unleashing-the-problem-solving-power</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, despite being introduced four years ago, T5-based LLMs, such as FLAN-T5, continue to outperform the latest decoder-based LLMs, such as LLAMA and VICUNA, on tasks that require general problem-solving skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flacuna-unleashing-the-problem-solving-power</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Deduction with Incomplete Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A growing body of work studies how to answer a question or verify a claim by generating a natural language "proof": a chain of deductive inferences yielding the answer based on a set of premises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Guided Additive Modeling For Supervised Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-guided-additive-modeling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning processes by exploiting restricted domain knowledge is an important task across a plethora of scientific areas, with more and more hybrid methods combining data-driven and model-based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-guided-additive-modeling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Address Matching using Siamese Transformer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-address-matching-using-siamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces a deep learning-based model designed to increase the efficiency of address matching for Portuguese addresses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-address-matching-using-siamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLCaps: Learning to Illuminate Low-Light Capsule Endoscopy with Curved Wavelet Attention and Reverse Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llcaps-learning-to-illuminate-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the exuberant development of the denoising diffusion probabilistic model (DDPM) in computer vision, we introduce a WCE LLIE framework based on the multi-scale convolutional neural network (CNN) and reverse diffusion process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llcaps-learning-to-illuminate-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Image Segmentation with Cross-Modality Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-image-segmentation-with-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interactive image segmentation aims to segment the target from the background with the manual guidance, which takes as input multimodal data such as images, clicks, scribbles, and bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-image-segmentation-with-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set Learning for Accurate and Calibrated Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set-learning-for-accurate-and-calibrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model overconfidence and poor calibration are common in machine learning and difficult to account for when applying standard empirical risk minimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/set-learning-for-accurate-and-calibrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDViT: Multi-domain Vision Transformer for Small Medical Image Segmentation Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdvit-multi-domain-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Naivly combining datasets from different domains can result in negative knowledge transfer (NKT), i. e., a decrease in model performance on some domains with non-negligible inter-domain heterogeneity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdvit-multi-domain-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NMS Threshold matters for Ego4D Moment Queries -- 2nd place solution to the Ego4D Moment Queries Challenge 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nms-threshold-matters-for-ego4d-moment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report describes our submission to the Ego4D Moment Queries Challenge 2023.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nms-threshold-matters-for-ego4d-moment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3C: Self-Supervised Stochastic Classifiers for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3c-self-supervised-stochastic-classifiers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot class-incremental learning (FSCIL) aims to learn progressively about new classes with very few labeled samples, without forgetting the knowledge of already learnt classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3c-self-supervised-stochastic-classifiers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Deep Neural Networks Learn Compositional Data: The Random Hierarchy Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-deep-neural-networks-learn-compositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the number of training data $P^*$ required by deep CNNs to learn this task (i) grows asymptotically as $n_c m^L$, which is only polynomial in the input dimensionality; (ii) coincides with the training set size such that the representation of a trained network becomes invariant to exchanges of synonyms; (iii) corresponds to the number of data at which the correlations between low-level features and classes become detectable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-deep-neural-networks-learn-compositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Images Generated by Deep Diffusion Models using their Local Intrinsic Dimensionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-images-generated-by-deep-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose using the lightweight multi Local Intrinsic Dimensionality (multiLID), which has been originally developed in context of the detection of adversarial examples, for the automatic detection of synthetic images and the identification of the according generator networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-images-generated-by-deep-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing Image Change Detection with Graph Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-image-change-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More specifically, by leveraging the concept of non-local operations and mapping the features obtained from the backbone network to the graph structure space, we propose a unified self-focus mechanism for bitemporal images. This approach enhances the information coupling between the two temporal images while effectively suppressing task-irrelevant interference, Based on a streamlined backbone architecture, namely ResNet18, our model demonstrates superior performance compared to other state-of-the-art methods (SOTA) on the GZ CD dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-image-change-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Neural Architecture Search: Challenges, Solutions, and Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-neural-architecture-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, zero-shot (or training-free) Neural Architecture Search (NAS) approaches have been proposed to liberate the NAS from training requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-neural-architecture-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceNLI: Evaluating the Consistency of Predicting Inferences in Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spacenli-evaluating-the-consistency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While many natural language inference (NLI) datasets target certain semantic phenomena, e. g., negation, tense & aspect, monotonicity, and presupposition, to the best of our knowledge, there is no NLI dataset that involves diverse types of spatial expressions and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spacenli-evaluating-the-consistency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Won't Get Fooled Again: Answering Questions with False Premises</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/won-t-get-fooled-again-answering-questions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we find that the PLMs already possess the knowledge required to rebut such questions, and the key is how to activate the knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/won-t-get-fooled-again-answering-questions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAFAR: Graph-Attention Feature-Augmentation for Registration A Fast and Light-weight Point Set Registration Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gafar-graph-attention-feature-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rigid registration of point clouds is a fundamental problem in computer vision with many applications from 3D scene reconstruction to geometry capture and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gafar-graph-attention-feature-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonDiffusion: Enabling Drag-style Manipulation on Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragondiffusion-enabling-drag-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we construct classifier guidance based on the strong correspondence of intermediate features in the diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragondiffusion-enabling-drag-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparison of Machine Learning Methods for Data with High-Cardinality Categorical Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-machine-learning-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-cardinality categorical variables are variables for which the number of different levels is large relative to the sample size of a data set, or in other words, there are few data points per level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparison-of-machine-learning-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAM: Relative Flatness Aware Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fam-relative-flatness-aware-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Their widespread adoption in practice, though, is dubious because of the lack of theoretically grounded connection between flatness and generalization, in particular in light of the reparameterization curse - certain reparameterizations of a neural network change most flatness measures but do not change generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fam-relative-flatness-aware-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARE: Towards Robust Text Explanations in Biomedical and Healthcare Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dare-towards-robust-text-explanations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This results in our DomainAdaptiveAREstimator (DARE) attribution robustness estimator, allowing us to properly characterize the domain-specific robustness of faithful explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dare-towards-robust-text-explanations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-scale Detection of Marine Debris in Coastal Areas with Sentinel-2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-detection-of-marine-debris-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, remote sensing can provide reliable estimates of plastic pollution by regularly monitoring and detecting marine debris in coastal areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-detection-of-marine-debris-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery with Language Models as Imperfect Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-with-language-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the causal relationships that underlie a system is a fundamental prerequisite to accurate decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-with-language-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Explore, then Exploit: Meta-Learning Intelligent Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/first-explore-then-exploit-meta-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue a core barrier prohibiting many RL approaches from learning intelligent exploration is that the methods attempt to explore and exploit simultaneously, which harms both exploration and exploitation as the goals often conflict.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/first-explore-then-exploit-meta-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULSAR at MEDIQA-Sum 2023: Large Language Models Augmented by Synthetic Dialogue Convert Patient Dialogues to Medical Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulsar-at-mediqa-sum-2023-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes PULSAR, our system submission at the ImageClef 2023 MediQA-Sum task on summarising patient-doctor dialogues into clinical records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulsar-at-mediqa-sum-2023-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Domain Hierarchical Event Schema Induction by Incremental Prompting and Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-domain-hierarchical-event-schema</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event schemas are a form of world knowledge about the typical progression of events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-domain-hierarchical-event-schema</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Controllable Transformer-Based Lexical Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-controllable-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, further evaluation of our approach on the part of the recent TSAR-2022 multilingual LS shared-task dataset shows that our model performs competitively when compared with the participating systems for English LS and even outperforms the GPT-3 model on several metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-controllable-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EHRSHOT: An EHR Benchmark for Few-Shot Evaluation of Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrshot-an-ehr-benchmark-for-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of foundation models creates new challenges for healthcare ML by requiring access to shared pretrained models to validate performance benefits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrshot-an-ehr-benchmark-for-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformed Protoform Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformed-protoform-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We update their model with the state-of-the-art seq2seq model: the Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformed-protoform-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClimateLearn: Benchmarking Machine Learning for Weather and Climate Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climatelearn-benchmarking-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modeling weather and climate is an essential endeavor to understand the near- and long-term impacts of climate change, as well as inform technology and policymaking for adaptation and mitigation efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climatelearn-benchmarking-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local primordial non-Gaussianity from the large-scale clustering of photometric DESI luminous red galaxies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-primordial-non-gaussianity-from-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use angular clustering of luminous red galaxies from the Dark Energy Spectroscopic Instrument (DESI) imaging surveys to constrain the local primordial non-Gaussianity parameter fNL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-primordial-non-gaussianity-from-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hybrid machine learning framework for clad characteristics prediction in metal additive manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-machine-learning-framework-for-clad</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework resolves many challenges of conventional modeling methods in MAM by solving t the issue of data scarcity using a hybrid approach and introducing an efficient, accurate, and scalable platform for clad characteristics prediction and optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-machine-learning-framework-for-clad</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Wound Filling Extraction on 3D Faces: A Auto-Segmentation and Wound Face Regeneration Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-wound-filling-extraction-on-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial wound segmentation plays a crucial role in preoperative planning and optimizing patient outcomes in various medical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-wound-filling-extraction-on-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CARE-MI: Chinese Benchmark for Misinformation Evaluation in Maternity and Infant Care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-mi-chinese-benchmark-for-misinformation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we present a benchmark, CARE-MI, for evaluating LLM misinformation in: 1) a sensitive topic, specifically the maternity and infant care domain; and 2) a language other than English, namely Chinese.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care-mi-chinese-benchmark-for-misinformation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Lie Group Symmetry Transformations with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-lie-group-symmetry-transformations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of detecting and quantifying the presence of symmetries in datasets is useful for model selection, generative modeling, and data analysis, amongst others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-lie-group-symmetry-transformations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentanglement in a GAN for Unconditional Speech Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentanglement-in-a-gan-for-unconditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We confirm that ASGAN's latent space is disentangled: we demonstrate how simple linear operations in the space can be used to perform several tasks unseen during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentanglement-in-a-gan-for-unconditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Retrieval-Augmented In-Context Learning for Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-retrieval-augmented-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been significant interest in zero and few-shot learning for dialogue state tracking (DST) due to the high cost of collecting and annotating task-oriented dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-retrieval-augmented-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Aware Audio-Grounded Generative Slot Filling for Limited Annotated Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-aware-audio-grounded-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Knowledge-Aware Audio-Grounded generative slot-filling framework, termed KA2G, that focuses on few-shot and zero-shot slot filling for ToD with speech input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-aware-audio-grounded-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Private Kernel Density Estimation via Locality Sensitive Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-private-kernel-density-estimation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study efficient mechanisms for differentially private kernel density estimation (DP-KDE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-private-kernel-density-estimation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretraining is All You Need: A Multi-Atlas Enhanced Transformer Framework for Autism Spectrum Disorder Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-is-all-you-need-a-multi-atlas</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through stratified cross-validation, we evaluate the proposed framework and show that it surpasses state-of-the-art performance on the ABIDE I dataset, with an average accuracy of 83. 7% and an AUC-score of 0. 832.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-is-all-you-need-a-multi-atlas</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDXL: Improving Latent Diffusion Models for High-Resolution Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdxl-improving-latent-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SDXL, a latent diffusion model for text-to-image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdxl-improving-latent-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskBEV: Joint Object Detection and Footprint Completion for Bird's-eye View 3D Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskbev-joint-object-detection-and-footprint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works in object detection in LiDAR point clouds mostly focus on predicting bounding boxes around objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskbev-joint-object-detection-and-footprint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spike-driven Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spike-driven-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we incorporate the spike-driven paradigm into Transformer by the proposed Spike-driven Transformer with four unique properties: 1) Event-driven, no calculation is triggered when the input of Transformer is zero; 2) Binary spike communication, all matrix multiplications associated with the spike matrix can be transformed into sparse additions; 3) Self-attention with linear complexity at both token and channel dimensions; 4) The operations between spike-form Query, Key, and Value are mask and addition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spike-driven-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H-DenseFormer: An Efficient Hybrid Densely Connected Transformer for Multimodal Tumor Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-denseformer-an-efficient-hybrid-densely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a hybrid densely connected network for tumor segmentation, named H-DenseFormer, which combines the representational power of the Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) and the Transformer structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-denseformer-an-efficient-hybrid-densely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embodied Task Planning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodied-task-planning-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equipping embodied agents with commonsense is important for robots to successfully complete complex human instructions in general environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embodied-task-planning-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
