<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 21:09:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing MMDiT-Based Text-to-Image Models for Similar Subject Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant improvements, we observe that semantic ambiguity persists when generating multiple similar subjects, as the guidance provided by overlap loss is not explicit enough.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-mmdit-based-text-to-image-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surveying the space of descriptions of a composite system with machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating machine learning into a fine-grained information theoretic analysis of composite random variables, our framework opens a new avenues for probing the structure of real-world complex systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surveying-the-space-of-descriptions-of-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helvipad: A Real-World Dataset for Omnidirectional Stereo Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite considerable progress in stereo depth estimation, omnidirectional imaging remains underexplored, mainly due to the lack of appropriate data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helvipad-a-real-world-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TimeMarker: A Versatile Video-LLM for Long and Short Video Understanding with Superior Temporal Localization Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapid development of large language models (LLMs) has significantly advanced multimodal large language models (LMMs), particularly in vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timemarker-a-versatile-video-llm-for-long-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Blind All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blind all-in-one image restoration models aim to recover a high-quality image from an input degraded with unknown distortions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-blind-all-in-one-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUPE: Heuristic Underwater Perceptual Enhancement with Semantic Collaborative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To strike a balance between visual quality and application, we propose a heuristic invertible network for underwater perception enhancement, dubbed HUPE, which enhances visual quality and demonstrates flexibility in handling other downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hupe-heuristic-underwater-perceptual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft Model Knows When to Stop: A Self-Verification Length Policy for Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speculative Decoding (SD) has become an important technique in accelerating the inference speed of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/draft-model-knows-when-to-stop-a-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeneQuery: A General QA-based Framework for Spatial Gene Expression Predictions from Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gene expression profiling provides profound insights into molecular mechanisms, but its time-consuming and costly nature often presents significant challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genequery-a-general-qa-based-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaVLN: Towards Visual Language Navigation in Continuous Indoor Environments with Moving Humans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Language Navigation is a task that challenges robots to navigate in realistic environments based on natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adavln-towards-visual-language-navigation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Open Vocabulary to Open World: Teaching Vision Language Models to Detect Novel Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address theses limitations, we propose a framework that enables OVD models to operate in open world settings, by identifying and incrementally learning novel objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-open-vocabulary-to-open-world-teaching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Evaluating Language Models with Template-based Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce Template-based Data Generation (TDG), a novel approach that leverages LLMs (GPT-4) to automatically generate parameterized meta-templates, which are then used to synthesize a vast array of high-quality problems and solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-evaluating-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isometry pursuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Isometry pursuit is a convex algorithm for identifying orthonormal column-submatrices of wide matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isometry-pursuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLS: Geometry-aware 3D Language Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has achieved significant performance on indoor surface reconstruction and open-vocabulary segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gls-geometry-aware-3d-language-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fourier-embedded Network for Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of deep learning provides a significant improvement of salient object detection combining both RGB and thermal images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fourier-embedded-network-for-bi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatRex: Taming Multimodal LLM for Joint Perception and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the data perspective, we build a fully automated data engine and construct the Rexverse-2M dataset which possesses multiple granularities to support the joint training of perception and understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITA: Automatic Framework for Designing of Resilient IoT Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing resilient Internet of Things (IoT) systems requires i) identification of IoT Critical Objects (ICOs) such as services, devices, and resources, ii) threat analysis, and iii) mitigation strategy selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rita-automatic-framework-for-designing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba Distillation for Low-resolution Fine-grained Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-resolution fine-grained image classification has recently made significant progress, largely thanks to the super-resolution techniques and knowledge distillation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-distillation-for-low-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLM Knows When to Speak: Enhancing Time-Sensitive Video Comprehension with Video-Text Duet Interaction Format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct MMDuetIT, a video-text training dataset designed to adapt VideoLLMs to video-text duet interaction format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-knows-when-to-speak-enhancing-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Surface Priors for Editable Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike other methods, our pipeline allows modifications applied to the extracted mesh to be propagated to the proxy representation, from which we recover the updated parameters of the Gaussians.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-surface-priors-for-editable-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Neural Networks Do Work with Pre-Defined Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel class of Convolutional Neural Networks called Pre-defined Filter Convolutional Neural Networks (PFCNNs), where all nxn convolution kernels with n>1 are pre-defined and constant during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-neural-networks-do-work-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral-Spatial Transformer with Active Transfer Learning for Hyperspectral Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel multi-stage active transfer learning (ATL) framework that integrates a Spatial-Spectral Transformer (SST) with an active learning process for efficient HSI classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-spatial-transformer-with-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SatVision-TOA: A Geospatial Foundation Model for Coarse-Resolution All-Sky Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satvision-toa-a-geospatial-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work advances pre-trained vision modeling for multispectral RS by learning from a variety of atmospheric and aerosol conditions to improve cloud and land surface monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satvision-toa-a-geospatial-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoA: Chain-of-Action for Generative Semantic Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coa-chain-of-action-for-generative-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These VLMs leverage a predefined set of categories to construct text prompts for zero-shot reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coa-chain-of-action-for-generative-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTS-UNMixers: Multivariate Time Series Forecasting via Channel-Time Dual Unmixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mts-unmixers-multivariate-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, MTS-UNMixers represent sequences over time as a mixture of multiple trends and cycles, with the time-correlated representation coefficients shared across both historical and future time periods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mts-unmixers-multivariate-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRiVE: Diffusion-based Rigging Empowers Generation of Versatile and Expressive Characters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drive-diffusion-based-rigging-empowers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in generative models have enabled high-quality 3D character reconstruction from multi-modal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drive-diffusion-based-rigging-empowers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs be Good Graph Judger for Knowledge Graph Construction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-be-good-graph-judger-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We seek to utilize the capacity of LLMs to function as a graph judger, a capability superior to their role only as a predictor for KG construction problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-be-good-graph-judger-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Word Pair-based Gaussian Sentence Similarity Algorithm For Bengali Extractive Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-word-pair-based-gaussian-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a novel Word pair-based Gaussian Sentence Similarity (WGSS) algorithm for calculating the semantic relation between two sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-word-pair-based-gaussian-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>g3D-LF: Generalizable 3D-Language Feature Fields for Embodied Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g3d-lf-generalizable-3d-language-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we prepare a large-scale 3D-language dataset to align the representations of the feature fields with language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g3d-lf-generalizable-3d-language-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Monotonic Attention in Transducer for Streaming Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-monotonic-attention-in-transducer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Streaming generation models are increasingly utilized across various fields, with the Transducer architecture being particularly popular in industrial applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-monotonic-attention-in-transducer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Bayesian Optimization via Localized Online Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-bayesian-optimization-via-localized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian optimization (BO) is a sequential approach for optimizing black-box objective functions using zeroth-order noisy observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-bayesian-optimization-via-localized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Words Matter: Leveraging Individual Text Embeddings for Code Generation in CLIP Test-Time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/words-matter-leveraging-individual-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language foundation models, such as CLIP, have shown unprecedented zero-shot performance across a wide range of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/words-matter-leveraging-individual-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-based Spiking Neural Networks for Object Detection: A Review of Datasets, Architectures, Learning Rules, and Implementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-spiking-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spiking Neural Networks (SNNs) represent a biologically inspired paradigm offering an energy-efficient alternative to conventional artificial neural networks (ANNs) for Computer Vision (CV) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-spiking-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Deployment of Transformer Models in Analog In-Memory Computing Hardware</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deployment-of-transformer-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, it supports on-chip adaptation to new hardware constraints and tasks without updating analog weights, providing a flexible and versatile solution for real-world AI applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-deployment-of-transformer-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Imbalance Learning: A Novel Slack-Factor Fuzzy SVM Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-imbalance-learning-a-novel-slack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world applications, class-imbalanced datasets pose significant challenges for machine learning algorithms, such as support vector machines (SVMs), particularly in effectively managing imbalance, noise, and outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-imbalance-learning-a-novel-slack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Explainable Treatment Policies with Clinician-Informed Representations: A Practical Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-explainable-treatment-policies-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our main contribution is to reveal the importance of clinical domain knowledge in developing state and action representations for effective, efficient, and interpretable targeting policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-explainable-treatment-policies-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation-Aware Graph Convolutional Networks for Multi-Label Node Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-label node classification is an important yet under-explored domain in graph mining as many real-world nodes belong to multiple categories rather than just a single one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Different Bias Under Different Criteria: Assessing Bias in LLMs with a Fact-Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-bias-under-different-criteria</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) often reflect real-world biases, leading to efforts to mitigate these effects and make the models unbiased.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-bias-under-different-criteria</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Networks Use Distance Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-use-distance-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present empirical evidence that neural networks with ReLU and Absolute Value activations learn distance-based representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-networks-use-distance-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Noisy Labels via Conditional Distributionally Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-labels-via-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to devise an efficient algorithm for CDRO, we derive a closed-form expression for the empirical robust risk and the optimal Lagrange multiplier of the dual problem, facilitating a principled balance between robustness and model fitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-noisy-labels-via-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training a neural netwok for data reduction and better generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-neural-netwok-for-data-reduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The motivation for sparse learners is to compress the inputs (features) by selecting only the ones needed for good generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-a-neural-netwok-for-data-reduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableAnimator: High-Quality Identity-Preserving Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, we propose a novel Hamilton-Jacobi-Bellman (HJB) equation-based optimization to further enhance the face quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isotropy Matters: Soft-ZCA Whitening of Embeddings for Semantic Code Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isotropy-matters-soft-zca-whitening-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low isotropy in an embedding space impairs performance on tasks involving semantic inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isotropy-matters-soft-zca-whitening-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Hamiltonian neural networks without backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-hamiltonian-neural-networks-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks that synergistically integrate data and physical laws offer great promise in modeling dynamical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-hamiltonian-neural-networks-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling nnU-Net for CBCT Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-nnu-net-for-cbct-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our approach to scaling the nnU-Net framework for multi-structure segmentation on Cone Beam Computed Tomography (CBCT) images, specifically in the scope of the ToothFairy2 Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-nnu-net-for-cbct-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Decoding Makes Visual Auto-Regressive Modeling Efficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decoding-makes-visual-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large model serves as the 'drafter', specializing in generating low-frequency content at smaller scales, while the smaller model serves as the 'refiner', solely focusing on predicting high-frequency details at larger scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decoding-makes-visual-auto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Efficiency of NLP-Inspired Methods for Tabular Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficiency-of-nlp-inspired-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in tabular deep learning (DL) have led to substantial performance improvements, surpassing the capabilities of traditional models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficiency-of-nlp-inspired-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$H^3$Fusion: Helpful, Harmless, Honest Fusion of Aligned LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-3-fusion-helpful-harmless-honest-fusion-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The former penalizes the selection errors of the expert-router, and the latter mediates the expert weights drifting during fine-tuning and dynamically adjusts the fusion behavior of the resulting model by canalizing the activations on the experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-3-fusion-helpful-harmless-honest-fusion-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding-IQA: Multimodal Language Grounding Model for Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-iqa-multimodal-language-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments demonstrate that our proposed task paradigm, dataset, and benchmark facilitate the more fine-grained IQA application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-iqa-multimodal-language-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSDFace: One-Step Diffusion Model for Face Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osdface-one-step-diffusion-model-for-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, existing methods often struggle to generate face images that are harmonious, realistic, and consistent with the subject's identity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osdface-one-step-diffusion-model-for-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-MeshGraphNet: Scalable Multi-Scale Graph Neural Networks for Physics Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-meshgraphnet-scalable-multi-scale-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce X-MeshGraphNet, a scalable, multi-scale extension of MeshGraphNet designed to address these challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-meshgraphnet-scalable-multi-scale-graph</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
