<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 09:16:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DepMamba: Progressive Fusion Mamba for Multimodal Depression Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depmamba-progressive-fusion-mamba-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although promising, current multimodal methods hinge on aligned or aggregated multimodal fusion, suffering two significant limitations: (i) inefficient long-range temporal modeling, and (ii) sub-optimal multimodal fusion between intermodal fusion and intramodal processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depmamba-progressive-fusion-mamba-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoPatchCore: An Effective Method to Memorize Normality for Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopatchcore-an-effective-method-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by PatchCore, our approach introduces a structure that prioritizes memory optimization and configures three types of memory tailored to the characteristics of video data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopatchcore-an-effective-method-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ducho meets Elliot: Large-scale Benchmarks for Multimodal Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-meets-elliot-large-scale-benchmarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In specific domains like fashion, music, and movie recommendation, the multi-faceted features characterizing products and services may influence each customer on online selling platforms differently, paving the way to novel multimodal recommendation models that can learn from such multimodal content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-meets-elliot-large-scale-benchmarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aided design of bridge aesthetics based on Stable Diffusion fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aided-design-of-bridge-aesthetics-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stable Diffusion fine-tuning technique is tried to assist bridge-type innovation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aided-design-of-bridge-aesthetics-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataGpt-SQL-7B: An Open-Source Language Model for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datagpt-sql-7b-an-open-source-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addressing the pivotal role of translating natural language queries into SQL commands, we propose a suite of compact, fine-tuned models and self-refine mechanisms to democratize data access and analysis for non-expert users, mitigating risks associated with closed-source Large Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datagpt-sql-7b-an-open-source-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIM 2024 Challenge on Video Saliency Prediction: Methods and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aim-2024-challenge-on-video-saliency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of the participants was to develop a method for predicting accurate saliency maps for the provided set of video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aim-2024-challenge-on-video-saliency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastGL: A GPU-Efficient Framework for Accelerating Sampling-Based GNN Training at Large Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastgl-a-gpu-efficient-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, through an in-depth analysis, we observe that the efficiency of existing sampling-based training frameworks is still limited due to the key bottlenecks lying in all three phases of sampling-based training, i. e., subgraph sample, memory IO, and computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastgl-a-gpu-efficient-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Robot Dogs for Construction Monitoring: A Comparative Analysis of Specifications and On-site Requirements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-robot-dogs-for-construction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robot dogs are receiving increasing attention in various fields of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-robot-dogs-for-construction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Model Cross-Stream Learning for Self-Supervised Human Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-model-cross-stream-learning-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by SkeletonBYOL, this paper further presents a Cross-Model and Cross-Stream (CMCS) framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-model-cross-stream-learning-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FineCops-Ref: A new Dataset and Task for Fine-Grained Compositional Referring Expression Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finecops-ref-a-new-dataset-and-task-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referring Expression Comprehension (REC) is a crucial cross-modal task that objectively evaluates the capabilities of language understanding, image comprehension, and language-to-image grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finecops-ref-a-new-dataset-and-task-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMCBench: Benchmarking Large Language Models' Resistance to Malicious Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmcbench-benchmarking-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their benefits, LLMs also pose notable risks, including the potential to generate harmful content and being abused by malicious developers to create malicious code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmcbench-benchmarking-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Exploration and Semantic Updating of Large-Scale Indoor Environments with Mobile Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-exploration-and-semantic-updating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new robotic system that enables a mobile robot to autonomously explore an unknown environment, build a semantic map of the environment, and subsequently update the semantic map to reflect environment changes, such as location changes of objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-exploration-and-semantic-updating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICSim: A Modular Simulator for Mixed-signal Compute-in-Memory based AI Accelerator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micsim-a-modular-simulator-for-mixed-signal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work demonstrates that MICSim can easily be combined with optimization strategies to perform design space exploration and used for chip-level Transformers CIM accelerators evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micsim-a-modular-simulator-for-mixed-signal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polyatomic Complexes: A topologically-informed learning representation for atomistic systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyatomic-complexes-a-topologically-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We open-source all code and datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyatomic-complexes-a-topologically-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlEdit: A MultiModal Local Clothing Image Editing Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controledit-a-multimodal-local-clothing-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal clothing image editing refers to the precise adjustment and modification of clothing images using data such as textual descriptions and visual images as control conditions, which effectively improves the work efficiency of designers and reduces the threshold for user design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controledit-a-multimodal-local-clothing-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenging the Performance-Interpretability Trade-off: An Evaluation of Interpretable Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenging-the-performance-interpretability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To uncover the merits and limitations of these models, this study examines the predictive performance of seven different GAMs in comparison to seven commonly used machine learning models based on a collection of twenty tabular benchmark datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenging-the-performance-interpretability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic 2D Gaussians: Geometrically accurate radiance fields for dynamic objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-2d-gaussians-geometrically-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel representation that can reconstruct accurate meshes from sparse image input, named Dynamic 2D Gaussians (D-2DGS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-2d-gaussians-geometrically-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>R-AIF: Solving Sparse-Reward Robotic Tasks from Pixels with Active Inference and World Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-aif-solving-sparse-reward-robotic-tasks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although research has produced promising results demonstrating the utility of active inference (AIF) in Markov decision processes (MDPs), there is relatively less work that builds AIF models in the context of environments and problems that take the form of partially observable Markov decision processes (POMDPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/r-aif-solving-sparse-reward-robotic-tasks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVT-Occ: Cost Volume Temporal Fusion for 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvt-occ-cost-volume-temporal-fusion-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-based 3D occupancy prediction is significantly challenged by the inherent limitations of monocular vision in depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvt-occ-cost-volume-temporal-fusion-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longitudinal Segmentation of MS Lesions via Temporal Difference Weighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longitudinal-segmentation-of-ms-lesions-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate segmentation of Multiple Sclerosis (MS) lesions in longitudinal MRI scans is crucial for monitoring disease progression and treatment efficacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longitudinal-segmentation-of-ms-lesions-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorful Diffuse Intrinsic Image Decomposition in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colorful-diffuse-intrinsic-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intrinsic image decomposition aims to separate the surface reflectance and the effects from the illumination given a single photograph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colorful-diffuse-intrinsic-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-Centered First Order Structure Tensor Scale-Space in 2D and 3D</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-centered-first-order-structure-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The structure tensor method is often used for 2D and 3D analysis of imaged structures, but its results are in many cases very dependent on the user's choice of method parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-centered-first-order-structure-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An adapted large language model facilitates multiple medical tasks in diabetes care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adapted-large-language-model-facilitates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduced a framework to train and validate diabetes-specific LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adapted-large-language-model-facilitates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A preliminary study on continual learning in computer vision using Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-on-continual-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the investigation by evaluating the performance of KANs in continual learning tasks within computer vision, specifically using the MNIST datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-on-continual-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Consideration to the Perceptron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-consideration-to-the-perceptron</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the gated perceptron, an enhancement of the conventional perceptron, which incorporates an additional input computed as the product of the existing inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-consideration-to-the-perceptron</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling fluffy clouds: field boundaries detection using time series of S2 and/or S1 imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-fluffy-clouds-field-boundaries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both models are evaluated under sparse and dense cloud coverage by exploiting spatio-temporal correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-fluffy-clouds-field-boundaries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Language Models to Self-Correct via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-self-correct-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we observe that training via SFT either suffers from a distribution mismatch between the training data and the model's own responses or implicitly prefers only a certain mode of correction behavior that is often not effective at test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-self-correct-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JourneyBench: A Challenging One-Stop Vision-Language Understanding Benchmark of Generated Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/journeybench-a-challenging-one-stop-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we release JourneyBench, a comprehensive human-annotated benchmark of generated images designed to assess the model's fine-grained multimodal reasoning abilities across five tasks: complementary multimodal chain of thought, multi-image VQA, imaginary image captioning, VQA with hallucination triggers, and fine-grained retrieval with sample-specific distractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/journeybench-a-challenging-one-stop-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Traj2Text: Learning-by-Synthesis Framework for Contextual Captioning of Human Movement Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2traj2text-learning-by-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Text2Traj2Text, a novel learning-by-synthesis framework for captioning possible contexts behind shopper's trajectory data in retail stores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2traj2text-learning-by-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Automatic 3D Annotation of Traffic Lights and Signs for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-automatic-3d-annotation-of-traffic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D detection of traffic management objects, such as traffic lights and road signs, is vital for self-driving cars, particularly for address-to-address navigation where vehicles encounter numerous intersections with these static objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-automatic-3d-annotation-of-traffic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should RAG Chatbots Forget Unimportant Conversations? Exploring Importance and Forgetting with Psychological Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/should-rag-chatbots-forget-unimportant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) has shown promise in enhancing long-term conversations, the increasing memory load as conversations progress degrades retrieval accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/should-rag-chatbots-forget-unimportant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oryx MLLM: On-Demand Spatial-Temporal Understanding at Arbitrary Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oryx-mllm-on-demand-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual data comes in various forms, ranging from small icons of just a few pixels to long videos spanning hours.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oryx-mllm-on-demand-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gaussian Discriminant Variational Autoencoder (GdVAE): A Self-Explainable Model with Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gaussian-discriminant-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual counterfactual explanation (CF) methods modify image concepts, e. g, shape, to change a prediction to a predefined outcome while closely resembling the original query image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gaussian-discriminant-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistic Minimal Pairs Elicit Linguistic Similarity in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-minimal-pairs-elicit-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel analysis that leverages linguistic minimal pairs to probe the internal linguistic representations of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-minimal-pairs-elicit-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Performance Tracking: Leveraging Large Language Models for Automated Construction of Scientific Leaderboards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-performance-tracking-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this dataset, we propose three experimental settings that simulate real-world scenarios where TDM triples are fully defined, partially defined, or undefined during leaderboard construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-performance-tracking-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DTopia-XL: Scaling High-quality 3D Asset Generation via Primitive Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dtopia-xl-scaling-high-quality-3d-asset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing demand for high-quality 3D assets across various industries necessitates efficient and automated 3D content creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3dtopia-xl-scaling-high-quality-3d-asset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaRecon: MRI Reconstruction with Structured State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambarecon-mri-reconstruction-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) is one of the most important medical imaging modalities as it provides superior resolution of soft tissues, albeit with a notable limitation in scanning speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambarecon-mri-reconstruction-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Logical Reasoning in Large Language Models through Graph-based Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-logical-reasoning-in-large-language-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in training and prompting strategies for Large Language Models (LLMs), these models continue to face challenges with complex logical reasoning tasks that involve long reasoning chains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-logical-reasoning-in-large-language-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channel-Aware Domain-Adaptive Generative Adversarial Network for Robust Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-domain-adaptive-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this issue, we propose a novel channel-aware data simulation method for robust ASR training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-domain-adaptive-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight and Real-Time Binaural Speech Enhancement Model with Spatial Cues Preservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-and-real-time-binaural-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Binaural speech enhancement (BSE) aims to jointly improve the speech quality and intelligibility of noisy signals received by hearing devices and preserve the spatial cues of the target for natural listening.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-and-real-time-binaural-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Profiling Patient Transcript Using Large Language Model Reasoning Augmentation for Alzheimer's Disease Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/profiling-patient-transcript-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's disease (AD) stands as the predominant cause of dementia, characterized by a gradual decline in speech and language capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/profiling-patient-transcript-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infrared Small Target Detection in Satellite Videos: A New Dataset and A Novel Recurrent Feature Refinement Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infrared-small-target-detection-in-satellite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the aforementioned challenges, in this paper, we first build a large-scale dataset for MIRST detection in satellite videos (namely IRSatVideo-LEO), and then develop a recurrent feature refinement (RFR) framework as the baseline method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infrared-small-target-detection-in-satellite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CritiPrefill: A Segment-wise Criticality-based Approach for Prefilling Acceleration in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critiprefill-a-segment-wise-criticality-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe a locality in query criticality during the prefilling phase of long-context processing: adjacent query tokens tend to focus on similar subsets of the past Key-Value (KV) cache.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critiprefill-a-segment-wise-criticality-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pyrtklib: An open-source package for tightly coupled deep learning and GNSS integration for positioning in urban canyons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyrtklib-an-open-source-package-for-tightly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is revolutionizing numerous fields, with increasing applications in Global Navigation Satellite Systems (GNSS) positioning algorithms in intelligent transportation systems (ITS) via deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyrtklib-an-open-source-package-for-tightly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaClinix: Hierarchical Gated Convolution and Mamba-Based U-Net for Enhanced 3D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaclinix-hierarchical-gated-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning, particularly convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and Transformers, has significantly advanced 3D medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambaclinix-hierarchical-gated-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompting Segment Anything Model with Domain-Adaptive Prototype for Generalizable Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-segment-anything-model-with-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Domain-Adaptive Prompt framework for fine-tuning the Segment Anything Model (termed as DAPSAM) to address single-source domain generalization (SDG) in segmenting medical images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompting-segment-anything-model-with-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Measure: Generating Valid, Consistent, and Reproducible Text-Based Measures for Social Science Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-measure-generating-valid-consistent-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing use of text as data in social science research necessitates the development of valid, consistent, reproducible, and efficient methods for generating text-based concept measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-measure-generating-valid-consistent-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurgPLAN++: Universal Surgical Phase Localization Network for Online and Offline Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgplan-universal-surgical-phase</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure a global understanding of the surgical procedure, we devise a phase localization strategy for SurgPLAN++ to predict phase segments across the entire video through phase proposals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgplan-universal-surgical-phase</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundus image enhancement through direct diffusion bridges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fundus-image-enhancement-through-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose FD3, a fundus image enhancement method based on direct diffusion bridges, which can cope with a wide range of complex degradations, including haze, blur, noise, and shadow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fundus-image-enhancement-through-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Knowledge Distillation of Large Language Models through Efficient Multi-Modal Distribution Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-knowledge-distillation-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation (KD) is an effective model compression method that can transfer the internal capabilities of large language models (LLMs) to smaller ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-knowledge-distillation-of-large</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
