<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 21:07:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Is Synthetic Voice Detection Research Going Into the Right Direction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-synthetic-voice-detection-research-going</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indeed, this evolution enabled the construction of effective frameworks and solutions able to be used in investigative and forensics scenarios for detection of fakes and, in general, manipulations in multimedia contents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-synthetic-voice-detection-research-going</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Finite Width Neural Tangent Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-finite-width-neural-tangent-kernel-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform the first in-depth analysis of the compute and memory requirements for NTK computation in finite width networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-finite-width-neural-tangent-kernel-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEAR: A Fully User-side Image Search System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clear-a-fully-user-side-image-search-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this framework, each user builds their own search system that meets their preference with a user-defined scoring function and user-defined interface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clear-a-fully-user-side-image-search-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language with Vision: a Study on Grounded Word and Sentence Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-with-vision-a-study-on-grounded-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By applying a learned alignment, we are able to generate visually grounded embeddings for unseen words, including abstract words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-with-vision-a-study-on-grounded-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Fair Representation via Distributional Contrastive Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fair-representation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a new type of contrastive loss motivated by Gaussian and Student-t kernels for distributional contrastive learning with theoretical analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fair-representation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Shapley Explanation via Contributive Cooperator Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-shapley-explanation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though Shapley value provides an effective explanation for a DNN model prediction, the computation relies on the enumeration of all possible input feature coalitions, which leads to the exponentially growing complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-shapley-explanation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOS: Score-based Oversampling for Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sos-score-based-oversampling-for-tabular-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, we are the first presenting a score-based tabular data oversampling method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sos-score-based-oversampling-for-tabular-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CookDial: A dataset for task-oriented dialogs grounded in procedural documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cookdial-a-dataset-for-task-oriented-dialogs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a new dialog dataset, CookDial, that facilitates research on task-oriented dialog systems with procedural knowledge understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cookdial-a-dataset-for-task-oriented-dialogs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Robust Overfitting of Adversarial Training and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-robust-overfitting-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we explore the causes of robust overfitting by comparing the data distribution of \emph{non-overfit} (weak adversary) and \emph{overfitted} (strong adversary) adversarial training, and observe that the distribution of the adversarial data generated by weak adversary mainly contain small-loss data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-robust-overfitting-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Derive Once (YODO): Automatic Differentiation for Efficient Sensitivity Analysis in Bayesian Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-derive-once-yodo-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sensitivity analysis measures the influence of a Bayesian network's parameters on a quantity of interest defined by the network, such as the probability of a variable taking a specific value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-derive-once-yodo-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>niksss at HinglishEval: Language-agnostic BERT-based Contextual Embeddings with Catboost for Quality Evaluation of the Low-Resource Synthetically Generated Code-Mixed Hinglish Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niksss-at-hinglisheval-language-agnostic-bert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the system description for the HinglishEval challenge at INLG 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/niksss-at-hinglisheval-language-agnostic-bert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Aesthetics with Language: A Photo Critique Dataset for Aesthetic Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-aesthetics-with-language-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this regard, we propose the Reddit Photo Critique Dataset (RPCD), which contains tuples of image and photo critiques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-aesthetics-with-language-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OADAT: Experimental and Synthetic Clinical Optoacoustic Data for Standardized Image Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oadat-experimental-and-synthetic-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, no standardized datasets generated with different types of experimental set-up and associated processing methods are available to facilitate advances in broader applications of OA in clinical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oadat-experimental-and-synthetic-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Human-Level Bimanual Dexterous Manipulation with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-level-bimanual-dexterous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose the Bimanual Dexterous Hands Benchmark (Bi-DexHands), a simulator that involves two dexterous hands with tens of bimanual manipulation tasks and thousands of target objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-level-bimanual-dexterous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Differentially Private Clustering via Hierarchically Separated Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-differentially-private-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the private $k$-median and $k$-means clustering problem in $d$ dimensional Euclidean space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-differentially-private-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMPL: Simulated Industrial Manufacturing and Process Control Learning Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpl-simulated-industrial-manufacturing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional biological and pharmaceutical manufacturing plants are controlled by human workers or pre-defined thresholds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smpl-simulated-industrial-manufacturing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reframed GES with a Neural Conditional Dependence Measure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reframed-ges-with-a-neural-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit the Greedy Equivalence Search (GES) algorithm, which is widely cited as a score-based algorithm for learning the MEC of the underlying causal structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reframed-ges-with-a-neural-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Graph-Enhanced Click Model for Web Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-enhanced-click-model-for-web-search-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better exploit search logs and model users' behavior patterns, numerous click models are proposed to extract users' implicit interaction feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-enhanced-click-model-for-web-search-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Correction of Human Translations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-correction-of-human-translations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that human errors in TEC exhibit a more diverse range of errors and far fewer translation fluency errors than the MT errors in automatic post-editing datasets, suggesting the need for dedicated TEC models that are specialized to correct human errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-correction-of-human-translations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RECAPP: Crafting a More Efficient Catalyst for Convex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recapp-crafting-a-more-efficient-catalyst-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accelerated proximal point algorithm (APPA), also known as "Catalyst", is a well-established reduction from convex optimization to approximate proximal point computation (i. e., regularized minimization).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recapp-crafting-a-more-efficient-catalyst-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoML Two-Sample Test</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automl-two-sample-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two-sample tests are important in statistics and machine learning, both as tools for scientific discovery as well as to detect distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automl-two-sample-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized adaptive clustering of deep nets is beneficial for client collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-adaptive-clustering-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of training personalized deep learning models in a decentralized peer-to-peer setting, focusing on the setting where data distributions differ between the clients and where different clients have different local learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-adaptive-clustering-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge-Tower: Building Bridges Between Encoders in Vision-Language Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridge-tower-building-bridges-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current VL models either use lightweight uni-modal encoders and learn to extract, align and fuse both modalities simultaneously in a cross-modal encoder, or feed the last-layer uni-modal features directly into the top cross-modal encoder, ignoring the semantic information at the different levels in the deep uni-modal encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridge-tower-building-bridges-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MineDojo: Building Open-Ended Embodied Agents with Internet-Scale Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minedojo-building-open-ended-embodied-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous agents have made great strides in specialist domains like Atari games and Go.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minedojo-building-open-ended-embodied-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedNew: A Communication-Efficient and Privacy-Preserving Newton-Type Method for Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednew-a-communication-efficient-and-privacy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Newton-type methods are popular in federated learning due to their fast convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fednew-a-communication-efficient-and-privacy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComENet: Towards Complete and Efficient Message Passing for 3D Molecular Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comenet-towards-complete-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To incorporate 3D information completely and efficiently, we propose a novel message passing scheme that operates within 1-hop neighborhood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comenet-towards-complete-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thompson Sampling for Robust Transfer in Multi-Task Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thompson-sampling-for-robust-transfer-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of online multi-task learning where the tasks are performed within similar but not necessarily identical multi-armed bandit environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thompson-sampling-for-robust-transfer-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating numerical methods by gradient-based meta-solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-numerical-methods-by-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In science and engineering applications, it is often required to solve similar computational problems repeatedly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-numerical-methods-by-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random projections and Kernelised Leave One Cluster Out Cross-Validation: Universal baselines and evaluation tools for supervised machine learning for materials properties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-projections-and-kernelised-leave-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find that the radial basis function improves the linear separability of chemical datasets in all 10 datasets tested and provide a framework for the application of this function in the LOCO-CV process to improve the outcome of LOCO-CV measurements regardless of machine learning algorithm, choice of metric, and choice of compound representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/random-projections-and-kernelised-leave-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plotly-Resampler: Effective Visual Analytics for Large Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plotly-resampler-effective-visual-analytics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that open source Python visualization toolkits empower data scientists in most visual analytics tasks, but lack the combination of scalability and interactivity to realize effective time series visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plotly-resampler-effective-visual-analytics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Adversarial Examples in Batches -- a geometrical approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-adversarial-examples-in-batches-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many deep learning methods have successfully solved complex tasks in computer vision and speech recognition applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-adversarial-examples-in-batches-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafeRL-Kit: Evaluating Efficient Reinforcement Learning Methods for Safe Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saferl-kit-evaluating-efficient-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safe reinforcement learning (RL) has achieved significant success on risk-sensitive tasks and shown promise in autonomous driving (AD) as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saferl-kit-evaluating-efficient-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Shadow Detection via Spatio-Temporal Interpolation Consistency Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-shadow-detection-via-spatio-temporal-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed approach is extensively validated on the ViSha dataset and a self-annotated dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-shadow-detection-via-spatio-temporal-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FD-CAM: Improving Faithfulness and Discriminability of Visual Explanation for CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fd-cam-improving-faithfulness-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel CAM weighting scheme, named FD-CAM, to improve both the faithfulness and discriminability of the CAM-based CNN visual explanation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fd-cam-improving-faithfulness-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DGMIL: Distribution Guided Multiple Instance Learning for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgmil-distribution-guided-multiple-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple Instance Learning (MIL) is widely used in analyzing histopathological Whole Slide Images (WSIs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dgmil-distribution-guided-multiple-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Factorization Machines via Saliency-Guided Mixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-factorization-machines-via-saliency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, considering that MixFM may generate redundant or even detrimental instances, we further put forward a novel Factorization Machine powered by Saliency-guided Mixup (denoted as SMFM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-factorization-machines-via-saliency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do navigation agents learn about their environment?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-navigation-agents-learn-about-their-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use iSEE to probe the dynamic representations produced by these agents for the presence of information about the agent as well as the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-navigation-agents-learn-about-their-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimA: Simple Softmax-free Attention for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sima-simple-softmax-free-attention-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, vision transformers have become very popular.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sima-simple-softmax-free-attention-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Algorithm for the SE(3)-Transformation on Neural Implicit Maps for Remapping Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-algorithm-for-the-se-3-transformation-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As our neural implicit map is transformable, our model supports remapping for this special map of latent features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-algorithm-for-the-se-3-transformation-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Class Separation as Inductive Bias in One Matrix</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-class-separation-as-inductive-bias-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a simple alternative: encoding maximum separation as an inductive bias in the network by adding one fixed matrix multiplication before computing the softmax activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-class-separation-as-inductive-bias-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDNet: Contrastive Disentangled Network for Fine-Grained Image Categorization of Ocular B-Scan Ultrasound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdnet-contrastive-disentangled-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Precise and rapid categorization of images in the B-scan ultrasound modality is vital for diagnosing ocular diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdnet-contrastive-disentangled-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders for Generic Event Boundary Detection CVPR'2022 Kinetics-GEBD Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-for-generic-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we apply Masked Autoencoders to improve algorithm performance on the GEBD tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-for-generic-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Lossless Neural Compression with Integer-Only Discrete Flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-lossless-neural-compression-with-integer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Integer-only Discrete Flows (IODF), an efficient neural compressor with integer-only arithmetic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-lossless-neural-compression-with-integer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Evaluation of Textual Backdoor Learning: Frameworks and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-evaluation-of-textual-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we highlight two issues in previous backdoor learning evaluations: (1) The differences between real-world scenarios (e. g. releasing poisoned datasets or models) are neglected, and we argue that each scenario has its own constraints and concerns, thus requires specific evaluation protocols; (2) The evaluation metrics only consider whether the attacks could flip the models' predictions on poisoned samples and retain performances on benign samples, but ignore that poisoned samples should also be stealthy and semantic-preserving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-evaluation-of-textual-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Implicit Feature Alignment Function for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-implicit-feature-alignment-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, IFA implicitly aligns the feature maps at different levels and is capable of producing segmentation maps in arbitrary resolutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-implicit-feature-alignment-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Sampling: Exploring Out-of-Distribution data for Re-balancing Long-tailed datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-sampling-exploring-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks usually perform poorly when the training dataset suffers from extreme class imbalance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-sampling-exploring-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Imputation and Cross-Attention Network Based on Incomplete Longitudinal and Multi-Modal Data for Alzheimer's Disease Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-imputation-and-cross-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, a multi-view imputation method combined with adversarial learning, which can handle a wide range of missing data situations and reduce imputation errors, was presented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-imputation-and-cross-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to talk so your robot will learn: Instructions, descriptions, and pragmatics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-talk-so-your-robot-will-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that social learning from a wider range of language -- in particular, expanding the field's present focus on instructions to include learning from descriptions -- is a promising approach for value alignment and reinforcement learning more broadly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-talk-so-your-robot-will-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Dialogue State Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dialogue-state-tracking-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a novel dialogue state tracking task to track the information of visual objects that are mentioned in video-grounded dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-dialogue-state-tracking-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Privacy Protection on Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-privacy-protection-on-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results show that generated adversarial examples can erase most content information in original examples or replace it with target speech content through speech enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-privacy-protection-on-speech</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
