<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 09:26:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Parametric Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-parametric-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on theoretical analysis, we observe that supervised contrastive loss tends to bias high-frequency classes and thus increases the difficulty of imbalanced learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-parametric-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Learn with Generative Models of Neural Network Checkpoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-learn-with-generative-models-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore a data-driven approach for learning to optimize neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-learn-with-generative-models-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal Case Document Similarity: You Need Both Network and Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-case-document-similarity-you-need-both</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments establish that our proposed network-based methods significantly improve the correlation with domain experts' opinion when compared to the existing methods for network-based legal document similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legal-case-document-similarity-you-need-both</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Attention GAN for Vehicle Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-attention-gan-for-vehicle-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The design of a safe and reliable Autonomous Driving stack (ADS) is one of the most challenging tasks of our era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-attention-gan-for-vehicle-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dataset Training of Transformers for Robust Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dataset-training-of-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the task of robust feature representations, aiming to generalize well on multiple datasets for action recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dataset-training-of-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FORESEE: Model-based Reinforcement Learning using Unscented Transform with application to Tuning of Control Barrier Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foresee-model-based-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, depending on the number of sigma points employed, can propagate either mean and covariance with minimal points, or higher-order moments with more points similarly to Monte Carlo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foresee-model-based-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where2comm: Communication-Efficient Collaborative Perception via Spatial Confidence Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where2comm-communication-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Where2comm has two distinct advantages: i) it considers pragmatic compression and uses less communication to achieve higher perception performance by focusing on perceptually critical areas; and ii) it can handle varying communication bandwidth by dynamically adjusting spatial areas involved in communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where2comm-communication-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Content-Emotion Duality via Disentanglement for Empathetic Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-content-emotion-duality-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve the task, it is essential to model the content-emotion duality of a dialogue, which is composed of the content view (i. e., what personal experiences are described) and the emotion view (i. e., the feelings of the speaker on these experiences).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-content-emotion-duality-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Device-friendly Guava fruit and leaf disease detection using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-friendly-guava-fruit-and-leaf-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a deep learning-based plant disease diagnostic system using images of fruits and leaves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/device-friendly-guava-fruit-and-leaf-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Motion Deblurring Training: A Segmentation-Based Method for Simulating Non-Uniform Motion Blurred Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-motion-deblurring-training-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful training of end-to-end deep networks for real motion deblurring requires datasets of sharp/blurred image pairs that are realistic and diverse enough to achieve generalization to real blurred images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-motion-deblurring-training-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Explainable Machine Learning Approach to Visual-Interactive Labeling: A Case Study on Non-communicable Disease Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-machine-learning-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that EBM is an excellent choice of predictive model by comparing it against a rule-based and four other machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-explainable-machine-learning-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Summarization with Oracle Expectation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-summarization-with-oracle-expectation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extractive summarization produces summaries by identifying and concatenating the most important sentences in a document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-summarization-with-oracle-expectation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Resolution in the Context of Efficient Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-resolution-in-the-context-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key finding is that the major cause of degradation is not information loss in the down-sampling process, but rather the mismatch between network architecture and input scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-resolution-in-the-context-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-stage image denoising with the wavelet transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-image-denoising-with-the-wavelet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep convolutional neural networks (CNNs) are used for image denoising via automatically mining accurate structure information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stage-image-denoising-with-the-wavelet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAD: A Large-Scale Benchmark for Traffic Accidents Detection from Video Surveillance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tad-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After integration and annotation by various dimensions, a large-scale traffic accidents dataset named TAD is proposed in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tad-a-large-scale-benchmark-for-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Detection with Hilbert-Schmidt Independence Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-hilbert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing works attempt to solve the problem by explicitly imposing uncertainty on classifiers when OOD inputs are exposed to the classifier during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-hilbert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-RawVSR: Real-World Raw Video Super-Resolution with a Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-rawvsr-real-world-raw-video-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our code and dataset are available at https://github. com/zmzhang1998/Real-RawVSR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-rawvsr-real-world-raw-video-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Projections to Linear Subspaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-projections-to-linear-subspaces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The merit of projecting data onto linear subspaces is well known from, e. g., dimension reduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-projections-to-linear-subspaces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Truly Understand Prompts? A Case Study with Negated Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-truly-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work has shown that there exists a scaling law between the size of Language Models (LMs) and their zero-shot performance on different downstream NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-truly-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAPA: Similarity-Aware Point Affiliation for Feature Upsampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sapa-similarity-aware-point-affiliation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce point affiliation into feature upsampling, a notion that describes the affiliation of each upsampled point to a semantic cluster formed by local decoder feature points with semantic similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sapa-similarity-aware-point-affiliation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Material Prediction for Design Automation Using Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-prediction-for-design-automation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful material selection is critical in designing and manufacturing products for design automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/material-prediction-for-design-automation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heterogeneous group CNN for image super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-heterogeneous-group-cnn-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To prevent loss of original information, a multi-level enhancement mechanism guides a CNN to achieve a symmetric architecture for promoting expressive ability of HGSRCNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-heterogeneous-group-cnn-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyRec: An easy-to-use, extendable and efficient framework for building industrial recommendation systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-an-easy-to-use-extendable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present EasyRec, an easy-to-use, extendable and efficient recommendation framework for building industrial recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyrec-an-easy-to-use-extendable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural State-Space Modeling with Latent Causal-Effect Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-modeling-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a novel neural formulation of state-space models (SSMs), we first introduce causal-effect modeling of the latent dynamics via a system of interacting neural ODEs that separately describes 1) the continuous-time dynamics of the internal intervention, and 2) its effect on the trajectory of the system's native state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-state-space-modeling-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAESim: A probabilistic approach for self-supervised prototype discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vaesim-a-probabilistic-approach-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we reconstruct the sample based on a similarity measure between the sample embedding and the prototypical vectors of the clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vaesim-a-probabilistic-approach-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of Deep Learning in Generating Structured Radiology Reports: A Transformer-Based Technique</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-deep-learning-in-generating-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our transformer-based model in this study outperformed previously applied approaches such as ANN and CNN models based on ROUGE-1, ROUGE-2, ROUGE-L, and BLEU scores of 0. 816, 0. 668, 0. 528, and 0. 743, respectively, while providing an interpretable structured report.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-deep-learning-in-generating-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Example Influence in Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-example-influence-in-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual Learning (CL) sequentially learns new tasks like human beings, with the goal to achieve better Stability (S, remembering past tasks) and Plasticity (P, adapting to new tasks).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-example-influence-in-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport-based Identity Matching for Identity-invariant Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-based-identity-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to find pairs of similar expressions from different identities, we define the inter-feature similarity as a transportation cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-based-identity-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Exponentially Modified Gaussian Oscillators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-exponentially-modified-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Acoustic modeling serves de-noising, data reconstruction, model-based testing and classification in audio processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-exponentially-modified-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dive into Self-Supervised Learning for Medical Image Analysis: Data, Models and Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-self-supervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) has achieved remarkable performance on various medical imaging tasks by dint of priors from massive unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-self-supervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Segment Assemblage Network for Ad Video Editing with Importance-Coherence Reward</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-segment-assemblage-network-for-ad</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing method performs well at video segmentation stages but suffers from the problems of dependencies on extra cumbersome models and poor performance at the segment assemblage stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-segment-assemblage-network-for-ad</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D$^{\bf{3}}$: Duplicate Detection Decontaminator for Multi-Athlete Tracking in Sports Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-bf-3-duplicate-detection-decontaminator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, the duplicate detection is newly and precisely defined as occlusion misreporting on the same athlete by multiple detection boxes in one frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-bf-3-duplicate-detection-decontaminator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-monotonic Resource Utilization in the Bandits with Knapsacks Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-monotonic-resource-utilization-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bandits with knapsacks (BwK) is an influential model of sequential decision-making under uncertainty that incorporates resource consumption constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-monotonic-resource-utilization-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Semantic Descriptors for Zero-Shot Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-semantic-descriptors-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces a new ZSAR method based on the relationships of actions-objects and actions-descriptive sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-semantic-descriptors-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Super-Resolution Using Stochastic Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-super-resolution-using-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first time SDEs have been used for such an application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-super-resolution-using-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing a Knowledge Graph Framework for Pharmacokinetic Natural Product-Drug Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-a-knowledge-graph-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NP-KG is a heterogeneous KG with biomedical ontologies, linked data, and full texts of the scientific literature, constructed with the Phenotype Knowledge Translator framework and the semantic relation extraction systems, SemRep and Integrated Network and Dynamic Reasoning Assembler.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-a-knowledge-graph-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dead or Murdered? Predicting Responsibility Perception in Femicide News Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dead-or-murdered-predicting-responsibility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then train regression models that predict the salience of GBV participants with respect to different dimensions of perceived responsibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dead-or-murdered-predicting-responsibility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composite Layers for Deep Anomaly Detection on 3D Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-layers-for-deep-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, our CompositeNets substantially outperform existing solutions for anomaly detection on point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-layers-for-deep-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Hashing with Semantic Concept Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hashing-with-semantic-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, to improve the unsupervised image retrieval performance, plenty of unsupervised hashing methods have been proposed by designing a semantic similarity matrix, which is based on the similarities between image features extracted by a pre-trained CNN model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hashing-with-semantic-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Efficient Reinforcement Learning for Full-length Game of StarCraft II</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate a set of RL techniques for the full-length game of StarCraft II.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Two-Stage Training Scheme for Deep Video Fight Detection Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-two-stage-training-scheme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a simple but effective method that solves the task from a new perspective: we design the fight detection model as a composition of an action-aware feature extractor and an anomaly score generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-two-stage-training-scheme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Guided Deep Dynamic 3D Garments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-guided-deep-dynamic-3d-garments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Technically, we model garment dynamics, driven using the input character motion, by predicting per-frame local displacements in a canonical state of the garment that is enriched with frame-dependent skinning weights to bring the garment to the global space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-guided-deep-dynamic-3d-garments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLSO: Grammar-guided Latent Space Optimization for Sample-efficient Robot Design Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glso-grammar-guided-latent-space-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Grammar-guided Latent Space Optimization (GLSO), a framework that transforms design automation into a low-dimensional continuous optimization problem by training a graph variational autoencoder (VAE) to learn a mapping between the graph-structured design space and a continuous latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glso-grammar-guided-latent-space-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor-Based Multi-Modality Feature Selection and Regression for Alzheimer's Disease Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-multi-modality-feature-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The assessment of Alzheimer's Disease (AD) and Mild Cognitive Impairment (MCI) associated with brain changes remains a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-multi-modality-feature-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I-SPLIT: Deep Network Interpretability for Split Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-split-deep-network-interpretability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A neuron is important if its gradient with respect to the correct class decision is high.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-split-deep-network-interpretability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Model for Regular Grammar Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-model-for-regular-grammar-induction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grammatical inference is a classical problem in computational learning theory and a topic of wider influence in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-model-for-regular-grammar-induction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate and Efficient Stereo Matching via Attention Concatenation Volume</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-efficient-stereo-matching-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel cost volume construction method, named attention concatenation volume (ACV), which generates attention weights from correlation clues to suppress redundant information and enhance matching-related information in the concatenation volume.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-efficient-stereo-matching-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantile-constrained Wasserstein projections for robust interpretability of numerical and machine learning models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-constrained-wasserstein-projections</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical experiments on real case studies, from the UQ and ML fields, highlight the computational feasibility of such studies and provide local and global insights on the robustness of black-box models to input perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-constrained-wasserstein-projections</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ET5: A Novel End-to-end Framework for Conversational Machine Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/et5-a-novel-end-to-end-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational machine reading comprehension (CMRC) aims to assist computers to understand an natural language text and thereafter engage in a multi-turn conversation to answer questions related to the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/et5-a-novel-end-to-end-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Frame Rate Agnostic Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-frame-rate-agnostic-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Frame Rate Agnostic MOT framework with Periodic training Scheme (FAPS) to tackle the FraMOT problem for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-frame-rate-agnostic-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
