<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 09:14:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SciTweets -- A Dataset and Annotation Framework for Detecting Scientific Online Discourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scitweets-a-dataset-and-annotation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific topics, claims and resources are increasingly debated as part of online discourse, where prominent examples include discourse related to COVID-19 or climate change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scitweets-a-dataset-and-annotation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning of Image Scale and Orientation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-image-scale-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of learning to assign a characteristic pose, i. e., scale and orientation, for an image region of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-image-scale-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Bitrate Neural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-bitrate-neural-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural approximations of scalar and vector fields, such as signed distance functions and radiance fields, have emerged as accurate, high-quality representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-bitrate-neural-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Emotion Strength Assessment for Seen and Unseen Speech Based on Data-Driven Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-emotion-strength-assessment-for-seen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a data-driven deep learning model, i. e. StrengthNet, to improve the generalization of emotion strength assessment for seen and unseen speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-emotion-strength-assessment-for-seen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XMorpher: Full Transformer for Deformable Medical Image Registration via Cross Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmorpher-full-transformer-for-deformable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effective backbone network is important to deep learning-based Deformable Medical Image Registration (DMIR), because it extracts and matches the features between two images to discover the mutual correspondence for fine registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xmorpher-full-transformer-for-deformable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Eyes Inspired Recurrent Neural Networks are More Robust Against Adversarial Noises</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-eyes-inspired-recurrent-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to human vision, computer vision based on convolutional neural networks (CNN) are more vulnerable to adversarial noises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-eyes-inspired-recurrent-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-to-Fine Vision-Language Pre-training with Fusion in the Backbone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-vision-language-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language (VL) pre-training has recently received considerable attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-vision-language-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Generalization in Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single image-level annotations only correctly describe an often small subset of an image's content, particularly when complex real-world scenes are depicted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PolyU-BPCoMa: A Dataset and Benchmark Towards Mobile Colorized Mapping Using a Backpack Multisensorial System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyu-bpcoma-a-dataset-and-benchmark-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Color checker boards are pasted in each surveyed area as targets and ground truth data are collected by an advanced terrestrial laser scanner (TLS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polyu-bpcoma-a-dataset-and-benchmark-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Data Mixing Prior for Improving Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-data-mixing-prior-for-improving-self-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More notably, our SDMP is the first method that successfully leverages data mixing to improve (rather than hurt) the performance of Vision Transformers in the self-supervised setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-data-mixing-prior-for-improving-self-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParamNet: A Multi-Layer Parametric Network for Joint Channel Estimation and Symbol Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paramnet-a-multi-layer-parametric-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a parametric-based network architecture for joint channel estimation and data detection in communications systems with hardware impairments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paramnet-a-multi-layer-parametric-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A smile is all you need: Predicting limiting activity coefficients from SMILES with natural language processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-smile-is-all-you-need-predicting-limiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This training strategy enables SPT to accurately predict limiting activity coefficients even for unknown molecules, cutting the mean prediction error in half compared to state-of-the-art models for activity coefficient predictions such as COSMO-RS, UNIFAC, and improving on recent machine learning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-smile-is-all-you-need-predicting-limiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Numerical Integration in Neural Ordinary Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-numerical-integration-in-neural-ordinary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of ordinary differential equations and neural networks, i. e., neural ordinary differential equations (Neural ODE), has been widely studied from various angles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-numerical-integration-in-neural-ordinary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Optimal Covariance with Imperfect Mean in Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-optimal-covariance-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, the generation performance on a subset of timesteps is crucial, which is greatly influenced by the covariance design in DPMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-optimal-covariance-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards ML Methods for Biodiversity: A Novel Wild Bee Dataset and Evaluations of XAI Methods for ML-Assisted Rare Species Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-ml-methods-for-biodiversity-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Insects are a crucial part of our ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-ml-methods-for-biodiversity-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Reliable Evaluation of Adversarial Robustness with Minimum-Margin Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-reliable-evaluation-of-adversarial-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The AutoAttack (AA) has been the most reliable method to evaluate adversarial robustness when considerable computational resources are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-reliable-evaluation-of-adversarial-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prefix Language Models are Unified Modal Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefix-language-models-are-unified-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the success of vision-language pre-training, we have witnessed the state-of-the-art has been pushed on multi-modal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefix-language-models-are-unified-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Ranking as Fair Division: Impact-Based Individual Fairness in Ranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-ranking-as-fair-division-impact-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our axioms of envy-freeness and dominance over uniform ranking postulate that for a fair ranking policy every item should prefer their own rank allocation over that of any other item, and that no item should be actively disadvantaged by the rankings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-ranking-as-fair-division-impact-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Aware End-to-end Mispronunciation Detection and Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-aware-end-to-end-mispronunciation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of assessing the pronunciation quality of constrained speech, the given transcriptions can play the role of a teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-aware-end-to-end-mispronunciation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S\textsuperscript{2}-FPN: Scale-ware Strip Attention Guided Feature Pyramid Network for Real-time Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-textsuperscript-2-fpn-scale-ware-strip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new model to achieve a trade-off between accuracy/speed for real-time road scene semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-textsuperscript-2-fpn-scale-ware-strip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecBole 2.0: Towards a More Up-to-Date Recommendation Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recbole-2-0-towards-a-more-up-to-date</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to support the study of recent advances in recommender systems, this paper presents an extended recommendation library consisting of eight packages for up-to-date topics and architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recbole-2-0-towards-a-more-up-to-date</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SIGMORPHON 2022 Shared Task on Morpheme Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sigmorphon-2022-shared-task-on-morpheme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SIGMORPHON 2022 shared task on morpheme segmentation challenged systems to decompose a word into a sequence of morphemes and covered most types of morphology: compounds, derivations, and inflections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-sigmorphon-2022-shared-task-on-morpheme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Generalization in Few-Shot Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single image-level annotations only correctly describe an often small subset of an image's content, particularly when complex real-world scenes are depicted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-generalization-in-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot object goal visual navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-object-goal-visual-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object goal visual navigation is a challenging task that aims to guide a robot to find the target object only based on its visual observation, and the target is limited to the classes specified in the training stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-object-goal-visual-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Discrete Deep Generative Models via Gapped Straight-Through Estimator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-discrete-deep-generative-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep generative models have succeeded in image processing, natural language processing, and reinforcement learning, training that involves discrete random variables remains challenging due to the high variance of its gradient estimation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-discrete-deep-generative-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Why Here and Not There?" -- Diverse Contrasting Explanations of Dimensionality Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-here-and-not-there-diverse-contrasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimensionality reduction is a popular preprocessing and a widely used tool in data mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-here-and-not-there-diverse-contrasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LET-3D-AP: Longitudinal Error Tolerant 3D Average Precision for Camera-Only 3D Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-3d-ap-longitudinal-error-tolerant-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The popular object detection metric 3D Average Precision (3D AP) relies on the intersection over union between predicted bounding boxes and ground truth bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-3d-ap-longitudinal-error-tolerant-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label Matching Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-matching-semi-supervised-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy this issue, we present a novel label assignment mechanism for self-training framework, namely proposal self-assignment, which injects the proposals from student into teacher and generates accurate pseudo labels to match each proposal in the student model accordingly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-matching-semi-supervised-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stand-Alone Inter-Frame Attention in Video Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stand-alone-inter-frame-attention-in-video-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new recipe of inter-frame attention block, namely Stand-alone Inter-Frame Attention (SIFA), that novelly delves into the deformation across frames to estimate local self-attention on each spatial location.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stand-alone-inter-frame-attention-in-video-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Precision Localization of Peripherally Inserted Central Catheter Tip through Model-Agnostic Multi-Stage Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-precision-localization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In internal validation, when MFCN was applied to the existing single model, MFP was improved by an average of 45%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-precision-localization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Astock: A New Dataset and Automated Stock Trading based on Stock-specific News Analyzing Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astock-a-new-dataset-and-automated-stock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we propose a self-supervised learning strategy based on SRLP to enhance the out-of-distribution generalization performance of our system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/astock-a-new-dataset-and-automated-stock</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Narratives through Dimensions of Analogy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-narratives-through-dimensions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments with language models and neuro-symbolic AI reasoners on these tasks reveal that state-of-the-art methods can be applied to reason by analogy with a limited success, motivating the need for further research towards comprehensive and scalable analogical reasoning by AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-narratives-through-dimensions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBGDT:Robust Mini-Batch Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbgdt-robust-mini-batch-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In high dimensions, most machine learning method perform fragile even there are a little outliers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbgdt-robust-mini-batch-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task Transfer and Domain Adaptation for Zero-Shot Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-transfer-and-domain-adaptation-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained language models have shown success in various areas of natural language processing, including reading comprehension tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-transfer-and-domain-adaptation-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoWhy-GCM: An extension of DoWhy for causal inference in graphical causal models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dowhy-gcm-an-extension-of-dowhy-for-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce DoWhy-GCM, an extension of the DoWhy Python library, that leverages graphical causal models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dowhy-gcm-an-extension-of-dowhy-for-causal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Estimation using the Underdamped Langevin Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-estimation-using-the-underdamped</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we consider the unbiased estimation of expectations w. r. t.~probability measures that have non-negative Lebesgue density, and which are known point-wise up-to a normalizing constant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-estimation-using-the-underdamped</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RF-Next: Efficient Receptive Field Search for Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rf-next-efficient-receptive-field-search-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our search scheme exploits both global search to find the coarse combinations and local search to get the refined receptive field combinations further.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rf-next-efficient-receptive-field-search-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing a Model-based Policy Stationary Distribution to Stabilize Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-a-model-based-policy-stationary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline reinforcement learning (RL) extends the paradigm of classical RL algorithms to purely learning from static datasets, without interacting with the underlying environment during the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-a-model-based-policy-stationary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopping Queries Dataset: A Large-Scale ESCI Benchmark for Improving Product Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-queries-dataset-a-large-scale-esci</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the "Shopping Queries Dataset", a large dataset of difficult Amazon search queries and results, publicly released with the aim of fostering research in improving the quality of search results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shopping-queries-dataset-a-large-scale-esci</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-task Framework for Infrared Small Target Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-framework-for-infrared-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, with the use of UNet as the backbone to maintain resolution and semantic information, our model can achieve a higher detection accuracy than other state-of-the-art methods by attaching a simple anchor-free head.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-framework-for-infrared-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Vulnerability of Randomized Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-vulnerability-of-randomized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we address this question both theoretically and empirically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-vulnerability-of-randomized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransVG++: End-to-End Visual Grounding with Language Conditioned Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transvg-end-to-end-visual-grounding-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For another, we devise Language Conditioned Vision Transformer that removes external fusion modules and reuses the uni-modal ViT for vision-language fusion at the intermediate layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transvg-end-to-end-visual-grounding-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling ResNets in the Large-depth Regime</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-resnets-in-the-large-depth-regime</link>
      <description><![CDATA[initializations, the only non-trivial dynamics is for $\alpha_L = 1/\sqrt{L}$ (other choices lead either to explosion or to identity mapping).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-resnets-in-the-large-depth-regime</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Dictionary Learning with Auxiliary Covariates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-dictionary-learning-with-auxiliary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Supervised dictionary learning (SDL) is a classical machine learning method that simultaneously seeks feature extraction and classification tasks, which are not necessarily a priori aligned objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-dictionary-learning-with-auxiliary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIFT: Language-Interfaced Fine-Tuning for Non-Language Machine Learning Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lift-language-interfaced-fine-tuning-for-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LIFT does not make any changes to the model architecture or loss function, and it solely relies on the natural language interface, enabling "no-code machine learning with LMs."]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lift-language-interfaced-fine-tuning-for-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Representation of Horn Clauses using GNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-representation-of-horn-clauses</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the second challenge, we explore graph representations of CHCs, and propose a new Relational Hypergraph Neural Network (R-HyGNN) architecture to learn program features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-representation-of-horn-clauses</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHQ-Summ: A Dataset for Consumer Healthcare Question Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chq-summ-a-dataset-for-consumer-healthcare</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quest for seeking health information has swamped the web with consumers' health-related questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chq-summ-a-dataset-for-consumer-healthcare</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Adversarial Attacks and Defenses in Vision Transformers trained with DINO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-adversarial-attacks-and-defenses-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work conducts the first analysis on the robustness against adversarial attacks on self-supervised Vision Transformers trained using DINO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-adversarial-attacks-and-defenses-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAVENDER: Unifying Video-Language Understanding as Masked Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lavender-unifying-video-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a unified VidL framework LAVENDER, where Masked Language Modeling (MLM) is used as the common interface for all pre-training and downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lavender-unifying-video-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Easy Example Mining for Weakly-supervised Gland Segmentation from Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-easy-example-mining-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing weakly-supervised semantic segmentation methods in computer vision achieve degenerative results for gland segmentation, since the characteristics and problems of glandular datasets are different from general object datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-easy-example-mining-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
