<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 09:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Abstractive Summarization of Diverse Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-abstractive-summarization-of-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first formally define fairness in abstractive summarization as not underrepresenting perspectives of any groups of people and propose four reference-free automatic metrics measuring the differences between target and source perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-abstractive-summarization-of-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen-Audio: Advancing Universal Audio Understanding via Unified Large-Scale Audio-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-audio-advancing-universal-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, instruction-following audio-language models have received broad attention for audio interaction with humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-audio-advancing-universal-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Open-Ended Visual Recognition with Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-ended-visual-recognition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Localizing and recognizing objects in the open-ended physical world poses a long-standing challenge within the domain of machine perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-open-ended-visual-recognition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Large Language Models Temporally Grounded?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-temporally-grounded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we provide LLMs with textual narratives and probe them with respect to their common-sense knowledge of the structure and duration of events, their ability to order events along a timeline, and self-consistency within their temporal model (e. g., temporal relations such as after and before are mutually exclusive for any pair of events).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-temporally-grounded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Efficient and Incremental Spectral Clustering via Parametric Spectral Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-and-incremental-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The findings of this research contribute to the advancement of clustering techniques and open new avenues for efficient and effective data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-and-incremental-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MC^2: A Multilingual Corpus of Minority Languages in China</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-2-a-multilingual-corpus-of-minority</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing LLMs exhibit limited abilities in understanding low-resource languages, including the minority languages in China, due to a lack of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mc-2-a-multilingual-corpus-of-minority</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models are Better Bug Detector Through Code-Pair Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-better-bug-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our task in real-world dataset of bug detection and two most powerful LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-better-bug-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Data Enhanced On-Policy Policy Gradient with Provable Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-data-enhanced-on-policy-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new hybrid RL algorithm that combines an on-policy actor-critic method with offline data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-data-enhanced-on-policy-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cattle Identification Using Muzzle Images and Deep Learning Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cattle-identification-using-muzzle-images-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional animal identification methods such as ear-tagging, ear notching, and branding have been effective but pose risks to the animal and have scalability issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cattle-identification-using-muzzle-images-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Complex Disease Trajectories using Deep Generative Models with Semi-Supervised Latent Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-disease-trajectories-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a deep generative time series approach using latent temporal processes for modeling and holistically analyzing complex disease trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-disease-trajectories-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Well Do Large Language Models Understand Syntax? An Evaluation by Asking Natural Language Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-large-language-models-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) bring us closer to achieving artificial general intelligence, the question persists: Do LLMs truly understand language, or do they merely mimic comprehension through pattern recognition?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-large-language-models-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-autoregressive Machine Translation with Probabilistic Context-free Grammar</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-machine-translation-with-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Non-autoregressive Transformer(NAT) significantly accelerates the inference of neural machine translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-machine-translation-with-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Retrieval with Multi-Stage Re-Ranking Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-retrieval-with-multi-stage-re-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We ranked the documents by BM25 and language models, and then re-ranks by a model ensemble or a larger language model for documents with high similarity to the query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-retrieval-with-multi-stage-re-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Reasoning in Large Language Models via Multi-Agent Peer Review Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reasoning-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further study demonstrates the effectiveness of integrating confidence in the reviews for math reasoning, and suggests a promising direction for human-mimicking multi-agent collaboration process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-reasoning-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-shot audio captioning with audio-language model guidance and audio context keywords</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-audio-captioning-with-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, our framework exploits a pre-trained large language model (LLM) for generating the text which is guided by a pre-trained audio-language model to produce captions that describe the audio content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-audio-captioning-with-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLatrieval: LLM-Verified Retrieval for Verifiable Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llatrieval-llm-verified-retrieval-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Verifiable generation aims to let the large language model (LLM) generate text with corresponding supporting documents, which enables the user to flexibly verify the answer and makes it more trustworthy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llatrieval-llm-verified-retrieval-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Stage Predict+Optimize for Mixed Integer Linear Programs with Unknown Parameters in Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-predict-optimize-for-mixed-integer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also give a training algorithm usable for all mixed integer linear programs, vastly generalizing the applicability of the framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-predict-optimize-for-mixed-integer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Language Models for Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-language-models-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we systematically review the recent advancements in code processing with language models, covering 50+ models, 30+ evaluation tasks, and 500 related works.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-language-models-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Semi-supervised Hierarchical Stacked Encoder for Legal Judgement Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semi-supervised-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting the judgment of a legal case from its unannotated case facts is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semi-supervised-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Well Do Text Embedding Models Understand Syntax?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-text-embedding-models-understand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text embedding models have significantly contributed to advancements in natural language processing by adeptly capturing semantic properties of textual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-well-do-text-embedding-models-understand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiPar: A Lightweight Parallel Learning Model for Practical In-Vehicle Network Intrusion Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipar-a-lightweight-parallel-learning-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through experiments, we prove that LiPar has great detection performance, running efficiency, and lightweight model size, which can be well adapted to the in-vehicle environment practically and protect the in-vehicle CAN bus security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipar-a-lightweight-parallel-learning-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On The Relationship Between Universal Adversarial Attacks And Sparse Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-relationship-between-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we show that sparse coding algorithms, and the neural network-based learned iterative shrinkage thresholding algorithm (LISTA) among them, suffer from this sensitivity, and that common attacks on neural networks can be expressed as attacks on the sparse representation of the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-relationship-between-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Evolved Diverse Data Sampling for Efficient Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-evolved-diverse-data-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key to our data sampling technique lies in the enhancement of diversity in the chosen subsets, as the model selects new data points most distinct from any existing ones according to its current embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-evolved-diverse-data-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test-Time Training for Semantic Segmentation with Output Contrastive Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-training-for-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning-based segmentation models have achieved impressive performance on public benchmarks, generalizing well to unseen environments remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-training-for-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Filter Context for Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-filter-context-for-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these problems, we propose FILCO, a method that improves the quality of the context provided to the generator by (1) identifying useful context based on lexical and information-theoretic approaches, and (2) training context filtering models that can filter retrieved contexts at test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-filter-context-for-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Knowledge Distillation via Confidence Amendment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces OOD knowledge distillation, a pioneering learning framework applicable whether or not training ID data is available, given a standard network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eval-GCSC: A New Metric for Evaluating ChatGPT's Performance in Chinese Spelling Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eval-gcsc-a-new-metric-for-evaluating-chatgpt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in the Chinese Spelling Correction (CSC) task, we observe a discrepancy: while ChatGPT performs well under human evaluation, it scores poorly according to traditional metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eval-gcsc-a-new-metric-for-evaluating-chatgpt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Physics-Inspired Regularization for Medical Image Registration with Hypernetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-physics-inspired-regularization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we adapt the HyperMorph framework to learn the effect of the two elasticity parameters of the linear elastic regularizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-physics-inspired-regularization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clearer Frames, Anytime: Resolving Velocity Ambiguity in Video Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clearer-frames-anytime-resolving-velocity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing video frame interpolation (VFI) methods blindly predict where each object is at a specific timestep t ("time indexing"), which struggles to predict precise object movements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clearer-frames-anytime-resolving-velocity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plum: Prompt Learning using Metaheuristic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plum-prompt-learning-using-metaheuristic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the emergence of large language models, prompt learning has become a popular method for optimizing and customizing these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plum-prompt-learning-using-metaheuristic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Light-curve Signals with a Deep Learning Based Object Detection Algorithm. II. A General Light Curve Classification Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-light-curve-signals-with-a-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train our model on datasets obtained from both space-based and ground-based multi-band observations of variable stars and transients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-light-curve-signals-with-a-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMIHS: Adaptation of Segment Anything Model for Intracranial Hemorrhage Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samihs-adaptation-of-segment-anything-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM), a vision foundation model trained on large-scale annotations, has recently continued raising awareness within medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samihs-adaptation-of-segment-anything-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USLR: an open-source tool for unbiased and smooth longitudinal registration of brain MR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uslr-an-open-source-tool-for-unbiased-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present USLR, a computational framework for longitudinal registration of brain MRI scans to estimate nonlinear image trajectories that are smooth across time, unbiased to any timepoint, and robust to imaging artefacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uslr-an-open-source-tool-for-unbiased-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction-Following Evaluation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-following-evaluation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One core capability of Large Language Models (LLMs) is to follow natural language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-following-evaluation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving ARC visual analogies with neural embeddings and vector arithmetic: A generalized method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-arc-visual-analogies-with-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project focuses on visual analogical reasoning and applies the initial generalized mechanism used to solve verbal analogies to the visual realm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-arc-visual-analogies-with-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Using Distribution-Based Compositionality Assessment to Evaluate Compositional Generalisation in Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-using-distribution-based-compositionality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a fully-automated procedure to create natural language compositionality benchmarks, making it simple and inexpensive to apply it further to other datasets and languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-using-distribution-based-compositionality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEC-DePenD: Non-Autoregressive Grammatical Error Correction with Decoupled Permutation and Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gec-depend-non-autoregressive-grammatical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grammatical error correction (GEC) is an important NLP task that is currently usually solved with autoregressive sequence-to-sequence models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gec-depend-non-autoregressive-grammatical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-efficient Stochastic methods for Memory-based Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-stochastic-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training Memory-based transformers can require a large amount of memory and can be quite inefficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-stochastic-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Attention Network for Cross-domain Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-attention-network-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent proposed cross-domain sequential recommendation models such as PiNet and DASL have a common drawback relying heavily on overlapped users in different domains, which limits their usage in practical recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-attention-network-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deformation-based morphometry framework for disentangling Alzheimer's disease from normal aging using learned normal aging templates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deformation-based-morphometry-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a deformation-based morphometry framework to estimate normal aging and AD-specific atrophy patterns of subjects from morphological MRI scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deformation-based-morphometry-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoDiffusion: Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation Using Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monodiffusion-self-supervised-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because the depth ground-truth is unavailable in the training phase, we develop a pseudo ground-truth diffusion process to assist the diffusion in MonoDiffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monodiffusion-self-supervised-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Voting Approach for Explainable Classification with Rule Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-voting-approach-for-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art results in typical classification tasks are mostly achieved by unexplainable machine learning methods, like deep neural networks, for instance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-voting-approach-for-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpNote: Black-box Large Language Models are Better Task Solvers with Experience Notebook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expnote-black-box-large-language-models-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Black-box Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown great power in solving various tasks and are considered general problem solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expnote-black-box-large-language-models-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Multiple Teachers for Test-Time Adaptation of Language-Guided Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multiple-teachers-for-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent approaches have explored language-guided classifiers capable of classifying examples from novel tasks when provided with task-specific natural language explanations, instructions or prompts (Sanh et al., 2022; R. Menon et al., 2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-multiple-teachers-for-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDDepth: Normal-Distance Assisted Monocular Depth Estimation and Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nddepth-normal-distance-assisted-monocular-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we develop a normal-distance head that outputs pixel-level surface normal and distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nddepth-normal-distance-assisted-monocular-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Histopathologic Cancer Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathologic-cancer-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research contributes a potential classification model for cancer prognosis to efficiently utilize the valuable information underlying the HE-stained histopathological images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histopathologic-cancer-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Law of Capacity Gap in Distilling Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-law-of-capacity-gap-in-distilling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pain is mainly resulted by the curse of capacity gap, which describes that a larger teacher LM cannot always lead to a better student LM than one distilled from a smaller teacher LM due to the affect of capacity gap increment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-law-of-capacity-gap-in-distilling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining black boxes with a SMILE: Statistical Model-agnostic Interpretability with Local Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-black-boxes-with-a-smile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning is currently undergoing an explosion in capability, popularity, and sophistication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-black-boxes-with-a-smile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Multi-Pivot Ensembling with Massively Multilingual Machine Translation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-pivot-ensembling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Massively multilingual machine translation models allow for the translation of a large number of languages with a single model, but have limited performance on low- and very-low-resource translation directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-pivot-ensembling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volcano: Mitigating Multimodal Hallucination through Self-Feedback Guided Revision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volcano-mitigating-multimodal-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through a qualitative analysis, we show that Volcano's feedback is properly grounded on the image than the initial response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/volcano-mitigating-multimodal-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
