<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 21:08:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Temporal Convolution Network:Towards Privacy-Centric Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-temporal-convolution-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this context, we propose HT-ConvNet (Hierarchical Temporal Convolution Network) to capture multi-scale temporal information without increasing computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-temporal-convolution-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TL-Training: A Task-Feature-Based Framework for Training Large Language Models in Tool Use</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tl-training-a-task-feature-based-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) achieve remarkable advancements by leveraging tools to interact with external environments, a critical step toward generalized AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tl-training-a-task-feature-based-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Only Way is Ethics: A Guide to Ethical Research with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-only-way-is-ethics-a-guide-to-ethical</link>
      <description><![CDATA['LLM Ethics Whitepaper' distils a thorough literature review into clear Do's and Don'ts, which we present also in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-only-way-is-ethics-a-guide-to-ethical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Clustering of Citizen Science Data Improves Downstream Species Distribution Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-clustering-of-citizen-science-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the opportunistic nature of these data lacks the sampling structure required by modeling methodologies that address a pervasive challenge in ecological data collection: imperfect detection, i. e., the likelihood of under-observing species on field surveys.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-clustering-of-citizen-science-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChangeDiff: A Multi-Temporal Change Detection Data Generator with Flexible Text Prompts via Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/changediff-a-multi-temporal-change-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose multi-class distribution-guided text prompts (MCDG-TP), allowing for layouts to be generated flexibly through controllable classes and their corresponding ratios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/changediff-a-multi-temporal-change-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Spatial-Temporal Learner for Precipitation Nowcasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-spatial-temporal-learner-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we leverage the benefits of self-supervised learning and integrate it with spatial-temporal learning to develop a novel model, SpaT-SparK.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-spatial-temporal-learner-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convolutional Deep Operator Networks for Learning Nonlinear Focused Ultrasound Wave Propagation in Heterogeneous Spinal Cord Anatomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-deep-operator-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focused ultrasound (FUS) therapy is a promising tool for optimally targeted treatment of spinal cord injuries (SCI), offering submillimeter precision to enhance blood flow at injury sites while minimizing impact on surrounding tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convolutional-deep-operator-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Large-scale UAV Route Planing with Global and Local Features via Reinforcement Graph Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-scale-uav-route-planing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results unequivocally demonstrate that our framework efficiently scales existing TSP solvers to handle large instances and consistently outperforms state-of-the-art (SOTA) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-scale-uav-route-planing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EF-Net: A Deep Learning Approach Combining Word Embeddings and Feature Fusion for Patient Disposition Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ef-net-a-deep-learning-approach-combining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In EF-Net, we attained an accuracy of 95. 33%, whereas in the Ensemble Model, we achieved an accuracy of 96%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ef-net-a-deep-learning-approach-combining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variability Need Not Imply Error: The Case of Adequate but Semantically Distinct Responses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variability-need-not-imply-error-the-case-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, Kuhn et al. (semantic entropy; 2022b) regard semantic variation amongst sampled responses as evidence that the model `struggles' with the prompt and that the LM is likely to err.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variability-need-not-imply-error-the-case-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Cross-Modal Interactions in Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-cross-modal-interactions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that InterSHAP accurately measures the presence of cross-modal interactions, can handle multiple modalities, and provides detailed explanations at a local level for individual samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-cross-modal-interactions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EGSRAL: An Enhanced 3D Gaussian Splatting based Renderer with Automated Labeling for Large-Scale Driving Scene</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egsral-an-enhanced-3d-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose EGSRAL, a 3D GS-based method that relies solely on training images without extra annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egsral-an-enhanced-3d-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novelty-Guided Data Reuse for Efficient and Diversified Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novelty-guided-data-reuse-for-efficient-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) has demonstrated its potential to tackle complex cooperative tasks, pushing the boundaries of AI in collaborative environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novelty-guided-data-reuse-for-efficient-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MarkovType: A Markov Decision Process Strategy for Non-Invasive Brain-Computer Interfaces Typing Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markovtype-a-markov-decision-process-strategy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first work to formulate the RSVP typing task as a POMDP for recursive classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/markovtype-a-markov-decision-process-strategy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using matrix-product states for time-series machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-matrix-product-states-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we develop and apply an MPS-based algorithm, MPSTime, for learning a joint probability distribution underlying an observed time-series dataset, and show how it can be used to tackle important time-series ML problems, including classification and imputation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-matrix-product-states-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt-based Unifying Inference Attack on Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-unifying-inference-attack-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, ProIA retains the crucial topological information of the graph during pre-training, enhancing the background knowledge of the inference attack model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-based-unifying-inference-attack-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CustomTTT: Motion and Appearance Customized Video Generation via Test-Time Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customttt-motion-and-appearance-customized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, given some reference images or videos, the parameter-efficient fine-tuning method, i. e. LoRA, can generate high-quality customized concepts, e. g., the specific subject or the motions from a reference video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/customttt-motion-and-appearance-customized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEAR: Conv-Like Linearization Revs Pre-Trained Diffusion Transformers Up</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clear-conv-like-linearization-revs-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion Transformers (DiT) have become a leading architecture in image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clear-conv-like-linearization-revs-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning Using a Kernel-Based Method Over Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-using-a-kernel-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel CIL method, called Kernel Linear Discriminant Analysis (KLDA), that can effectively avoid CF and ICS problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-using-a-kernel-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASPIRE: Assistive System for Performance Evaluation in IR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aspire-assistive-system-for-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information Retrieval (IR) evaluation involves far more complexity than merely presenting performance measures in a table.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aspire-assistive-system-for-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score-based Generative Diffusion Models for Social Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-generative-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the prevalence of social networks on online platforms, social recommendation has become a vital technique for enhancing personalized recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-based-generative-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RESQUE: Quantifying Estimator to Task and Distribution Shift for Sustainable Model Reusability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resque-quantifying-estimator-to-task-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a strategy for sustainability of deep learning, reusing an existing model by retraining it rather than training a new model from scratch is critical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resque-quantifying-estimator-to-task-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficulty-aware Balancing Margin Loss for Long-tailed Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-aware-balancing-margin-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When trained with severely imbalanced data, deep neural networks often struggle to accurately recognize classes with only a few samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-aware-balancing-margin-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting Interpretable Task-Specific Circuits from Large Language Models for Faster Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-interpretable-task-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This leads us to the following question: Is it possible to extract the minimal subset from an LLM that is able to perform a specific task in a faster, standalone manner?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-interpretable-task-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PruneVid: Visual Token Pruning for Efficient Video Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prunevid-visual-token-pruning-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce PruneVid, a visual token pruning method designed to enhance the efficiency of multi-modal video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prunevid-visual-token-pruning-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Curation of Invertebrate Image Datasets Using Feature Embeddings and Automatic Size Comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-curation-of-invertebrate-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer vision applications rely on high-quality datasets, making data curation important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-curation-of-invertebrate-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Representation from Personalized Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-representation-from-personalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern vision models excel at general purpose downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-representation-from-personalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APIRL: Deep Reinforcement Learning for REST API Fuzzing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apirl-deep-reinforcement-learning-for-rest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[REST APIs have become key components of web services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/apirl-deep-reinforcement-learning-for-rest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Align Anything: Training All-Modality Models to Follow Instructions with Language Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-anything-training-all-modality-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we make the first attempt to fine-tune all-modality models (i. e. input and output with any modality, also named any-to-any models) using human preference data across all modalities (including text, image, audio, and video), ensuring its behavior aligns with human intentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/align-anything-training-all-modality-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIR: Unifying Individual and Cooperative Exploration in Collective Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-unifying-individual-and-cooperative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploration in cooperative multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) remains challenging for value-based agents due to the absence of an explicit policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/air-unifying-individual-and-cooperative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dimensional Visual Prompt Enhanced Image Restoration via Mamba-Transformer Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-visual-prompt-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The self-attention mechanism of Transformer is applied to focus on channel modeling, avoiding high computation burdens that are in quadratic growth with image's spatial dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-visual-prompt-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interpretable Radiology Report Generation via Concept Bottlenecks using a Multi-Agentic RAG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-radiology-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study enhances interpretability in Chest X-ray (CXR) classification by using concept bottleneck models (CBMs) and a multi-agent Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) system for report generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-radiology-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tuning Whisper on Low-Resource Languages for Real-World Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-whisper-on-low-resource-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our data generation process improves performance in several real-world applications and leads to the development of a new state-of-the-art speech-to-text (STT) model for Swiss German.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tuning-whisper-on-low-resource-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi Agent Reinforcement Learning for Sequential Satellite Assignment Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-for-24</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assignment problems are a classic combinatorial optimization problem in which a group of agents must be assigned to a group of tasks such that maximum utility is achieved while satisfying assignment constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-reinforcement-learning-for-24</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebLLM: A High-Performance In-Browser LLM Inference Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webllm-a-high-performance-in-browser-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[WebLLM paves the way for universally accessible, privacy-preserving, personalized, and locally powered LLM applications in web browsers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webllm-a-high-performance-in-browser-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Template-Driven LLM-Paraphrased Framework for Tabular Math Word Problem Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-driven-llm-paraphrased-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Template-driven LLM-paraphrased (TeLL) framework for generating high-quality TMWP samples with diverse backgrounds and accurate tables, questions, answers, and solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/template-driven-llm-paraphrased-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enriching Social Science Research via Survey Item Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enriching-social-science-research-via-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By benchmarking deep learning systems for each of the two stages independently and sequentially, we demonstrate that the task is feasible, but observe that errors propagate from the first stage, leading to a lower overall task performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enriching-social-science-research-via-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniGPT-Pancreas: Multimodal Large Language Model for Pancreas Cancer Classification and Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-pancreas-multimodal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the pancreas tumor detection task, the IoU score was 0. 168 on the MSD dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minigpt-pancreas-multimodal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deciphering the Underserved: Benchmarking LLM OCR for Low-Resource Scripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deciphering-the-underserved-benchmarking-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the potential of Large Language Models (LLMs), particularly GPT-4o, for Optical Character Recognition (OCR) in low-resource scripts such as Urdu, Albanian, and Tajik, with English serving as a benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deciphering-the-underserved-benchmarking-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathSpeech: Leveraging Small LMs for Accurate Conversion in Mathematical Speech-to-Formula</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathspeech-leveraging-small-lms-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In various academic and professional settings, such as mathematics lectures or research presentations, it is often necessary to convey mathematical expressions orally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathspeech-leveraging-small-lms-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DefFiller: Mask-Conditioned Diffusion for Salient Steel Surface Defect Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deffiller-mask-conditioned-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current saliency-based defect detection methods show promise in industrial settings, but the unpredictability of defects in steel production environments complicates dataset creation, hampering model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deffiller-mask-conditioned-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choose Your Explanation: A Comparison of SHAP and GradCAM in Human Activity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/choose-your-explanation-a-comparison-of-shap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explaining machine learning (ML) models using eXplainable AI (XAI) techniques has become essential to make them more transparent and trustworthy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/choose-your-explanation-a-comparison-of-shap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGTC: Semantic-Guided Triplet Co-training for Sparsely Annotated Semi-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgtc-semantic-guided-triplet-co-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel Semantic-Guided Triplet Co-training (SGTC) framework, which achieves high-end medical image segmentation by only annotating three orthogonal slices of a few volumetric samples, significantly alleviating the burden of radiologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgtc-semantic-guided-triplet-co-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Generalized Few-Shot Semantic Segmentation via Effective Knowledge Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-generalized-few-shot-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, existing GFSS approaches suffer from a lack of contextual information for novel classes due to their limited samples, we thereby introduce a context consistency learning scheme to transfer the contextual knowledge from base to novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-generalized-few-shot-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacLight: Multi-scene Aggregation Convolutional Learning for Traffic Signal Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maclight-multi-scene-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning methods have proposed promising traffic signal control policy that can be trained on large road networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maclight-multi-scene-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PreNeT: Leveraging Computational Features to Predict Deep Neural Network Training Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prenet-leveraging-computational-features-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training deep learning models, particularly Transformer-based architectures such as Large Language Models (LLMs), demands substantial computational resources and extended training periods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prenet-leveraging-computational-features-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient MedSAMs: Segment Anything in Medical Images on Laptop</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-medsams-segment-anything-in-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Promptable segmentation foundation models have emerged as a transformative approach to addressing the diverse needs in medical images, but most existing models require expensive computing, posing a big barrier to their adoption in clinical practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-medsams-segment-anything-in-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistic Features Extracted by GPT-4 Improve Alzheimer's Disease Detection based on Spontaneous Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-features-extracted-by-gpt-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Disease (AD) is a significant and growing public health concern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-features-extracted-by-gpt-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MR-GDINO: Efficient Open-World Continual Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr-gdino-efficient-open-world-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite promising results on seen classes, such OW abilities on unseen classes are largely degenerated due to catastrophic forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mr-gdino-efficient-open-world-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Masked Time-Series Modeling via Dropping Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-masked-time-series-modeling-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores how to enhance existing masked time-series modeling by randomly dropping sub-sequence level patches of time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-masked-time-series-modeling-via</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
