<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 21:06:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Personalized Dense Retrieval Framework for Unified Information Access</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-personalized-dense-retrieval-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing a universal model that can efficiently and effectively respond to a wide range of information access requests -- from retrieval to recommendation to question answering -- has been a long-lasting goal in the information retrieval community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-personalized-dense-retrieval-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Frame Interpolation with Densely Queried Bilateral Correlation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-frame-interpolation-with-densely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better model correlations and to produce more accurate motion fields, we propose the Densely Queried Bilateral Correlation (DQBC) that gets rid of the receptive field dependency problem and thus is more friendly to small and fast-moving objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-frame-interpolation-with-densely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESPT: A Self-Supervised Episodic Spatial Pretext Task for Improving Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espt-a-self-supervised-episodic-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this definition, the ESPT-augmented FSL objective promotes learning more transferable feature representations that capture the local spatial features of different images and their inter-relational structural information in each input episode, thus enabling the model to generalize better to new categories with only a few samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espt-a-self-supervised-episodic-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Happened 3 Seconds Ago? Inferring the Past with Thermal Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-happened-3-seconds-ago-inferring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inferring past human motion from RGB images is challenging due to the inherent uncertainty of the prediction problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-happened-3-seconds-ago-inferring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of latent space distribution on the segmentation of images with multiple annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-latent-space-distribution-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the Generalized Probabilistic U-Net, which extends the Probabilistic U-Net by allowing more general forms of the Gaussian distribution as the latent space distribution that can better approximate the uncertainty in the reference segmentations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-latent-space-distribution-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STIR: Siamese Transformer for Image Retrieval Postprocessing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stir-siamese-transformer-for-image-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current metric learning approaches for image retrieval are usually based on learning a space of informative latent representations where simple approaches such as the cosine distance will work well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stir-siamese-transformer-for-image-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Control-Centric Benchmark for Video Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-control-centric-benchmark-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video is a promising source of knowledge for embodied agents to learn models of the world's dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-control-centric-benchmark-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffsurv: Differentiable sorting for censored time-to-event data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsurv-differentiable-sorting-for-censored</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we demonstrate the benefits of the algorithmic supervision enabled by Diffsurv by presenting a novel method for top-k risk prediction that outperforms current methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffsurv-differentiable-sorting-for-censored</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptive and Generalizable Network Architectures and Training Strategies for Semantic Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-and-generalizable-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As previous UDA&DG semantic segmentation methods are mostly based on outdated networks, we benchmark more recent architectures, reveal the potential of Transformers, and design the DAFormer network tailored for UDA&DG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptive-and-generalizable-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compensation Learning in Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compensation-learning-in-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Compensation Learning in Semantic Segmentation, a framework to identify and compensate ambiguities as well as label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compensation-learning-in-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiQ -- A Declarative, Non-intrusive, Dynamic and Transparent Observability and Optimization System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiq-a-declarative-non-intrusive-dynamic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a non-intrusive, declarative, dynamic and transparent system called `HiQ` to track Python program runtime information without compromising on the run-time system performance and losing insight.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hiq-a-declarative-non-intrusive-dynamic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGOS: Voxel Grid Optimization for View Synthesis from Sparse Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgos-voxel-grid-optimization-for-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose VGOS, an approach for fast (3-5 minutes) radiance field reconstruction from sparse inputs (3-10 views) to address these issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgos-voxel-grid-optimization-for-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning with Uncertainty-Based Client Clustering for Fleet-Wide Fault Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-uncertainty-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To quantify dataset similarity between clients without explicitly sharing data, each client sets aside a local test dataset and evaluates the other clients' model prediction accuracy and uncertainty on this test dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-uncertainty-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Infinite-Length Input Capacity for Large-scale Language Models with Self-Controlled Memory System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-infinite-length-input-capacity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose the Self-Controlled Memory (SCM) system to unleash infinite-length input capacity for large-scale language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-infinite-length-input-capacity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feed-Forward Optimization With Delayed Feedback for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feed-forward-optimization-with-delayed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Backpropagation has long been criticized for being biologically implausible, relying on concepts that are not viable in natural learning processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feed-forward-optimization-with-delayed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenBox: A Python Toolkit for Generalized Black-box Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openbox-a-python-toolkit-for-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Black-box optimization (BBO) has a broad range of applications, including automatic machine learning, experimental design, and database knob tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openbox-a-python-toolkit-for-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Explainable Face Verification based on Similarity Score Argument Backpropagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-explainable-face-verification-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainable Face Recognition is gaining growing attention as the use of the technology is gaining ground in security-critical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-explainable-face-verification-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Ophthalmology SAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-ophthalmology-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on Segment Anything (SAM), we propose a simple but effective learnable prompt layer suitable for multiple target segmentation in ophthalmology multi-modal images, named Learnable Ophthalmology Segment Anything (SAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-ophthalmology-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAL: Simultaneous Label Hierarchy Exploration And Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-simultaneous-label-hierarchy-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Label hierarchy is an important source of external knowledge that can enhance classification performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-simultaneous-label-hierarchy-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HausaNLP at SemEval-2023 Task 12: Leveraging African Low Resource TweetData for Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hausanlp-at-semeval-2023-task-12-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the findings of SemEval-2023 Task 12, a shared task on sentiment analysis for low-resource African languages using Twitter dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hausanlp-at-semeval-2023-task-12-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reformulating CTR Prediction: Learning Invariant Feature Interactions for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reformulating-ctr-prediction-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, such a manner inevitably learns unstable feature interactions, i. e., the ones that exhibit strong correlations in historical data but generalize poorly for future serving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reformulating-ctr-prediction-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game-based Platforms for Artificial Intelligence Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-based-platforms-for-artificial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Games have been the perfect test-beds for artificial intelligence research for the characteristics that widely exist in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game-based-platforms-for-artificial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Association to Generation: Text-only Captioning by Unsupervised Cross-modal Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-association-to-generation-text-only</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although previous works have created generation capacity for CLIP through additional language models, a modality gap between the CLIP representations of different modalities and the inability of CLIP to model the offset of this gap, which fails the concept to transfer across modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-association-to-generation-text-only</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable and low-precision training for large-scale vision-language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-and-low-precision-training-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce new methods for 1) accelerating and 2) stabilizing training for large language-vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-and-low-precision-training-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering the Representation of Spiking Neural Networks Trained with Surrogate Gradient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-representation-of-spiking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, some essential questions exist pertaining to SNNs that are little studied: Do SNNs trained with surrogate gradient learn different representations from traditional Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs)?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-representation-of-spiking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive definite nonparametric regression using an evolutionary algorithm with application to covariance function estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-definite-nonparametric-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also extend our method to estimate covariance functions for point-referenced data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-definite-nonparametric-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Datasets and Market Environments for Financial Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-datasets-and-market-environments-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The financial market is a particularly challenging playground for deep reinforcement learning due to its unique feature of dynamic datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-datasets-and-market-environments-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing MBIB -- the first Media Bias Identification Benchmark Task and Dataset Collection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-mbib-the-first-media-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A unified benchmark encourages the development of more robust systems and shifts the current paradigm in media bias detection evaluation towards solutions that tackle not one but multiple media bias types simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-mbib-the-first-media-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Privacy via Distributionally Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-privacy-via-distributionally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the problem affords a strong dual, and we exploit this duality to develop converging hierarchies of finite-dimensional upper and lower bounding problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-privacy-via-distributionally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixNeRF: Memory Efficient NeRF with Feature Mixed-up Hash Table</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixnerf-memory-efficient-nerf-with-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural radiance field (NeRF) has shown remarkable performance in generating photo-realistic novel views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixnerf-memory-efficient-nerf-with-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Attention Transfer Based Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-attention-transfer-based-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous knowledge distillation methods have shown their impressive performance on model compression tasks, however, it is hard to explain how the knowledge they transferred helps to improve the performance of the student network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-attention-transfer-based-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proto-Value Networks: Scaling Representation Learning with Auxiliary Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proto-value-networks-scaling-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combined with a suitable off-policy learning rule, the result is a representation learning algorithm that can be understood as extending Mahadevan & Maggioni (2007)'s proto-value functions to deep reinforcement learning -- accordingly, we call the resulting object proto-value networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proto-value-networks-scaling-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaNPC: Exploring Non-Parametric Classifier for Test-Time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adanpc-exploring-non-parametric-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, when the adaptation target is a series of domains, the adaptation accuracy of AdaNPC is 50% higher than advanced TTA methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adanpc-exploring-non-parametric-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THUIR at WSDM Cup 2023 Task 1: Unbiased Learning to Rank</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-at-wsdm-cup-2023-task-1-unbiased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the approaches we have used to participate in the WSDM Cup 2023 Task 1: Unbiased Learning to Rank.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thuir-at-wsdm-cup-2023-task-1-unbiased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent Induction from Conversations for Task-Oriented Dialogue Track at DSTC 11</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-induction-from-conversations-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With increasing demand for and adoption of virtual assistants, recent work has investigated ways to accelerate bot schema design through the automatic induction of intents or the induction of slots and dialogue states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-induction-from-conversations-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iMixer: hierarchical Hopfield network implies an invertible, implicit and iterative MLP-Mixer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imixer-hierarchical-hopfield-network-implies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we generalize the correspondence to the recently introduced hierarchical Hopfield network, and find iMixer, a novel generalization of MLP-Mixer model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imixer-hierarchical-hopfield-network-implies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change detection needs change information: improving deep 3D point cloud change detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-detection-needs-change-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, the last network, entitled Encoder Fusion SiamKPConv, overtakes SoTA with more than 5% of mean of IoU over classes of change emphasizing the value of having the network focus on change information for change detection task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-detection-needs-change-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of Segment Anything Model for Civil Infrastructure Defect Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In conclusion, the SAM and U-Net model presented in this study offer promising solutions for detecting cracks in concrete structures and leveraging the strengths of both models that can lead to more accurate and comprehensive results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morphological Classification of Extragalactic Radio Sources Using Gradient Boosting Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphological-classification-of-extragalactic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent contributions in the field of morphological classification of extragalactic radio sources have proposed classifiers based on convolutional neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphological-classification-of-extragalactic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-assisted coding: Experiments with GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-assisted-coding-experiments-with-gpt-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We report several experiments using GPT-4 to generate computer code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-assisted-coding-experiments-with-gpt-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Massive Multitask Chinese Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-massive-multitask-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This test encompasses four major domains, including medicine, law, psychology, and education, with 15 subtasks in medicine and 8 subtasks in education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-massive-multitask-chinese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MG-ShopDial: A Multi-Goal Conversational Dataset for e-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-shopdial-a-multi-goal-conversational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce MG-ShopDial: a dataset of conversations mixing different goals in the domain of e-commerce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mg-shopdial-a-multi-goal-conversational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-Supervised Temporal Action Localization with Bidirectional Semantic Consistency Constraint</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-temporal-action-7</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed Bi-SCC firstly adopts a temporal context augmentation to generate an augmented video that breaks the correlation between positive actions and their co-scene actions in the inter-video; Then, a semantic consistency constraint (SCC) is used to enforce the predictions of the original video and augmented video to be consistent, hence suppressing the co-scene actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-temporal-action-7</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximal Curriculum for Reinforcement Learning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-curriculum-for-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of curriculum design for reinforcement learning (RL) agents in contextual multi-task settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-curriculum-for-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Pillar-based Re-ranking for Image-Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-pillar-based-re-ranking-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-text retrieval aims to bridge the modality gap and retrieve cross-modal content based on semantic similarities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-pillar-based-re-ranking-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel Spiking Neurons with High Efficiency and Long-term Dependencies Learning Ability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-spiking-neurons-with-high-efficiency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vanilla spiking neurons in Spiking Neural Networks (SNNs) use charge-fire-reset neuronal dynamics, which can only be simulated in serial and can hardly learn long-time dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-spiking-neurons-with-high-efficiency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMUPoser: Full-Body Pose Estimation using IMUs in Phones, Watches, and Earbuds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imuposer-full-body-pose-estimation-using-imus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking body pose on-the-go could have powerful uses in fitness, mobile gaming, context-aware virtual assistants, and rehabilitation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imuposer-full-body-pose-estimation-using-imus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>(Local) Differential Privacy has NO Disparate Impact on Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-differential-privacy-has-no-disparate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as the collection of multiple sensitive information becomes more prevalent across various industries, collecting a single sensitive attribute under LDP may not be sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-differential-privacy-has-no-disparate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flickr-PAD: New Face High-Resolution Presentation Attack Detection Database</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flickr-pad-new-face-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This will help researchers to compare new approaches to existing algorithms on a wider database.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flickr-pad-new-face-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DQS3D: Densely-matched Quantization-aware Semi-supervised 3D Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dqs3d-densely-matched-quantization-aware-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While this paradigm is natural for image-level or pixel-level prediction, adapting it to the detection problem is challenged by the issue of proposal matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dqs3d-densely-matched-quantization-aware-semi</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
