<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 09:15:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SepsisLab: Early Sepsis Prediction with Uncertainty Quantification and Active Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sepsislab-early-sepsis-prediction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinicians and potential sepsis patients can benefit from the system in early prediction and diagnosis of sepsis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sepsislab-early-sepsis-prediction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Tensor PCA via Tensor Decomposition for Unsupervised Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-tensor-pca-via-tensor-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, introducing Tensor Decomposition (TD) methods into unsupervised feature selection (UFS) has been a rising research point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-tensor-pca-via-tensor-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Negative Mining For Temporal Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-negative-mining-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When compared with static networks, temporal networks present two specific challenges for negative sampling: positive sparsity and positive shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-negative-mining-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dlordinal: a Python package for deep ordinal classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlordinal-a-python-package-for-deep-ordinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[dlordinal is a new Python library that unifies many recent deep ordinal classification methodologies available in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlordinal-a-python-package-for-deep-ordinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalify: scale propagation for efficient low-precision LLM training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalify-scale-propagation-for-efficient-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-precision formats such as float8 have been introduced in machine learning accelerated hardware to improve computational efficiency for large language models training and inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalify-scale-propagation-for-efficient-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Vision-Language Subspace Projection for Few-shot CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-vision-language-subspace-projection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language models such as CLIP are capable of mapping the different modality data into a unified feature space, enabling zero/few-shot inference by measuring the similarity of given images and texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-vision-language-subspace-projection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Aligning Language Models with Textual Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-aligning-language-models-with-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ALT (ALignment with Textual feedback), an approach that aligns language models with user preferences expressed in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-aligning-language-models-with-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding-Free Transformer with Inference Spatial Reduction for Efficient Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-free-transformer-with-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the decoder, we explore the optimized structure for considering the globality, which can improve the semantic segmentation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/embedding-free-transformer-with-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nerva: a Truly Sparse Implementation of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerva-a-truly-sparse-implementation-of-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Nerva, a fast neural network library under development in C++.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerva-a-truly-sparse-implementation-of-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intent-Guided Heterogeneous Graph Contrastive Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-guided-heterogeneous-graph-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Learning (CL)-based recommender systems have gained prominence in the context of Heterogeneous Graph (HG) due to their capacity to enhance the consistency of representations across different views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intent-guided-heterogeneous-graph-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Based Ensemble Learning For Speech Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-based-ensemble-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The visualization of the effect of uncertainty and its ensemble learning results show potential improvements in speech classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-based-ensemble-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforced Prompt Personalization for Recommendation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-prompt-personalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate the superiority of RPP/RPP+ over traditional recommender models, few-shot methods, and other prompt-based methods, underscoring the significance of instance-wise prompting for LLMs in recommendation tasks and validating the effectiveness of RPP/RPP+.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforced-prompt-personalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Environmental Monitoring through Multispectral Imaging: The WasteMS Dataset for Semantic Segmentation of Lakeside Waste</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-environmental-monitoring-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces WasteMS, the first multispectral dataset established for the semantic segmentation of lakeside waste.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-environmental-monitoring-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Could've Asked That: Reformulating Unanswerable Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-could-ve-asked-that-reformulating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We curate CouldAsk, an evaluation benchmark composed of existing and new datasets for document-grounded question answering, specifically designed to study reformulating unanswerable questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-could-ve-asked-that-reformulating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Variance-Reduced Iterative Hard Thresholding in Graph Sparsity Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-variance-reduced-iterative-hard</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic optimization algorithms are widely used for large-scale data analysis due to their low per-iteration costs, but they often suffer from slow asymptotic convergence caused by inherent variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-variance-reduced-iterative-hard</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raindrop Clarity: A Dual-Focused Dataset for Day and Night Raindrop Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raindrop-clarity-a-dual-focused-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are 5, 442 daytime raindrop images and 9, 744 nighttime raindrop images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raindrop-clarity-a-dual-focused-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Feature Learning via Regularisation: Integrating Neural Networks and Kernel Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-feature-learning-via-regularisation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new method for feature learning and function estimation in supervised learning via regularised empirical risk minimisation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-feature-learning-via-regularisation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RT-DETRv2: Improved Baseline with Bag-of-Freebies for Real-Time Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-detrv2-improved-baseline-with-bag-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RT-DETRv2 builds upon the previous state-of-the-art real-time detector, RT-DETR, and opens up a set of bag-of-freebies for flexibility and practicality, as well as optimizing the training strategy to achieve enhanced performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rt-detrv2-improved-baseline-with-bag-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-aware Multi-task Learning for Pedestrian Intent and Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-multi-task-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effectiveness of PTINet in predicting pedestrian behavior paves the way for the development of automated systems capable of seamlessly interacting with pedestrians in urban settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-multi-task-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden or Inferred: Fair Learning-To-Rank with Unknown Demographics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-or-inferred-fair-learning-to-rank-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine a spectrum of fair LTR strategies ranging from fair LTR with and without demographic features hidden versus inferred to fairness-unaware LTR followed by fair re-ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-or-inferred-fair-learning-to-rank-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Query Refinement Framework for Bird's-Eye-View Semantic Segmentation from Surrounding Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-query-refinement-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During training, we enforce both the lowest and final query maps to align with the ground-truth BEV semantic map to help our model effectively capture the global and local characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-query-refinement-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dependency Transformer Grammars: Integrating Dependency Structures into Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dependency-transformer-grammars-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Syntactic Transformer language models aim to achieve better generalization through simultaneously modeling syntax trees and sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dependency-transformer-grammars-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M4: Multi-Proxy Multi-Gate Mixture of Experts Network for Multiple Instance Learning in Histopathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4-multi-proxy-multi-gate-mixture-of-experts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple instance learning (MIL) has been successfully applied for whole slide images (WSIs) analysis in computational pathology, enabling a wide range of prediction tasks from tumor subtyping to inferring genetic mutations and multi-omics biomarkers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m4-multi-proxy-multi-gate-mixture-of-experts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channel-Aware Low-Rank Adaptation in Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-low-rank-adaptation-in-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The former adopts individual channel treatment and has been shown to be more robust to distribution shifts, but lacks sufficient capacity to model meaningful channel interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/channel-aware-low-rank-adaptation-in-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take a Step and Reconsider: Sequence Decoding for Self-Improved Neural Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-step-and-reconsider-sequence-decoding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The constructive approach within Neural Combinatorial Optimization (NCO) treats a combinatorial optimization problem as a finite Markov decision process, where solutions are built incrementally through a sequence of decisions guided by a neural policy network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-step-and-reconsider-sequence-decoding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Knowledge Tracing Models via k-Sparse Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-knowledge-tracing-models-via-k</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that our \textsc{sparseKT} is able to help attentional KT models get rid of irrelevant student interactions and have comparable predictive performance when compared to 11 state-of-the-art KT models on three publicly available real-world educational datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-knowledge-tracing-models-via-k</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low dimensional representation of multi-patient flow cytometry datasets using optimal transport for minimal residual disease detection in leukemia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-dimensional-representation-of-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore statistical learning methods based on optimal transport (OT) to achieve a relevant low-dimensional representation of multi-patient flow cytometry measurements (FCM) datasets considered as high-dimensional probability distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-dimensional-representation-of-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrevPredMap: Exploring Temporal Modeling with Previous Predictions for Online Vectorized HD Map Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prevpredmap-exploring-temporal-modeling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the previous-predictions-based query generator is designed to separately encode different types of information from previous predictions, which are then effectively utilized by the dynamic-position-query decoder to generate current predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prevpredmap-exploring-temporal-modeling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoFormer: Local Frequency Transformer for Image Deblurring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loformer-local-frequency-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the computational complexity of self-attention (SA), prevalent techniques for image deblurring often resort to either adopting localized SA or employing coarse-grained global SA methods, both of which exhibit drawbacks such as compromising global modeling or lacking fine-grained correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loformer-local-frequency-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Gaussian Splatting: Survey, Technologies, Challenges, and Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-gaussian-splatting-survey-technologies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has emerged as a prominent technique with the potential to become a mainstream method for 3D representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-gaussian-splatting-survey-technologies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Spherical Superpixels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spherical-superpixels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the years, the use of superpixel segmentation has become very popular in various applications, serving as a preprocessing step to reduce data size by adapting to the content of the image, regardless of its semantic content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-spherical-superpixels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Who's Harry Potter: Towards Targeted Unlearning from a Causal Intervention Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-who-s-harry-potter-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates Who's Harry Potter (WHP), a pioneering yet insufficiently understood method for LLM unlearning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-who-s-harry-potter-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVPE: Divided View Position Embedding for Multi-View 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvpe-divided-view-position-embedding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse query-based paradigms have achieved significant success in multi-view 3D detection for autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvpe-divided-view-position-embedding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanVid: Demystifying Training Data for Camera-controllable Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanvid-demystifying-training-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, these approaches prioritize 2D human motion and overlook the significance of camera motions in videos, leading to limited control and unstable video generation. To demystify the training data, we present HumanVid, the first large-scale high-quality dataset tailored for human image animation, which combines crafted real-world and synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanvid-demystifying-training-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generation of Training Data from HD Maps in the Lanelet2 Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generation-of-training-data-from-hd-maps-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this addition Lanelet2 unifies map based automated driving, machine learning inference and training, all from a single source of map data and format.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generation-of-training-data-from-hd-maps-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Trajectory Generation Through Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-trajectory-generation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a Reversible Trajectory-to-CNN Transformation (RTCT) that adapts trajectories into a format suitable for CNN-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-trajectory-generation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks: A suitable Alternative to MLPs in Latent 3D Medical Image Classification?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-a-suitable-alternative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as graph neural networks (GNNs) have become a practicable choice for various tasks in medical research in the recent past, we direct attention to the question of how effective GNNs are compared to MLP prediction heads for the task of 3D medical image classification, proposing them as a potential alternative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-a-suitable-alternative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAN or MLP: A Fairer Comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-or-mlp-a-fairer-comparison</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper does not introduce a novel method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kan-or-mlp-a-fairer-comparison</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Matters in Range View 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-matters-in-range-view-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining the above findings, we establish a new state-of-the-art model for range-view 3D object detection -- improving AP by 2. 2% on the Waymo Open dataset while maintaining a runtime of 10 Hz.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-matters-in-range-view-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOAP: Enhancing Spatio-Temporal Relation and Motion Information Capturing for Few-Shot Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-enhancing-spatio-temporal-relation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High frame-rate (HFR) videos of action recognition improve fine-grained expression while reducing the spatio-temporal relation and motion information density.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soap-enhancing-spatio-temporal-relation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hi-EF: Benchmarking Emotion Forecasting in Human-interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi-ef-benchmarking-emotion-forecasting-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Emotion Forecasting (EF) task grounded in the theory that an individuals emotions are easily influenced by the emotions or other information conveyed during interactions with another person.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hi-ef-benchmarking-emotion-forecasting-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCNR: Fast Compressive Neural Representation of Visualization Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcnr-fast-compressive-neural-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present FCNR, a fast compressive neural representation for tens of thousands of visualization images under varying viewpoints and timesteps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcnr-fast-compressive-neural-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Utility of Speech and Audio Foundation Models for Marmoset Call Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-utility-of-speech-and-audio-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Marmoset monkeys encode vital information in their calls and serve as a surrogate model for neuro-biologists to understand the evolutionary origins of human vocal communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-utility-of-speech-and-audio-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Separable Translation Network for Multimodal Image Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-separable-translation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, a novel unsupervised cross-domain separable translation network (CSTN) is proposed, which uniquely integrates a within-domain self-reconstruction and a cross-domain image translation and cycle-reconstruction workflow with change detection constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-separable-translation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINDER: Repairing the Singular Defects of DINOv2</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinder-repairing-the-singular-defects-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformer models trained on large-scale datasets, although effective, often exhibit artifacts in the patch token they extract.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinder-repairing-the-singular-defects-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrimeGuard: Safe and Helpful LLMs through Tuning-Free Routing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primeguard-safe-and-helpful-llms-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose PrimeGuard, a novel ITG method that utilizes structured control flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primeguard-safe-and-helpful-llms-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pareto Front Approximation for Multi-Objective Session-Based Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pareto-front-approximation-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces MultiTRON, an approach that adapts Pareto front approximation techniques to multi-objective session-based recommender systems using a transformer neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pareto-front-approximation-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deeper look at depth pruning of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deeper-look-at-depth-pruning-of-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are not only resource-intensive to train but even more costly to deploy in production.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deeper-look-at-depth-pruning-of-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coarse-to-Fine Proposal Refinement Framework for Audio Temporal Forgery Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-proposal-refinement-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, a novel form of audio partial forgery has posed challenges to its forensics, requiring advanced countermeasures to detect subtle forgery manipulations within long-duration audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coarse-to-fine-proposal-refinement-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-Aware Robust Learning from Long-Tailed Data with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-robust-learning-from-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of these methods is limited because they use only the training samples within each class for class centroid estimation, making the quality of centroids susceptible to long-tailed distributions and noisy labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-robust-learning-from-long</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
