<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2023 21:06:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brightfield vs Fluorescent Staining Dataset–A Test Bed Image Set for Machine Learning based Virtual Staining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brightfield-vs-fluorescent-staining-dataset-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differential fluorescent staining is an effective tool widely adopted for the visualization, segmentation and quantification of cells and cellular substructures as a part of standard microscopic imaging protocols.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brightfield-vs-fluorescent-staining-dataset-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>360BEV: Panoramic Semantic Mapping for Indoor Bird's-Eye View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/360bev-panoramic-semantic-mapping-for-indoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, mapping from 360{\deg} panoramas to BEV semantics, the 360BEV task, is established for the first time to achieve holistic representations of indoor scenes in a top-down view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/360bev-panoramic-semantic-mapping-for-indoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language-Assisted Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-assisted-sign-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sign languages are visual languages which convey information by signers' handshape, facial expression, body movement, and so forth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-assisted-sign-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Healthcare Embeddings for Improving Patient Care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-healthcare-embeddings-for-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose DECENT, an auto-encoding heterogeneous co-evolving dynamic neural network, for learning heterogeneous dynamic embeddings of patients, doctors, rooms, and medications from diverse data streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-healthcare-embeddings-for-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indeterminate Probability Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indeterminate-probability-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, for our proposed neural network framework, the output of neural network is defined as probability events, and based on the statistical analysis of these events, the inference model for classification task is deduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indeterminate-probability-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tale of Two Circuits: Grokking as Competition of Sparse and Dense Subnetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-circuits-grokking-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grokking is a phenomenon where a model trained on an algorithmic task first overfits but, then, after a large amount of additional training, undergoes a phase transition to generalize perfectly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tale-of-two-circuits-grokking-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wearing Masks Implies Refuting Trump?: Towards Target-specific User Stance Prediction across Events in COVID-19 and US Election 2020</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearing-masks-implies-refuting-trump-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People who share similar opinions towards controversial topics could form an echo chamber and may share similar political views toward other topics as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wearing-masks-implies-refuting-trump-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDLens: Model Hijacking-resilient Federated Learning for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stdlens-model-hijacking-resilient-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the insights, we introduce a three-tier forensic framework to identify and expel Trojaned gradients and reclaim the performance over the course of FL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stdlens-model-hijacking-resilient-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRCoN-LO: Long-term Recurrent Convolutional Network-based LiDAR Odometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorcon-lo-long-term-recurrent-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a deep learning-based LiDAR odometry estimation method called LoRCoN-LO that utilizes the long-term recurrent convolutional network (LRCN) structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lorcon-lo-long-term-recurrent-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Understanding Differences in Attribution Methods via Systematic Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-understanding-differences-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose a post-processing smoothing step that significantly improves the performance of some attribution methods, and discuss its applicability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-understanding-differences-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstract Visual Reasoning: An Algebraic Approach for Solving Raven's Progressive Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstract-visual-reasoning-an-algebraic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce algebraic machine reasoning, a new reasoning framework that is well-suited for abstract reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstract-visual-reasoning-an-algebraic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Neural Representation for Cooperative Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, extensive experiments demonstrate the robustness and superior effectiveness of our proposed NeRCo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix the Noise: Disentangling Source Feature for Controllable Domain Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fix-the-noise-disentangling-source-feature-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This allows our method to smoothly control the degree to which it preserves source features while generating images from an entirely new domain using only a single model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fix-the-noise-disentangling-source-feature-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Treasure Beneath Multiple Annotations: An Uncertainty-aware Edge Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-treasure-beneath-multiple-annotations-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning-based edge detectors heavily rely on pixel-wise labels which are often provided by multiple annotators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-treasure-beneath-multiple-annotations-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Alignment of Vision to Language Through Parameter-Efficient Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-alignment-of-vision-to-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that a minimal set of parameter updates ($<$7%) can achieve the same performance as full-model training, and updating specific components ($<$1% of parameters) can match 75% of full-model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-alignment-of-vision-to-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning a 3D Morphable Face Reflectance Model from Low-cost Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-3d-morphable-face-reflectance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes the first 3D morphable face reflectance model with spatially varying BRDF using only low-cost publicly-available data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-3d-morphable-face-reflectance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpikeCV: Open a Continuous Computer Vision Era</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikecv-open-a-continuous-computer-vision-era</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SpikeCV focuses on encapsulation for spike data, standardization for dataset interfaces, modularization for vision tasks, and real-time applications for challenging scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikecv-open-a-continuous-computer-vision-era</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local convergence of multi-agent systems towards triangular patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-convergence-of-multi-agent-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Geometric pattern formation is an important emergent behavior in many applications involving large-scale multi-agent systems, such as sensor networks deployment and collective transportation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-convergence-of-multi-agent-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-Based 3D Human Pose Estimation with Multi-Hypothesis Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-3d-human-pose-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, JPMA is proposed to assemble multiple hypotheses generated by D3DP into a single 3D pose for practical use.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-based-3d-human-pose-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-efficient Large Scale Place Recognition with Graded Similarity Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-large-scale-place-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the fact that two images of the same place only partially share visual cues due to camera pose differences, we deploy an automatic re-annotation strategy to re-label VPR datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-large-scale-place-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are uGLAD? Time will tell!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-uglad-time-will-tell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation of multivariate time series data is a technique for identifying meaningful patterns or changes in the time series that can signal a shift in the system's behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-uglad-time-will-tell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiased Contrastive Learning for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-contrastive-learning-for-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This solution is designed to tackle the popularity bias issue in recommendation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiased-contrastive-learning-for-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Optimization for Function Compositions with Applications to Dynamic Pricing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-for-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bayesian Optimization (BO) is used to find the global optima of black box functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-optimization-for-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamically Expandable Graph Convolution for Streaming Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamically-expandable-graph-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized recommender systems have been widely studied and deployed to reduce information overload and satisfy users' diverse needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamically-expandable-graph-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficulty in learning chirality for Transformer fed with SMILES</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-in-learning-chirality-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen development of descriptor generation based on representation learning of extremely diverse molecules, especially those that apply natural language processing (NLP) models to SMILES, a literal representation of molecular structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-in-learning-chirality-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcriptomics-based matching of drugs to diseases with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcriptomics-based-matching-of-drugs-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we present a deep learning approach to conduct hypothesis-free, transcriptomics-based matching of drugs for diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transcriptomics-based-matching-of-drugs-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT-Seg: Cost Aggregation for Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-seg-cost-aggregation-for-open-vocabulary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the problem of transferring these capabilities learned from image-level supervision to the pixel-level task of segmentation and addressing arbitrary unseen categories at inference makes this task challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-seg-cost-aggregation-for-open-vocabulary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVCNet: Scribble-based Video Colorization Network with Temporal Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svcnet-scribble-based-video-colorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It addresses three common issues in the scribble-based video colorization area: colorization vividness, temporal consistency, and color bleeding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svcnet-scribble-based-video-colorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubly Regularized Entropic Wasserstein Barycenters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-regularized-entropic-wasserstein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, it can be estimated efficiently: given $n$ samples from each of the probability measures, it converges in relative entropy to the population barycenter at a rate $n^{-1/2}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doubly-regularized-entropic-wasserstein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSTFormer: Motion Inspired Spatial-temporal Transformer with Dynamic-aware Attention for long-term Vessel Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mstformer-motion-inspired-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Against this background, we propose MSTFormer, a motion inspired vessel trajectory prediction method based on Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mstformer-motion-inspired-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessor-Guided Learning for Continual Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessor-guided-learning-for-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an assessor-guided learning strategy for continual learning where an assessor guides the learning process of a base learner by controlling the direction and pace of the learning process thus allowing an efficient learning of new environments while protecting against the catastrophic interference problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessor-guided-learning-for-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manipulating Transfer Learning for Property Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-transfer-learning-for-property</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate attacks in which an adversary can manipulate the upstream model to conduct highly effective and specific property inference attacks (AUC score $> 0. 9$), without incurring significant performance loss on the main task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manipulating-transfer-learning-for-property</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALOFT: A Lightweight MLP-like Architecture with Dynamic Low-frequency Transform for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloft-a-lightweight-mlp-like-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the local operation of the convolution kernel makes the model focus too much on local representations (e. g., texture), which inherently causes the model more prone to overfit to the source domains and hampers its generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aloft-a-lightweight-mlp-like-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-complexity Deep Video Compression with A Distributed Coding Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-complexity-deep-video-compression-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prevalent predictive coding-based video compression methods rely on a heavy encoder to reduce the temporal redundancy, which makes it challenging to deploy them on resource-constrained devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-complexity-deep-video-compression-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIFA: Accurate and Interpretable Text-to-Image Faithfulness Evaluation with Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tifa-accurate-and-interpretable-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce TIFA (Text-to-Image Faithfulness evaluation with question Answering), an automatic evaluation metric that measures the faithfulness of a generated image to its text input via visual question answering (VQA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tifa-accurate-and-interpretable-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-MLB: Multilevel Benchmark for Event-Based Camera Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-mlb-multilevel-benchmark-for-event-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event cameras, such as dynamic vision sensors (DVS), are biologically inspired vision sensors that have advanced over conventional cameras in high dynamic range, low latency and low power consumption, showing great application potential in many fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-mlb-multilevel-benchmark-for-event-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart-Tree: Neural Medial Axis Approximation of Point Clouds for 3D Tree Skeletonization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-tree-neural-medial-axis-approximation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train and test the method using a multi-species synthetic tree data set and perform qualitative analysis on a real-life tree point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-tree-neural-medial-axis-approximation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting the open-world objects with the help of the Brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-the-open-world-objects-with-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose leveraging the VL as the ``Brain'' of the open-world detector by simply generating unknown labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-the-open-world-objects-with-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Context-aware Classifier for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-context-aware-classifier-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation is still a challenging task for parsing diverse contexts in different scenes, thus the fixed classifier might not be able to well address varying feature distributions during testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-context-aware-classifier-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Object-Centric Temporal Modeling for Efficient Multi-View 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-object-centric-temporal-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a long-sequence modeling framework, named StreamPETR, for multi-view 3D object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-object-centric-temporal-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Multiscale Surface Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-multiscale-surface-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surface meshes are a favoured domain for representing structural and functional information on the human cortex, but their complex topology and geometry pose significant challenges for deep learning analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-multiscale-surface-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused and Collaborative Feedback Integration for Interactive Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-and-collaborative-feedback</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interactive image segmentation aims at obtaining a segmentation mask for an image using simple user annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-and-collaborative-feedback</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Verified Training for Robust Image Classifications via Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-verified-training-for-robust-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Via abstraction, all perturbed images are mapped into intervals before feeding into neural networks for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-verified-training-for-robust-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Room: Extracting Textured 3D Meshes from 2D Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2room-extracting-textured-3d-meshes-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Text2Room, a method for generating room-scale textured 3D meshes from a given text prompt as input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2room-extracting-textured-3d-meshes-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel Class Discovery for 3D Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-class-discovery-for-3d-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we address the new problem of NCD for point cloud semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-class-discovery-for-3d-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance-aware Approximation of Global Channel Pruning for Multitask CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-aware-approximation-of-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Global channel pruning (GCP) aims to remove a subset of channels (filters) across different layers from a deep model without hurting the performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-aware-approximation-of-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAFS: Class Adaptive Framework for Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cafs-class-adaptive-framework-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike existing semi-supervised semantic segmentation frameworks, CAFS constructs a validation set on a labeled dataset, to leverage the calibration performance for each class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cafs-class-adaptive-framework-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning A Sparse Transformer Network for Effective Image Deraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-sparse-transformer-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome this problem, we propose an effective DeRaining network, Sparse Transformer (DRSformer) that can adaptively keep the most useful self-attention values for feature aggregation so that the aggregated features better facilitate high-quality image reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-a-sparse-transformer-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIFT: Sparse Iso-FLOP Transformations for Maximizing Training Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sift-sparse-iso-flop-transformations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These works aim to reduce training FLOPs but training with sparse weights often leads to accuracy loss or requires longer train schedules, making the resulting training efficiency less clear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sift-sparse-iso-flop-transformations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equiangular Basis Vectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equiangular-basis-vectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The learning objective of these methods can be summarized as mapping the learned feature representations to the samples' label space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equiangular-basis-vectors</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
