<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 09:12:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Catheterization with Open-source Simulator and Expert Trajectory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-catheterization-with-open-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endovascular robots have been actively developed in both academia and industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autonomous-catheterization-with-open-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous Local-SGD Training for Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-local-sgd-training-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local stochastic gradient descent (Local-SGD), also referred to as federated averaging, is an approach to distributed optimization where each device performs more than one SGD update per communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-local-sgd-training-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To deform or not: treatment-aware longitudinal registration for breast DCE-MRI during neoadjuvant chemotherapy via unsupervised keypoints detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-deform-or-not-treatment-aware-longitudinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a clinical dataset with 1630 MRI scans from 314 patients treated with NAC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-deform-or-not-treatment-aware-longitudinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explain Thyself Bully: Sentiment Aided Cyberbullying Detection with Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-thyself-bully-sentiment-aided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While plenty of research is going on to develop better models for cyberbullying detection in monolingual language, there is very little research on the code-mixed languages and explainability aspect of cyberbullying.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explain-thyself-bully-sentiment-aided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Objects With Lighting: A Real-World Dataset for Evaluating Reconstruction and Rendering for Object Relighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objects-with-lighting-a-real-world-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing an object from photos and placing it virtually in a new environment goes beyond the standard novel view synthesis task as the appearance of the object has to not only adapt to the novel viewpoint but also to the new lighting conditions and yet evaluations of inverse rendering methods rely on novel view synthesis data or simplistic synthetic datasets for quantitative analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/objects-with-lighting-a-real-world-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-lingual Offensive Language Detection: A Systematic Review of Datasets, Transfer Approaches and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-offensive-language-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey presents a systematic and comprehensive exploration of Cross-Lingual Transfer Learning (CLTL) techniques in offensive language detection in social media.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-offensive-language-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Sensing ChatGPT: Solving Remote Sensing Tasks with ChatGPT and Visual Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-chatgpt-solving-remote-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the flourishing large language models(LLM), especially ChatGPT, have shown exceptional performance in language understanding, reasoning, and interaction, attracting users and researchers from multiple fields and domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remote-sensing-chatgpt-solving-remote-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Mamba: Efficient Visual Representation Learning with Bidirectional State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-efficient-visual-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results demonstrate that Vim is capable of overcoming the computation & memory constraints on performing Transformer-style understanding for high-resolution images and it has great potential to become the next-generation backbone for vision foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-mamba-efficient-visual-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIN-SLAM: LiDAR SLAM Using a Point-Based Implicit Neural Representation for Achieving Global Map Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pin-slam-lidar-slam-using-a-point-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a SLAM system for building globally consistent maps, called PIN-SLAM, that is based on an elastic and compact point-based implicit neural map representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pin-slam-lidar-slam-using-a-point-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idempotence and Perceptual Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idempotence-and-perceptual-image-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we find that theoretically: 1) Conditional generative model-based perceptual codec satisfies idempotence; 2) Unconditional generative model with idempotence constraint is equivalent to conditional generative codec.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idempotence-and-perceptual-image-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Multiple Domain Translation through Controlled Disentanglement in Variational Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multiple-domain-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of this latent variables is imposed to depend exclusively on the domain, while the other one must depend on the rest of the variability factors of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multiple-domain-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compose and Conquer: Diffusion-Based 3D Depth Aware Composable Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compose-and-conquer-diffusion-based-3d-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing the limitations of text as a source of accurate layout representation in text-conditional diffusion models, many works incorporate additional signals to condition certain attributes within a generated image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compose-and-conquer-diffusion-based-3d-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Emotions, Demographic Information and Implicit User Feedback in Task-Oriented Document-Grounded Dialogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-emotions-demographic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of task-oriented and document-grounded dialogue systems depends on users accepting and enjoying using them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-emotions-demographic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BENO: Boundary-embedded Neural Operators for Elliptic PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beno-boundary-embedded-neural-operators-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce Boundary-Embedded Neural Operators (BENO), a novel neural operator architecture that embeds the complex geometries and inhomogeneous boundary values into the solving of elliptic PDEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beno-boundary-embedded-neural-operators-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADCNet: a unified framework for predicting the activity of antibody-drug conjugates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adcnet-a-unified-framework-for-predicting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Antibody-drug conjugate (ADC) has revolutionized the field of cancer treatment in the era of precision medicine due to their ability to precisely target cancer cells and release highly effective drug.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adcnet-a-unified-framework-for-predicting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RWKV-TS: Beyond Traditional Recurrent Neural Network for Time Series Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rwkv-ts-beyond-traditional-recurrent-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of competitive performance, low latency, and efficient memory usage positions RWKV-TS as a promising avenue for future research in time series tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rwkv-ts-beyond-traditional-recurrent-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trapped in texture bias? A large scale comparison of deep instance segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trapped-in-texture-bias-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In summary we evaluate 68 models on 61 versions of MS COCO for a total of 4148 evaluations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trapped-in-texture-bias-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vlogger: Make Your Dream A Vlog</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlogger-make-your-dream-a-vlog</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More importantly, Vlogger can generate over 5-minute vlogs from open-world descriptions, without loss of video coherence on script and actor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlogger-make-your-dream-a-vlog</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating distribution shift in machine learning-augmented hybrid simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-distribution-shift-in-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of distribution shift generally arising in machine-learning augmented hybrid simulation, where parts of simulation algorithms are replaced by data-driven surrogates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-distribution-shift-in-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEL: A Continual Learning Model for Disease Outbreak Prediction by Leveraging Domain Adaptation via Elastic Weight Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cel-a-continual-learning-model-for-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This model aims to mitigate the catastrophic forgetting phenomenon in a domain incremental setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cel-a-continual-learning-model-for-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Piecewise-Affine Based Motion Model for Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-piecewise-affine-based-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose to model motion from the source image to the driving frame in highly-expressive diffeomorphism spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-piecewise-affine-based-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tri$^{2}$-plane: Volumetric Avatar Reconstruction with Feature Pyramid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tri-2-plane-volumetric-avatar-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed considerable achievements in facial avatar reconstruction with neural volume rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tri-2-plane-volumetric-avatar-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-Based Visual Odometry on Non-Holonomic Ground Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-visual-odometry-on-non-holonomic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the promise of superior performance under challenging conditions, event-based motion estimation remains a hard problem owing to the difficulty of extracting and tracking stable features from event streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-based-visual-odometry-on-non-holonomic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rigid Protein-Protein Docking via Equivariant Elliptic-Paraboloid Interface Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigid-protein-protein-docking-via-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study of rigid protein-protein docking plays an essential role in a variety of tasks such as drug design and protein engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rigid-protein-protein-docking-via-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging State and History Representations: Understanding Self-Predictive RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-state-and-history-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These findings culminate in a set of practical guidelines for RL practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-state-and-history-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenDPD: An Open-Source End-to-End Learning &amp; Benchmarking Framework for Wideband Power Amplifier Modeling and Digital Pre-Distortion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opendpd-an-open-source-end-to-end-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise in communication capacity, deep neural networks (DNN) for digital pre-distortion (DPD) to correct non-linearity in wideband power amplifiers (PAs) have become prominent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opendpd-an-open-source-end-to-end-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferflow: an Efficient and Highly Configurable Inference Engine for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferflow-an-efficient-and-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Inferflow, an efficient and highly configurable inference engine for large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferflow-an-efficient-and-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Registration of algebraic varieties using Riemannian optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/registration-of-algebraic-varieties-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is particularly useful when the two point clouds describe different parts of an objects (which may not even be overlapping), on the condition that the surface of the object may be well approximated by a set of polynomial equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/registration-of-algebraic-varieties-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Causal Relationship in Indefinite Data: Baseline Model and New Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-causal-relationship-in-indefinite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These highpoints make the probabilistic model capable of overcoming challenges brought by the coexistence of multi-structure data and multi-value representations and pave the way for the extension of latent confounders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-causal-relationship-in-indefinite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UV-SAM: Adapting Segment Anything Model for Urban Village Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uv-sam-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Urban villages, defined as informal residential areas in or around urban centers, are characterized by inadequate infrastructures and poor living conditions, closely related to the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs) on poverty, adequate housing, and sustainable cities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uv-sam-adapting-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forging Vision Foundation Models for Autonomous Driving: Challenges, Methodologies, and Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forging-vision-foundation-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of large foundation models, trained on extensive datasets, is revolutionizing the field of AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forging-vision-foundation-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reproducibility Study of Goldilocks: Just-Right Tuning of BERT for TAR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducibility-study-of-goldilocks-just</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this context, we show that there is no need for further pre-training if a domain-specific BERT backbone is used within the active learning pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducibility-study-of-goldilocks-just</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Test for Attention Map in Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-test-for-attention-map-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a statistical test for ViT's attentions, enabling us to use the attentions as reliable quantitative evidence indicators for ViT's decision-making with a rigorously controlled error rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-test-for-attention-map-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Resource-efficient LLM and Multimodal Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-resource-efficient-llm-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large foundation models, including large language models (LLMs), vision transformers (ViTs), diffusion, and LLM-based multimodal models, are revolutionizing the entire machine learning lifecycle, from training to deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-resource-efficient-llm-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calpric: Inclusive and Fine-grain Labeling of Privacy Policies with Crowdsourcing and Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calpric-inclusive-and-fine-grain-labeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we present Calpric , which combines automatic text selection and segmentation, active learning and the use of crowdsourced annotators to generate a large, balanced training set for privacy policies at low cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calpric-inclusive-and-fine-grain-labeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Vulnerabilities in Stable Diffusion via Targeted Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-vulnerabilities-in-stable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we formulate the problem of targeted adversarial attack on Stable Diffusion and propose a framework to generate adversarial prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-vulnerabilities-in-stable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AesBench: An Expert Benchmark for Multimodal Large Language Models on Image Aesthetics Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesbench-an-expert-benchmark-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An obvious obstacle lies in the absence of a specific benchmark to evaluate the effectiveness of MLLMs on aesthetic perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aesbench-an-expert-benchmark-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Faiss library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-faiss-library</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Faiss library is dedicated to vector similarity search, a core functionality of vector databases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-faiss-library</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-Based CNN-BiLSTM for Sleep State Classification of Spatiotemporal Wide-Field Calcium Imaging Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-cnn-bilstm-for-sleep-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparison with Existing Method: On a 3-hour WFCI recording, the CNN-BiLSTM achieved a kappa of 0. 67, comparable to a kappa of 0. 65 corresponding to the human EEG/EMG-based scoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-based-cnn-bilstm-for-sleep-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Completely Occluded and Dense Object Instance Segmentation Using Box Prompt-Based Segmentation Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completely-occluded-and-dense-object-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CFNet, a coarse-to-fine IS framework for completely occluded and dense objects, which is based on box prompt-based segmentation foundation models (BSMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/completely-occluded-and-dense-object-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2HQV: High-Quality Video Generation from Event Camera via Theory-Inspired Model-Aided Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2hqv-high-quality-video-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose \textbf{E2HQV}, a novel E2V paradigm designed to produce high-quality video frames from events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2hqv-high-quality-video-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Linear Array Pushbroom Image Restoration: A Degradation Pipeline and Jitter-Aware Restoration Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-linear-array-pushbroom-image-restoration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both the proposed JARNet and LAP image synthesis pipeline establish a foundation for addressing this intricate challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-linear-array-pushbroom-image-restoration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn What You Need in Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-what-you-need-in-personalized-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized federated learning aims to address data heterogeneity across local clients in federated learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-what-you-need-in-personalized-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KADEL: Knowledge-Aware Denoising Learning for Commit Message Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kadel-knowledge-aware-denoising-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, previous methods are trained on the entire dataset without considering the fact that a portion of commit messages adhere to good practice (i. e., good-practice commits), while the rest do not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kadel-knowledge-aware-denoising-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Denoise Distillation: Simple Stochastic Noises Induce Efficient Knowledge Transfer for Dense Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-denoise-distillation-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation is the process of transferring knowledge from a more powerful large model (teacher) to a simpler counterpart (student).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-denoise-distillation-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayes Conditional Distribution Estimation for Knowledge Distillation Based on Conditional Mutual Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayes-conditional-distribution-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve this estimate for KD, in this paper we introduce the concept of conditional mutual information (CMI) into the estimation of BCPD and propose a novel estimator called the maximum CMI (MCMI) method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayes-conditional-distribution-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Semi-Dense 6-DoF Tracking of an Event Camera in Challenging Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-semi-dense-6-dof-tracking-of-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-based localization is a cost-effective and thus attractive solution for many intelligent mobile platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-semi-dense-6-dof-tracking-of-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Inter-Layer Expert Affinity for Accelerating Mixture-of-Experts Model Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inter-layer-expert-affinity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike previous methods, our solution can be directly applied to pre-trained MoE models without any fine-tuning or accuracy degradation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inter-layer-expert-affinity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Weisfeiler-Lehman: A Quantitative Framework for GNN Expressiveness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-weisfeiler-lehman-a-quantitative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we identify a fundamental expressivity measure termed homomorphism expressivity, which quantifies the ability of GNN models to count graphs under homomorphism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-weisfeiler-lehman-a-quantitative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ModelNet-O: A Large-Scale Synthetic Dataset for Occlusion-Aware Point Cloud Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelnet-o-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experiments, we demonstrate that our PointMLS achieves state-of-the-art results on ModelNet-O and competitive results on regular datasets, and it is robust and effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelnet-o-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
