<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 09:14:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-Guided Residual U-Net with SE Connection and ASPP for Watershed-Based Cell Segmentation in Microscopy Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-residual-u-net-with-se</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel framework called RA-SE-ASPP-Net, which incorporates Residual Blocks, Attention Mechanism, Squeeze-and-Excitation connection, and Atrous Spatial Pyramid Pooling to achieve precise and robust cell segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-residual-u-net-with-se</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Disparate Benefits of Deep Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-disparate-benefits-of-deep-ensembles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we identify the per-group difference in predictive diversity of ensemble members as the potential cause of the disparate benefits effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-disparate-benefits-of-deep-ensembles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Generative Models Unveil Patterns in Medical Images Through Vision-Language Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-generative-models-unveil-patterns-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep generative models have significantly advanced medical imaging analysis by enhancing dataset size and quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-generative-models-unveil-patterns-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Function Placement in Virtual Networks: An Online Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-function-placement-in-virtual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a model for the virtual function placement problem and several novel algorithms using ideas based on multi-armed bandits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-function-placement-in-virtual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Graph Quantized Tokenizers for Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-graph-quantized-tokenizers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers serve as the backbone architectures of Foundational Models, where a domain-specific tokenizer helps them adapt to various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-graph-quantized-tokenizers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Capabilities of Masked Generative Models for Image Synthesis via Self-Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-capabilities-of-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key factor in the performance of continuous diffusion models stems from the guidance methods, which enhance the sample quality at the expense of diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-capabilities-of-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLM-Grounder: A VLM Agent for Zero-Shot 3D Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlm-grounder-a-vlm-agent-for-zero-shot-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D visual grounding is crucial for robots, requiring integration of natural language and 3D scene understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlm-grounder-a-vlm-agent-for-zero-shot-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking Inward: Language Models Can Learn About Themselves by Introspection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-inward-language-models-can-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study introspection by finetuning LLMs to predict properties of their own behavior in hypothetical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-inward-language-models-can-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preference Diffusion for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-diffusion-for-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommender systems predict personalized item rankings based on user preference distributions derived from historical behavior data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preference-diffusion-for-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>signwriting-evaluation: Effective Sign Language Evaluation via SignWriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/signwriting-evaluation-effective-sign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of automatic evaluation metrics tailored for SignWriting presents a significant obstacle in developing effective transcription and translation models for signed languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/signwriting-evaluation-effective-sign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Estimation of Partial Dependence Functions using Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-estimation-of-partial-dependence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By estimating PD functions for arbitrary feature subsets, \texttt{FastPD} can be used to extract PD-based interpretations such as SHAP, PD plots and higher order interaction effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-estimation-of-partial-dependence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Movie Gen: A Cast of Media Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/movie-gen-a-cast-of-media-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our models set a new state-of-the-art on multiple tasks: text-to-video synthesis, video personalization, video editing, video-to-audio generation, and text-to-audio generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/movie-gen-a-cast-of-media-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Use of Audio to Improve Dialogue Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-audio-to-improve-dialogue</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the significant progress of speech technologies, spoken goal-oriented dialogue systems are becoming increasingly popular.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-audio-to-improve-dialogue</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EH-MAM: Easy-to-Hard Masked Acoustic Modeling for Self-Supervised Speech Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eh-mam-easy-to-hard-masked-acoustic-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present EH-MAM (Easy-to-Hard adaptive Masked Acoustic Modeling), a novel self-supervised learning approach for speech representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eh-mam-easy-to-hard-masked-acoustic-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Prompt-leveraged Weakly Supervised Cancer Segmentation based on Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-prompt-leveraged-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the superiority of the proposed method, experimental studies are conducted on histopathological breast cancer datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-prompt-leveraged-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Me Identify: Is an LLM+VQA System All We Need to Identify Visual Concepts?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/help-me-identify-is-an-llm-vqa-system-all-we</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An ability to learn about new objects from a small amount of visual data and produce convincing linguistic justification about the presence/absence of certain concepts (that collectively compose the object) in novel scenarios is an important characteristic of human cognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/help-me-identify-is-an-llm-vqa-system-all-we</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLaMP 2: Multimodal Music Information Retrieval Across 101 Languages Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clamp-2-multimodal-music-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Challenges in managing linguistic diversity and integrating various musical modalities are faced by current music information retrieval systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clamp-2-multimodal-music-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG-DDR: Optimizing Retrieval-Augmented Generation Using Differentiable Data Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-ddr-optimizing-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments on various knowledge-intensive tasks demonstrate that DDR significantly outperforms the SFT method, particularly for LLMs with smaller-scale parameters that depend more on the retrieved knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-ddr-optimizing-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Free-Form Decision-Making Inconsistency of Language Models in Military Crisis Simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-free-form-decision-making</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that inconsistency due to semantically equivalent prompt variations can exceed response inconsistency from temperature sampling for most studied models across different levels of ablations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-free-form-decision-making</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniDrive: Towards Universal Driving Perception Across Camera Configurations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidrive-towards-universal-driving-perception</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose a virtual configuration optimization method by minimizing the expected projection error between original cameras and virtual cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidrive-towards-universal-driving-perception</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-DiffuB: A Contextualized Sequence-to-Sequence Text Diffusion Model with Meta-Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-diffub-a-contextualized-sequence-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The diffusion model, a new generative modeling paradigm, has achieved significant success in generating images, audio, video, and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-diffub-a-contextualized-sequence-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remember, Retrieve and Generate: Understanding Infinite Visual Concepts as Your Personalized Assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remember-retrieve-and-generate-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve generation quality and alignment with user-specific information, we design a pipeline for data collection and create a specialized dataset for personalized training of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remember-retrieve-and-generate-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORCHID: A Chinese Debate Corpus for Target-Independent Stance Detection and Argumentative Dialogue Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orchid-a-chinese-debate-corpus-for-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue agents have been receiving increasing attention for years, and this trend has been further boosted by the recent progress of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orchid-a-chinese-debate-corpus-for-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DepthSplat: Connecting Gaussian Splatting and Depth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthsplat-connecting-gaussian-splatting-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian splatting and single/multi-view depth estimation are typically studied in isolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depthsplat-connecting-gaussian-splatting-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusing States and Matching Scores: A New Framework for Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusing-states-and-matching-scores-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial Imitation Learning is traditionally framed as a two-player zero-sum game between a learner and an adversarially chosen cost function, and can therefore be thought of as the sequential generalization of a Generative Adversarial Network (GAN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusing-states-and-matching-scores-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ORSO: Accelerating Reward Design via Online Reward Selection and Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orso-accelerating-reward-design-via-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reward shaping is a critical component in reinforcement learning (RL), particularly for complex tasks where sparse rewards can hinder learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orso-accelerating-reward-design-via-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Pattern to Align Them All: Integrating Different Modalities to Define Multi-Modal Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-pattern-to-align-them-all-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to reason with and integrate different sensory inputs is the foundation underpinning human intelligence and it is the reason for the growing interest in modelling multi-modal information within Knowledge Graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-pattern-to-align-them-all-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActionCOMET: A Zero-shot Approach to Learn Image-specific Commonsense Concepts about Actions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actioncomet-a-zero-shot-approach-to-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present baseline results of ActionCOMET over the collected dataset and compare them with the performance of the best existing VQA approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actioncomet-a-zero-shot-approach-to-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cliqueformer: Model-Based Optimization with Structured Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliqueformer-model-based-optimization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expressive large-scale neural networks enable training powerful models for prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliqueformer-model-based-optimization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Bias in Vision Language Models: Signposts, Pitfalls, and the Road Ahead</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-bias-in-vision-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Vision Language Models (VLMs) gain widespread use, their fairness remains under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-bias-in-vision-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aiXcoder-7B: A Lightweight and Effective Large Language Model for Code Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aixcoder-7b-a-lightweight-and-effective-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a lightweight and effective LLM for code completion named aiXcoder-7B.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aixcoder-7b-a-lightweight-and-effective-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PUMA: Empowering Unified MLLM with Multi-granular Visual Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-empowering-unified-mllm-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work represents a significant step towards a truly unified MLLM capable of adapting to the granularity demands of various visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puma-empowering-unified-mllm-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedINST: Meta Dataset of Biomedical Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medinst-meta-dataset-of-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of large language model (LLM) techniques in the field of medical analysis has brought about significant advancements, yet the scarcity of large, diverse, and well-annotated datasets remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medinst-meta-dataset-of-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniG: Modelling Unitary 3D Gaussians for View-consistent 3D Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unig-modelling-unitary-3d-gaussians-for-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present UniG, a view-consistent 3D reconstruction and novel view synthesis model that generates a high-fidelity representation of 3D Gaussians from sparse images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unig-modelling-unitary-3d-gaussians-for-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GDeR: Safeguarding Efficiency, Balancing, and Robustness via Prototypical Graph Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gder-safeguarding-efficiency-balancing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training high-quality deep models necessitates vast amounts of data, resulting in overwhelming computational and memory demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gder-safeguarding-efficiency-balancing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness-Enhancing Ensemble Classification in Water Distribution Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-enhancing-ensemble-classification-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As relevant examples such as the future criminal detection software [1] show, fairness of AI-based and social domain affecting decision support tools constitutes an important area of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-enhancing-ensemble-classification-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoLDU: Low-Rank Adaptation via Lower-Diag-Upper Decomposition for Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loldu-low-rank-adaptation-via-lower-diag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, LoRA utilize random initialization and optimization of low-rank matrices to approximate updated weights, which can result in suboptimal convergence and an accuracy gap compared to full fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loldu-low-rank-adaptation-via-lower-diag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Deep Transformer Models for Time Series Forecasting via Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-deep-transformer-models-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach complements existing analysis studies and contributes to a better understanding of transformer models in the context of time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-deep-transformer-models-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiamSeg: Self-Training with Contrastive Learning for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamseg-self-training-with-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation of remote sensing (RS) images is a challenging task with significant potential across various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siamseg-self-training-with-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Babbling to Fluency: Evaluating the Evolution of Language Models in Terms of Human Language Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-babbling-to-fluency-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, in generation tasks, LMs are more similar to human performance in areas where information is easier to extract from the corpus, such as average word length, clauses, and auxiliary verbs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-babbling-to-fluency-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAda-Net: A Self-Supervised Adaptive Stereo Estimation CNN For Remote Sensing Image Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sada-net-a-self-supervised-adaptive-stereo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stereo estimation has made many advancements in recent years with the introduction of deep-learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sada-net-a-self-supervised-adaptive-stereo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starbucks: Improved Training for 2D Matryoshka Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starbucks-improved-training-for-2d-matryoshka</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective approaches that can scale embedding model depth (i. e. layers) and embedding size allow for the creation of models that are highly scalable across different computational resources and task requirements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/starbucks-improved-training-for-2d-matryoshka</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting Temporal Graph Neural Networks with Koopman Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-temporal-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second relies on sparse identification of nonlinear dynamics (SINDy), a popular method for discovering governing equations, which we use for the first time as a general tool for explainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-temporal-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance of Gaussian Mixture Model Classifiers on Embedded Feature Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-of-gaussian-mixture-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our first contribution is to investigate GMM based classification performance taking advantage of the embedded spaces CLIP and ImageBind.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-of-gaussian-mixture-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do LLMs Have Political Correctness? Analyzing Ethical Biases and Jailbreak Vulnerabilities in AI Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-have-political-correctness-analyzing-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve into the intentional biases injected into LLMs for safety purposes and examine methods to circumvent these safety alignment techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-llms-have-political-correctness-analyzing-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red and blue language: Word choices in the Trump &amp; Harris 2024 presidential debate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-and-blue-language-word-choices-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Political debates are a peculiar type of political discourse, in which candidates directly confront one another, addressing not only the the moderator's questions, but also their opponent's statements, as well as the concerns of voters from both parties and undecided voters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-and-blue-language-word-choices-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Defenses Against Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-defenses-against-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models excel at performing inference over text to extract information, summarize information, or generate additional text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-defenses-against-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoAL: Automated Active Learning with Differentiable Query Strategy Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoal-automated-active-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AutoAL consists of two neural nets, named SearchNet and FitNet, which are optimized concurrently under a differentiable bi-level optimization framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoal-automated-active-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Auto Evaluation for Assessing Multilingual LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-auto-evaluation-for-assessing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This would enable benchmarking of general-purpose multilingual LLMs and facilitate meta-evaluation of Evaluator LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-auto-evaluation-for-assessing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Design Space of Visual Context Representation in Video MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-design-space-of-visual-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we explore the scaling effects in frame selection and token selection respectively, and fit the corresponding function curve by conducting extensive empirical experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-design-space-of-visual-context</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
