<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 21:07:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Brand Visibility in Packaging: A Deep Learning Approach for Logo Detection, Saliency-Map Prediction, and Logo Placement Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brand-visibility-in-packaging-a-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the third step, by integrating logo detection with a saliency map generation, the framework provides a comprehensive brand attention score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brand-visibility-in-packaging-a-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniCtrl: Improving the Spatiotemporal Consistency of Text-to-Video Diffusion Models via Training-Free Unified Attention Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unictrl-improving-the-spatiotemporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Diffusion Models have been developed for video generation, usually integrating text and image conditioning to enhance control over the generated content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unictrl-improving-the-spatiotemporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-RWKV: Efficient and Scalable Visual Perception with RWKV-Like Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-rwkv-efficient-and-scalable-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have revolutionized computer vision and natural language processing, but their high computational complexity limits their application in high-resolution image processing and long-context analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-rwkv-efficient-and-scalable-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Specialization: Assessing the Capabilities of MLLMs in Age and Gender Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-specialization-assessing-the-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we attempted various ways to fine-tune the ShareGPT4V model for this specific task, aiming to achieve state-of-the-art results in this particular challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-specialization-assessing-the-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AllSpark: Reborn Labeled Features from Unlabeled in Transformer for Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allspark-reborn-labeled-features-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further introduce a Semantic Memory along with a Channel Semantic Grouping strategy to ensure that unlabeled features adequately represent labeled features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allspark-reborn-labeled-features-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Specialization: Assessing the Capabilities of MLLMs in Age and Gender Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-specialization-assessing-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we attempted various ways to fine-tune the ShareGPT4V model for this specific task, aiming to achieve state-of-the-art results in this particular challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-specialization-assessing-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NusaBERT: Teaching IndoBERT to be Multilingual and Multicultural</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusabert-teaching-indobert-to-be-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Indonesia's linguistic landscape is remarkably diverse, encompassing over 700 languages and dialects, making it one of the world's most linguistically rich nations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusabert-teaching-indobert-to-be-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEE-QA: Exploring Effective and Efficient Question-Answer Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eee-qa-exploring-effective-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current approaches to question answering rely on pre-trained language models (PLMs) like RoBERTa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eee-qa-exploring-effective-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matrix Completion with Convex Optimization and Column Subset Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrix-completion-with-convex-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present two algorithms that implement our Columns Selected Matrix Completion (CSMC) method, each dedicated to a different size problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrix-completion-with-convex-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VTG-GPT: Tuning-Free Zero-Shot Video Temporal Grounding with GPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtg-gpt-tuning-free-zero-shot-video-temporal-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video temporal grounding (VTG) aims to locate specific temporal segments from an untrimmed video based on a linguistic query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtg-gpt-tuning-free-zero-shot-video-temporal-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourier-basis Functions to Bridge Augmentation Gap: Rethinking Frequency Augmentation in Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-basis-functions-to-bridge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, common visual augmentations might not guarantee extensive robustness of computer vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-basis-functions-to-bridge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Quantum Neural Network Advantage for Radar-Based Drone Detection and Classification in Low Signal-to-Noise Ratio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-quantum-neural-network-advantage-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the performance of a Hybrid Quantum Neural Network (HQNN) and a comparable classical Convolution Neural Network (CNN) for detection and classification problem using a radar.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-quantum-neural-network-advantage-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAGLE: Eigen Aggregation Learning for Object-Centric Unsupervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-eigen-aggregation-learning-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation has innately relied on extensive pixel-level labeled annotated data, leading to the emergence of unsupervised methodologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-eigen-aggregation-learning-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a-DCF: an architecture agnostic metric with application to spoofing-robust speaker verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dcf-an-architecture-agnostic-metric-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spoofing detection is today a mainstream research topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dcf-an-architecture-agnostic-metric-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Poverty Be Reduced by Acting on Discrimination? An Agent-based Model for Policy Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-poverty-be-reduced-by-acting-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We classify policies as discriminatory or non-discriminatory against the poor, with the support of specialized NGOs, and we observe the results in the AABM in terms of the impact on wealth inequality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-poverty-be-reduced-by-acting-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Graph Generator: Feature-Conditioned Graph Generation using Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-graph-generator-feature-conditioned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph generation has emerged as a crucial task in machine learning, with significant challenges in generating graphs that accurately reflect specific properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-graph-generator-feature-conditioned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Biomolecule and Natural Language through Multi-Modal Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-biomolecule-and-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The integration of biomolecular modeling with natural language (BL) has emerged as a promising interdisciplinary area at the intersection of artificial intelligence, chemistry and biology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-biomolecule-and-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving LLM Code Generation with Grammar Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-llm-code-generation-with-grammar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SynCode a novel framework for efficient and general syntactical decoding of code with large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-llm-code-generation-with-grammar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNA Family: Boosting Weight-Sharing NAS with Block-Wise Supervisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dna-family-boosting-weight-sharing-nas-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this problem, we modularize a large search space into blocks with small search spaces and develop a family of models with the distilling neural architecture (DNA) techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dna-family-boosting-weight-sharing-nas-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-PQ: Serving LLM on Heterogeneous Clusters with Phase-Aware Partition and Adaptive Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-pq-serving-llm-on-heterogeneous-clusters</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The immense sizes of LLMs have led to very high resource demand and cost for running the models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-pq-serving-llm-on-heterogeneous-clusters</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Two-Stage Algorithm for Cost-Efficient Multi-instance Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-algorithm-for-cost-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual explanations constitute among the most popular methods for analyzing the predictions of black-box systems since they can recommend cost-efficient and actionable changes to the input to turn an undesired system's output into a desired output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-two-stage-algorithm-for-cost-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Validity of Automatically Generated Feedback via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-validity-of-automatically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a framework for feedback generation that optimizes both correctness and alignment using reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-validity-of-automatically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenGraph: Towards Open Graph Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengraph-towards-open-graph-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By effectively capturing the graph's underlying structure, these GNNs have shown great potential in enhancing performance in graph learning tasks, such as link prediction and node classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengraph-towards-open-graph-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting Automation: Intent-Based User Instruction Classification with Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-automation-intent-based-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our system represents user instructions as intents, allowing for dynamic control of electrical circuits without relying on predefined commands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-automation-intent-based-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotion Analysis in NLP: Trends, Gaps and Roadmap for Future Directions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-analysis-in-nlp-trends-gaps-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then discuss four lacunae: (1) the absence of demographic and cultural aspects does not account for the variation in how emotions are perceived, but instead assumes they are universally experienced in the same manner; (2) the poor fit of emotion categories from the two main emotion theories to the task; (3) the lack of standardized EA terminology hinders gap identification, comparison, and future goals; and (4) the absence of interdisciplinary research isolates EA from insights in other fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotion-analysis-in-nlp-trends-gaps-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParallelPARC: A Scalable Pipeline for Generating Natural-Language Analogies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallelparc-a-scalable-pipeline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate our pipeline and create ProPara-Logy, a dataset of analogies between scientific processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallelparc-a-scalable-pipeline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Compositional Typed Semantics for Universal Dependencies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-compositional-typed-semantics-for-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce UD Type Calculus, a compositional, principled, and language-independent system of semantic types and logical forms for lexical items which builds on a widely-used language-general dependency syntax framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-compositional-typed-semantics-for-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Segmentation Models with Mask-Preserved Attribute Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-segmentation-models-with-mask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate a broad variety of semantic segmentation models, spanning from conventional close-set models to recent open-vocabulary large models on their robustness to different types of variations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-segmentation-models-with-mask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF-VPT: Learning Novel View Representations with Neural Radiance Fields via View Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-vpt-learning-novel-view-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the cascading learning of NeRF-VPT introduces adaptability to scenarios with sparse inputs, resulting in a significant enhancement of accuracy for sparse-view novel view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-vpt-learning-novel-view-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Unbiased Diffusion Models From Biased Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-unbiased-diffusion-models-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While directly applying it to score-matching is intractable, we discover that using the time-dependent density ratio both for reweighting and score correction can lead to a tractable form of the objective function to regenerate the unbiased data density.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-unbiased-diffusion-models-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaiMA: Feature-aware In-context Learning for Multi-domain Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faima-feature-aware-in-context-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing research narrowly focuses on single-domain applications constrained by methodological limitations and data scarcity, the reality is that sentiment naturally traverses multiple domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faima-feature-aware-in-context-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Greedy Coordinate Gradient via Probe Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-greedy-coordinate-gradient-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety of Large Language Models (LLMs) has become a central issue given their rapid progress and wide applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-greedy-coordinate-gradient-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DINER: Debiasing Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis with Multi-variable Causal Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diner-debiasing-aspect-based-sentiment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most of the present debiasing methods focus on single-variable causal inference, which is not suitable for ABSA with two input variables (the target aspect and the review).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diner-debiasing-aspect-based-sentiment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pairwise Alignment Improves Graph Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-alignment-improves-graph-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph-based methods, pivotal for label inference over interconnected objects in many real-world applications, often encounter generalization challenges, if the graph used for model training differs significantly from the graph used for testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-alignment-improves-graph-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polynormer: Polynomial-Expressive Graph Transformer in Linear Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polynormer-polynomial-expressive-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable the base model permutation equivariant, we integrate it with graph topology and node features separately, resulting in local and global equivariant attention models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polynormer-polynomial-expressive-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STAR: Constraint LoRA with Dynamic Active Learning for Data-Efficient Fine-Tuning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-constraint-lora-with-dynamic-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For poor model calibration, we incorporate the regularization method during LoRA training to keep the model from being over-confident, and the Monte-Carlo dropout mechanism is employed to enhance the uncertainty estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-constraint-lora-with-dynamic-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Subtext: Evaluating Large Language Models on Short Story Summarization with Writers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-subtext-evaluating-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate recent Large language Models (LLMs) on the challenging task of summarizing short stories, which can be lengthy, and include nuanced subtext or scrambled timelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-subtext-evaluating-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can a Confident Prior Replace a Cold Posterior?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-a-confident-prior-replace-a-cold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we introduce a "DirClip" prior that is practical to sample and nearly matches the performance of a cold posterior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-a-confident-prior-replace-a-cold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Inductive Biases for Surface Normal Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-inductive-biases-for-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the growing demand for accurate surface normal estimation models, existing methods use general-purpose dense prediction models, adopting the same inductive biases as other tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-inductive-biases-for-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributional Dataset Distillation with Subtask Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-dataset-distillation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[What does a neural network learn when training from a task-specific dataset?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributional-dataset-distillation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Efficient Local Search for Genetic Programming Based Loss Function Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-efficient-local-search-for-genetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop upon the topic of loss function learning, an emergent meta-learning paradigm that aims to learn loss functions that significantly improve the performance of the models trained under them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-efficient-local-search-for-genetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoTeC: A German Naturalistic Eye-tracking-while-reading Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/potec-a-german-naturalistic-eye-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Potsdam Textbook Corpus (PoTeC) is a naturalistic eye-tracking-while-reading corpus containing data from 75 participants reading 12 scientific texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/potec-a-german-naturalistic-eye-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Logical Constraints but without Shortcut Satisfaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-logical-constraints-but-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new framework for learning with logical constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-logical-constraints-but-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskLRF: Self-supervised Pretraining via Masked Autoencoding of Local Reference Frames for Rotation-invariant 3D Point Set Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masklrf-self-supervised-pretraining-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following the successes in the fields of vision and language, self-supervised pretraining via masked autoencoding of 3D point set data, or Masked Point Modeling (MPM), has achieved state-of-the-art accuracy in various downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masklrf-self-supervised-pretraining-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Construction with Flexible Nodes for Traffic Demand Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-construction-with-flexible-nodes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges, this paper introduces a novel graph construction method tailored to free-floating traffic mode.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-construction-with-flexible-nodes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peacock: A Family of Arabic Multimodal Large Language Models and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peacock-a-family-of-arabic-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have proven effective in a wide range of tasks requiring complex reasoning and linguistic comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peacock-a-family-of-arabic-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Consistent Decoding for More Factual Open Responses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-consistent-decoding-for-more-factual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare this "Sample & Select" method to greedy decoding, beam search, nucleus sampling, and the recently introduced hallucination avoiding decoders of DoLA, P-CRR, and S-CRR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-consistent-decoding-for-more-factual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imitation Learning Datasets: A Toolkit For Creating Datasets, Training Agents and Benchmarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-learning-datasets-a-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imitation learning field requires expert data to train agents in a task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-learning-datasets-a-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Few-shot 3D Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-few-shot-3d-point-cloud-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The former arises from non-uniform point sampling, allowing models to distinguish the density disparities between foreground and background for easier segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-few-shot-3d-point-cloud-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisionLLaMA: A Unified LLaMA Interface for Vision Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionllama-a-unified-llama-interface-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models are built on top of a transformer-based architecture to process textual inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionllama-a-unified-llama-interface-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
