<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 09:16:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep-Based Approach for Multi-Descriptor Feature Extraction: Applications on SAR Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-based-approach-for-multi-descriptor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges of SAR images, we utilize the R2D2 network and propose a training scheme specifically tailored for these images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-based-approach-for-multi-descriptor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FPPL: An Efficient and Non-IID Robust Federated Continual Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fppl-an-efficient-and-non-iid-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, an efficient and non-IID robust federated continual learning framework, called Federated Prototype-Augmented Prompt Learning (FPPL), is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fppl-an-efficient-and-non-iid-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted Manipulation and Deception Emerge when Optimizing LLMs for User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-manipulation-and-deception-emerge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As LLMs become more widely deployed, there is increasing interest in directly optimizing for feedback from end users (e. g. thumbs up) in addition to feedback from paid annotators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-manipulation-and-deception-emerge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Cognitive Diagnosis with Disentangled Representation Learning for Learner Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-cognitive-diagnosis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the success of collaborative modeling in various domains, such as recommender systems, we aim to investigate how collaborative signals among learners contribute to the diagnosis of human cognitive states (i. e., knowledge proficiency) in the context of intelligent education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-cognitive-diagnosis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Speech Recognition: A Single Model for Auditory, Visual, and Audiovisual Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-speech-recognition-a-single-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that training a single model for all three tasks enhances VSR and AVSR performance, overcoming typical optimisation challenges when training from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-speech-recognition-a-single-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Landscape for Generative Sequence Models for Specialized Data Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-landscape-for-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) research often aims to develop models that generalize reliably across complex datasets, yet this remains challenging in fields where data is scarce, intricate, or inaccessible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-landscape-for-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders are Parameter-Efficient Federated Continual Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-are-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although advanced prompt-based continual learning methods leverage pre-trained transformers to mitigate catastrophic forgetting, they do not adequately address the non-IID challenges in federated learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-are-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Reclustering Barrier in Centroid-based Deep Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-reclustering-barrier-in-centroid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work investigates an important phenomenon in centroid-based deep clustering (DC) algorithms: Performance quickly saturates after a period of rapid early gains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-reclustering-barrier-in-centroid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Variational Autoencoders with Intrinsic Dimension and Information Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-variational-autoencoders-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents an analysis of the hidden representations of Variational Autoencoders (VAEs) using the Intrinsic Dimension (ID) and the Information Imbalance (II).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-variational-autoencoders-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Geometric Estimation of Depth and Surface Normal from Monocular 360° Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-geometric-estimation-of-depth-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our first innovation is our MTL architecture, which enhances predictions for both tasks by integrating geometric information from depth and surface normal estimation, enabling a deeper understanding of 3D scene structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-geometric-estimation-of-depth-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Formulation of LiDAR Mapping with Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-formulation-of-lidar-mapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we reexamine the process through which a Neural Radiance Field (NeRF) can be trained to produce novel LiDAR views of a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-formulation-of-lidar-mapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typicalness-Aware Learning for Failure Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/typicalness-aware-learning-for-failure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that, with the cross-entropy loss, model predictions are optimized to align with the corresponding labels via increasing logit magnitude or refining logit direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/typicalness-aware-learning-for-failure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Human-AI Cooperation: An Inclusive Embodied Social Intelligence Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-human-ai-cooperation-an-inclusive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In CHAIC, the goal is for an embodied agent equipped with egocentric observations to assist a human who may be operating under physical constraints -- e. g., unable to reach high places or confined to a wheelchair -- in performing common household or outdoor tasks as efficiently as possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-human-ai-cooperation-an-inclusive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OwMatch: Conditional Self-Labeling with Consistency for Open-World Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owmatch-conditional-self-labeling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the emergence of open-world SSL (OwSSL) introduces a more practical challenge, wherein unlabeled data may encompass samples from unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/owmatch-conditional-self-labeling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnSegMedGAT: Unsupervised Medical Image Segmentation using Graph Attention Networks Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsegmedgat-unsupervised-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The data-intensive nature of supervised classification drives the interest of the researchers towards unsupervised approaches, especially for problems such as medical image segmentation, where labeled data is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsegmedgat-unsupervised-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGViz: Diagnose and Visualize Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragviz-diagnose-and-visualize-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a built-in user interface, retrieval index, and Large Language Model (LLM) backbone, RAGViz provides two main functionalities: (1) token and document-level attention visualization, and (2) generation comparison upon context document addition and removal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragviz-diagnose-and-visualize-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeeR-VLA: Dynamic Inference of Multimodal Large Language Models for Efficient Robot Execution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deer-vla-dynamic-inference-of-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLLMs have demonstrated remarkable comprehension and reasoning capabilities with complex language and visual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deer-vla-dynamic-inference-of-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Length Image Tokenization via Recurrent Allocation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-length-image-tokenization-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our encoder-decoder architecture recursively processes 2D image tokens, distilling them into 1D latent tokens over multiple iterations of recurrent rollouts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-length-image-tokenization-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Unlabeled Data with Multiple Expert Teachers for Open Vocabulary Aerial Object Detection and Its Orientation Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-unlabeled-data-with-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we put forth a novel formulation of the aerial object detection problem, namely open-vocabulary aerial object detection (OVAD), which can detect objects beyond training categories without costly collecting new labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-unlabeled-data-with-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating the Traces You Need: A Conditional Generative Model for Process Mining Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-the-traces-you-need-a-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address this challenge by introducing a conditional model for process data generation based on a conditional variational autoencoder (CVAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-the-traces-you-need-a-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HACD: Harnessing Attribute Semantics and Mesoscopic Structure for Community Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hacd-harnessing-attribute-semantics-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous research has effectively leveraged network topology and attribute information for attributed community detection, these methods overlook two critical issues: (i) the semantic similarity between node attributes within the community, and (ii) the inherent mesoscopic structure, which differs from the pairwise connections of the micro-structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hacd-harnessing-attribute-semantics-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeToken: Uniform Micro-environment Token Boosts Post-Translational Modification Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metoken-uniform-micro-environment-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Post-translational modifications (PTMs) profoundly expand the complexity and functionality of the proteome, regulating protein attributes and interactions that are crucial for biological processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metoken-uniform-micro-environment-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training-free Regional Prompting for Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-regional-prompting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have demonstrated excellent capabilities in text-to-image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-free-regional-prompting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBDRes-U-Net: Multi-Scale Lightweight Brain Tumor Segmentation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbdres-u-net-multi-scale-lightweight-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate segmentation of brain tumors plays a key role in the diagnosis and treatment of brain tumor diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbdres-u-net-multi-scale-lightweight-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation of Nanorobots with Artificial Intelligence and Reinforcement Learning for Advanced Cancer Cell Detection and Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-nanorobots-with-artificial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nanorobots are a promising development in targeted drug delivery and the treatment of neurological disorders, with potential for crossing the blood-brain barrier (BBB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-of-nanorobots-with-artificial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking Forward and Backward: Effective Backward Planning with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-forward-and-backward-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have exhibited remarkable reasoning and planning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-forward-and-backward-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Creative Short Story Generation in Humans and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-creative-short-story-generation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Storytelling is a fundamental aspect of human communication, relying heavily on creativity to produce narratives that are novel, appropriate, and surprising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-creative-short-story-generation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Where to Edit Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-where-to-edit-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model editing aims to data-efficiently correct predictive errors of large pre-trained models while ensuring generalization to neighboring failures and locality to minimize unintended effects on unrelated examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-where-to-edit-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRMArena: Understanding the Capacity of LLM Agents to Perform Professional CRM Tasks in Realistic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crmarena-understanding-the-capacity-of-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Customer Relationship Management (CRM) systems are vital for modern enterprises, providing a foundation for managing customer interactions and data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crmarena-understanding-the-capacity-of-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridge-IF: Learning Inverse Protein Folding with Markov Bridges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridge-if-learning-inverse-protein-folding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill these gaps, we propose Bridge-IF, a generative diffusion bridge model for inverse folding, which is designed to learn the probabilistic dependency between the distributions of backbone structures and protein sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridge-if-learning-inverse-protein-folding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xDiT: an Inference Engine for Diffusion Transformers (DiTs) with Massive Parallelism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xdit-an-inference-engine-for-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Parallel inference is essential for real-time DiTs deployments, but relying on a single parallel method is impractical due to poor scalability at large scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xdit-an-inference-engine-for-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Representation Collapse in Vector Quantized Models with One Linear Layer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-representation-collapse-in-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, VQ models are often hindered by the problem of representation collapse in the latent space, which leads to low codebook utilization and limits the scalability of the codebook for large-scale training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-representation-collapse-in-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAttack: Robust Black-box Attack on LiDAR-based Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidattack-robust-black-box-attack-on-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since DNN is vulnerable to carefully crafted adversarial examples, adversarial attack on LiDAR sensors have been extensively studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidattack-robust-black-box-attack-on-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Compute-Optimal Protein Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-compute-optimal-protein-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore optimally training protein language models, an area of significant interest in biological research where guidance on best practices is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-compute-optimal-protein-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting K-mer Profile for Effective and Scalable Genome Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-k-mer-profile-for-effective-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the model to recent genome foundation models and demonstrate that while the models are comparable in performance, the proposed model is significantly more effective in terms of scalability, a crucial aspect for performing metagenomic binning of real-world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-k-mer-profile-for-effective-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPLLaVA: Varied Video Sequence Understanding With Prompt Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppllava-varied-video-sequence-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we identify the key issue as the redundant content in videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppllava-varied-video-sequence-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan-Large: An Open-Source MoE Model with 52 Billion Activated Parameters by Tencent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan-large-an-open-source-moe-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Hunyuan-Large, which is currently the largest open-source Transformer-based mixture of experts model, with a total of 389 billion parameters and 52 billion activation parameters, capable of handling up to 256K tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan-large-an-open-source-moe-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LayerDAG: A Layerwise Autoregressive Diffusion Model for Directed Acyclic Graph Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerdag-a-layerwise-autoregressive-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By interpreting the partial order of nodes as a sequence of bipartite graphs, LayerDAG leverages autoregressive generation to model directional dependencies and employs diffusion models to capture logical dependencies within each bipartite graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerdag-a-layerwise-autoregressive-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Trust Estimation in Human-Robot Collaboration Using Beta Reputation at Fine-grained Timescales</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-trust-estimation-in-human-robot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, manually crafting a reward function is the usual method of building a performance indicator, which is labor-intensive and time-consuming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-trust-estimation-in-human-robot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning General-Purpose Biomedical Volume Representations using Randomized Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-general-purpose-biomedical-volume</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current volumetric biomedical foundation models struggle to generalize as public 3D datasets are small and do not cover the broad diversity of medical procedures, conditions, anatomical regions, and imaging protocols.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-general-purpose-biomedical-volume</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding Sparse Tuning for Low Memory Usage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-sparse-tuning-for-low-memory-usage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method named SNELL (Sparse tuning with kerNELized LoRA) for sparse tuning with low memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-sparse-tuning-for-low-memory-usage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Steering Vectors by Targeting Sparse Autoencoder Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-steering-vectors-by-targeting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To control the behavior of language models, steering methods attempt to ensure that outputs of the model satisfy specific pre-defined properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-steering-vectors-by-targeting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment-Based Adversarial Training (ABAT) for Improving the Robustness and Accuracy of EEG-Based BCIs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-based-adversarial-training-abat-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data alignment aligns EEG trials from different domains to reduce their distribution discrepancies, and adversarial training further robustifies the classification boundary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-based-adversarial-training-abat-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosing Medical Datasets with Training Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-medical-datasets-with-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The framework used is Data Maps, which classifies data points into categories such as easy-to-learn, hard-to-learn, and ambiguous (Swayamdipta et al., 2020).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnosing-medical-datasets-with-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FilterNet: Harnessing Frequency Filters for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filternet-harnessing-frequency-filters-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While numerous forecasters have been proposed using different network architectures, the Transformer-based models have state-of-the-art performance in time series forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filternet-harnessing-frequency-filters-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classifier-guided Gradient Modulation for Enhanced Multimodal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifier-guided-gradient-modulation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods to balance the training process always have some limitations on the loss functions, optimizers and the number of modalities and only consider modulating the magnitude of the gradients while ignoring the directions of the gradients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifier-guided-gradient-modulation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FactorizePhys: Matrix Factorization for Multidimensional Attention in Remote Physiological Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorizephys-matrix-factorization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate FSAM's effectiveness, we developed FactorizePhys, an end-to-end 3D-CNN architecture for estimating blood volume pulse signals from raw video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorizephys-matrix-factorization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoCE: Adaptive Mixture of Contextualization Experts for Byte-based Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moce-adaptive-mixture-of-contextualization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Byte-based machine translation systems have shown significant potential in massively multilingual settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moce-adaptive-mixture-of-contextualization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Weight Decay for Robust Fine-Tuning of Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-weight-decay-for-robust-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This exploration is beneficial for finding good loss basins when training from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-weight-decay-for-robust-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Multi-Robot Coverage Path Planning on Grids with Path Deconfliction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-robot-coverage-path-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study Multi-Robot Coverage Path Planning (MCPP) on a 4-neighbor 2D grid G, which aims to compute paths for multiple robots to cover all cells of G. Traditional approaches are limited as they first compute coverage trees on a quadrant coarsened grid H and then employ the Spanning Tree Coverage (STC) paradigm to generate paths on G, making them inapplicable to grids with partially obstructed 2x2 blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-robot-coverage-path-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
