<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 09:12:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Music Hierarchies with a Graph-Based Neural Decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-music-hierarchies-with-a-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a data-driven framework to parse musical sequences into dependency trees, which are hierarchical structures used in music cognition research and music analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-music-hierarchies-with-a-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Sampling-based Meta-Learning for Molecular Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sampling-based-meta-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To effectively utilize many-to-many correlations of molecules and properties, we propose a Graph Sampling-based Meta-learning (GS-Meta) framework for few-shot molecular property prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sampling-based-meta-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect Any Deepfakes: Segment Anything Meets Face Forgery Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-any-deepfakes-segment-anything-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancements in computer vision have stimulated remarkable progress in face forgery techniques, capturing the dedicated attention of researchers committed to detecting forgeries and precisely localizing manipulated areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-any-deepfakes-segment-anything-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised 3D registration through optimization-guided cyclical self-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-3d-registration-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art deep learning-based registration methods employ three different learning strategies: supervised learning, which requires costly manual annotations, unsupervised learning, which heavily relies on hand-crafted similarity metrics designed by domain experts, or learning from synthetic data, which introduces a domain shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-3d-registration-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BinaryViT: Pushing Binary Vision Transformers Towards Convolutional Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binaryvit-pushing-binary-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing popularity and the increasing size of vision transformers (ViTs), there has been an increasing interest in making them more efficient and less computationally costly for deployment on edge devices with limited computing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binaryvit-pushing-binary-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Model for Endoscopy Video Analysis via Large-scale Self-supervised Pre-train</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-for-endoscopy-video-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models have exhibited remarkable success in various applications, such as disease diagnosis and text report generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-for-endoscopy-video-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Performance of 1D-Convolution Neural Networks to Predict Concentration of Mixture Components from Raman Spectra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-performance-of-1d-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finding the optimal algorithm for a specific bioreactor environment is challenging due to the lack of freely available Raman mixture datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-performance-of-1d-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical Data Imputation for Multimodal Data Sets: A Probabilistic Nearest-Neighbor Kernel Density Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-data-imputation-for-multimodal-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare our method with previous data imputation methods using artificial and real-world data with different data missing scenarios and various data missing rates, and show that our method can cope with complex original data structure, yields lower data imputation errors, and provides probabilistic estimates with higher likelihood than current methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-data-imputation-for-multimodal-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAUTILUS: boosting Bayesian importance nested sampling with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nautilus-boosting-bayesian-importance-nested</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel approach to boost the efficiency of the importance nested sampling (INS) technique for Bayesian posterior and evidence estimation using deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nautilus-boosting-bayesian-importance-nested</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computationally Assisted Quality Control for Public Health Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computationally-assisted-quality-control-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing outlier detection frameworks perform poorly on this task because they do not account for the data volume or for the statistical properties of public health streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computationally-assisted-quality-control-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManimML: Communicating Machine Learning Architectures with Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manimml-communicating-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A user can take a preexisting neural network architecture and easily write a specification for an animation in ManimML, which will then automatically compose animations for different components of the system into a final animation of the entire neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manimml-communicating-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-source Semantic Graph-based Multimodal Sarcasm Explanation Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-semantic-graph-based-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Sarcasm Explanation (MuSE) is a new yet challenging task, which aims to generate a natural language sentence for a multimodal social post (an image as well as its caption) to explain why it contains sarcasm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-semantic-graph-based-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimPLe: Similarity-Aware Propagation Learning for Weakly-Supervised Breast Cancer Segmentation in DCE-MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-similarity-aware-propagation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The network first utilizes the pseudo-masks generated using the extreme points to train itself, by minimizing a contrastive loss, which encourages the network to learn more representative features for cancerous voxels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-similarity-aware-propagation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MNISQ: A Large-Scale Quantum Circuit Dataset for Machine Learning on/for Quantum Computers in the NISQ era</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnisq-a-large-scale-quantum-circuit-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In fact, also the Machine Learning research related to quantum computers undertakes a dual challenge: enhancing machine learning exploiting the power of quantum computers, while also leveraging state-of-the-art classical machine learning methodologies to help the advancement of quantum computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnisq-a-large-scale-quantum-circuit-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provable Advantage of Curriculum Learning on Parity Targets with Mixed Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-advantage-of-curriculum-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results have shown that curriculum learning, i. e., presenting simpler examples before more complex ones, can improve the efficiency of learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-advantage-of-curriculum-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokenization and the Noiseless Channel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenization-and-the-noiseless-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subword tokenization is a key part of many NLP pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenization-and-the-noiseless-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Relationship Between RNN Hidden State Vectors and Semantic Ground Truth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-relationship-between-rnn-hidden-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine the assumption that the hidden-state vectors of recurrent neural networks (RNNs) tend to form clusters of semantically similar vectors, which we dub the clustering hypothesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-relationship-between-rnn-hidden-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end Autonomous Driving: Challenges and Frontiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-autonomous-driving-challenges-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The autonomous driving community has witnessed a rapid growth in approaches that embrace an end-to-end algorithm framework, utilizing raw sensor input to generate vehicle motion plans, instead of concentrating on individual tasks such as detection and motion prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-autonomous-driving-challenges-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroGen: Zero-shot Multimodal Controllable Text Generation with Multiple Oracles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerogen-zero-shot-multimodal-controllable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatically generating textual content with desired attributes is an ambitious task that people have pursued long.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerogen-zero-shot-multimodal-controllable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Time and Memory Efficiency of Genetic Algorithms by Storing Populations as Minimum Spanning Trees of Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-time-and-memory-efficiency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many applications of evolutionary algorithms the computational cost of applying operators and storing populations is comparable to the cost of fitness evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-time-and-memory-efficiency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond CO2 Emissions: The Overlooked Impact of Water Consumption of Information Retrieval Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-co2-emissions-the-overlooked-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As in other fields of artificial intelligence, the information retrieval community has grown interested in investigating the power consumption associated with neural models, particularly models of search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-co2-emissions-the-overlooked-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Representation Power of SPLADE Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-representation-power-of-splade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SPLADE (SParse Lexical AnD Expansion) model is a highly effective approach to learned sparse retrieval, where documents are represented by term impact scores derived from large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-representation-power-of-splade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Single- and Multi- Objective Optimization Quality for Evolutionary Equation Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-single-and-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary differential equation discovery proved to be a tool to obtain equations with less a priori assumptions than conventional approaches, such as sparse symbolic regression over the complete possible terms library.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-single-and-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ducho: A Unified Framework for the Extraction of Multimodal Features in Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-a-unified-framework-for-the-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the outlined aspects, we propose Ducho, a unified framework for the extraction of multimodal features in recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-a-unified-framework-for-the-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised MRI Reconstruction with Unrolled Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-mri-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) produces excellent soft tissue contrast, albeit it is an inherently slow imaging modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-mri-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL4CO: an Extensive Reinforcement Learning for Combinatorial Optimization Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4co-an-extensive-reinforcement-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope RL4CO will encourage the exploration of novel solutions to complex real-world tasks, allowing to compare with existing methods through a standardized interface that decouples the science from the software engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4co-an-extensive-reinforcement-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCDAL: A Perturbation Consistency-Driven Active Learning Approach for Medical Image Segmentation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcdal-a-perturbation-consistency-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose an AL-based method that can be simultaneously applied to 2D medical image classification, segmentation, and 3D medical image segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcdal-a-perturbation-consistency-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would I have gotten that reward? Long-term credit assignment by counterfactual contribution analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/would-i-have-gotten-that-reward-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that measuring contributions w. r. t.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/would-i-have-gotten-that-reward-long-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIS-FM: 3D Medical Image Segmentation using Foundation Models Pretrained on a Large-Scale Unannotated Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mis-fm-3d-medical-image-segmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed model was pretrained with 110k unannotated 3D CT volumes, and experiments with different downstream segmentation targets including head and neck organs, thoracic/abdominal organs showed that our pretrained model largely outperformed training from scratch and several state-of-the-art self-supervised training methods and segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mis-fm-3d-medical-image-segmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Predictive Accuracy of Neural Temporal Point Process Models for Continuous-time Event Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-predictive-accuracy-of-neural-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we present a comprehensive large-scale experimental study that systematically evaluates the predictive accuracy of state-of-the-art neural TPP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-predictive-accuracy-of-neural-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical Phase and Instrument Recognition: How to identify appropriate Dataset Splits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-phase-and-instrument-recognition-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: The development of machine learning models for surgical workflow and instrument recognition from temporal data represents a challenging task due to the complex nature of surgical workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-phase-and-instrument-recognition-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralFuse: Learning to Improve the Accuracy of Access-Limited Neural Network Inference in Low-Voltage Regimes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralfuse-learning-to-improve-the-accuracy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we introduce NeuralFuse, a novel add-on module that addresses the accuracy-energy tradeoff in low-voltage regimes by learning input transformations to generate error-resistant data representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralfuse-learning-to-improve-the-accuracy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medoid splits for efficient random forests in metric spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medoid-splits-for-efficient-random-forests-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper revisits an adaptation of the random forest algorithm for Fr\'echet regression, addressing the challenge of regression in the context of random objects in metric spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medoid-splits-for-efficient-random-forests-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Drunkard's Odometry: Estimating Camera Motion in Deforming Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-drunkard-s-odometry-estimating-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating camera motion in deformable scenes poses a complex and open research challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-drunkard-s-odometry-estimating-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macro Placement by Wire-Mask-Guided Black-Box Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macro-placement-by-wire-mask-guided-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[WireMask-BBO has the potential to significantly improve the quality and efficiency of chip floorplanning, which makes it appealing to researchers and practitioners in EDA and will also promote the application of BBO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macro-placement-by-wire-mask-guided-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaturalInversion: Data-Free Image Synthesis Improving Real-World Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naturalinversion-data-free-image-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce NaturalInversion, a novel model inversion-based method to synthesize images that agrees well with the original data distribution without using real data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naturalinversion-data-free-image-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Model-Based Multi-Agent Mean-Field Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-model-based-multi-agent-mean-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many applications, e. g., in shared mobility, require coordinating a large number of agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-model-based-multi-agent-mean-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Training Multi-Modal Dense Retrievers for Outside-Knowledge Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-multi-modal-dense-retrievers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach leads to 26. 9% Precision@5 improvements compared to the current state-of-the-art asymmetric architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-multi-modal-dense-retrievers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Language Models can be Poets too: An AI Writing Assistant and Constrained Text Generation Studio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-language-models-can-be-poets-too-an-ai-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a simple and universally applicable technique for modifying the output of a language model by compositionally applying filter functions to the language models vocabulary before a unit of text is generated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/most-language-models-can-be-poets-too-an-ai-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBBQ: A Chinese Bias Benchmark Dataset Curated with Human-AI Collaboration for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbbq-a-chinese-bias-benchmark-dataset-curated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a Chinese Bias Benchmark dataset that consists of over 100K questions jointly constructed by human experts and generative language models, covering stereotypes and societal biases in 14 social dimensions related to Chinese culture and values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cbbq-a-chinese-bias-benchmark-dataset-curated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More efficient manual review of automatically transcribed tabular data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-manual-review-of-automatically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We allocated those 90, 000 codes to human reviewers, who used our annotation tool to review the codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-manual-review-of-automatically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatLaw: Open-Source Legal Large Language Model with Integrated External Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlaw-open-source-legal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a self-attention method to enhance the ability of large models to overcome errors present in reference data, further optimizing the issue of model hallucinations at the model level and improving the problem-solving capabilities of large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlaw-open-source-legal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Computational Complexity for Convolutional Layers by Skipping Zeros</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper gives C-K-S algorithm (ConvV2, KS-deconv, Sk-dilated), which skips these 0s in two ways: trim the filters to exclude padded 0s; transform sparse tensors to dense tensors, to avoid inserted 0s in deconvolution and dilated-convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-computational-complexity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Surgical Instruments Segmentation to Unseen Domains with One-to-Many Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-surgical-instruments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we mitigate data-related issues by efficiently leveraging minimal source images to generate synthetic surgical instrument segmentation datasets and achieve outstanding generalization performance on unseen real domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-surgical-instruments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curious Replay for Model-based Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curious-replay-for-model-based-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Agents must be able to adapt quickly as an environment changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curious-replay-for-model-based-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Sampling and Aggregation Operations in GNN Frameworks with GPU Initiated Direct Storage Accesses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-sampling-and-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose the GPU Initiated Direct Storage Access (GIDS) dataloader, to enable GPU-oriented GNN training for large-scale graphs while efficiently utilizing all hardware resources, such as CPU memory, storage, and GPU memory with a hybrid data placement strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-sampling-and-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT a Biomedical Expert? -- Exploring the Zero-Shot Performance of Current GPT Models in Biomedical Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-biomedical-expert-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assessed the performance of commercial Large Language Models (LLMs) GPT-3. 5-Turbo and GPT-4 on tasks from the 2023 BioASQ challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-biomedical-expert-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On information captured by neural networks: connections with memorization and generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-information-captured-by-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the popularity and success of deep learning, there is limited understanding of when, how, and why neural networks generalize to unseen examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-information-captured-by-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separable Physics-Informed Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separable-physics-informed-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The number of training points (collocation points) required on these challenging PDEs grows substantially, but it is severely limited due to the expensive computational costs and heavy memory overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separable-physics-informed-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Points for Energy Renovation (PointER): A LiDAR-Derived Point Cloud Dataset of One Million English Buildings Linked to Energy Characteristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/points-for-energy-renovation-pointer-a-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building point clouds in new regions can be generated with the open-source code published alongside the paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/points-for-energy-renovation-pointer-a-lidar</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
