<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 09:12:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Tool for the Procedural Generation of Shaders using Interactive Evolutionary Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tool-for-the-procedural-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a tool for exploring the design space of shaders using an interactive evolutionary algorithm integrated with the Unity editor, a well-known commercial tool for video game development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-tool-for-the-procedural-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini in Reasoning: Unveiling Commonsense in Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gemini-in-reasoning-unveiling-commonsense-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, our study undertakes a thorough evaluation of Gemini's performance in complex reasoning tasks that necessitate the integration of commonsense knowledge across modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gemini-in-reasoning-unveiling-commonsense-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth Forest: Toward Multi-Scale Truthfulness in Large Language Models through Intervention without Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-forest-toward-multi-scale-truthfulness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Truth Forest, a method that enhances truthfulness in LLMs by uncovering hidden truth representations using multi-dimensional orthogonal probes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/truth-forest-toward-multi-scale-truthfulness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FerKD: Surgical Label Adaptation for Efficient Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferkd-surgical-label-adaptation-for-efficient-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, FerKD achieves 81. 2% on ImageNet-1K with ResNet-50, outperforming FKD and FunMatch by remarkable margins.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ferkd-surgical-label-adaptation-for-efficient-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-free Optimization in Early Training Steps for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-free-optimization-in-early-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we propose a novel optimization method that can effectively remove the inherent noise term in the early steps of vanilla training by estimating the optimal centroid and directly optimizing toward the estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-free-optimization-in-early-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Understanding with Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-understanding-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the burgeoning growth of online video platforms and the escalating volume of video content, the demand for proficient video understanding tools has intensified markedly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-understanding-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIJack: Security and Privacy Risk Simulator for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aijack-security-and-privacy-risk-simulator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces AIJack, an open-source library designed to assess security and privacy risks associated with the training and deployment of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aijack-security-and-privacy-risk-simulator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action-Item-Driven Summarization of Long Meeting Transcripts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-item-driven-summarization-of-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, this paper introduces three novel methods for dividing up long transcripts into topic-based sections to improve the time efficiency of our algorithm, as well as to resolve the issue of large language models (LLMs) forgetting long-term dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-item-driven-summarization-of-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking with Human-Intent Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-with-human-intent-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The perception component then generates the tracking results based on the embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-with-human-intent-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Point Cloud Forecasting enables Scalable Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-point-cloud-forecasting-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To resolve this, we bring up a new pre-training task termed as visual point cloud forecasting - predicting future point clouds from historical visual input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-point-cloud-forecasting-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation for Supervised Graph Outlier Detection with Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-for-supervised-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the fundamental challenges confronting supervised graph outlier detection algorithms is the prevalent issue of class imbalance, where the scarcity of outlier instances compared to normal instances often results in suboptimal performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-for-supervised-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINN surrogate of Li-ion battery models for parameter inference. Part II: Regularization and application of the pseudo-2D model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinn-surrogate-of-li-ion-battery-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the computational cost of Bayesian calibration, numerical solvers for physics-based models can be replaced with faster surrogates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinn-surrogate-of-li-ion-battery-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Image Restoration through Removing Degradations in Textual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-restoration-through-removing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the cross-modal assistance, we propose to map the degraded images into textual representations for removing the degradations, and then convert the restored textual representations into a guidance image for assisting image restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-restoration-through-removing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Multi-axis Representation in Frequency Domain for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-axis-representation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our block performs a Fourier transform on the three axes of the input features and assigns the external weight in the frequency domain, which is generated by our External Weights Generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-axis-representation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Visual Reinforcement Learning with Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-visual-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning policies that can generalize to unseen environments is a fundamental challenge in visual reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-visual-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Universal Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-universal-image-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several unsupervised image segmentation approaches have been proposed which eliminate the need for dense manually-annotated segmentation masks; current models separately handle either semantic segmentation (e. g., STEGO) or class-agnostic instance segmentation (e. g., CutLER), but not both (i. e., panoptic segmentation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-universal-image-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupversied feature correlation model to predict breast abnormal variation maps in longitudinal mammograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupversied-feature-correlation-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we focus on improving the early detection and accurate diagnosis of breast abnormalities, which is crucial for improving patient outcomes and reducing the mortality rate of breast cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupversied-feature-correlation-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PG-LBO: Enhancing High-Dimensional Bayesian Optimization with Pseudo-Label and Gaussian Process Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-lbo-enhancing-high-dimensional-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this technique, we assign appropriate training weights to unlabeled data to enhance the construction of a discriminative latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pg-lbo-enhancing-high-dimensional-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseProp: Efficient Event-Based Simulation and Training of Sparse Recurrent Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparseprop-efficient-event-based-simulation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SparseProp, a novel event-based algorithm for simulating and training sparse SNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparseprop-efficient-event-based-simulation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-Align: Teaching LMMs for Visual Scoring via Discrete Text-Defined Levels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-align-teaching-lmms-for-visual-scoring-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The explosion of visual content available online underscores the requirement for an accurate machine assessor to robustly evaluate scores across diverse types of visual contents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-align-teaching-lmms-for-visual-scoring-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Persistent Homology: Persistence Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-persistent-homology-persistence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel family of descriptors for persistence diagrams, reconceptualizing them as signals in $\mathbb R^2_+$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-persistent-homology-persistence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Degree Biases in Message Passing Mechanism by Utilizing Community Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-degree-biases-in-message-passing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Community-aware Graph Transformers, namely CGT, to learn degree-unbiased representations based on learnable augmentations and graph transformers by extracting within community structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-degree-biases-in-message-passing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Function-Space Regularization in Neural Networks: A Probabilistic Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/function-space-regularization-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we approach regularization in neural networks from a probabilistic perspective and show that by viewing parameter-space regularization as specifying an empirical prior distribution over the model parameters, we can derive a probabilistically well-motivated regularization technique that allows explicitly encoding information about desired predictive functions into neural network training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/function-space-regularization-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fourth International Verification of Neural Networks Competition (VNN-COMP 2023): Summary and Results</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fourth-international-verification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report summarizes the 4th International Verification of Neural Networks Competition (VNN-COMP 2023), held as a part of the 6th Workshop on Formal Methods for ML-Enabled Autonomous Systems (FoMLAS), that was collocated with the 35th International Conference on Computer-Aided Verification (CAV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-fourth-international-verification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experiential Co-Learning of Software-Developing Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experiential-co-learning-of-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have brought significant changes to various domains, especially through LLM-driven autonomous agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/experiential-co-learning-of-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffKG: Knowledge Graph Diffusion Model for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffkg-knowledge-graph-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this research gap, we propose a novel knowledge graph diffusion model for recommendation, referred to as DiffKG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffkg-knowledge-graph-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Flossing: Improving Gradient Descent through Dynamic Control of Jacobians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-flossing-improving-gradient-descent-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For challenging tasks, we show that gradient flossing during training can further increase the time horizon that can be bridged by backpropagation through time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-flossing-improving-gradient-descent-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PINN surrogate of Li-ion battery models for parameter inference. Part I: Implementation and multi-fidelity hierarchies for the single-particle model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinn-surrogate-of-li-ion-battery-models-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The techniques used to develop a PINN surrogate of the SPM are extended in Part II for the PINN surrogate for the P2D battery model, and explore the Bayesian calibration capabilities of both surrogates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pinn-surrogate-of-li-ion-battery-models-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Sparse 3D Panoptic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-sparse-3d-panoptic-occupancy-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To exploit the sparsity property and ensure instance-awareness, we introduce a novel fully sparse panoptic occupancy network, termed SparseOcc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-sparse-3d-panoptic-occupancy-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Inference of Mixture-of-Experts Language Models with Offloading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-of-mixture-of-experts-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the problem of running large MoE language models on consumer hardware with limited accelerator memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-of-mixture-of-experts-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tractable Function-Space Variational Inference in Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tractable-function-space-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing that the primary object of interest in most settings is the distribution over functions induced by the posterior distribution over neural network parameters, we frame Bayesian inference in neural networks explicitly as inferring a posterior distribution over functions and propose a scalable function-space variational inference method that allows incorporating prior information and results in reliable predictive uncertainty estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tractable-function-space-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iFusion: Inverting Diffusion for Pose-Free Reconstruction from Sparse Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ifusion-inverting-diffusion-for-pose-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our strategy unfolds in three steps: (1) We invert the diffusion model for camera pose estimation instead of synthesizing novel views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ifusion-inverting-diffusion-for-pose-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Vision from Models Rivals Learning Vision from Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-vision-from-models-rivals-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SynCLR, a novel approach for learning visual representations exclusively from synthetic images and synthetic captions, without any real data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-vision-from-models-rivals-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Active Sampling Reduce Causal Confusion in Offline Reinforcement Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-active-sampling-reduce-causal-confusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer this question, we consider a set of tailored offline reinforcement learning datasets that exhibit causal ambiguity and assess the ability of active sampling techniques to reduce causal confusion at evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-active-sampling-reduce-causal-confusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amodal Ground Truth and Completion in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amodal-ground-truth-and-completion-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, we use 3D data to establish an automatic pipeline to determine authentic ground truth amodal masks for partially occluded objects in real images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amodal-ground-truth-and-completion-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalization of the Convolution Theorem and its Connections to Non-Stationarity and the Graph Frequency Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalization-of-the-convolution-theorem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel convolution theorem which encompasses the well known convolution theorem in (graph) signal processing as well as the one related to time-varying filters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalization-of-the-convolution-theorem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Explanations of Image-Text Representations via Multi-Modal Information Bottleneck Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-explanations-of-image-text-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language pretrained models have seen remarkable success, but their application to safety-critical settings is limited by their lack of interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-explanations-of-image-text-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empirical fits to inclusive electron-carbon scattering data obtained by deep-learning methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-fits-to-inclusive-electron-carbon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To test these models, we compare their predictions to a~test dataset, excluded from the training process, a~dataset lying beyond the covered kinematic region, and theoretical predictions obtained within the spectral function approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empirical-fits-to-inclusive-electron-carbon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI for Math: Part I -- MathPile: A Billion-Token-Scale Pretraining Corpus for Math</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-for-math-part-i-mathpile-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our meticulous data collection and processing efforts included a complex suite of preprocessing, prefiltering, language identification, cleaning, filtering, and deduplication, ensuring the high quality of our corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-for-math-part-i-mathpile-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSPP: A Unified Benchmarking Tool for Time-series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tspp-a-unified-benchmarking-tool-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently there has been increasing interest in developing and deploying deep graph learning algorithms for many tasks, such as fraud detection and recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tspp-a-unified-benchmarking-tool-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Count What You Want: Exemplar Identification and Few-shot Counting of Human Actions in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/count-what-you-want-exemplar-identification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To develop and evaluate our approach, we introduce a diverse and realistic dataset consisting of real-world data from 37 subjects and 50 action categories, encompassing both sensor and audio data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/count-what-you-want-exemplar-identification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Dynamic Correlations and Mitigating Noise by Hierarchical Convolution for Long-term Sequence Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-dynamic-correlations-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, a hierarchical convolution structure is introduced to extract the information from the series at various scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-dynamic-correlations-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Contrastive Variational Graph Auto-Encoder for Node Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-contrastive-variational-graph-auto-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to a newly identified term, our lower bound can escape Posterior Collapse and has more flexibility to account for the difference between the inference and generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-contrastive-variational-graph-auto-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Aggregations for High-Dimensional Multiplex Graph Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-aggregations-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose HMGE, a novel embedding method based on hierarchical aggregation for high-dimensional multiplex graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-aggregations-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenge LLMs to Reason About Reasoning: A Benchmark to Unveil Cognitive Depth in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenge-llms-to-reason-about-reasoning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a novel evaluation paradigm for Large Language Models, one that challenges them to engage in meta-reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenge-llms-to-reason-about-reasoning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Anytime Multi-Agent Path Finding Using Bandit-Based Large Neighborhood Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-anytime-multi-agent-path-finding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art anytime MAPF is based on Large Neighborhood Search (LNS), where a fast initial solution is iteratively optimized by destroying and repairing a fixed number of parts, i. e., the neighborhood, of the solution, using randomized destroy heuristics and prioritized planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-anytime-multi-agent-path-finding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Learning in 4D: a Quaternion-valued Laplacian to Enhance Spectral GCNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-learning-in-4d-a-quaternion-valued</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce QuaterGCN, a spectral Graph Convolutional Network (GCN) with quaternion-valued weights at whose core lies the Quaternionic Laplacian, a quaternion-valued Laplacian matrix by whose proposal we generalize two widely-used Laplacian matrices: the classical Laplacian (defined for undirected graphs) and the complex-valued Sign-Magnetic Laplacian (proposed to handle digraphs with weights of arbitrary sign).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-learning-in-4d-a-quaternion-valued</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamGaussian4D: Generative 4D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamgaussian4d-generative-4d-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remarkable progress has been made in 4D content generation recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreamgaussian4d-generative-4d-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Physics-Based Learned Reconstruction Methods for Real-Time 3D Near-Field MIMO Radar Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-physics-based-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results show the effectiveness of the developed physics-based learned reconstruction approach in terms of both run-time and image quality at highly compressive settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-physics-based-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyGPT-V: Efficient Multimodal Large Language Model via Small Backbones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinygpt-v-efficient-multimodal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of advanced multimodel learning, multimodal large language models (MLLMs) such as GPT-4V have made remarkable strides towards bridging language and visual elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinygpt-v-efficient-multimodal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
