<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:07:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging LDA Feature Extraction to Augment Human Activity Recognition Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-lda-feature-extraction-to-augment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces a hybrid feature extraction approach that combines Linear Discriminant Analysis (LDA) and Multilayer Perceptron (MLP) methods to address the challenges of reducing feature vector dimensionality and accurately classifying smartphone-based human activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-lda-feature-extraction-to-augment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Retinal Blood Vessel Segmentation Models for Cross-Dataset and Cross-Disease Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-retinal-blood-vessel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we provide a rigorous benchmark for various architectural and training choices commonly used in the literature on the largest dataset published to date.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-retinal-blood-vessel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Hand Gesture Recognition: Integrating Skeleton-Based Data Fusion and Multi-Stream CNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-hand-gesture-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study focuses on Hand Gesture Recognition (HGR), which is vital for perceptual computing across various real-world contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-hand-gesture-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dual Attention-aided DenseNet-121 for Classification of Glaucoma from Fundus Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-attention-aided-densenet-121-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning and computer vision methods are nowadays predominantly used in the field of ophthalmology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-attention-aided-densenet-121-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrating the Efficacy of Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks in Vision Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-kolmogorov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of deep learning, the Kolmogorov-Arnold Network (KAN) has emerged as a potential alternative to multilayer projections (MLPs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstrating-the-efficacy-of-kolmogorov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2GS: Event Enhanced Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2gs-event-enhanced-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Event Enhanced Gaussian Splatting (E2GS), a novel method that incorporates event data into Gaussian Splatting, which has recently made significant advances in the field of novel view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2gs-event-enhanced-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Common Information in Multi-view Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-common-information-in-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an innovative and mathematically rigorous definition for computing common information from multi-view data, drawing inspiration from G\'acs-K\"orner common information in information theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-common-information-in-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Good, Bad and Ugly Arguments Generated by ChatGPT: a New Dataset, its Methodology and Associated Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-good-bad-and-ugly-arguments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, there is a pressing need for tools to identify ``fake arguments'' generated by such models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-good-bad-and-ugly-arguments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICLEval: Evaluating In-Context Learning Ability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icleval-evaluating-in-context-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In-Context Learning (ICL) is a critical capability of Large Language Models (LLMs) as it empowers them to comprehend and reason across interconnected inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icleval-evaluating-in-context-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoA: Mixture of Sparse Attention for Automatic Large Language Model Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moa-mixture-of-sparse-attention-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this uniform approach fails to capture the diverse attention patterns inherent in LLMs, ignoring their distinct accuracy-latency trade-offs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moa-mixture-of-sparse-attention-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoLRM: Geometry-Aware Large Reconstruction Model for High-Quality 3D Gaussian Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolrm-geometry-aware-large-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce the Geometry-Aware Large Reconstruction Model (GeoLRM), an approach which can predict high-quality assets with 512k Gaussians and 21 input images in only 11 GB GPU memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geolrm-geometry-aware-large-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STARD: A Chinese Statute Retrieval Dataset with Real Queries Issued by Non-professionals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stard-a-chinese-statute-retrieval-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Statute retrieval aims to find relevant statutory articles for specific queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stard-a-chinese-statute-retrieval-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenoTEX: A Benchmark for Evaluating LLM-Based Exploration of Gene Expression Data in Alignment with Bioinformaticians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genotex-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-llm-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose GenoTEX as a promising resource for benchmarking and enhancing AI-driven methods for genomics data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genotex-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-llm-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Passage Embeddings for Efficient Listwise Reranking with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-passage-embeddings-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, in this paper, we propose PE-Rank, leveraging the single passage embedding as a good context compression for efficient listwise passage reranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-passage-embeddings-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECLIPSE: Expunging Clean-label Indiscriminate Poisons via Sparse Diffusion Purification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eclipse-expunging-clean-label-indiscriminate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, to address the trade-off of the inconsistency in the assimilation sensitivity of different poisons by Gaussian noise, we propose a lightweight corruption compensation module to effectively eliminate residual poisons, providing a more universal defense approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eclipse-expunging-clean-label-indiscriminate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLP-KG: A System for Exploratory Search of Scientific Literature in Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlp-kg-a-system-for-exploratory-search-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific literature searches are often exploratory, whereby users are not yet familiar with a particular field or concept but are interested in learning more about it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlp-kg-a-system-for-exploratory-search-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online detection and infographic explanation of spam reviews with data drift adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-detection-and-infographic-explanation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spam reviews are a pervasive problem on online platforms due to its significant impact on reputation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-detection-and-infographic-explanation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DistiLRR: Transferring Code Repair for Low-Resource Programming Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilrr-transferring-code-repair-for-low</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable performance on code generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilrr-transferring-code-repair-for-low</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESC-Eval: Evaluating Emotion Support Conversations in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esc-eval-evaluating-emotion-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the awesome development of role-playing agents, we propose an ESC Evaluation framework (ESC-Eval), which uses a role-playing agent to interact with ESC models, followed by a manual evaluation of the interactive dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/esc-eval-evaluating-emotion-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Interaction via Primitive-based Adversarial Training For Compositional Zero-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-interaction-via-primitive-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the success of vanilla adversarial learning in Cross-Domain Few-Shot Learning, we take a step further and devise a model-agnostic and Primitive-Based Adversarial training (PBadv) method to deal with this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-interaction-via-primitive-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact discovery is polynomial for sparse causal Bayesian networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-discovery-is-polynomial-for-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal Bayesian networks are widely used tools for summarising the dependencies between variables and elucidating their putative causal relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-discovery-is-polynomial-for-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelfReg-UNet: Self-Regularized UNet for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfreg-unet-self-regularized-unet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although numerous follow-up studies have also been dedicated to improving the performance of standard UNet, few have conducted in-depth analyses of the underlying interest pattern of UNet in medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selfreg-unet-self-regularized-unet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behaviour Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behaviour-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Filling the gap, we formalize behaviour distillation, a setting that aims to discover and then condense the information required for training an expert policy into a synthetic dataset of state-action pairs, without access to expert data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behaviour-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Remote Sensing Change Detection With A Mask View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-remote-sensing-change-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, we further propose the instance network CDMaskFormer customized for the change detection task, which includes: (i) a Spatial-temporal convolutional attention-based instantiated change extractor to capture spatio-temporal context simultaneously with lightweight operations; and (ii) a scene-guided axial attention-instantiated transformer decoder to extract more spatial details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-remote-sensing-change-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modality Safety Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modality-safety-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) becomes increasingly integrated into various facets of human life, ensuring the safety and ethical alignment of such systems is paramount.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modality-safety-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UDA: A Benchmark Suite for Retrieval Augmented Generation in Real-world Document Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uda-a-benchmark-suite-for-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) has improved Large Language Models (LLMs) in collaborating with external data, yet significant challenges exist in real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uda-a-benchmark-suite-for-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This actually looks like that: Proto-BagNets for local and global interpretability-by-design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-actually-looks-like-that-proto-bagnets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability is a key requirement for the use of machine learning models in high-stakes applications, including medical diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/this-actually-looks-like-that-proto-bagnets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedOdyssey: A Medical Domain Benchmark for Long Context Evaluation Up to 200K Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medodyssey-a-medical-domain-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some benchmarks in the generic domain have also followed up on evaluating long-context capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medodyssey-a-medical-domain-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVSIM: Data-Driven Non-Reactive Autonomous Vehicle Simulation and Benchmarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navsim-data-driven-non-reactive-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On a large set of challenging scenarios, we observe that simple methods with moderate compute requirements such as TransFuser can match recent large-scale end-to-end driving architectures such as UniAD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navsim-data-driven-non-reactive-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GIEBench: Towards Holistic Evaluation of Group Indentity-based Empathy for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/giebench-towards-holistic-evaluation-of-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) continue to develop and gain widespread application, the ability of LLMs to exhibit empathy towards diverse group identities and understand their perspectives is increasingly recognized as critical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/giebench-towards-holistic-evaluation-of-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Wavelet Guided Attention Module for Skin Cancer Classification with Gradient-based Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-wavelet-guided-attention-module-for-skin</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel model, which uses a novel attention mechanism to pinpoint the differences in features across the spatial dimensions and symmetry of the lesion, thereby focusing on the dissimilarities of various classes based on symmetry, uniformity in texture and color, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-wavelet-guided-attention-module-for-skin</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Attention in Hierarchical Transformers for Tabular Time-series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-attention-in-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At first, rows (or columns) are encoded separately by computing attention between their fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-attention-in-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Preserved Blood Glucose Level Cross-Prediction: An Asynchronous Decentralized Federated Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserved-blood-glucose-level-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Newly diagnosed Type 1 Diabetes (T1D) patients often struggle to obtain effective Blood Glucose (BG) prediction models due to the lack of sufficient BG data from Continuous Glucose Monitoring (CGM), presenting a significant "cold start" problem in patient care.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserved-blood-glucose-level-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Greedy Policy for Proposal Batch Selection in Expensive Multi-Objective Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-greedy-policy-for-proposal-batch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Active learning is increasingly adopted for expensive multi-objective combinatorial optimization problems, but it involves a challenging subset selection problem, optimizing the batch acquisition score that quantifies the goodness of a batch for evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-greedy-policy-for-proposal-batch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FA-Net: A Fuzzy Attention-aided Deep Neural Network for Pneumonia Detection in Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fa-net-a-fuzzy-attention-aided-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method achieves accuracy rates of 97. 15\% and 79. 79\% for the binary and multi-class classification setups, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fa-net-a-fuzzy-attention-aided-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Multi-modality Fusion and Prototype-based Feature Refinement for Clinically Significant Prostate Cancer Classification in Transrectal Ultrasound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-multi-modality-fusion-and-prototype</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel learning framework for clinically significant prostate cancer (csPCa) classification using multi-modality TRUS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-multi-modality-fusion-and-prototype</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Infinite-Long Prefix in Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-infinite-long-prefix-in-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompting and contextual-based fine-tuning methods, which we call Prefix Learning, have been proposed to enhance the performance of language models on various downstream tasks that can match full parameter fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-infinite-long-prefix-in-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights into LLM Long-Context Failures: When Transformers Know but Don't Tell</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-llm-long-context-failures-when</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) exhibit positional bias, struggling to utilize information from the middle or end of long contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insights-into-llm-long-context-failures-when</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visible-Thermal Tiny Object Detection: A Benchmark Dataset and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visible-thermal-tiny-object-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the proposed RGBT-Tiny dataset and SAFit measure, extensive evaluations have been conducted, including 23 recent state-of-the-art algorithms that cover four different types (i. e., visible generic detection, visible SOD, thermal SOD and RGBT object detection).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visible-thermal-tiny-object-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step-Back Profiling: Distilling User History for Personalized Scientific Writing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-back-profiling-distilling-user-history</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regarding our experiments, we construct a Personalized Scientific Writing (PSW) dataset to study multiuser personalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-back-profiling-distilling-user-history</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prism: A Framework for Decoupling and Assessing the Capabilities of VLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-a-framework-for-decoupling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Language Models (VLMs) demonstrate remarkable proficiency in addressing a wide array of visual questions, which requires strong perception and reasoning faculties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-a-framework-for-decoupling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairX: A comprehensive benchmarking tool for model analysis using fairness, utility, and explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairx-a-comprehensive-benchmarking-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present FairX, an open-source Python-based benchmarking tool designed for the comprehensive analysis of models under the umbrella of fairness, utility, and eXplainability (XAI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairx-a-comprehensive-benchmarking-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Driven Guided Decoding Mechanism for Diagnostic Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-guided-decoding-mechanism-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accuracy of a diagnostic text, however, strongly depends on how well the key medical conditions depicted in the images are expressed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-guided-decoding-mechanism-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAGER: Two-Stream Generative Recommender with Behavior-Semantic Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eager-two-stream-generative-recommender-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative retrieval has recently emerged as a promising approach to sequential recommendation, framing candidate item retrieval as an autoregressive sequence generation problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eager-two-stream-generative-recommender-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAGLAS: An atlas of text-attributed graph datasets in the era of large graph and language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taglas-an-atlas-of-text-attributed-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In TAGLAS, we collect and integrate more than 23 TAG datasets with domains ranging from citation graphs to molecule graphs and tasks from node classification to graph question-answering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taglas-an-atlas-of-text-attributed-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecting the Dots: LLMs can Infer and Verbalize Latent Structure from Disparate Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-the-dots-llms-can-infer-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a step towards answering this question, we study inductive out-of-context reasoning (OOCR), a type of generalization in which LLMs infer latent information from evidence distributed across training documents and apply it to downstream tasks without in-context learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-the-dots-llms-can-infer-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Optimism: Exploration With Partially Observable Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-optimism-exploration-with-partially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploration in reinforcement learning (RL) remains an open challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-optimism-exploration-with-partially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Fine-Grained Classification by Structure and Subject Preserving Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-fine-grained-classification-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these models have been used to generate training data for classification tasks, their effectiveness in full-dataset training of FGVC models remains under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-fine-grained-classification-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency Models Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-models-made-easy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consistency models (CMs) are an emerging class of generative models that offer faster sampling than traditional diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-models-made-easy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CollaFuse: Collaborative Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collafuse-collaborative-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to these challenges, we introduce a novel approach for distributed collaborative diffusion models inspired by split learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collafuse-collaborative-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
