<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 09:18:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling fluffy clouds: field boundaries detection using time series of S2 and/or S1 imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-fluffy-clouds-field-boundaries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Both models are evaluated under sparse and dense cloud coverage by exploiting spatio-temporal correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-fluffy-clouds-field-boundaries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVT-Occ: Cost Volume Temporal Fusion for 3D Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvt-occ-cost-volume-temporal-fusion-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-based 3D occupancy prediction is significantly challenged by the inherent limitations of monocular vision in depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvt-occ-cost-volume-temporal-fusion-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A preliminary study on continual learning in computer vision using Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-on-continual-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the investigation by evaluating the performance of KANs in continual learning tasks within computer vision, specifically using the MNIST datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-on-continual-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An adapted large language model facilitates multiple medical tasks in diabetes care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adapted-large-language-model-facilitates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduced a framework to train and validate diabetes-specific LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adapted-large-language-model-facilitates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature-Centered First Order Structure Tensor Scale-Space in 2D and 3D</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-centered-first-order-structure-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The structure tensor method is often used for 2D and 3D analysis of imaged structures, but its results are in many cases very dependent on the user's choice of method parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-centered-first-order-structure-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iteration of Thought: Leveraging Inner Dialogue for Autonomous Large Language Model Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iteration-of-thought-leveraging-inner</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this insight, we propose the Iteration of Thought (IoT) framework for enhancing LLM responses by generating "thought"-provoking prompts vis a vis an input query and the current iteration of an LLM's response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iteration-of-thought-leveraging-inner</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Language Models to Self-Correct via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-self-correct-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we observe that training via SFT either suffers from a distribution mismatch between the training data and the model's own responses or implicitly prefers only a certain mode of correction behavior that is often not effective at test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-self-correct-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Automatic 3D Annotation of Traffic Lights and Signs for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-automatic-3d-annotation-of-traffic-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D detection of traffic management objects, such as traffic lights and road signs, is vital for self-driving cars, particularly for address-to-address navigation where vehicles encounter numerous intersections with these static objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-automatic-3d-annotation-of-traffic-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Gaussian Discriminant Variational Autoencoder (GdVAE): A Self-Explainable Model with Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gaussian-discriminant-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual counterfactual explanation (CF) methods modify image concepts, e. g, shape, to change a prediction to a predefined outcome while closely resembling the original query image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-gaussian-discriminant-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oryx MLLM: On-Demand Spatial-Temporal Understanding at Arbitrary Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oryx-mllm-on-demand-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual data comes in various forms, ranging from small icons of just a few pixels to long videos spanning hours.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oryx-mllm-on-demand-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pyrtklib: An open-source package for tightly coupled deep learning and GNSS integration for positioning in urban canyons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyrtklib-an-open-source-package-for-tightly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) is revolutionizing numerous fields, with increasing applications in Global Navigation Satellite Systems (GNSS) positioning algorithms in intelligent transportation systems (ITS) via deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyrtklib-an-open-source-package-for-tightly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance and Power: Systematic Evaluation of AI Workloads on Accelerators with CARAML</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-and-power-systematic-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of machine learning (ML) technologies has driven the development of specialized hardware accelerators designed to facilitate more efficient model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-and-power-systematic-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CritiPrefill: A Segment-wise Criticality-based Approach for Prefilling Acceleration in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critiprefill-a-segment-wise-criticality-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe a locality in query criticality during the prefilling phase of long-context processing: adjacent query tokens tend to focus on similar subsets of the past Key-Value (KV) cache.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critiprefill-a-segment-wise-criticality-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tight and Efficient Upper Bound on Spectral Norm of Convolutional Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-and-efficient-upper-bound-on-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controlling the spectral norm of the Jacobian matrix, which is related to the convolution operation, has been shown to improve generalization, training stability and robustness in CNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tight-and-efficient-upper-bound-on-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRDF-NeRF: Neural Radiance Fields with Optical Satellite Images and BRDF Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brdf-nerf-neural-radiance-fields-with-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the anisotropic reflectance of complex Earth surfaces from satellite imagery is crucial for numerous applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brdf-nerf-neural-radiance-fields-with-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Controlled Study on Long Context Extension and Generalization in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-controlled-study-on-long-context-extension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Broad textual understanding and in-context learning require language models that utilize full document contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-controlled-study-on-long-context-extension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Chinese Continuous Sign Language Dataset Based on Complex Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-chinese-continuous-sign-language-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current bottleneck in continuous sign language recognition (CSLR) research lies in the fact that most publicly available datasets are limited to laboratory environments or television program recordings, resulting in a single background environment with uniform lighting, which significantly deviates from the diversity and complexity found in real-life scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-chinese-continuous-sign-language-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen2.5-Coder Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen2-5-coder-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we introduce the Qwen2. 5-Coder series, a significant upgrade from its predecessor, CodeQwen1. 5.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen2-5-coder-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetry-Based Structured Matrices for Efficient Approximately Equivariant Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-based-structured-matrices-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a general framework -- based on a novel construction of symmetry-based structured matrices -- to build approximately equivariant NNs with significantly reduced parameter counts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetry-based-structured-matrices-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAgICoRe: Multi-Agent, Iterative, Coarse-to-Fine Refinement for Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicore-multi-agent-iterative-coarse-to-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to ensure effective refinement, we employ a multi-agent loop with three agents: Solver, Reviewer (which generates targeted feedback based on step-wise RM scores), and the Refiner (which incorporates feedback).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicore-multi-agent-iterative-coarse-to-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEOW: MEMOry Supervised LLM Unlearning Via Inverted Facts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meow-memory-supervised-llm-unlearning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM Unlearning, a post-hoc approach to remove this information from trained LLMs, offers a promising solution to mitigate these risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meow-memory-supervised-llm-unlearning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Factuality of Large Language Models in the Legal Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-factuality-of-large-language-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the factuality of large language models (LLMs) as knowledge bases in the legal domain, in a realistic usage scenario: we allow for acceptable variations in the answer, and let the model abstain from answering when uncertain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-factuality-of-large-language-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Long-Term Safety and Uncertainty in Safe Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-long-term-safety-and-uncertainty-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety is one of the key issues preventing the deployment of reinforcement learning techniques in real-world robots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/handling-long-term-safety-and-uncertainty-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>multiPI-TransBTS: A Multi-Path Learning Framework for Brain Tumor Image Segmentation Based on Multi-Physical Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipi-transbts-a-multi-path-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Brain Tumor Segmentation (BraTS) plays a critical role in clinical diagnosis, treatment planning, and monitoring the progression of brain tumors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipi-transbts-a-multi-path-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Human and AI Values based on Generative Psychometrics with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-human-and-ai-values-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces Generative Psychometrics for Values (GPV), an LLM-based, data-driven value measurement paradigm, theoretically grounded in text-revealed selective perceptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-human-and-ai-values-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Control Systems for Autonomous Quadrotors against Cyber-Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secure-control-systems-for-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a state-of-the-art deep learning-based approach, an optimal false data injection attack scheme is proposed to deteriorate a quadrotor's tracking performance with limited attack energy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secure-control-systems-for-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Imaging for Long-Term Prediction of Solar Irradiance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-imaging-for-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The occlusion of the sun by clouds is one of the primary sources of uncertainties in solar power generation, and is a factor that affects the wide-spread use of solar power as a primary energy source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-imaging-for-long-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WiLoR: End-to-end 3D Hand Localization and Reconstruction in-the-wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wilor-end-to-end-3d-hand-localization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, 3D hand pose estimation methods have garnered significant attention due to their extensive applications in human-computer interaction, virtual reality, and robotics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wilor-end-to-end-3d-hand-localization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Estimation of a Class of Distances Between Covariance Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-estimation-of-a-class-of-distances</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This family of distances is particularly useful as it takes into consideration the fact that covariance matrices lie in the Riemannian manifold of positive definite matrices, thereby including a variety of commonly used metrics, such as the Euclidean distance, Jeffreys' divergence, and the log-Euclidean distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-estimation-of-a-class-of-distances</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitting Multilevel Factor Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-multilevel-factor-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the inverse of an invertible PSD MLR matrix is also an MLR matrix with the same sparsity in factors, and we use the recursive Sherman-Morrison-Woodbury matrix identity to obtain the factors of the inverse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-multilevel-factor-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TART: An Open-Source Tool-Augmented Framework for Explainable Table-based Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tart-an-open-source-tool-augmented-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current Large Language Models (LLMs) exhibit limited ability to understand table structures and to apply precise numerical reasoning, which is crucial for tasks such as table question answering (TQA) and table-based fact verification (TFV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tart-an-open-source-tool-augmented-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-Driven 3D Segmentation and Affordance Transfer in Gaussian Splatting Using 2D Masks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-driven-3d-segmentation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a byproduct, we discovered that inference-time gradients can also be used to prune Gaussians, resulting in up to 21% compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-driven-3d-segmentation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autopet III challenge: Incorporating anatomical knowledge into nnUNet for lesion segmentation in PET/CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-iii-challenge-incorporating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The autoPET III Challenge focuses on advancing automated segmentation of tumor lesions in PET/CT images in a multitracer multicenter setting, addressing the clinical need for quantitative, robust, and generalizable solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopet-iii-challenge-incorporating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized compression and compressive search of large datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-compression-and-compressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude that panCAKES is an efficient, general-purpose algorithm for exact compressive search on large datasets that obey the manifold hypothesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-compression-and-compressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Grid Graph Neural Networks with Self-Attention for Computational Mechanics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grid-graph-neural-networks-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel model merging Self-Attention with Message Passing in GNNs, achieving a 15\% reduction in RMSE on the well known flow past a cylinder benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-grid-graph-neural-networks-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen2-VL: Enhancing Vision-Language Model's Perception of the World at Any Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen2-vl-enhancing-vision-language-model-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Qwen2-VL Series, an advanced upgrade of the previous Qwen-VL models that redefines the conventional predetermined-resolution approach in visual processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen2-vl-enhancing-vision-language-model-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChefFusion: Multimodal Foundation Model Integrating Recipe and Food Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheffusion-multimodal-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant work has been conducted in the domain of food computing, yet these studies typically focus on single tasks such as t2t (instruction generation from food titles and ingredients), i2t (recipe generation from food images), or t2i (food image generation from recipes).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheffusion-multimodal-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-in-one foundational models learning across quantum chemical levels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-foundational-models-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce the all-in-one (AIO) ANI model architecture based on multimodal learning which can learn an arbitrary number of QC levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/all-in-one-foundational-models-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the Challenge of Detecting Character Knowledge Errors in LLM Role-Playing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-challenge-of-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) role-playing has gained widespread attention, where the authentic character knowledge is crucial for constructing realistic LLM role-playing agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-the-challenge-of-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unraveling the Hessian: A Key to Smooth Convergence in Loss Function Landscapes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-the-hessian-a-key-to-smooth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The loss landscape of neural networks is a critical aspect of their training, and understanding its properties is essential for improving their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unraveling-the-hessian-a-key-to-smooth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Data Subset Selection to Generalize Training Across Models: Transductive and Inductive Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-data-subset-selection-to-generalize-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose $\texttt{SubSelNet}$, a trainable subset selection framework, that generalizes across architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-data-subset-selection-to-generalize-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Development and bilingual evaluation of Japanese medical large language model within reasonably low computational resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-and-bilingual-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent success of large language models (LLMs) and the scaling law has led to a widespread adoption of larger models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/development-and-bilingual-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedLF: Adaptive Logit Adjustment and Feature Optimization in Federated Long-Tailed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlf-adaptive-logit-adjustment-and-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on benchmark datasets CIFAR-10-LT and CIFAR-100-LT demonstrate that our approach effectively mitigates the problem of model performance degradation due to data heterogeneity and long-tailed distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedlf-adaptive-logit-adjustment-and-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vista3D: Unravel the 3D Darkside of a Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista3d-unravel-the-3d-darkside-of-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We embark on the age-old quest: unveiling the hidden dimensions of objects from mere glimpses of their visible parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vista3d-unravel-the-3d-darkside-of-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAF-Net: A Dual-Branch Feature Decomposition Fusion Network with Domain Adaptive for Infrared and Visible Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daf-net-a-dual-branch-feature-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared and visible image fusion aims to combine complementary information from both modalities to provide a more comprehensive scene understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daf-net-a-dual-branch-feature-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesizing Evolving Symbolic Representations for Autonomous Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-evolving-symbolic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Reinforcement Learning(DRL) is an effective tool for agents to learn policies in low-level state spaces to solve highly complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesizing-evolving-symbolic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Element Ordering on LM Agent Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-element-ordering-on-lm-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we find that the ordering in which elements are presented to the language model is surprisingly impactful--randomizing element ordering in a webpage degrades agent performance comparably to removing all visible text from an agent's state representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-element-ordering-on-lm-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysMamba: Efficient Remote Physiological Measurement with SlowFast Temporal Difference Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physmamba-efficient-remote-physiological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial-video based Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) aims at measuring physiological signals and monitoring heart activity without any contact, showing significant potential in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physmamba-efficient-remote-physiological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULOC: Learning to Localize in Complex Large-Scale Environments with Ultra-Wideband Ranges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uloc-learning-to-localize-in-complex-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While UWB-based methods can achieve high localization accuracy in small-scale areas, their accuracy and reliability are significantly challenged in large-scale environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uloc-learning-to-localize-in-complex-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynthSOD: Developing an Heterogeneous Dataset for Orchestra Music Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthsod-developing-an-heterogeneous-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in music source separation have significantly progressed, particularly in isolating vocals, drums, and bass elements from mixed tracks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthsod-developing-an-heterogeneous-dataset</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
