<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 21:08:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Arabic Sentiment Analysis: ArSen Benchmark and the Improved Fuzzy Deep Hybrid Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-arabic-sentiment-analysis-arsen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sentiment analysis is pivotal in Natural Language Processing for understanding opinions and emotions in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-arabic-sentiment-analysis-arsen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEARD: Benchmarking the Adversarial Robustness for Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beard-benchmarking-the-adversarial-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dataset Distillation (DD) is an emerging technique that compresses large-scale datasets into significantly smaller synthesized datasets while preserving high test performance and enabling the efficient training of large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beard-benchmarking-the-adversarial-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heuristical Comparison of Vision Transformers Against Convolutional Neural Networks for Semantic Segmentation on Remote Sensing Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heuristical-comparison-of-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper focuses on the heuristic comparison of three key factors of using (or not using) ViT for semantic segmentation of remote sensing aerial images on the iSAID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heuristical-comparison-of-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Deviation Learning for Visual Anomaly Detection with Data Contamination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-deviation-learning-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual anomaly detection targets to detect images that notably differ from normal pattern, and it has found extensive application in identifying defective parts within the manufacturing industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-deviation-learning-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The \emph{Optimist}: Towards Fully Automated Graph Theory Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emph-optimist-towards-fully-automated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the \emph{Optimist}, an autonomous system developed to advance automated conjecture generation in graph theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emph-optimist-towards-fully-automated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Matching Filtering and Refinement by Planes and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-matching-filtering-and-refinement-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a modular, non-deep learning method for filtering and refining sparse correspondences in image matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-matching-filtering-and-refinement-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SINETRA: a Versatile Framework for Evaluating Single Neuron Tracking in Behaving Animals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinetra-a-versatile-framework-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately tracking neuronal activity in behaving animals presents significant challenges due to complex motions and background noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sinetra-a-versatile-framework-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCAN: Bootstrapping Contrastive Pre-training for Data Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scan-bootstrapping-contrastive-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we individually pre-train seven CLIP models on two large-scale image-text pair datasets, and two MoCo models on the ImageNet dataset, resulting in a total of 16 pre-trained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scan-bootstrapping-contrastive-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caravan MultiMet: Extending Caravan with Multiple Weather Nowcasts and Forecasts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caravan-multimet-extending-caravan-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Caravan large-sample hydrology dataset (Kratzert et al., 2023) was created to standardize and harmonize streamflow data from various regional datasets, combined with globally available meteorological forcing and catchment attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caravan-multimet-extending-caravan-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFTIQ: Multi-Flow Tracker with Independent Matching Quality Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mftiq-multi-flow-tracker-with-independent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present MFTIQ, a novel dense long-term tracking model that advances the Multi-Flow Tracker (MFT) framework to address challenges in point-level visual tracking in video sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mftiq-multi-flow-tracker-with-independent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DROJ: A Prompt-Driven Attack against Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droj-a-prompt-driven-attack-against-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce a novel approach, Directed Rrepresentation Optimization Jailbreak (DROJ), which optimizes jailbreak prompts at the embedding level to shift the hidden representations of harmful queries towards directions that are more likely to elicit affirmative responses from the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droj-a-prompt-driven-attack-against-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adaptive Open-Source Dataset Generation Framework for Machine Learning Tasks in Logic Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-open-source-dataset-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an adaptive logic synthesis dataset generation framework designed to enhance machine learning applications within the logic synthesis process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-open-source-dataset-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Reasoning Costs - The Path of Optimization for Chain of Thought via Sparse Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-reasoning-costs-the-path-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to address the chain of thought in the large language model inference cost surge, this research proposes to use a sparse attention mechanism that only focuses on a few relevant tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-reasoning-costs-the-path-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Height Estimation Using Shadow Length in Satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-height-estimation-using-shadow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We addressed this issue by using shadow length as an additional cue to compensate for the loss of building height estimation using single-view imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-height-estimation-using-shadow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Fixed Watermark is Fragile: Towards Semantic-Aware Watermark for EaaS Copyright Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-fixed-watermark-is-fragile-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we reveal that previous watermarking schemes possess semantic-independent characteristics and propose the Semantic Perturbation Attack (SPA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-fixed-watermark-is-fragile-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DriveThru: a Document Extraction Platform and Benchmark Datasets for Indonesian Local Language Archives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivethru-a-document-extraction-platform-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most of these efforts have been focused on creating manual resources thus difficult to scale to more languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drivethru-a-document-extraction-platform-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MICCAI-CDMRI 2023 QuantConn Challenge Findings on Achieving Robust Quantitative Connectivity through Harmonized Preprocessing of Diffusion MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miccai-cdmri-2023-quantconn-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is a pressing need to harmonize the preprocessing of DW-MRI datasets to ensure the derivation of robust quantitative diffusion metrics across acquisitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miccai-cdmri-2023-quantconn-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lattice-based stochastic models motivate non-linear diffusion descriptions of memory-based dispersal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lattice-based-stochastic-models-motivate-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advantage of working with the individual-based model is that it is straightforward to propose and implement memory effects within the simulation in a way that is more biologically intuitive than simply proposing heuristic extensions of classical PDE models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lattice-based-stochastic-models-motivate-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTELS: Towards Dynamic Granularity of Timeline Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtels-towards-dynamic-granularity-of-timeline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid proliferation of online news has posed significant challenges in tracking the continuous development of news topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dtels-towards-dynamic-granularity-of-timeline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the "Heatmap + Monte Carlo Tree Search" Paradigm for Solving Large Scale TSP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-heatmap-monte-carlo-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Travelling Salesman Problem (TSP) remains a fundamental challenge in combinatorial optimization, inspiring diverse algorithmic strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-heatmap-monte-carlo-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAHL: Domain-specific Automated Hallucination Evaluation of Long-Form Text through a Benchmark Dataset in Biomedicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dahl-domain-specific-automated-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce DAHL, a benchmark dataset and automated evaluation system designed to assess hallucination in long-form text generation, specifically within the biomedical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dahl-domain-specific-automated-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are nuclear masks all you need for improved out-of-domain generalisation? A closer look at cancer classification in histopathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-nuclear-masks-all-you-need-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain generalisation in computational histopathology is challenging because the images are substantially affected by differences among hospitals due to factors like fixation and staining of tissue and imaging equipment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-nuclear-masks-all-you-need-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Vision Foundation Models for High-Performance, Training-Free Open Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-vision-foundation-models-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce Trident, a training-free framework that first splices features extracted by CLIP and DINO from sub-images, then leverages SAM's encoder to create a correlation matrix for global aggregation, enabling a broadened receptive field for effective segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-vision-foundation-models-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local-Global Attention: An Adaptive Mechanism for Multi-Scale Feature Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-attention-an-adaptive-mechanism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, attention mechanisms have significantly enhanced the performance of object detection by focusing on key feature information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-attention-an-adaptive-mechanism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TockyLocus: Quantitative Analysis Methods for Flow Cytometric Fluorescent Timer Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tockylocus-quantitative-analysis-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce rigorous algorithms for a data categorization method, designated as the Tocky locus approach, which uses normalized and trigonometric-transformed Fluorescent Timer data, suitable for quantitative analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tockylocus-quantitative-analysis-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Selection Stability of Stability Selection and Its Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-selection-stability-of-stability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper seeks to broaden the use of an established stability estimator to evaluate the overall stability of the stability selection framework, moving beyond single-variable analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-selection-stability-of-stability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHRS-Bot-Nova: Improved Multimodal Large Language Model for Remote Sensing Vision-Language Interpretation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhrs-bot-nova-improved-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce LHRS-Bot-Nova, an MLLM specialized in understanding remote sensing (RS) images, designed to expertly perform a wide range of RS understanding tasks aligned with human instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhrs-bot-nova-improved-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAFES: Sequential Privacy and Fairness Enhancing Data Synthesis for Responsible AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safes-sequential-privacy-and-fairness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As data-driven and AI-based decision making gains widespread adoption in most disciplines, it is crucial that both data privacy and decision fairness are appropriately addressed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safes-sequential-privacy-and-fairness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A survey of probabilistic generative frameworks for molecular simulations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-probabilistic-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a nutshell, (i) Neural Spline Flows do best at capturing mode asymmetry present in low-dimensional data, (ii) Conditional Flow Matching outperforms other models for high-dimensional data with low complexity, and (iii) Denoising Diffusion Probabilistic Models appears the best for low-dimensional data with high complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-probabilistic-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interaction Testing in Variation Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-testing-in-variation-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, the TV measure is suitable for providing explanations in the natural regime and answering questions such as ``why is $X$ associated with $Y$?''.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-testing-in-variation-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-aware Denoised Fine-tuning of Off-the-shelf Models for Certified Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-denoised-fine-tuning-of-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find that such a fine-tuning can be done by updating a small fraction of parameters of the classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-denoised-fine-tuning-of-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Structure of the U.S. Income Distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-structure-of-the-u-s-income-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[I show that U. S. incomes follow a one-parameter family of probability distributions over more than fifty years of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-structure-of-the-u-s-income-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyGen: A Collaborative Human-AI Approach to Python Package Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygen-a-collaborative-human-ai-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The principles of automation and innovation serve as foundational elements for advancement in contemporary science and technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygen-a-collaborative-human-ai-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hopfield-Fenchel-Young Networks: A Unified Framework for Associative Memory Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hopfield-fenchel-young-networks-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Associative memory models, such as Hopfield networks and their modern variants, have garnered renewed interest due to advancements in memory capacity and connections with self-attention in transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hopfield-fenchel-young-networks-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Perspective Stance Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-perspective-stance-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subjective NLP tasks usually rely on human annotations provided by multiple annotators, whose judgments may vary due to their diverse backgrounds and life experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-perspective-stance-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recommender systems and reinforcement learning for building control and occupant interaction: A text-mining driven review of scientific literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recommender-systems-and-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite broad applications, their use in optimizing indoor environments and energy efficiency is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recommender-systems-and-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimax Optimal Two-Sample Testing under Local Differential Privacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-optimal-two-sample-testing-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the trade-off between privacy and statistical utility in private two-sample testing under local differential privacy (LDP) for both multinomial and continuous data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-optimal-two-sample-testing-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refusal in LLMs is an Affine Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refusal-in-llms-is-an-affine-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose affine concept editing (ACE) as an approach for steering language models' behavior by intervening directly in activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refusal-in-llms-is-an-affine-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Accelerated Quantum Transport Simulations in Nanoelectronics: From Break Junctions to Field-Effect Transistors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-accelerated-quantum-transport</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum transport calculations are essential for understanding and designing nanoelectronic devices, yet the trade-off between accuracy and computational efficiency has long limited their practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-accelerated-quantum-transport</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogLLM: Log-based Anomaly Detection Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logllm-log-based-anomaly-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Software systems often record important runtime information in logs to help with troubleshooting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logllm-log-based-anomaly-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MBA-SLAM: Motion Blur Aware Dense Visual SLAM with Radiance Fields Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mba-slam-motion-blur-aware-dense-visual-slam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, we demonstrate that MBA-SLAM surpasses previous state-of-the-art methods in both camera localization and map reconstruction, showcasing superior performance across a range of datasets, including synthetic and real datasets featuring sharp images as well as those affected by motion blur, highlighting the versatility and robustness of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mba-slam-motion-blur-aware-dense-visual-slam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XiYan-SQL: A Multi-Generator Ensemble Framework for Text-to-SQL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xiyan-sql-a-multi-generator-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, we implement the ICL approach with an example selection method based on named entity recognition to prevent overemphasis on entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xiyan-sql-a-multi-generator-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steady-State and Dynamical Behavior of a PDE Model of Multilevel Selection with Pairwise Group-Level Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steady-state-and-dynamical-behavior-of-a-pde</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary competition often occurs simultaneously at multiple levels of organization, in which traits or behaviors that are costly for an individual can provide collective benefits to groups to which the individual belongs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steady-state-and-dynamical-behavior-of-a-pde</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Vector Auto Regression and Neural Network Model for Order Flow Imbalance Prediction in High Frequency Trading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-vector-auto-regression-and-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In high frequency trading, accurate prediction of Order Flow Imbalance (OFI) is crucial for understanding market dynamics and maintaining liquidity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-vector-auto-regression-and-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLV$^2$-Net: Rater-Based Majority-Label Voting for Consistent Meningeal Lymphatic Vessel Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlv-2-net-rater-based-majority-label-voting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meningeal lymphatic vessels (MLVs) are responsible for the drainage of waste products from the human brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlv-2-net-rater-based-majority-label-voting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saliency Map-based Image Retrieval using Invariant Krawtchouk Moments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-map-based-image-retrieval-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the widespread adoption of digital devices equipped with cameras and the rapid development of Internet technology, numerous content-based image retrieval systems and novel image feature extraction techniques have emerged in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-map-based-image-retrieval-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VALTEST: Automated Validation of Language Model Generated Test Cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valtest-automated-validation-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated significant potential in automating software testing, specifically in generating unit test cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valtest-automated-validation-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter Inference via Differentiable Diffusion Bridge Importance Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-inference-via-differentiable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a methodology for performing parameter inference in high-dimensional, non-linear diffusion processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-inference-via-differentiable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks in Supply Chain Analytics and Optimization: Concepts, Perspectives, Dataset and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-in-supply-chain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have recently gained traction in transportation, bioinformatics, language and image processing, but research on their application to supply chain management remains limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-in-supply-chain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Objective and Unbiased Decision Assessments with LLM-Enhanced Hierarchical Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-objective-and-unbiased-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How objective and unbiased are we while making decisions?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-objective-and-unbiased-decision</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
