<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 21:07:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Mode-Driven Graph Convolutional Network for Spatiotemporal Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-mode-driven-graph-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also study the significance of each mode and the impact of bandwidth constraints on different horizon predictions in traffic flow data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-mode-driven-graph-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Object Detection for Automatic Tooth-marked Tongue Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-object-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel fully automated Weakly Supervised method using Vision transformer and Multiple instance learning WSVM for tongue extraction and tooth-marked tongue recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-object-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Sound Source Localization via False Negative Elimination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-sound-source-localization-via-false</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel audio-visual learning framework which is instantiated with two individual learning schemes: self-supervised predictive learning (SSPL) and semantic-aware contrastive learning (SACL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-sound-source-localization-via-false</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF-CA: Dynamic Reconstruction of X-ray Coronary Angiography with Extremely Sparse-views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-ca-dynamic-reconstruction-of-x-ray</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These techniques enforce the separation of the coronary artery from the background by enforcing dynamic structure sparsity and scene smoothness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-ca-dynamic-reconstruction-of-x-ray</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBO: Inpainting-Based Occlusion to Enhance Explainable Artificial Intelligence Evaluation in Histopathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibo-inpainting-based-occlusion-to-enhance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate that IBO significantly improves perceptual fidelity, achieving nearly twice the improvement in LPIPS scores compared to the best existing occlusion strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ibo-inpainting-based-occlusion-to-enhance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turbulence Strength $C_n^2$ Estimation from Video using Physics-based Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turbulence-strength-c-n-2-estimation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a comparative analysis of classical image gradient methods for $C_n^2$ estimation and modern deep learning-based methods leveraging convolutional neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turbulence-strength-c-n-2-estimation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAU: A Dual-Branch Network to Enhance Long-Tailed Recognition via Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sau-a-dual-branch-network-to-enhance-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we proposed the use of synthetic data as a complement to long-tailed datasets to eliminate the impact of data imbalance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sau-a-dual-branch-network-to-enhance-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap Segmentation Foundation Model under Distribution Shift via Object-Centric Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrap-segmentation-foundation-model-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models have made incredible strides in achieving zero-shot or few-shot generalization, leveraging prompt engineering to mimic the problem-solving approach of human intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrap-segmentation-foundation-model-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illuminating the Diversity-Fitness Trade-Off in Black-Box Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illuminating-the-diversity-fitness-trade-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We emphasize that the main goal of our work is not to present a new algorithm but to look at the problem in a more fundamental and theoretically tractable way by asking the question: What trade-off exists between the minimum distance within batches of solutions and the average quality of their fitness?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/illuminating-the-diversity-fitness-trade-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM2Point: Segment Any 3D as Videos in Zero-shot and Promptable Manners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2point-segment-any-3d-as-videos-in-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce SAM2Point, a preliminary exploration adapting Segment Anything Model 2 (SAM 2) for zero-shot and promptable 3D segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2point-segment-any-3d-as-videos-in-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-Optimal Policy Identification in Robust Constrained Markov Decision Processes via Epigraph Form</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-policy-identification-in-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first prove that the conventional Lagrangian max-min formulation with policy gradient methods can become trapped in suboptimal solutions by encountering a sum of conflicting gradients from the objective and constraint functions during its inner minimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-policy-identification-in-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WavTokenizer: an Efficient Acoustic Discrete Codec Tokenizer for Audio Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavtokenizer-an-efficient-acoustic-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the reduced number of tokens, WavTokenizer achieves state-of-the-art reconstruction quality with outstanding UTMOS scores and inherently contains richer semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavtokenizer-an-efficient-acoustic-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptSmooth: Certifying Robustness of Medical Vision-Language Models via Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptsmooth-certifying-robustness-of-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, PromptSmooth requires only a single model to handle multiple noise levels, which substantially reduces the computational cost compared to traditional methods that rely on training a separate model for each noise level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptsmooth-certifying-robustness-of-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMT-GP: Combined Latent Mean-Teacher and Gaussian Process for Semi-supervised Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmt-gp-combined-latent-mean-teacher-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, we use a mean-teacher-assisted Gaussian process learning strategy to establish a connection between the latent and pseudo-latent vectors obtained from the labeled and unlabeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmt-gp-combined-latent-mean-teacher-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MST-KD: Multiple Specialized Teachers Knowledge Distillation for Fair Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mst-kd-multiple-specialized-teachers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our strategy learns a project of these four teachers into a common space and distill that information to a student network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mst-kd-multiple-specialized-teachers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted Cause Discovery with Data-Driven Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-cause-discovery-with-data-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel machine learning approach for inferring causal variables of a target variable from observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-cause-discovery-with-data-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Robust Early Detection of Alzheimer's Disease via an Integrated Multimodal Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-robust-early-detection-of-alzheimer-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Disease (AD) is a complex neurodegenerative disorder marked by memory loss, executive dysfunction, and personality changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-robust-early-detection-of-alzheimer-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DetectBERT: Towards Full App-Level Representation Learning to Detect Android Malware</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detectbert-towards-full-app-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in ML and DL have significantly improved Android malware detection, yet many methodologies still rely on basic static analysis, bytecode, or function call graphs that often fail to capture complex malicious behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detectbert-towards-full-app-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Graph Neural Networks Work for High Entropy Alloys?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-graph-neural-networks-work-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have excelled in predictive modeling for both crystals and molecules, owing to the expressiveness of graph representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-graph-neural-networks-work-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PACiM: A Sparsity-Centric Hybrid Compute-in-Memory Architecture via Probabilistic Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pacim-a-sparsity-centric-hybrid-compute-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, traditional approximate techniques often significantly trade off accuracy for power efficiency, and fail to reduce data transfer between main memory and CiM banks, which dominates power consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pacim-a-sparsity-centric-hybrid-compute-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible framework for generating synthetic electrocardiograms and photoplethysmograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-framework-for-generating-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, we trained an LSTM to detect ECG R-peaks using both real ECG signals from the MIT-BIH arrythmia set and our new generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-framework-for-generating-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-free variational learning with conditional mixture networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-free-variational-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work shows that fast variational methods can reduce the compute requirements of Bayesian methods by eliminating the need for gradient computation or sampling, but are often limited to simple models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-free-variational-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ART: Actually Robust Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/art-actually-robust-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current interest in deep learning captures the attention of many programmers and researchers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/art-actually-robust-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Infusing Auxiliary Knowledge for Distracted Driver Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-infusing-auxiliary-knowledge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distracted driving is a leading cause of road accidents globally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-infusing-auxiliary-knowledge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GL-TSVM: A robust and smooth twin support vector machine with guardian loss function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gl-tsvm-a-robust-and-smooth-twin-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To remedy it, we introduce the guardian loss (G-loss), a novel loss function distinguished by its asymmetric, bounded, and smooth characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gl-tsvm-a-robust-and-smooth-twin-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Control for Diffusion Bridge in Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-control-for-diffusion-bridge-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration refers to the process of restoring a damaged low-quality image back to its corresponding high-quality image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-control-for-diffusion-bridge-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UV-free Texture Generation with Denoising and Geodesic Heat Diffusions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uv-free-texture-generation-with-denoising-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Seams, distortions, wasted UV space, vertex-duplication, and varying resolution over the surface are the most prominent issues of the standard UV-based texturing of meshes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uv-free-texture-generation-with-denoising-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Negative Samples in Generative Biomedical Entity Linking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-negative-samples-in-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these models are usually trained only with positive samples--entities that match the input mention's identifier--and do not explicitly learn from hard negative samples, which are entities that look similar but have different meanings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-negative-samples-in-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mismatched: Evaluating the Limits of Image Matching Approaches and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mismatched-evaluating-the-limits-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the rapid pace of research and the frequent introduction of new image matching methods, it is essential to evaluate them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mismatched-evaluating-the-limits-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreasonable Ineffectiveness of Nucleus Sampling on Mitigating Text Memorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-ineffectiveness-of-nucleus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work analyses the text memorization behavior of large language models (LLMs) when subjected to nucleus sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-unreasonable-ineffectiveness-of-nucleus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Recommender Systems Promote Local Music? A Reproducibility Study Using Music Streaming Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-recommender-systems-promote-local-music-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper examines the influence of recommender systems on local music representation, discussing prior findings from an empirical study on the LFM-2b public dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-recommender-systems-promote-local-music-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GradBias: Unveiling Word Influence on Bias in Text-to-Image Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradbias-unveiling-word-influence-on-bias-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenBias detects and quantifies biases, while GradBias determines the contribution of individual prompt words on biases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradbias-unveiling-word-influence-on-bias-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring the Accuracy of Automatic Speech Recognition Solutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-accuracy-of-automatic-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study shows that despite the recent improvements of ASR, common services lack reliability in accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-the-accuracy-of-automatic-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs generate structurally realistic social networks but overestimate political homophily</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-generate-structurally-realistic-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To answer these questions, we develop three prompting methods for network generation and compare the generated networks to real social networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-generate-structurally-realistic-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Reasoning: A Non-Technical Introduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-reasoning-a-non-technical-introduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the concept and a default implementation of Guided Reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-reasoning-a-non-technical-introduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CogVLM2: Visual Language Models for Image and Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogvlm2-visual-language-models-for-image-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Beginning with VisualGLM and CogVLM, we are continuously exploring VLMs in pursuit of enhanced vision-language fusion, efficient higher-resolution architecture, and broader modalities and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cogvlm2-visual-language-models-for-image-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Modality-agnostic Label-efficient Segmentation with Entropy-Regularized Distribution Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-modality-agnostic-label-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we innovate in the pseudo-label generation to make our ERDA consistently effective across both 2D and 3D data modalities for segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-modality-agnostic-label-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Pose-Based Temporal Action Segmentation for Figure Skating: A Fine-Grained and Jump Procedure-Aware Annotation Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pose-based-temporal-action-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the experimental results, we validated the usefulness of 3D pose features as input and the fine-grained dataset for the TAS model in figure skating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-pose-based-temporal-action-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResVG: Enhancing Relation and Semantic Understanding in Multiple Instances for Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resvg-enhancing-relation-and-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method generates additional training data by synthesizing images containing multiple objects of the same category and pseudo queries based on their spatial relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resvg-enhancing-relation-and-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have witnessed Spiking Neural Networks (SNNs) gaining attention for their ultra-low energy consumption and high biological plausibility compared with traditional Artificial Neural Networks (ANNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissecting Out-of-Distribution Detection and Open-Set Recognition: A Critical Analysis of Methods and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-out-of-distribution-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting test-time distribution shift has emerged as a key capability for safely deployed machine learning models, with the question being tackled under various guises in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissecting-out-of-distribution-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eigen-Cluster VIS: Improving Weakly-supervised Video Instance Segmentation by Leveraging Spatio-temporal Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigen-cluster-vis-improving-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method is based on two key innovations: a Temporal Eigenvalue Loss (TEL) and a clip-level Quality Cluster Coefficient (QCC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigen-cluster-vis-improving-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examination of Code generated by Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examination-of-code-generated-by-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs), such as ChatGPT and Copilot, are transforming software development by automating code generation and, arguably, enable rapid prototyping, support education, and boost productivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examination-of-code-generated-by-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Conditional Image Generation with Explainable Latent Space Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-conditional-image-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of image synthesis, achieving fidelity to a reference image while adhering to conditional prompts remains a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-conditional-image-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Facial Expression Recognition of Static and Dynamic Emotions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-facial-expression-recognition-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial expression recognition (FER) aims to analyze emotional states from static images and dynamic sequences, which is pivotal in enhancing anthropomorphic communication among humans, robots, and digital avatars by leveraging AI technologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-facial-expression-recognition-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-MoD: Making LLaVA Tiny via MoE Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-mod-making-llava-tiny-via-moe-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LLaVA-MoD, a novel framework designed to enable the efficient training of small-scale Multimodal Language Models (s-MLLM) by distilling knowledge from large-scale MLLM (l-MLLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-mod-making-llava-tiny-via-moe-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Benefits of Visual Stabilization for Frame- and Event-based Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-benefits-of-visual-stabilization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assuming that the camera's attitude is available, we evaluate the benefits of stabilization in two perception applications: feature tracking and estimating the translation component of the camera's ego-motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-benefits-of-visual-stabilization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SITransformer: Shared Information-Guided Transformer for Extreme Multimodal Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sitransformer-shared-information-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extreme Multimodal Summarization with Multimodal Output (XMSMO) becomes an attractive summarization approach by integrating various types of information to create extremely concise yet informative summaries for individual modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sitransformer-shared-information-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Levenshtein: Leveraging Multiple Algorithms for Robust Word Error Rate Computations And Granular Error Classifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-levenshtein-leveraging-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Word Error Rate (WER) is the common measure of accuracy for Automatic Speech Recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-levenshtein-leveraging-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstanSeg: an embedding-based instance segmentation algorithm optimized for accurate, efficient and portable cell segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instanseg-an-embedding-based-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cell and nucleus segmentation are fundamental tasks for quantitative bioimage analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instanseg-an-embedding-based-instance</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
