<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 09:13:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>XEngine: Optimal Tensor Rematerialization for Neural Networks in Heterogeneous Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xengine-optimal-tensor-rematerialization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this, we formulate a mixed-integer quadratic program (MIQP) to schedule operators of deep learning networks on heterogeneous systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xengine-optimal-tensor-rematerialization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Training Dynamics: Identifying Mislabeled Data Beyond Manually Designed Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-training-dynamics-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While mislabeled or ambiguously-labeled samples in the training set could negatively affect the performance of deep models, diagnosing the dataset and identifying mislabeled samples helps to improve the generalization power.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-training-dynamics-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photo-Realistic Out-of-domain GAN inversion via Invertibility Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photo-realistic-out-of-domain-gan-inversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel framework that enhances the fidelity of human face inversion by designing a new module to decompose the input images to ID and OOD partitions with invertibility masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/photo-realistic-out-of-domain-gan-inversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Pre-Trained Weights Through Meta-Heuristics Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-pre-trained-weights-through-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning algorithms have been extensively researched throughout the last decade, leading to unprecedented advances in a broad range of applications, such as image classification and reconstruction, object recognition, and text categorization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-pre-trained-weights-through-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visconde: Multi-document QA with GPT-3 and Neural Reranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visconde-multi-document-qa-with-gpt-3-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a question-answering system that can answer questions whose supporting evidence is spread over multiple (potentially long) documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visconde-multi-document-qa-with-gpt-3-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are reasoners with Self-Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-reasoners-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new method called self-verification that uses the conclusion of the CoT as a condition to build a new sample and asks the LLM to re-predict the original conditions which be masked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-reasoners-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Label Smoothing on Multi-hop Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-label-smoothing-on-multi-hop</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Label smoothing is a regularization technique widely used in supervised learning to improve the generalization of models on various tasks, such as image classification and machine translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-label-smoothing-on-multi-hop</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Prompts for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-prompts-for-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of laborious human engineering, we propose prompt adaptation, a general framework that automatically adapts original user input to model-preferred prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-prompts-for-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reference-based Image and Video Super-Resolution via C2-Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-based-image-and-video-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these challenges, we propose C2-Matching in this work, which performs explicit robust matching crossing transformation and resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reference-based-image-and-video-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answering Complex Logical Queries on Knowledge Graphs via Query Tree Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answering-complex-logical-queries-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose QTO (Query Tree Optimization) that can efficiently find the exact optimal solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answering-complex-logical-queries-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-guided Text Prompt for Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-guided-text-prompt-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel Position-guided Text Prompt (PTP) paradigm to enhance the visual grounding ability of cross-modal models trained with VLP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-guided-text-prompt-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Accident Prediction in Driving Scenes: A Multimodality Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-accident-prediction-in-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, the text description provides a dense semantic description guidance for the primary context of the traffic scene, while the driver attention provides a traction to focus on the critical region closely correlating with safe driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-accident-prediction-in-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query-as-context Pre-training for Dense Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-as-context-pre-training-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Query-as-context pre-training assumes that the predicted query is a special context for the document and uses contrastive learning or contextual masked auto-encoding learning to compress the document and query into dense vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-as-context-pre-training-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Diffusion for Language Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-for-language-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have achieved great success in modeling continuous data modalities such as images, audio, and video, but have seen limited use in discrete domains such as language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-diffusion-for-language-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomized Quantization for Data Agnostic Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-quantization-for-data-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towards this end, masking has emerged as a generic and powerful tool where content is withheld along the sequential dimension, e. g., spatial in images, temporal in audio, and syntactic in language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/randomized-quantization-for-data-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergent Analogical Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-analogical-reasoning-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advent of large language models - large neural networks trained on a simple predictive objective over a massive corpus of natural language - has reinvigorated debate over whether human cognitive capacities might emerge in such generic models given sufficient training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-analogical-reasoning-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferring General Multimodal Pretrained Models to Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferring-general-multimodal-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a new method, OFA-OCR, to transfer multimodal pretrained models to text recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferring-general-multimodal-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Diffusion: Learning Multi-Modal Diffusion Models for Joint Audio and Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-diffusion-learning-multi-modal-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generate joint audio-video pairs, we propose a novel Multi-Modal Diffusion model (i. e., MM-Diffusion), with two-coupled denoising autoencoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-diffusion-learning-multi-modal-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Million-scale Object Detection with Large Vision Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/million-scale-object-detection-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past few years, developing a broad, universal, and general-purpose computer vision system has become a hot topic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/million-scale-object-detection-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation Ability Map: Interpret deep features for medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-ability-map-interpret-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, our method can provide a mean SA score which can give a performance estimation of the output on the test images without ground-truth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-ability-map-interpret-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Language Model Behaviors with Model-Written Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-language-model-behaviors-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find some of the first examples of inverse scaling in RL from Human Feedback (RLHF), where more RLHF makes LMs worse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-language-model-behaviors-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLOOM+1: Adding Language Support to BLOOM for Zero-Shot Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bloom-1-adding-language-support-to-bloom-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The BLOOM model is a large open-source multilingual language model capable of zero-shot learning, but its pretraining was limited to 46 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bloom-1-adding-language-support-to-bloom-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving QMLTP Problems by Translation to Higher-order Logic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-qmltp-problems-by-translation-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes an evaluation of Automated Theorem Proving (ATP) systems on problems taken from the QMLTP library of first-order modal logic problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-qmltp-problems-by-translation-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NusaCrowd: Open Source Initiative for Indonesian NLP Resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusacrowd-open-source-initiative-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present NusaCrowd, a collaborative initiative to collect and unite existing resources for Indonesian languages, including opening access to previously non-public resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nusacrowd-open-source-initiative-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Object-level Point Augmentor for Semi-supervised 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-object-level-point-augmentor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an object-level point augmentor (OPA) that performs local transformations for semi-supervised 3D object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-object-level-point-augmentor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marginal-Certainty-aware Fair Ranking Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginal-certainty-aware-fair-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In MCFair, we first develop a ranking objective that includes uncertainty, fairness, and user utility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marginal-certainty-aware-fair-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextually Enhanced ES-dRNN with Dynamic Attention for Short-Term Load Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextually-enhanced-es-drnn-with-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These cells enable the model to capture short-term, long-term and seasonal dependencies across time series as well as to weight dynamically the input information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextually-enhanced-es-drnn-with-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Digital "Echo Chambers": The Role of Viewpoint Diversity in Political Discussion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-digital-echo-chambers-the-role-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the diversity scores for both Fragmentation and Representation are lower for immigration than for DST.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-digital-echo-chambers-the-role-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don't Forget Your ABC's: Evaluating the State-of-the-Art in Chat-Oriented Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-forget-your-abc-s-evaluating-the-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been great recent advancement in human-computer chat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/don-t-forget-your-abc-s-evaluating-the-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUCRe: Leveraging Scene Structure for Underwater Color Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sucre-leveraging-scene-structure-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By following points in multiple images and tracking their intensities at different distances to the sensor we constrain the optimization of the image formation model parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sucre-leveraging-scene-structure-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JEMMA: An Extensible Java Dataset for ML4Code Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jemma-an-extensible-java-dataset-for-ml4code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the utility of the dataset, we also report results from two empirical studies on our data, ultimately showing that significant work lies ahead in the design of context-aware source code models that can reason over a broader network of source code entities in a software project, the very task that JEMMA is designed to help with.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jemma-an-extensible-java-dataset-for-ml4code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Better Choice: Entire-space Datasets for Aspect Sentiment Triplet Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-better-choice-entire-space-datasets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect sentiment triplet extraction (ASTE) aims to extract aspect term, sentiment and opinion term triplets from sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-better-choice-entire-space-datasets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Struct: A Machine Learning Pipeline for Mining Structured Data from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2struct-a-machine-learning-pipeline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many analysis and prediction tasks require the extraction of structured data from unstructured texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2struct-a-machine-learning-pipeline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Citi Bike Demand Evolution Using Dynamic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-citi-bike-demand-evolution-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we attempt to apply a graph neural network model to predict bike demand in the New York City, Citi Bike dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-citi-bike-demand-evolution-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style-Hallucinated Dual Consistency Learning: A Unified Framework for Visual Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-hallucinated-dual-consistency-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we present a novel style hallucination module (SHM) to generate style-diversified samples that are essential to consistency learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-hallucinated-dual-consistency-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recall, Expand and Multi-Candidate Cross-Encode: Fast and Accurate Ultra-Fine Entity Typing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recall-expand-and-multi-candidate-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also found MCCE is very effective in fine-grained (130 types) and coarse-grained (9 types) entity typing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recall-expand-and-multi-candidate-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MeSH Suggester: A Library and System for MeSH Term Suggestion for Systematic Review Boolean Query Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-suggester-a-library-and-system-for-mesh</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One challenge to creating an effective systematic review Boolean query is the selection of effective MeSH Terms to include in the query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesh-suggester-a-library-and-system-for-mesh</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Uncertainty Distribution in Deep Learning for Unsupervised Underwater Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-uncertainty-distribution-in-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This makes it difficult to train supervised deep learning models on large and diverse datasets, which can limit the model's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-uncertainty-distribution-in-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking the Role of Scale for In-Context Learning: An Interpretability-based Case Study at 66 Billion Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-role-of-scale-for-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using a 66 billion parameter language model (OPT-66B) across a diverse set of 14 downstream tasks, we find this is indeed the case: $\sim$70% of attention heads and $\sim$20% of feed forward networks can be removed with minimal decline in task performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-role-of-scale-for-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Wavelet Representation for Compact Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-wavelet-representation-for-compact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There have been recent studies on how to reduce these computational inefficiencies by using additional data structures, such as grids or trees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-wavelet-representation-for-compact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confidence-aware Training of Smoothed Classifiers for Certified Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-training-of-smoothed-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under the smoothed classifiers, the fundamental trade-off between accuracy and (adversarial) robustness has been well evidenced in the literature: i. e., increasing the robustness of a classifier for an input can be at the expense of decreased accuracy for some other inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confidence-aware-training-of-smoothed-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEATs: Audio Pre-Training with Acoustic Tokenizers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beats-audio-pre-training-with-acoustic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first iteration, we use random projection as the acoustic tokenizer to train an audio SSL model in a mask and label prediction manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beats-audio-pre-training-with-acoustic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Robots to Evaluate Robots: Example-Based Interactive Reward Functions for Policy Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-robots-to-evaluate-robots-example</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physical interactions can often help reveal information that is not readily apparent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-robots-to-evaluate-robots-example</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flattening-Net: Deep Regular 2D Representation for 3D Point Cloud Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flattening-net-deep-regular-2d-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an unsupervised deep neural architecture called Flattening-Net to represent irregular 3D point clouds of arbitrary geometry and topology as a completely regular 2D point geometry image (PGI) structure, in which coordinates of spatial points are captured in colors of image pixels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flattening-net-deep-regular-2d-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Open-set Recognition for Memory Workload</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-open-set-recognition-for-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How can we accurately identify new memory workloads while classifying known memory workloads?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-open-set-recognition-for-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are We Ready for Vision-Centric Driving Streaming Perception? The ASAP Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-we-ready-for-vision-centric-driving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the problem, we propose the Autonomous-driving StreAming Perception (ASAP) benchmark, which is the first benchmark to evaluate the online performance of vision-centric perception in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-we-ready-for-vision-centric-driving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Global Distribution for Federated Learning with Label Distribution Skew</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-global-distribution-for-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It introduces a global Generative Adversarial Network to model the global data distribution without access to local datasets, so the global model can be trained using the global information of data distribution without privacy leakage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-global-distribution-for-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling Styles in Neural Machine Translation with Activation Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-styles-in-neural-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we re-visit this task and propose a multiway stylized machine translation (MSMT) benchmark, which includes multiple categories of styles in four language directions to push the boundary of this task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlling-styles-in-neural-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evolutionary Multitasking Algorithm with Multiple Filtering for High-Dimensional Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolutionary-multitasking-algorithm-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, this paper devises a new EMT algorithm for FS in high-dimensional classification, which first adopts different filtering methods to produce multiple tasks and then modifies a competitive swarm optimizer to efficiently solve these related tasks via knowledge transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolutionary-multitasking-algorithm-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trusting the Explainers: Teacher Validation of Explainable Artificial Intelligence for Course Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trusting-the-explainers-teacher-validation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models for learning analytics have become increasingly popular over the last few years; however, these approaches are still not widely adopted in real-world settings, likely due to a lack of trust and transparency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trusting-the-explainers-teacher-validation-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
