<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 21:07:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised multimodal modeling of cognitive and brain health trajectories for early dementia prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multimodal-modeling-of-cognitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to supervised classification approaches that require labeled data, we propose an unsupervised multimodal trajectory modeling (MTM) approach based on a mixture of state space models that captures changes in longitudinal data (i. e., trajectories) and stratifies individuals without using clinical diagnosis for model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-multimodal-modeling-of-cognitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenBA-V2: Reaching 77.3% High Compression Ratio with Fast Multi-Stage Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openba-v2-reaching-77-3-high-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have played an important role in many fields due to their powerful capabilities. However, their massive number of parameters leads to high deployment requirements and incurs significant inference costs, which impedes their practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openba-v2-reaching-77-3-high-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link Stealing Attacks Against Inductive Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-stealing-attacks-against-inductive-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper fills the gap by conducting a systematic privacy analysis of inductive GNNs through the lens of link stealing attacks, one of the most popular attacks that are specifically designed for GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-stealing-attacks-against-inductive-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting the Most Conflicting Pair of Candidates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-the-most-conflicting-pair-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study committee elections from a perspective of finding the most conflicting candidates, that is, candidates that imply the largest amount of conflict, as per voter preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-the-most-conflicting-pair-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Models for Atypical Serotonergic Cells Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-models-for-atypical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose deep learning models capable of discriminating typical and atypical serotonergic neurons from non-serotonergic cells with high accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-models-for-atypical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning of Time Series Representation via Diffusion Process and Imputation-Interpolation-Forecasting Mask</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time Series Representation Learning (TSRL) focuses on generating informative representations for various Time Series (TS) modeling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-of-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outlier-robust Kalman Filtering through Generalised Bayes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-kalman-filtering-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We derive a novel, provably robust, and closed-form Bayesian update rule for online filtering in state-space models in the presence of outliers and misspecified measurement models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/outlier-robust-kalman-filtering-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CuMo: Scaling Multimodal LLM with Co-Upcycled Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cumo-scaling-multimodal-llm-with-co-upcycled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Multimodal Large Language Models (LLMs) have focused primarily on scaling by increasing text-image pair data and enhancing LLMs to improve performance on multimodal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cumo-scaling-multimodal-llm-with-co-upcycled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Edge Federated Learning for Intelligent Mobile-Health Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-edge-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, enabling learning from distributed data over such edge Internet of Things (IoT) systems (e. g., mobile-health and wearable technologies, involving sensitive personal/medical data) in a privacy-preserving fashion presents a major challenge mainly due to their stringent resource constraints, i. e., limited computing capacity, communication bandwidth, memory storage, and battery lifetime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-edge-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Dialect Robustness of Language Models via Conversation Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-dialect-robustness-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With an evergrowing number of LLMs reporting superlative performance for English, their ability to perform equitably for different dialects of English (i. e., dialect robustness) needs to be ascertained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-dialect-robustness-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain of Attack: a Semantic-Driven Contextual Multi-Turn attacker for LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-attack-a-semantic-driven-contextual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CoA is a semantic-driven contextual multi-turn attack method that adaptively adjusts the attack policy through contextual feedback and semantic relevance during multi-turn of dialogue with a large model, resulting in the model producing unreasonable or harmful content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-attack-a-semantic-driven-contextual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Level Superoptimizer for Tensor Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-level-superoptimizer-for-tensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Mirage, the first multi-level superoptimizer for tensor programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-level-superoptimizer-for-tensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-Space Visual Prompting for Efficient Vision-Language Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-space-visual-prompting-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current solutions for efficiently constructing large vision-language (VL) models follow a two-step paradigm: projecting the output of pre-trained vision encoders to the input space of pre-trained language models as visual prompts; and then transferring the models to downstream VL tasks via end-to-end parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-space-visual-prompting-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MasterWeaver: Taming Editability and Identity for Personalized Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masterweaver-taming-editability-and-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present MasterWeaver, a test-time tuning-free method designed to generate personalized images with both faithful identity fidelity and flexible editability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masterweaver-taming-editability-and-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Multimodal LLMs as World Models for Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-multimodal-llms-as-world-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a sober look at the application of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) within the domain of autonomous driving and challenge/verify some common assumptions, focusing on their ability to reason and interpret dynamic driving scenarios through sequences of images/frames in a closed-loop control environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-multimodal-llms-as-world-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Visual Speech Recognition based on Regulated Transformer and Spatio-Temporal Fusion Strategy for Driver Assistive Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-speech-recognition-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The article introduces a novel audio-visual speech command recognition transformer (AVCRFormer) specifically designed for robust AVSR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-speech-recognition-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Care: Assessing the Healthcare Implications of Pre-training Data on Language Model Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-care-assessing-the-healthcare</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are increasingly essential in processing natural languages, yet their application is frequently compromised by biases and inaccuracies originating in their training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-care-assessing-the-healthcare</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Stream Keypoint Attention Network for Sign Language Recognition and Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-keypoint-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting framework is denoted as MSKA-SLR, which is expanded into a sign language translation (SLT) model through the straightforward addition of an extra translation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-stream-keypoint-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Real-World Robot Manipulation Policies in Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-real-world-robot-manipulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then employ these approaches to create SIMPLER, a collection of simulated environments for manipulation policy evaluation on common real robot setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-real-world-robot-manipulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Hierarchical Graph Alignment Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hierarchical-graph-alignment-kernels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typical R-convolution graph kernels invoke the kernel functions that decompose graphs into non-isomorphic substructures and compare them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-hierarchical-graph-alignment-kernels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rectified Gaussian kernel multi-view k-means clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectified-gaussian-kernel-multi-view-k-means</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show two new variants of multi-view k-means (MVKM) algorithms to address multi-view data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectified-gaussian-kernel-multi-view-k-means</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Statements in Text: A Domain-Agnostic Few-Shot Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-statements-in-text-a-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we propose and release a qualitative and versatile few-shot learning methodology as a common paradigm for any claim-based textual classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-statements-in-text-a-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenFactCheck: A Unified Framework for Factuality Evaluation of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openfactcheck-a-unified-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increased use of large language models (LLMs) across a variety of real-world applications calls for mechanisms to verify the factual accuracy of their outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openfactcheck-a-unified-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Multimodal Large Language Models with Visual Tokens Withdrawal for Rapid Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is inspired by two intriguing phenomena we have observed: (1) the attention sink phenomenon that is prevalent in LLMs also persists in MLLMs, suggesting that initial tokens and nearest tokens receive the majority of attention, while middle vision tokens garner minimal attention in deep layers; (2) the presence of information migration, which implies that visual information is transferred to subsequent text tokens within the first few layers of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Text-to-Image Diffusion Models Are Versatile Representation Learners for Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-text-to-image-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This has led to the emergence of pre-trained vision-language models as a tool for transferring representations learned from internet-scale data to downstream tasks and new domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-text-to-image-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous max-flow augmentation of self-supervised few-shot learning on SPECT left ventricles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-max-flow-augmentation-of-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single-Photon Emission Computed Tomography (SPECT) left ventricular assessment protocols are important for detecting ischemia in high-risk patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-max-flow-augmentation-of-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lumina-T2X: Transforming Text into Any Modality, Resolution, and Duration via Flow-based Large Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumina-t2x-transforming-text-into-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sora unveils the potential of scaling Diffusion Transformer for generating photorealistic images and videos at arbitrary resolutions, aspect ratios, and durations, yet it still lacks sufficient implementation details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lumina-t2x-transforming-text-into-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characteristic Learning for Provable One Step Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristic-learning-for-provable-one-step</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the characteristic generator, a novel one-step generative model that combines the efficiency of sampling in Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) with the stable performance of flow-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristic-learning-for-provable-one-step</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LayerPlexRank: Exploring Node Centrality and Layer Influence through Algebraic Connectivity in Multiplex Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerplexrank-exploring-node-centrality-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the calculation of centrality in complex networks becomes increasingly vital across technological, biological, and social systems, precise and scalable ranking methods are essential for understanding these networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layerplexrank-exploring-node-centrality-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-HMC: Parameter Inference with Diffusion Model driven Hamiltonian Monte Carlo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-hmc-parameter-inference-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work uses a single diffusion generative model to address these interlinked objectives -- as a surrogate model or emulator for cold dark matter density fields conditional on input cosmological parameters, and as a parameter inference model that solves the inverse problem of constraining the cosmological parameters of an input field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-hmc-parameter-inference-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Power of MLLMs for Transferable Text-to-Image Person ReID</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-mllms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose a novel method that uses MLLMs to caption images according to various templates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-power-of-mllms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiasKG: Adversarial Knowledge Graphs to Induce Bias in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biaskg-adversarial-knowledge-graphs-to-induce</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new methodology for attacking language models with knowledge graph augmented generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biaskg-adversarial-knowledge-graphs-to-induce</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Educational Program Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-educational-program-repair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of large language models (LLMs) has sparked enormous interest due to their potential application across a range of educational tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-educational-program-repair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sparse Tensor Generator with Efficient Feature Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sparse-tensor-generator-with-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse tensor operations are gaining attention in emerging applications such as social networks, deep learning, diagnosis, crime, and review analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sparse-tensor-generator-with-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HILCodec: High Fidelity and Lightweight Neural Audio Codec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hilcodec-high-fidelity-and-lightweight-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advancement of end-to-end neural audio codecs enables compressing audio at very low bitrates while reconstructing the output audio with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hilcodec-high-fidelity-and-lightweight-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAMPLER: Learning to Retrieve Cross-Lingual In-Context Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xampler-learning-to-retrieve-cross-lingual-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies have shown that leveraging off-the-shelf or fine-tuned retrievers, capable of retrieving high-quality in-context examples, significantly improves in-context learning of English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xampler-learning-to-retrieve-cross-lingual-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADELIE: Aligning Large Language Models on Information Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adelie-aligning-large-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) usually fall short on information extraction (IE) tasks and struggle to follow the complex instructions of IE tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adelie-aligning-large-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding adaptive shrinkage by co-data to improve regression-based prediction and feature selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-adaptive-shrinkage-by-co-data-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, group-adaptive shrinkage is compared with the better-known sparse group-lasso by evaluating feature selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-adaptive-shrinkage-by-co-data-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenthicNet: A global compilation of seafloor images for deep learning applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benthicnet-a-global-compilation-of-seafloor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in underwater imaging enable the collection of extensive seafloor image datasets that are necessary for monitoring important benthic ecosystems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benthicnet-a-global-compilation-of-seafloor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenESS: Event-based Semantic Scene Understanding with Open Vocabularies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openess-event-based-semantic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event-based semantic segmentation (ESS) is a fundamental yet challenging task for event camera sensing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openess-event-based-semantic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Codecfake Dataset and Countermeasures for the Universally Detection of Deepfake Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-codecfake-dataset-and-countermeasures-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proliferation of Audio Language Model (ALM) based deepfake audio, there is an urgent need for effective detection methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-codecfake-dataset-and-countermeasures-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health Index Estimation Through Integration of General Knowledge with Unsupervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/health-index-estimation-through-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hybrid models combining prior knowledge about degradation with deep learning models have been proposed to overcome this challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/health-index-estimation-through-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Data Layout Optimization with Worst-case Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-data-layout-optimization-with-worst</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an algorithmic framework OReO that makes online reorganization decisions to balance the benefits of improved query performance with the costs of reorganization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-data-layout-optimization-with-worst</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pedestrian Attribute Recognition as Label-balanced Multi-label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-attribute-recognition-as-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rooting in the scarcity of most attributes, realistic pedestrian attribute datasets exhibit unduly skewed data distribution, from which two types of model failures are delivered: (1) label imbalance: model predictions lean greatly towards the side of majority labels; (2) semantics imbalance: model is easily overfitted on the under-represented attributes due to their insufficient semantic diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pedestrian-attribute-recognition-as-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataSP: A Differential All-to-All Shortest Path Algorithm for Learning Costs and Predicting Paths with Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datasp-a-differential-all-to-all-shortest</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning latent costs of transitions on graphs from trajectories demonstrations under various contextual features is challenging but useful for path planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/datasp-a-differential-all-to-all-shortest</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Data-Efficient 3D Scene Understanding for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-data-efficient-3d-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient data utilization is crucial for advancing 3D scene understanding in autonomous driving, where reliance on heavily human-annotated LiDAR point clouds challenges fully supervised methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-data-efficient-3d-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TENet: Targetness Entanglement Incorporating with Multi-Scale Pooling and Mutually-Guided Fusion for RGB-E Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tenet-targetness-entanglement-incorporating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is currently strong interest in improving visual object tracking by augmenting the RGB modality with the output of a visual event camera that is particularly informative about the scene motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tenet-targetness-entanglement-incorporating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Adaptation for Foundation Model-based Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-adaptation-for-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It becomes a new open challenge to enable the foundation model to capture user preference changes in a timely manner with reasonable communication and computation costs while preserving privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-adaptation-for-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Noisy Class Posterior with Part-level Labels for Noisy Label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-noisy-class-posterior-with-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing this framework with part-level labels, we can learn the noisy class posteriors more precisely by guiding the model to integrate information from various parts, ultimately improving the classification performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-noisy-class-posterior-with-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selective Classification Under Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-classification-under-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In selective classification (SC), a classifier abstains from making predictions that are likely to be wrong to avoid excessive errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selective-classification-under-distribution</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
