<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 21:07:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GD-MAE: Generative Decoder for MAE Pre-training on LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gd-mae-generative-decoder-for-mae-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous 3D MAE frameworks, which either design a complex decoder to infer masked information from maintained regions or adopt sophisticated masking strategies, we instead propose a much simpler paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gd-mae-generative-decoder-for-mae-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZeroKBC: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Zero-Shot Knowledge Base Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerokbc-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there has been limited research on the zero-shot KBC settings, where we need to deal with unseen entities and relations that emerge in a constantly growing knowledge base.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zerokbc-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-aware Message Broadcasting for Efficient Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-message-broadcasting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this way, our message broadcasting encourages the group tokens to learn more informative and diverse information for effective domain alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-message-broadcasting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IncepFormer: Efficient Inception Transformer with Pyramid Pooling for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incepformer-efficient-inception-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation usually benefits from global contexts, fine localisation information, multi-scale features, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incepformer-efficient-inception-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternVideo: General Video Foundation Models via Generative and Discriminative Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-general-video-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, InternVideo efficiently explores masked video modeling and video-language contrastive learning as the pretraining objectives, and selectively coordinates video representations of these two complementary frameworks in a learnable manner to boost various video applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internvideo-general-video-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Switching to Discriminative Image Captioning by Relieving a Bottleneck of Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switching-to-discriminative-image-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discriminativeness is a desirable feature of image captions: captions should describe the characteristic details of input images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switching-to-discriminative-image-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Data Heterogeneity in Federated Learning with Class Prototypes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose FedNH, a novel method that improves the local models' performance for both personalization and generalization by combining the uniformity and semantics of class prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-data-heterogeneity-in-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniGeo: Unifying Geometry Logical Reasoning via Reformulating Mathematical Expression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unigeo-unifying-geometry-logical-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Naturally, we also present a unified multi-task Geometric Transformer framework, Geoformer, to tackle calculation and proving problems simultaneously in the form of sequence generation, which finally shows the reasoning ability can be improved on both two tasks by unifying formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unigeo-unifying-geometry-logical-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PØDA: Prompt-driven Zero-shot Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poda-prompt-driven-zero-shot-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptation has been vastly investigated in computer vision but still requires access to target images at train time, which might be intractable in some conditions, especially for long-tail samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poda-prompt-driven-zero-shot-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking AutoML algorithms on a collection of binary problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-automl-algorithms-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated machine learning (AutoML) algorithms have grown in popularity due to their high performance and flexibility to adapt to different problems and data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-automl-algorithms-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FretNet: Continuous-Valued Pitch Contour Streaming for Polyphonic Guitar Tablature Transcription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fretnet-continuous-valued-pitch-contour</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a GTT formulation that estimates continuous-valued pitch contours, grouping them according to their string and fret of origin.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fretnet-continuous-valued-pitch-contour</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dist-PU: Positive-Unlabeled Learning from a Label Distribution Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dist-pu-positive-unlabeled-learning-from-a-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positive-Unlabeled (PU) learning tries to learn binary classifiers from a few labeled positive examples with many unlabeled ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dist-pu-positive-unlabeled-learning-from-a-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Testing of Computer Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-testing-of-computer-vision-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision models often fail systematically on groups of data that share common semantic characteristics (e. g., rare objects or unusual scenes), but identifying these failure modes is a challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-testing-of-computer-vision-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Next Boundary Detection for Instance Segmentation of Tree Rings in Microscopy Images of Shrub Cross Sections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-next-boundary-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze the problem of detecting tree rings in microscopy images of shrub cross sections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-next-boundary-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss Adapted Plasticity in Deep Neural Networks to Learn from Data with Unreliable Sources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-adapted-plasticity-in-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When data is streaming from multiple sources, conventional training methods update model weights often assuming the same level of reliability for each source; that is: a model does not consider data quality of each source during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-adapted-plasticity-in-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document-Level Abstractive Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-abstractive-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of automatic text summarization produces a concise and fluent text summary while preserving key information and overall meaning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-abstractive-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Bridged Causal Interaction Network for Causal Emotion Entailment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-bridged-causal-interaction-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, social-interaction CSK serves as emotion-level bridge (E-bridge) and action-level bridge (A-bridge) to connect candidate utterances with the target one, which provides explicit causal clues for the Emotional Interaction module and Actional Interaction module to reason the target emotion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-bridged-causal-interaction-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FacT: Factor-Tuning for Lightweight Adaptation on Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-factor-tuning-for-lightweight-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has explored the potential to adapt a pre-trained vision transformer (ViT) by updating only a few parameters so as to improve storage efficiency, called parameter-efficient transfer learning (PETL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fact-factor-tuning-for-lightweight-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards human-compatible autonomous car: A study of non-verbal Turing test in automated driving with affective transition modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-compatible-autonomous-car-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Participants rode in autonomous cars (driven by either human or AI drivers) as a passenger and judged whether the driver was human or AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-human-compatible-autonomous-car-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Point Cloud Segmentation with Noisy Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-segmentation-with-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle boundary-level label noise, we also propose a variant ``PNAL-boundary " with a progressive boundary label cleaning strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-point-cloud-segmentation-with-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Conditional Diffusion Networks for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-conditional-diffusion-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rich semantics are further regarded as semantic prior to trigger the learning of Diffusion Transformer, which produces the output sentence in a diffusion process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-conditional-diffusion-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QEBVerif: Quantization Error Bound Verification of Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qebverif-quantization-error-bound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While promising attempts have been made to verify the quantization error bound between DNNs and their quantized counterparts, they are not complete and more importantly do not support fully quantified neural networks, namely, only weights are quantized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qebverif-quantization-error-bound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Baseline for Weather Forecasting Using Spatiotemporal Context Aggregation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-baseline-for-weather-forecasting-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional weather forecasting relies on domain expertise and computationally intensive numerical simulation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-baseline-for-weather-forecasting-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximal methods for point source localisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-methods-for-point-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point source localisation is generally modelled as a Lasso-type problem on measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-methods-for-point-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-resolution Probabilistic Rain Prediction from Satellite Data Using 3D U-Nets and EarthFormers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-probabilistic-rain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the model performance, multi-model ensemble and threshold optimization were used to produce the final probabilistic rain prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-probabilistic-rain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionInst: Diffusion Model for Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusioninst-diffusion-model-for-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes DiffusionInst, a novel framework that represents instances as instance-aware filters and formulates instance segmentation as a noise-to-filter denoising process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusioninst-diffusion-model-for-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Machine Translation with Contrastive Translation Memories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-machine-translation-with-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented Neural Machine Translation models have been successful in many translation scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-machine-translation-with-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSDA3D: Semi-supervised Domain Adaptation for 3D Object Detection from Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssda3d-semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these UDA solutions just yield unsatisfactory 3D detection results when there is a severe domain shift, e. g., from Waymo (64-beam) to nuScenes (32-beam).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssda3d-semi-supervised-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a more efficient computation of individual attribute and policy contribution for post-hoc explanation of cooperative multi-agent systems using Myerson values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-efficient-computation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A quantitative assessment of the global importance of an agent in a team is as valuable as gold for strategists, decision-makers, and sports coaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-more-efficient-computation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VISEM-Tracking: Human Spermatozoa Tracking Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visem-tracking-human-spermatozoa-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, more data is needed to train supervised machine learning approaches in order to improve accuracy and reliability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visem-tracking-human-spermatozoa-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union-set Multi-source Model Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/union-set-multi-source-model-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model adaptation is proposed as a new domain adaptation problem which requires access to a pre-trained model instead of data for the source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/union-set-multi-source-model-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust convex biclustering with a tuning-free method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-convex-biclustering-with-a-tuning-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a tuning-free method for automatically selecting the optimal robustification parameter with high efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-convex-biclustering-with-a-tuning-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACRO: A multi-language toolkit for supporting Automated Checking of Research Outputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acro-a-multi-language-toolkit-for-supporting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper discusses the development of an open source tool ACRO, (Automatic Checking of Research Outputs) to assist researchers and data governance teams by distinguishing between: research output that is safe to publish; output that requires further analysis; and output that cannot be published because it creates substantial risk of disclosing private data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acro-a-multi-language-toolkit-for-supporting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dissimilar Nodes Improve Graph Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissimilar-nodes-improve-graph-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The existing Active Graph Embedding framework proposes to use centrality score, density score, and entropy score to evaluate the value of unlabeled nodes, and it has been shown to be capable of bringing some improvement to the node classification tasks of Graph Convolutional Networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dissimilar-nodes-improve-graph-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Med-Query: Steerable Parsing of 9-DoF Medical Anatomies with Query Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-query-steerable-parsing-of-9-dof-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For rib parsing, CT scans have been annotated at the rib instance-level for quantitative evaluation, similarly for spine vertebrae and abdominal organs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/med-query-steerable-parsing-of-9-dof-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataless FaceSwap Detection Approach Using Synthetic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataless-faceswap-detection-approach-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face swapping technology used to create "Deepfakes" has advanced significantly over the past few years and now enables us to create realistic facial manipulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataless-faceswap-detection-approach-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Architectures for FSCV, a Comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-architectures-for-fscv-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examined multiple deep neural network (DNN) architectures for suitability in predicting neurotransmitter concentrations from labeled in vitro fast scan cyclic voltammetry (FSCV) data collected on carbon fiber electrodes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-architectures-for-fscv-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding natural image stimuli from fMRI data with a surface-based convolutional network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-natural-image-stimuli-from-fmri-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel approach for this task, which we call Cortex2Image, to decode visual stimuli with high semantic fidelity and rich fine-grained detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-natural-image-stimuli-from-fmri-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L2SR: Learning to Sample and Reconstruct for Accelerated MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l2sr-learning-to-sample-and-reconstruct-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accelerated MRI aims to find a pair of samplers and reconstructors to reduce acquisition time while maintaining the reconstruction quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l2sr-learning-to-sample-and-reconstruct-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images Speak in Images: A Generalist Painter for In-Context Visual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-speak-in-images-a-generalist-painter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Painter, a generalist model which addresses these obstacles with an "image"-centric solution, that is, to redefine the output of core vision tasks as images, and specify task prompts as also images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/images-speak-in-images-a-generalist-painter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Imbalanced Data with Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-imbalanced-data-with-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we systematically investigate the ViTs' performance in LTR and propose LiVT to train ViTs from scratch only with LT data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-imbalanced-data-with-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Stroke-Level Modifications for Scene Text Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-stroke-level-modifications-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, two new datasets (Tamper-Syn2k and Tamper-Scene) are proposed to fill the blank of public evaluation datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-stroke-level-modifications-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIDE: Time Derivative Diffusion for Deep Learning on Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-time-derivative-diffusion-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A prominent paradigm for graph neural networks is based on the message passing framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tide-time-derivative-diffusion-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-general Crowd Counting in Unseen Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-general-crowd-counting-in-unseen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to train a model based on a single source domain which can generalize well on any unseen domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-general-crowd-counting-in-unseen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SceneRF: Self-Supervised Monocular 3D Scene Reconstruction with Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scenerf-self-supervised-monocular-3d-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the latter are conditioned on a single frame, scene reconstruction is achieved from the fusion of multiple synthesized novel depth views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scenerf-self-supervised-monocular-3d-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceQAN: Face Image Quality Assessment Through Adversarial Noise Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faceqan-face-image-quality-assessment-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to face image quality assessment, called FaceQAN, that is based on adversarial examples and relies on the analysis of adversarial noise which can be calculated with any FR model learned by using some form of gradient descent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faceqan-face-image-quality-assessment-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Neural Topic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-neural-topic-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the last years, topic modeling has emerged as a powerful technique for organizing and summarizing big collections of documents or searching for particular patterns in them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-neural-topic-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftCTC $\unicode{x2013}$ Semi-Supervised Learning for Text Recognition using Soft Pseudo-Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softctc-unicode-x2013-semi-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores semi-supervised training for sequence tasks, such as Optical Character Recognition or Automatic Speech Recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softctc-unicode-x2013-semi-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SASFormer: Transformers for Sparsely Annotated Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sasformer-transformers-for-sparsely-annotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a simple yet effective sparse annotated semantic segmentation framework based on segformer, dubbed SASFormer, that achieves remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sasformer-transformers-for-sparsely-annotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location-Aware Self-Supervised Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/location-aware-self-supervised-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose to pretrain networks for semantic segmentation by predicting the relative location of image parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/location-aware-self-supervised-transformers</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
