<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 21:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Reliability of Solutions in Linear Ordering Problem: New Probabilistic Insight and Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-of-solutions-in-linear-ordering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, our goal is to characterize the reliability of the solutions that can be obtained by the linear ordering problem (LOP) which is used to order $M$ objects from their pairwise comparisons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-of-solutions-in-linear-ordering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset of Industrial Metal Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-of-industrial-metal-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The close correspondence between synthetic and real-world data, and controlled variations, will facilitate sim-to-real research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-of-industrial-metal-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning with Bidirectional Transformers for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-with-bidirectional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning with Transformer-based sequence encoder has gained predominance for sequential recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-with-bidirectional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this Change the Answer to that Problem? Correlating Descriptions of Bug and Code Changes for Evaluating Patch Correctness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-change-the-answer-to-that-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, our intuition is that natural language processing can provide the necessary representations and models for assessing the semantic correlation between a bug (question) and a patch (answer).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-change-the-answer-to-that-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Plain Vision Transformer Towards Remote Sensing Foundation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-plain-vision-transformer-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we resort to plain vision transformers with about 100 million parameters and make the first attempt to propose large vision models customized for RS tasks and explore how such large models perform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-plain-vision-transformer-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LWGNet: Learned Wirtinger Gradients for Fourier Ptychographic Phase Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwgnet-learned-wirtinger-gradients-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fourier Ptychographic Microscopy (FPM) is an imaging procedure that overcomes the traditional limit on Space-Bandwidth Product (SBP) of conventional microscopes through computational means.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwgnet-learned-wirtinger-gradients-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Entity Linking Features for Emerging Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-entity-linking-features-for-emerging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity linking (EL) is the process of linking entity mentions appearing in text with their corresponding entities in a knowledge base.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-entity-linking-features-for-emerging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFNRec: Utilizing False Negative Samples for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufnrec-utilizing-false-negative-samples-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel method that can Utilize False Negative samples for sequential Recommendation (UFNRec) to improve model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufnrec-utilizing-false-negative-samples-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Medical Image Segmentation via Random Amplitude Mixup and Domain-Specific Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-medical-image-segmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the performance of our method on two public generalizable segmentation benchmarks in medical images, which validates our method could achieve the state-of-the-art performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-medical-image-segmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Message Passing for Visual Relationship Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-message-passing-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual relationship detection aims to detect the interactions between objects in an image; however, this task suffers from combinatorial explosion due to the variety of objects and interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-message-passing-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label-Free Synthetic Pretraining of Object Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-free-synthetic-pretraining-of-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our "SOLID" approach consists of two main components: (1) generating synthetic images using a collection of unlabelled 3D models with optimized scene arrangement; (2) pretraining an object detector on "instance detection" task - given a query image depicting an object, detecting all instances of the exact same object in a target image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-free-synthetic-pretraining-of-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snowpack Estimation in Key Mountainous Water Basins from Openly-Available, Multimodal Data Sources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snowpack-estimation-in-key-mountainous-water</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately estimating the snowpack in key mountainous basins is critical for water resource managers to make decisions that impact local and global economies, wildlife, and public policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snowpack-estimation-in-key-mountainous-water</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimistic Optimisation of Composite Objective with Exponentiated Update</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimistic-optimisation-of-composite</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the algorithms have efficient implementations for popular composite objectives and constraints and can be converted to stochastic optimisation algorithms with the optimal accelerated rate for smooth objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimistic-optimisation-of-composite</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRIT-VLP: Grouped Mini-batch Sampling for Efficient Vision and Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-vlp-grouped-mini-batch-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to the mainstream VLP methods, we highlight that two routinely applied steps during pre-training have crucial impact on the performance of the pre-trained model: in-batch hard negative sampling for image-text matching (ITM) and assigning the large masking probability for the masked language modeling (MLM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-vlp-grouped-mini-batch-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth Quality-Inspired Feature Manipulation for Efficient RGB-D and Video Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-quality-inspired-feature-manipulation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the fact that depth quality is a key factor influencing the accuracy, we propose an efficient depth quality-inspired feature manipulation (DQFM) process, which can dynamically filter depth features according to depth quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-quality-inspired-feature-manipulation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Map of Diverse Synthetic Stable Roommates Instances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-map-of-diverse-synthetic-stable-roommates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focusing on Stable Roommates (SR) instances, we contribute to the toolbox for conducting experiments for stable matching problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-map-of-diverse-synthetic-stable-roommates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Vision with Transformers: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vision-with-transformers-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of the transformer architecture in natural language processing has recently triggered attention in the computer vision field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-vision-with-transformers-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CheXRelNet: An Anatomy-Aware Model for Tracking Longitudinal Relationships between Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexrelnet-an-anatomy-aware-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the progress in utilizing deep learning to automate chest radiograph interpretation and disease diagnosis tasks, change between sequential Chest X-rays (CXRs) has received limited attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexrelnet-an-anatomy-aware-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstractive Meeting Summarization: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstractive-meeting-summarization-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning, and especially the invention of encoder-decoder architectures, has significantly improved the performance of abstractive summarization systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstractive-meeting-summarization-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPB-REC: Non-parametric Assessment of Uncertainty in Deep-learning-based MRI Reconstruction from Undersampled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/npb-rec-non-parametric-assessment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrated the added-value of our approach on the multi-coil brain MRI dataset, from the fastmri challenge, in comparison to the baseline E2E-VarNet with and without inference-time dropout.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/npb-rec-non-parametric-assessment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SKDCGN: Source-free Knowledge Distillation of Counterfactual Generative Networks using cGANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skdcgn-source-free-knowledge-distillation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, as an additional contribution, our paper conducts a thorough study on the composition mechanism of the CGNs, to gain a better understanding of how each mechanism influences the classification accuracy of an invariant classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skdcgn-source-free-knowledge-distillation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Diverse Document Representations with Deep Query Interactions for Dense Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-diverse-document-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new dense retrieval model which learns diverse document representations with deep query interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-diverse-document-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning for Quantum Technologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the dramatic progress in machine learning has begun to impact many areas of science and technology significantly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-and-machine-learning-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Graph Representation Learning Based Surgical Workflow Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-graph-representation-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, we propose a graph representation learning framework to comprehensively represent instrument motions in the surgical workflow anticipation problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-graph-representation-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving Fine-Grain Feature Information in Classification via Entropic Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-fine-grain-feature-information-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we are interested in the problem of solving fine-grain classification or regression, using a model trained on coarse-grain labels only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-fine-grain-feature-information-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No More Strided Convolutions or Pooling: A New CNN Building Block for Low-Resolution Images and Small Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-more-strided-convolutions-or-pooling-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional neural networks (CNNs) have made resounding success in many computer vision tasks such as image classification and object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-more-strided-convolutions-or-pooling-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Online Action Detection for Infant General Movements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-online-action-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although general movements assessment(GMA) has shown promising results in early CP detection, it is laborious.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-online-action-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Egocentric Hand-Object Segmentation: Dataset, Model, and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-egocentric-hand-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Egocentric videos offer fine-grained information for high-fidelity modeling of human behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-egocentric-hand-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Numerical Solvers for Large-Scale Simulation of Dynamical System via NeurVec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-numerical-solvers-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional numerical solvers used in the simulation are significantly limited by the step size for time integration, which hampers efficiency and feasibility especially when high accuracy is desired.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-numerical-solvers-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Granger Causality using Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granger-causality-using-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It helps in answering the question whether one time series is helpful in forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granger-causality-using-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph R-CNN: Towards Accurate 3D Object Detection with Semantic-Decorated Local Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-r-cnn-towards-accurate-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dynamic farthest voxel sampling is then applied to evenly sample the points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-r-cnn-towards-accurate-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Socially Intelligent Genetic Agents for the Emergence of Explicit Norms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socially-intelligent-genetic-agents-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Norms help regulate a society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socially-intelligent-genetic-agents-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDO-s3DCNNs: Partial Differential Operator Based Steerable 3D CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdo-s3dcnns-partial-differential-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Steerable models can provide very general and flexible equivariance by formulating equivariance requirements in the language of representation theory and feature fields, which has been recognized to be effective for many vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pdo-s3dcnns-partial-differential-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Fairness Is Basically Demographic Parity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-fairness-is-basically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Making fair decisions is crucial to ethically implementing machine learning algorithms in social settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-fairness-is-basically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Randomization-Enhanced Depth Simulation and Restoration for Perceiving and Grasping Specular and Transparent Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-randomization-enhanced-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Commercial depth sensors usually generate noisy and missing depths, especially on specular and transparent objects, which poses critical issues to downstream depth or point cloud-based tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-randomization-enhanced-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Analysis of the Laplace and Neural Tangent Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-analysis-of-the-laplace-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impracticality of this limit, the neural tangent kernel has allowed for a more direct study of neural networks and a gaze through the veil of their black box.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-analysis-of-the-laplace-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When can I Speak? Predicting initiation points for spoken dialogue agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-can-i-speak-predicting-initiation-points</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current spoken dialogue systems initiate their turns after a long period of silence (700-1000ms), which leads to little real-time feedback, sluggish responses, and an overall stilted conversational flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-can-i-speak-predicting-initiation-points</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-enabled Spatial Phase Unwrapping for 3D Measurement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-enabled-spatial-phase</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This system necessitates a robust spatial phase unwrapping (SPU) algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-enabled-spatial-phase</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Pancreatic Tumor Detection by Utilizing Clinically-Relevant Secondary Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-pancreatic-tumor-detection-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pancreatic cancer is one of the global leading causes of cancer-related deaths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-pancreatic-tumor-detection-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen CLIP Models are Efficient Video Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frozen-clip-models-are-efficient-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video recognition has been dominated by the end-to-end learning paradigm -- first initializing a video recognition model with weights of a pretrained image model and then conducting end-to-end training on videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frozen-clip-models-are-efficient-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow Me: Conversation Planning for Target-driven Recommendation Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-me-conversation-planning-for-target</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation dialogue systems aim to build social bonds with users and provide high-quality recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-me-conversation-planning-for-target</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoViT: Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation with a Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monovit-self-supervised-monocular-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised monocular depth estimation is an attractive solution that does not require hard-to-source depth labels for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monovit-self-supervised-monocular-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Adaptive and Altruistic PSO-based Deep Feature Selection Method for Pneumonia Detection from Chest X-Rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-and-altruistic-pso-based-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method successfully eliminates non-informative features obtained from the ResNet50 model, thereby improving the Pneumonia detection ability of the overall framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-and-altruistic-pso-based-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Is Invariant to Context and Vice Versa: On Learning Invariance for Out-Of-Distribution Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-is-invariant-to-context-and-vice-versa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If the context in every class is evenly distributed, OOD would be trivial because the context can be easily removed due to an underlying principle: class is invariant to context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-is-invariant-to-context-and-vice-versa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oversquashing in GNNs through the lens of information contraction and graph expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oversquashing-in-gnns-through-the-lens-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the spectral expansion properties of our algorithm with that of an existing curvature-based non-local rewiring strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oversquashing-in-gnns-through-the-lens-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HSIC-InfoGAN: Learning Unsupervised Disentangled Representations by Maximising Approximated Mutual Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsic-infogan-learning-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maximisation of mutual information is achieved by introducing an auxiliary network and training with a latent regression loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hsic-infogan-learning-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-Guided Collaborative Attention for Nighttime Thermal Infrared Image Colorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-guided-collaborative-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nighttime thermal infrared (NTIR) image colorization, also known as translation of NTIR images into daytime color images (NTIR2DC), is a promising research direction to facilitate nighttime scene perception for humans and intelligent systems under unfavorable conditions (e. g., complete darkness).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-guided-collaborative-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Resolution and Degradation Clues as Self-supervised Signal for Low Quality Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-resolution-and-degradation-clues-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image restoration algorithms such as super resolution (SR) are indispensable pre-processing modules for object detection in low quality images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-resolution-and-degradation-clues-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance As Identity: A Generic Online Paradigm for Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-as-identity-a-generic-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new online VIS paradigm named Instance As Identity (IAI), which models temporal information for both detection and tracking in an efficient way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-as-identity-a-generic-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gaze into the Internal Logic of Graph Neural Networks, with Logic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-gaze-into-the-internal-logic-of-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem is known as graph node property prediction and our approach will consist in emulating with help of a Prolog program the key information propagation steps of a Graph Neural Network's training and inference stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-gaze-into-the-internal-logic-of-graph</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
