<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 21:08:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Behavior Cloning Regularization for Stable Offline-to-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-behavior-cloning-regularization-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline reinforcement learning, by learning from a fixed dataset, makes it possible to learn agent behaviors without interacting with the environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-behavior-cloning-regularization-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLIF: A Unified Gated Leaky Integrate-and-Fire Neuron for Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glif-a-unified-gated-leaky-integrate-and-fire</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose GLIF, a unified spiking neuron, to fuse different bio-features in different neuronal behaviors, enlarging the representation space of spiking neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glif-a-unified-gated-leaky-integrate-and-fire</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redistributor: Transforming Empirical Data Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistributor-transforming-empirical-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an algorithm and package, Redistributor, which forces a collection of scalar samples to follow a desired distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redistributor-transforming-empirical-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spectral Method for Assessing and Combining Multiple Data Visualizations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spectral-method-for-assessing-and-combining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then it leverages the eigenscores to obtain a consensus visualization, which has much improved { quality over the individual visualizations in capturing the underlying true data structure.}]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spectral-method-for-assessing-and-combining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Data Supervised Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-supervised-salient-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel yet effective method for SOD, coined SODGAN, which can generate infinite high-quality image-mask pairs requiring only a few labeled data, and these synthesized pairs can replace the human-labeled DUTS-TR to train any off-the-shelf SOD model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-supervised-salient-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance Segmentation for Chinese Character Stroke Extraction, Datasets and Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-segmentation-for-chinese-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, there are no standardized benchmarks to provide a fair comparison between different stroke extraction methods, which, we believe, is a major impediment to the development of Chinese character stroke understanding and related tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-segmentation-for-chinese-character</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GlobalFlowNet: Video Stabilization using Deep Distilled Global Motion Estimates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globalflownet-video-stabilization-using-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in this work, we introduce a more general representation scheme, which adapts any existing optical flow network to ignore the moving objects and obtain a spatially smooth approximation of the global motion between video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/globalflownet-video-stabilization-using-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointly-Supervised Panoptic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointly-supervised-panoptic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new approach to applying point-level annotations for weakly-supervised panoptic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointly-supervised-panoptic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geo-SIC: Learning Deformable Geometric Shapes in Deep Image Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-sic-learning-deformable-geometric-shapes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a newly designed framework that (i) simultaneously derives features from both image and latent shape spaces with large intra-class variations; and (ii) gains increased model interpretability by allowing direct access to the underlying geometric features of image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-sic-learning-deformable-geometric-shapes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S3E: A Large-scale Multimodal Dataset for Collaborative SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3e-a-large-scale-multimodal-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advanced request to employ a team of robots to perform a task collaboratively, the research community has become increasingly interested in collaborative simultaneous localization and mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s3e-a-large-scale-multimodal-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Color Distributions Prior for Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-color-distributions-prior-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing image enhancement methods are typically designed to address either the over- or under-exposure problem in the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-color-distributions-prior-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEMETR: Diagnosing Evaluation Metrics for Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demetr-diagnosing-evaluation-metrics-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While machine translation evaluation metrics based on string overlap (e. g., BLEU) have their limitations, their computations are transparent: the BLEU score assigned to a particular candidate translation can be traced back to the presence or absence of certain words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demetr-diagnosing-evaluation-metrics-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salient Object Detection via Dynamic Scale Routing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salient-object-detection-via-dynamic-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, instead of using the vanilla convolution with fixed kernel sizes for the encoder design, we propose the dynamic pyramid convolution (DPConv), which dynamically selects the best-suited kernel sizes w. r. t.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salient-object-detection-via-dynamic-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEW-UNet: Multi-axis representation learning in frequency domain for medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mew-unet-multi-axis-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our block performs a Fourier transform on the three axes of the input feature and assigns the external weight in the frequency domain, which is generated by our Weights Generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mew-unet-multi-axis-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Search Is What You Need For Neural Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-search-is-what-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our findings, we further assess the contrastive search decoding method using off-the-shelf LMs on four generation tasks across 16 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-search-is-what-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Anomaly Detection for Auditing Data and Impact of Categorical Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-detection-for-auditing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As One Hot encoding of high cardinal dataset invokes the "curse of dimensionality", we experiment with GEL encoding and embedding layer for representing categorical attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-anomaly-detection-for-auditing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Reuse Distractors to support Multiple Choice Question Generation in Education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-reuse-distractors-to-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies how a large existing set of manually created answers and distractors for questions over a variety of domains, subjects, and languages can be leveraged to help teachers in creating new MCQs, by the smart reuse of existing distractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-reuse-distractors-to-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Filter upon Diversity-Improved Decoding for Diversity-Faithfulness Tradeoff in NLG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-filter-upon-diversity-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some Natural Language Generation (NLG) tasks require both faithfulness and diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-filter-upon-diversity-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EBEN: Extreme bandwidth extension network applied to speech signals captured with noise-resilient microphones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eben-extreme-bandwidth-extension-network-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Extreme Bandwidth Extension Network (EBEN), a generative adversarial network (GAN) that enhances audio measured with noise-resilient microphones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eben-extreme-bandwidth-extension-network-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Few-Shot Relation Extraction with Label Prompt Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-few-shot-relation-extraction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that our approach is able to lead to improved class representations, yielding significantly better results on the few-shot relation extraction task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-few-shot-relation-extraction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EBEN: Extreme Bandwidth Extension Network  applied to speech signals captured with noise-resilient microphones</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eben-extreme-bandwidth-extension-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Extreme Bandwidth Extension Network (EBEN), a generative adversarial network (GAN) that enhances audio measured with noise-resilient microphones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eben-extreme-bandwidth-extension-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Points to Functions: Infinite-dimensional Representations in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-points-to-functions-infinite-dimensional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, it is reasonable to ask if there is an intermediate time step at which the preserved information is optimal for a given downstream task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-points-to-functions-infinite-dimensional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PALT: Parameter-Lite Transfer of Language Models for Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palt-parameter-lite-transfer-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, we outperform the fully finetuning approaches on a KG completion benchmark by tuning only 1% of the parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/palt-parameter-lite-transfer-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help me write a poem: Instruction Tuning as a Vehicle for Collaborative Poetry Writing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/help-me-write-a-poem-instruction-tuning-as-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core component of our system is a language model fine-tuned on a diverse collection of instructions for poetry writing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/help-me-write-a-poem-instruction-tuning-as-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Relation Classification via Efficient and Effective Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-relation-classification-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompting pre-trained language models has achieved impressive performance on various NLP tasks, especially in low data regimes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-relation-classification-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Mode Connectivity for Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-mode-connectivity-for-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) How does the PLM's task knowledge change along the path connecting two minima?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-mode-connectivity-for-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interpretable Summary Evaluation via Allocation of Contextual Embeddings to Reference Text Topics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-summary-evaluation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite extensive recent advances in summary generation models, evaluation of auto-generated summaries still widely relies on single-score systems insufficient for transparent assessment and in-depth qualitative analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-summary-evaluation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eigen Memory Tree</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigen-memory-tree</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces the Eigen Memory Tree (EMT), a novel online memory model for sequential learning scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigen-memory-tree</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio MFCC-gram Transformers for respiratory insufficiency detection in COVID-19</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-mfcc-gram-transformers-for-respiratory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work explores speech as a biomarker and investigates the detection of respiratory insufficiency (RI) by analyzing speech samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-mfcc-gram-transformers-for-respiratory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From exemplar to copy: the scribal appropriation of a Hadewijch manuscript computationally explored</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-exemplar-to-copy-the-scribal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study is devoted to two of the oldest known manuscripts in which the oeuvre of the medieval mystical author Hadewijch has been preserved: Brussels, KBR, 2879-2880 (ms. A) and Brussels, KBR, 2877-2878 (ms. B).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-exemplar-to-copy-the-scribal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Recommendation with Auxiliary Item Relationships via Multi-Relational Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-recommendation-with-auxiliary-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it remains a significant challenge to model auxiliary item relationships in SR. To simultaneously model high-order item-item transitions in sequences and auxiliary item relationships, we propose a Multi-relational Transformer capable of modeling auxiliary item relationships for SR (MT4SR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-recommendation-with-auxiliary-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Pricing in P2P Energy Systems Using Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-pricing-in-p2p-energy-systems-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The microgrid considers consumers, prosumers, the service provider, and a community battery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-pricing-in-p2p-energy-systems-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapters for Enhanced Modeling of Multilingual Knowledge and Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapters-for-enhanced-modeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a lightweight adapter set to enhance MLLMs with cross-lingual entity alignment and facts from MLKGs for many languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapters-for-enhanced-modeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural generalization is hard for sequence-to-sequence models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-generalization-is-hard-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequence-to-sequence (seq2seq) models have been successful across many NLP tasks, including ones that require predicting linguistic structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-generalization-is-hard-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergent World Representations: Exploring a Sequence Model Trained on a Synthetic Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-world-representations-exploring-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models show a surprising range of capabilities, but the source of their apparent competence is unclear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergent-world-representations-exploring-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused Concatenation for Context-Aware Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-concatenation-for-context-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A straightforward approach to context-aware neural machine translation consists in feeding the standard encoder-decoder architecture with a window of consecutive sentences, formed by the current sentence and a number of sentences from its context concatenated to it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-concatenation-for-context-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascading Biases: Investigating the Effect of Heuristic Annotation Strategies on Data and Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-biases-investigating-the-effect-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cognitive psychologists have documented that humans use cognitive heuristics, or mental shortcuts, to make quick decisions while expending less effort.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-biases-investigating-the-effect-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlled Text Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-reduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Producing a reduced version of a source text, as in generic or focused summarization, inherently involves two distinct subtasks: deciding on targeted content and generating a coherent text conveying it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-reduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Joint Training Really Help Cascaded Speech Translation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-joint-training-really-help-cascaded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, in speech translation, the straightforward approach - cascading a recognition system with a translation system - delivers state-of-the-art results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-joint-training-really-help-cascaded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong-TransCenter: Improved Multi-Object Tracking based on Transformers with Dense Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-transcenter-improved-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TransCenter is the first center-based transformer framework for MOT, and is also among the first to show the benefits of using transformer-based architectures for MOT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-transcenter-improved-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReaRev: Adaptive Reasoning for Question Answering over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rearev-adaptive-reasoning-for-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, termed ReaRev, introduces a new way to KGQA reasoning with respect to both instruction decoding and execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rearev-adaptive-reasoning-for-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EUR-Lex-Sum: A Multi- and Cross-lingual Dataset for Long-form Summarization in the Legal Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eur-lex-sum-a-multi-and-cross-lingual-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing summarization datasets come with two main drawbacks: (1) They tend to focus on overly exposed domains, such as news articles or wiki-like texts, and (2) are primarily monolingual, with few multilingual datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eur-lex-sum-a-multi-and-cross-lingual-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Different Tunes Played with Equal Skill: Exploring a Unified Optimization Subspace for Delta Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-tunes-played-with-equal-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fathom the mystery, we hypothesize that the adaptations of different DETs could all be reparameterized as low-dimensional optimizations in a unified optimization subspace, which could be found by jointly decomposing independent solutions of different DETs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/different-tunes-played-with-equal-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-based Drug Design with Equivariant Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-based-drug-design-with-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we formulate SBDD as a 3D-conditional generation problem and present DiffSBDD, an E(3)-equivariant 3D-conditional diffusion model that generates novel ligands conditioned on protein pockets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-based-drug-design-with-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Long-Term Memory in 3D Mazes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-long-term-memory-in-3d-mazes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most benchmark tasks in reinforcement learning do not test long-term memory in agents, slowing down progress in this important research direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-long-term-memory-in-3d-mazes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA FLARE: Federated Learning from Simulation to Real-World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nvidia-flare-federated-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning (FL) enables building robust and generalizable AI models by leveraging diverse datasets from multiple collaborators without centralizing the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nvidia-flare-federated-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monocular Dynamic View Synthesis: A Reality Check</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-dynamic-view-synthesis-a-reality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the recent progress on dynamic view synthesis (DVS) from monocular video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monocular-dynamic-view-synthesis-a-reality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graded-Q Reinforcement Learning with Information-Enhanced State Encoder for Hierarchical Collaborative Multi-Vehicle Pursuit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graded-q-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing works on MVP pay little attention to the importance of information exchange and cooperation among pursuing vehicles under the complex urban traffic environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graded-q-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution Image Editing via Multi-Stage Blended Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-editing-via-multi-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first use Blended Diffusion to edit the image at a low resolution, and then upscale it in multiple stages, using a super-resolution model and Blended Diffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-editing-via-multi-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermodynamics-informed neural networks for physically realistic mixed reality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermodynamics-informed-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The imminent impact of immersive technologies in society urges for active research in real-time and interactive physics simulation for virtual worlds to be realistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermodynamics-informed-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
