<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:15:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DomainGallery: Few-shot Domain-driven Image Generation by Attribute-centric Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domaingallery-few-shot-domain-driven-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent progress in text-to-image models pretrained on large-scale datasets has enabled us to generate various images as long as we provide a text prompt describing what we want.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domaingallery-few-shot-domain-driven-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Tumour Removing and Missing Modality Generation using 3D WDM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumour-removing-and-missing-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the inpainting task of BraTS 2024, the use of a large and variable number of healthy masks and the stability and efficiency of the 3D wavelet diffusion model resulted in 0. 007, 22. 61 and 0. 842 in the validation set and 0. 07 , 22. 8 and 0. 91 in the testing set (MSE, PSNR and SSIM respectively).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-tumour-removing-and-missing-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDQunat: Absorbing Outliers by Low-Rank Components for 4-Bit Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdqunat-absorbing-outliers-by-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we co-design an inference engine Nunchaku that fuses the kernels of the low-rank branch into those of the low-bit branch to cut off redundant memory access.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdqunat-absorbing-outliers-by-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Rectified Flow for Inversion and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-rectified-flow-for-inversion-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rectified-flow-based diffusion transformers, such as FLUX and OpenSora, have demonstrated exceptional performance in the field of image and video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-rectified-flow-for-inversion-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuroFly: A framework for whole-brain single neuron reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurofly-a-framework-for-whole-brain-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we introduce NeuroFly, a validated framework for large-scale automatic single neuron reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurofly-a-framework-for-whole-brain-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Bradley-Terry Models in Preference-Based Reward Modeling: Foundations, Theory, and Alternatives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-bradley-terry-models-in-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Bradley-Terry (BT) model is a common and successful practice in reward modeling for Large Language Model (LLM) alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-bradley-terry-models-in-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM2CLIP: Powerful Language Model Unlock Richer Visual Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm2clip-powerful-language-model-unlock</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose LLM2CLIP, a novel approach that embraces the power of LLMs to unlock CLIP's potential.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm2clip-powerful-language-model-unlock</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust and Efficient Fine-tuning of LLMs with Bayesian Reparameterization of Low-Rank Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-efficient-fine-tuning-of-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are highly resource-intensive to fine-tune due to their enormous size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-efficient-fine-tuning-of-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning IR: Straightforward Fine-tuning and Inference of Transformer-based Language Models for Information Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightning-ir-straightforward-fine-tuning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A wide range of transformer-based language models have been proposed for information retrieval tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightning-ir-straightforward-fine-tuning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanos: Enhancing Conversational Agents with Skill-of-Mind-Infused Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thanos-enhancing-conversational-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To increase social bonding with interlocutors, humans naturally acquire the ability to respond appropriately in a given situation by considering which conversational skill is most suitable for the response - a process we call skill-of-mind.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thanos-enhancing-conversational-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACCIO: Table Understanding Enhanced via Contrastive Learning with Aggregations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accio-table-understanding-enhanced-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this idea, in this paper, we introduce ACCIO, tAble understanding enhanCed via Contrastive learnIng with aggregatiOns, a novel approach to enhancing table understanding by contrasting original tables with their pivot summaries through contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accio-table-understanding-enhanced-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Prediction Neural Network (UpNet): Embedding Artificial Neural Network in Bayesian Inversion Framework to Quantify the Uncertainty of Remote Sensing Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-prediction-neural-network-upnet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been widely used in the retrieval of biophysical variables (BV).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-prediction-neural-network-upnet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Abnormal Stop Detection for Long Distance Coaches with Low-Frequency GPS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-abnormal-stop-detection-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an unsupervised method that helps transportation managers to efficiently discover the Abnormal Stop Detection (ASD) for long distance coaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-abnormal-stop-detection-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FASSILA: A Corpus for Algerian Dialect Fake News Detection and Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fassila-a-corpus-for-algerian-dialect-fake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of low-resource languages, the Algerian dialect (AD) faces challenges due to the absence of annotated corpora, hindering its effective processing, notably in Machine Learning (ML) applications reliant on corpora for training and assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fassila-a-corpus-for-algerian-dialect-fake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZAHA: Introducing the Level of Facade Generalization and the Large-Scale Point Cloud Facade Semantic Segmentation Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zaha-introducing-the-level-of-facade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facade semantic segmentation is a long-standing challenge in photogrammetry and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zaha-introducing-the-level-of-facade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Graph Attention Networks with Structural Motifs for Predicting Cell Line-Specific Synergistic Drug Combinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-attention-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, I believe that the proposed equivariant geometric deep learning framework serves as an effective tool for virtually screening anticancer drug combinations for further validation in a wet lab environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-attention-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peri-midFormer: Periodic Pyramid Transformer for Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peri-midformer-periodic-pyramid-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to break through the limitations of the previous methods, we decouple the implied complex periodic variations into inclusion and overlap relationships among different level periodic components based on the observation of the multi-periodicity therein and its inclusion relationships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peri-midformer-periodic-pyramid-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Low-Rank Adaptation Using IVON</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-low-rank-adaptation-using-ivon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We replace AdamW by the Improved Variational Online Newton (IVON) algorithm to finetune large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-low-rank-adaptation-using-ivon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPGD: Steepest Perturbed Gradient Descent Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgd-steepest-perturbed-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization algorithms are pivotal in advancing various scientific and industrial fields but often encounter obstacles such as trapping in local minima, saddle points, and plateaus (flat regions), which makes the convergence to reasonable or near-optimal solutions particularly challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spgd-steepest-perturbed-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Calibration of Win Rate Estimation with LLM Evaluators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-calibration-of-win-rate-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) show the potential of using LLMs as evaluators for assessing the quality of text generations from LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-calibration-of-win-rate-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring short-form factuality in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-short-form-factuality-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SimpleQA, a benchmark that evaluates the ability of language models to answer short, fact-seeking questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-short-form-factuality-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Aware Resource Management for C-V2X Platooning via Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-resource-management-for-c-v2x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach leverages the semantic information to optimize the allocation of communication resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aware-resource-management-for-c-v2x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVSplat360: Feed-Forward 360 Scene Synthesis from Sparse Views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat360-feed-forward-360-scene-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To evaluate MVSplat360's performance, we introduce a new benchmark using the challenging DL3DV-10K dataset, where MVSplat360 achieves superior visual quality compared to state-of-the-art methods on wide-sweeping or even 360{\deg} NVS tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat360-feed-forward-360-scene-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Trade-offs: Policy Summarization for Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-trade-offs-policy-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the solution set is typically large and multi-dimensional, where each policy (e. g., a neural network) is represented by its objective values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-trade-offs-policy-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social EgoMesh Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-egomesh-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately estimating the 3D pose of the camera wearer in egocentric video sequences is crucial to modeling human behavior in virtual and augmented reality applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-egomesh-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Multi-Task Brain Tumour Segmentation with Synthetic Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-multi-task-brain-tumour-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of automated tools in clinical practice has increased due to the development of more and more sophisticated and reliable algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-multi-task-brain-tumour-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Federated Analytics via Differentially Private Measurements of Statistical Heterogeneity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-federated-analytics-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is a common problem in the study of differential privacy that the usage of a statistically heterogeneous dataset results in a significant loss of accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-federated-analytics-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Brightness Adaptation for Robust Multi-modal Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-brightness-adaptation-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose the Brightness Adaptive multimodal dynamic fusion framework (BA-Fusion), which achieves robust image fusion despite dynamic brightness fluctuations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-brightness-adaptation-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGDrivSim: A Benchmark for the Imitation Gap in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igdrivsim-a-benchmark-for-the-imitation-gap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce \textbf{IGDrivSim}, a benchmark built on top of the Waymax simulator, designed to investigate the effects of the imitation gap in learning autonomous driving policy from human expert demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/igdrivsim-a-benchmark-for-the-imitation-gap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Collaborative Content Moderation Framework for Toxicity Detection based on Conformalized Estimates of Annotation Disagreement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-collaborative-content-moderation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Content moderation typically combines the efforts of human moderators and machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-collaborative-content-moderation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Moral Beliefs across LLMs through a Pluralistic Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-moral-beliefs-across-llms-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, through moral debates, we investigate the firmness of these models to their moral choices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-moral-beliefs-across-llms-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bio-xLSTM: Generative modeling, representation and in-context learning of biological and chemical sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bio-xlstm-generative-modeling-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Transformers have yielded impressive results, their quadratic runtime dependency on the sequence length complicates their use for long genomic sequences and in-context learning on proteins and chemical sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bio-xlstm-generative-modeling-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Stability Gap in Continual Learning: The Role of the Classification Head</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-stability-gap-in-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the nearest-mean classifier (NMC) as a tool to attribute the influence of the backbone and the classification head on the stability gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-stability-gap-in-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Both Text and Images Leaked! A Systematic Analysis of Multimodal LLM Data Contamination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/both-text-and-images-leaked-a-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid progression of multimodal large language models (MLLMs) has demonstrated superior performance on various multimodal benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/both-text-and-images-leaked-a-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Recurrent Sticky Hierarchical Dirichlet Process Hidden Markov Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-recurrent-sticky-hierarchical-dirichlet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A sticky HDP-HMM has been proposed to strengthen the self-persistence probability in the HDP-HMM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-recurrent-sticky-hierarchical-dirichlet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Fourier Filtering Network with Contrastive Learning for UAV-based Unaligned Bi-modal Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fourier-filtering-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the UAV RGB-T 2400 and three weakly aligned datasets demonstrate that AlignSal achieves both real-time inference speed and better performance and generalizability compared to sixteen state-of-the-art BSOD models across most evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fourier-filtering-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMNCutter: Affinity-Attention-Guided Multi-View Normalized Cutter for Unsupervised Surgical Instrument Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amncutter-affinity-attention-guided-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent unsupervised surgical instrument segmentation (USIS) methods primarily rely on pseudo-labels derived from low-level features such as color and optical flow, but these methods show limited effectiveness and generalizability in complex and unseen endoscopic scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amncutter-affinity-attention-guided-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXPLORA: Efficient Exemplar Subset Selection for Complex Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explora-efficient-exemplar-subset-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Answering reasoning-based complex questions over text and hybrid sources, including tables, is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explora-efficient-exemplar-subset-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBIN: Robust and Invisible Watermarks for Diffusion Models with Adversarial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robin-robust-and-invisible-watermarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[They empirically inject a watermark that is both invisible and robust and passively achieve concealment by limiting the strength of the watermark, thus reducing the robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robin-robust-and-invisible-watermarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconsidering the Performance of GAE in Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconsidering-the-performance-of-gae-in-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various graph neural networks (GNNs) with advanced training techniques and model designs have been proposed for link prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconsidering-the-performance-of-gae-in-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QUILL: Quotation Generation Enhancement of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quill-quotation-generation-enhancement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the LLMs' quotation generation abilities, we construct a bilingual knowledge base that is broad in scope and rich in dimensions, containing up to 32, 022 quotes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quill-quotation-generation-enhancement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Model Adaptation at Test Time: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-model-adaptation-at-test-time-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning algorithms have achieved remarkable success across various disciplines, use cases and applications, under the prevailing assumption that training and test samples are drawn from the same distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-model-adaptation-at-test-time-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEG: Medical Knowledge-Augmented Large Language Models for Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meg-medical-knowledge-augmented-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate our method on four popular medical multiple-choice datasets and show that LLMs greatly benefit from the factual grounding provided by knowledge graph embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meg-medical-knowledge-augmented-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Number Cookbook: Number Understanding of Language Models and How to Improve It</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/number-cookbook-number-understanding-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also finetune practical-scale LLMs on our proposed NUPA tasks and find that 1) naive finetuning can improve NUPA a lot on many but not all tasks, and 2) surprisingly, techniques designed to enhance NUPA prove ineffective for finetuning pretrained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/number-cookbook-number-understanding-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Touchstone Benchmark: Are We on the Right Way for Evaluating AI Algorithms for Medical Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/touchstone-benchmark-are-we-on-the-right-way</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are committed to expanding this benchmark to encourage more innovation of AI algorithms for the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/touchstone-benchmark-are-we-on-the-right-way</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Graph Network Approximations of High-Degree Polynomials for Force Field Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-network-approximations-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in equivariant deep models have shown promise in accurately predicting atomic potentials and force fields in molecular dynamics simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-graph-network-approximations-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA3DIP: Segment Any 3D Instance with Potential 3D Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa3dip-segment-any-3d-instance-with-potential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we present ScanNetV2-INS with complete ground truth labels and supplement additional instances for 3D class-agnostic instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa3dip-segment-any-3d-instance-with-potential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Mutation-Acyclicity of Quivers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-mutation-acyclicity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) has emerged as a powerful tool in mathematical research in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-mutation-acyclicity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexicalization Is All You Need: Examining the Impact of Lexical Knowledge in a Compositional QALD System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicalization-is-all-you-need-examining-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue in this paper that lexicalization, that is explicit knowledge about the potential interpretations of a word with respect to the given vocabulary, significantly eases the task and increases the performance of QA systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicalization-is-all-you-need-examining-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo-labeling with Keyword Refining for Few-Supervised Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-with-keyword-refining-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the former employs the repetition penalized sampling to encourage the model to yield concise pseudo-labeled sentences with less repetition, and selects the most relevant sentences upon a pretrained video-text model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-labeling-with-keyword-refining-for-few</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
