<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 09:14:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Prompts Made Easy: Gradient-Based Discrete Optimization for Prompt Tuning and Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-prompts-made-easy-gradient-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the text-to-image setting, the method creates hard prompts for diffusion models, allowing API users to easily generate, discover, and mix and match image concepts without prior knowledge on how to prompt the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-prompts-made-easy-gradient-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-Level Contrastive Learning for Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel low-dimensional Supervised Cluster-level Contrastive Learning (SCCL) method, which first reduces the high-dimensional SCL space to a three-dimensional affect representation space Valence-Arousal-Dominance (VAD), then performs cluster-level contrastive learning to incorporate measurable emotion prototypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-level-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An entity-guided text summarization framework with relational heterogeneous graph neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-entity-guided-text-summarization-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, entities are leveraged to construct a sentence-entity graph with weighted multi-type edges to model sentence relations, and a relational heterogeneous GNN for summarization is proposed to calculate node encodings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-entity-guided-text-summarization-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity-Aware Dual Co-Attention Network for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-aware-dual-co-attention-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fake news and misinformation spread rapidly on the Internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-aware-dual-co-attention-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hebbian and Gradient-based Plasticity Enables Robust Memory and Rapid Learning in RNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hebbian-and-gradient-based-plasticity-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comparing different plasticity rules under the same framework shows that Hebbian plasticity is well-suited for several memory and associative learning tasks; however, it is outperformed by gradient-based plasticity on few-shot regression tasks which require the model to infer the underlying mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hebbian-and-gradient-based-plasticity-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Lightweight Cross-domain Sequential Recommendation via External Attention-enhanced Graph Convolution Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-lightweight-cross-domain-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-domain Sequential Recommendation (CSR) is an emerging yet challenging task that depicts the evolution of behavior patterns for overlapped users by modeling their interactions from multiple domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-lightweight-cross-domain-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Reliable is Your Regression Model's Uncertainty Under Real-World Distribution Shifts?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-reliable-is-your-regression-model-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then employ our benchmark to evaluate many of the most common uncertainty estimation methods, as well as two state-of-the-art uncertainty scores from the task of out-of-distribution detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-reliable-is-your-regression-model-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanMAC: Masked Motion Completion for Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanmac-masked-motion-completion-for-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the training stage, we learn a motion diffusion model that generates motions from random noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanmac-masked-motion-completion-for-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Misinformation Video Detection: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-misinformation-video-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With information consumption via online video streaming becoming increasingly popular, misinformation video poses a new threat to the health of the online information ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-misinformation-video-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Benefits of Training Expert Language Models over Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-training-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, Language Models (LMs) instruction-tuned on multiple tasks, also known as multitask-prompted fine-tuning (MT), have shown the capability to generalize to unseen tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-benefits-of-training-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identification of Power System Oscillation Modes using Blind Source Separation based on Copula Statistic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-power-system-oscillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We access the performance of the proposed method on numerical simulation signals and recorded data from a simulation of time domain analysis on the classical 11-Bus 4-Machine test system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-power-system-oscillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing the State-of-the-Art to Customers: A Neural Agent Assistant Framework for Customer Service Support</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bringing-the-state-of-the-art-to-customers-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building Agent Assistants that can help improve customer service support requires inputs from industry users and their customers, as well as knowledge about state-of-the-art Natural Language Processing (NLP) technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bringing-the-state-of-the-art-to-customers-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diverse Probabilistic Trajectory Forecasting with Admissibility Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-probabilistic-trajectory-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting multiple trajectories for road users is important for automated driving systems: ego-vehicle motion planning indeed requires a clear view of the possible motions of the surrounding agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diverse-probabilistic-trajectory-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Causal Embedding With Contrastive Learning For Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-causal-embedding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most previous studies neglect user's conformity and entangle interest with it, which may cause the recommender systems fail to provide satisfying results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-causal-embedding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long Horizon Temperature Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-horizon-temperature-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LHTS is compatible with all likelihood-based models, and optimizes for the long-horizon likelihood of samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-horizon-temperature-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Gaussian process regression enables accurate prediction of protein and small molecule properties with uncertainty quantitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-gaussian-process-regression-enables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the performance of xGPR with the reported performance of various deep learning models on 20 benchmarks, including small molecule, protein sequence and tabular data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-gaussian-process-regression-enables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revised Conditional t-SNE: Looking Beyond the Nearest Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revised-conditional-t-sne-looking-beyond-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional t-SNE (ct-SNE) is a recent extension to t-SNE that allows removal of known cluster information from the embedding, to obtain a visualization revealing structure beyond label information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revised-conditional-t-sne-looking-beyond-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate Intervention Analysis using AI Model Guided by Statistical Physics Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climate-intervention-analysis-using-ai-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model, AiBEDO, is capable of capturing the complex, multi-timescale effects of radiation perturbations on global and regional surface climate, allowing for a substantial acceleration of the exploration of the impacts of spatially-heterogenous climate forcers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climate-intervention-analysis-using-ai-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Affordance Annotation for Egocentric Hand-Object Interaction Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-affordance-annotation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object affordance is an important concept in hand-object interaction, providing information on action possibilities based on human motor capacity and objects' physical property thus benefiting tasks such as action anticipation and robot imitation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-affordance-annotation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution GAN Inversion for Degraded Images in Large Diverse Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-gan-inversion-for-degraded</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A generic method for generating a high-quality image from the degraded one is in demand.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-gan-inversion-for-degraded</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Class-Incremental Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-class-incremental-learning-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep models, e. g., CNNs and Vision Transformers, have achieved impressive achievements in many vision tasks in the closed world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-class-incremental-learning-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness Implies Fairness in Casual Algorithmic Recourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-implies-fairness-in-casual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic recourse aims to disclose the inner workings of the black-box decision process in situations where decisions have significant consequences, by providing recommendations to empower beneficiaries to achieve a more favorable outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-implies-fairness-in-casual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Effect of Metadata on Scientific Literature Tagging: A Cross-Field Cross-Model Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-metadata-on-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the exponential growth of scientific publications on the Web, there is a pressing need to tag each paper with fine-grained topics so that researchers can track their interested fields of study rather than drowning in the whole literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-effect-of-metadata-on-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OSRT: Omnidirectional Image Super-Resolution with Distortion-aware Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osrt-omnidirectional-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Omnidirectional images (ODIs) have obtained lots of research interest for immersive experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osrt-omnidirectional-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Privacy-Preserving Hybrid Federated Learning Framework for Financial Crime Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-privacy-preserving-hybrid-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Developing a mechanism for battling financial crimes is an impending task that requires in-depth collaboration from multiple institutions, and yet such collaboration imposed significant technical challenges due to the privacy and security requirements of distributed financial data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-privacy-preserving-hybrid-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Deeper Understanding of Concept Bottleneck Models Through End-to-End Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-deeper-understanding-of-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs) first map raw input(s) to a vector of human-defined concepts, before using this vector to predict a final classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-deeper-understanding-of-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchDCT: Patch Refinement for High Quality Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchdct-patch-refinement-for-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further refine masks obtained by compressed vectors, we propose for the first time a compressed vector based multi-stage refinement framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchdct-patch-refinement-for-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuG: A Multimodal Classification Benchmark on Game Data with Tabular, Textual, and Visual Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mug-a-multimodal-classification-benchmark-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal learning has attracted the interest of the machine learning community due to its great potential in a variety of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mug-a-multimodal-classification-benchmark-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Lexical Simplification for English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-lexical-simplification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning Transformer-based approaches have recently shown exciting results on sentence simplification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-lexical-simplification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixFormer: End-to-End Tracking with Iterative Mixed Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixformer-end-to-end-tracking-with-iterative-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our core design is to utilize the flexibility of attention operations, and propose a Mixed Attention Module (MAM) for simultaneous feature extraction and target information integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixformer-end-to-end-tracking-with-iterative-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution for PSG competition with ECCV'22 SenseHuman Workshop</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-psg-competition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Panoptic Scene Graph (PSG) generation aims to generate scene graph representations based on panoptic segmentation instead of rigid bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-psg-competition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detection and Localization of Melanoma Skin Cancer in Histopathological Whole Slide Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-and-localization-of-melanoma-skin</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CPATH systems with deep learning (DL) models have the potential to identify the presence of melanoma by exploiting underlying morphological and cellular features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detection-and-localization-of-melanoma-skin</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Control-Oriented Dynamical Structure from Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-control-oriented-dynamical-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even for known nonlinear dynamical systems, feedback controller synthesis is a difficult problem that often requires leveraging the particular structure of the dynamics to induce a stable closed-loop system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-control-oriented-dynamical-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-Down Beats Bottom-Up in 3D Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-down-beats-bottom-up-in-3d-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most 3D instance segmentation methods exploit a bottom-up strategy, typically including resource-exhaustive post-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-down-beats-bottom-up-in-3d-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TR3D: Towards Real-Time Indoor 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tr3d-towards-real-time-indoor-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model with early feature fusion, which we refer to as TR3D+FF, outperforms existing 3D object detection approaches on the SUN RGB-D dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tr3d-towards-real-time-indoor-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLSbench: Domain Adaptation Under Relaxed Label Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlsbench-domain-adaptation-under-relaxed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, popular deep domain adaptation heuristics tend to falter when faced with shifts in label proportions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlsbench-domain-adaptation-under-relaxed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L'explicabilité au service de l'extraction de connaissances : application à des données médicales</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-explicabilite-au-service-de-l-extraction-de</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, one of the challenges of data mining is to present the statistical relationships of a dataset when they can be highly non-linear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-explicabilite-au-service-de-l-extraction-de</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropout Injection at Test Time for Post Hoc Uncertainty Quantification in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-injection-at-test-time-for-post-hoc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among Bayesian methods, Monte-Carlo dropout provides principled tools for evaluating the epistemic uncertainty of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-injection-at-test-time-for-post-hoc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization of Topology-Aware Job Allocation on a High-Performance Computing Cluster by Neural Simulated Annealing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-topology-aware-job-allocation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the DCAS, an approach called neural simulated algorithm (NSA), which is an extension to simulated algorithm (SA) that learns a repair operator and employs them in a guided heuristic search, is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-topology-aware-job-allocation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Self-Supervised Learning via Risk Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-self-supervised-learning-via-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our decomposition consists of four error components: approximation, representation usability, probe generalization, and encoder generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-self-supervised-learning-via-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Indexing Variational Bayes: Interpretable Domain Index for Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-indexing-variational-bayes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous studies have shown that leveraging domain index can significantly boost domain adaptation performance \cite{arXiv:2007. 01807, arXiv:2202. 03628}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-indexing-variational-bayes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust, but Verify: Using Self-Supervised Probing to Improve Trustworthiness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-using-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trustworthy machine learning is of primary importance to the practical deployment of deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-using-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INCREASE: Inductive Graph Representation Learning for Spatio-Temporal Kriging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increase-inductive-graph-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It aims to infer knowledge for (the things at) unobserved locations using the data from (the things at) observed locations during a given time period of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increase-inductive-graph-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representations of Bi-Level Knowledge Graphs for Reasoning beyond Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-bi-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define a bi-level knowledge graph that consists of the base-level and the higher-level triplets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-bi-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-based Out-of-Distribution Detection for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-out-of-distribution-detection-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paves a way for a simple, powerful and efficient OOD detection model for GNN-based learning on graphs, which we call GNNSafe.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-out-of-distribution-detection-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Contrastive Learning Recovers the Correct Aleatoric Uncertainty of Ambiguous Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-contrastive-learning-recovers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that these distributions recover the correct posteriors of the data-generating process, including its level of aleatoric uncertainty, up to a rotation of the latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-contrastive-learning-recovers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide the Learner: Controlling Product of Experts Debiasing Method Based on Token Attribution Similarities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-the-learner-controlling-product-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A popular workaround is to train a robust model by re-weighting training examples based on a secondary biased model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-the-learner-controlling-product-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation for Time Series Under Feature and Label Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-for-time-series-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, tasks in the source and target domains can have vastly different label distributions, making it difficult for UDA to mitigate label shifts and recognize labels that only exist in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-for-time-series-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoFT: Enhancing Faithfulness and Diversity for Table-to-Text Generation via Logic Form Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loft-enhancing-faithfulness-and-diversity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Logical Table-to-Text (LT2T) generation is tasked with generating logically faithful sentences from tables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loft-enhancing-faithfulness-and-diversity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Action Detection with RGB and Pose Information using Two Stream Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-action-detection-with-rgb-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As participants of the MediaEval 2022 Sport Task, we propose a two-stream network approach for the classification and detection of table tennis strokes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-action-detection-with-rgb-and</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
