<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 21:06:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TreeLearn: A Comprehensive Deep Learning Method for Segmenting Individual Trees from Forest Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treelearn-a-comprehensive-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We trained TreeLearn on forest point clouds of 6665 trees, labeled using the Lidar360 software.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treelearn-a-comprehensive-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperspectral Image Denoising via Self-Modulating Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-image-denoising-via-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of the model lies a novel block, which we call spectral self-modulating residual block (SSMRB), that allows the network to transform the features in an adaptive manner based on the adjacent spectral data, enhancing the network's ability to handle complex noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspectral-image-denoising-via-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Burned Area Delineation through Multitask Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-burned-area-delineation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this dataset, we provide annotations for multiple tasks, including burned area delineation and land cover segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-burned-area-delineation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M$^3$Net: Multilevel, Mixed and Multistage Attention Network for Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-net-multilevel-mixed-and-multistage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these, we propose the M$^3$Net, i. e., the Multilevel, Mixed and Multistage attention network for Salient Object Detection (SOD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-net-multilevel-mixed-and-multistage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiaCorrect: Error Correction Back-end For Speaker Diarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diacorrect-error-correction-back-end-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an error correction framework, named DiaCorrect, to refine the output of a diarization system in a simple yet effective way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diacorrect-error-correction-back-end-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oobleck: Resilient Distributed Training of Large Models Using Pipeline Templates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oobleck-resilient-distributed-training-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Oobleck enables resilient distributed training of large DNN models with guaranteed fault tolerance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oobleck-resilient-distributed-training-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Estimation for Omni-Directional Saliency Maps Using Learnable Equator Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-estimation-for-omni-directional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel saliency-map estimation model for the omni-directional images by extracting overlapping 2-dimensional (2D) plane images from omni-directional images at various directions and angles of view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-estimation-for-omni-directional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning with Deep Streaming Regularized Discriminant Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-deep-streaming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning is increasingly sought after in real world machine learning applications, as it enables learning in a more human-like manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-deep-streaming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HealthFC: A Dataset of Health Claims for Evidence-Based Medical Fact-Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthfc-a-dataset-of-health-claims-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Seeking health-related advice on the internet has become a common practice in the digital era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthfc-a-dataset-of-health-claims-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust e-NeRF: NeRF from Sparse &amp; Noisy Events under Non-Uniform Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-e-nerf-nerf-from-sparse-noisy-events</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such promise and potential of event cameras and NeRF inspired recent works to investigate on the reconstruction of NeRF from moving event cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-e-nerf-nerf-from-sparse-noisy-events</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double Domain Guided Real-Time Low-Light Image Enhancement for Ultra-High-Definition Transportation Surveillance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-domain-guided-real-time-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-time transportation surveillance is an essential part of the intelligent transportation system (ITS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-domain-guided-real-time-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Transferable are Attribute Controllers on Pretrained Multilingual Translation Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-transferable-are-attribute-controllers-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given recent progress in pretrained massively multilingual translation models, we use them as a foundation to transfer the attribute controlling capabilities to languages without supervised data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-transferable-are-attribute-controllers-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-UDA: Temporal Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in Sequential Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-uda-temporal-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep perception models have to reliably cope with an open-world setting of domain shifts induced by different geographic regions, sensor properties, mounting positions, and several other reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-uda-temporal-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Speech Recognition for Low-resource Languages with Automatic Labels From Whisper Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-speech-recognition-for-low-resource</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from previous methods that tried to improve the VSR performance for the target language by using knowledge learned from other languages, we explore whether we can increase the amount of training data itself for the different languages without human intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-speech-recognition-for-low-resource</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdSEE: Investigating the Impact of Image Style Editing on Advertisement Attractiveness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adsee-investigating-the-impact-of-image-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online advertisements are important elements in e-commerce sites, social media platforms, and search engines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adsee-investigating-the-impact-of-image-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCT: A Simple Baseline for Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning via Salient Channels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sct-a-simple-baseline-for-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, many parameter-efficient fine-tuning (PEFT) methods have been proposed, and their experiments demonstrate that tuning only 1% of extra parameters could surpass full fine-tuning in low-data resource scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sct-a-simple-baseline-for-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Differential Privacy in Graph Neural Networks: a Reconstruction Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-differential-privacy-in-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on a decentralized notion of Differential Privacy, namely Local Differential Privacy, and apply randomization mechanisms to perturb both feature and label data at the node level before the data is collected by a central server for model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-differential-privacy-in-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed neural networks for highly compressible flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This thesis shows that physics-informed neural networks struggle with highly compressible problems for two independent reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimization of Rank Losses for Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-rank-losses-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It provides an upperbound for rank losses and ensures robust training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimization-of-rank-losses-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salient Object Detection in Optical Remote Sensing Images Driven by Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salient-object-detection-in-optical-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[KTM models the contextual correlation knowledge of two middle-level features of different scales based on the self-attention mechanism, and transfers the knowledge to the raw features to generate more discriminative features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salient-object-detection-in-optical-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedJudge: Federated Legal Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedjudge-federated-legal-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, in this paper, we propose the first Federated Legal Large Language Model (FedJudge) framework, which fine-tunes Legal LLMs efficiently and effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedjudge-federated-legal-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Priority Reweighing for Generalizing Fairness Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-priority-reweighing-for-generalizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our adaptive reweighing method prioritizes samples closer to the decision boundary and assigns a higher weight to improve the generalizability of fair classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-priority-reweighing-for-generalizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Last-layer Retraining for Group Robustness with Fewer Annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-last-layer-retraining-for-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine this impractical requirement and find that last-layer retraining can be surprisingly effective with no group annotations (other than for model selection) and only a handful of class annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-last-layer-retraining-for-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-PDNet: Accurate Joint Plane Instance Segmentation and Monocular Depth Estimation with Cross-Task Distillation and Boundary Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-pdnet-accurate-joint-plane-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we propose X-PDNet, a framework for the multitask learning of plane instance segmentation and depth estimation with improvements in the following two aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-pdnet-accurate-joint-plane-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Large Language Models for Knowledge Engineering (LLMKE): A Case Study on Wikidata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-large-language-models-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore the use of Large Language Models (LLMs) for knowledge engineering tasks in the context of the ISWC 2023 LM-KBC Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-large-language-models-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChemBERTa-2: Fine-Tuning for Molecule’s HIV Replication Inhibition Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemberta-2-fine-tuning-for-molecules-hiv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two versions of Large Language ChemBERTa-2 models, pre-trained with two different methods, were fine-tuned in this work for HIV replication inhibition prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemberta-2-fine-tuning-for-molecules-hiv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-tune the pretrained ATST model for sound event detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tune-the-pretrained-atst-model-for-sound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the fine-tuning method of the pretrained models for SED.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-tune-the-pretrained-atst-model-for-sound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breathing New Life into 3D Assets with Generative Repainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breathing-new-life-into-3d-assets-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based text-to-image models ignited immense attention from the vision community, artists, and content creators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breathing-new-life-into-3d-assets-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syn-Att: Synthetic Speech Attribution via Semi-Supervised Unknown Multi-Class Ensemble of CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syn-att-synthetic-speech-attribution-via-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a novel strategy is proposed to attribute a synthetic speech track to the generator that is used to synthesize it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syn-att-synthetic-speech-attribution-via-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unimodal Aggregation for CTC-based Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimodal-aggregation-for-ctc-based-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, the feature frames with unimodal weights are integrated and further processed by a decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unimodal-aggregation-for-ctc-based-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Arterial Segmentation via Single 2D Projections and Depth Supervision in Contrast-Enhanced CT Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-arterial-segmentation-via-single-2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel method to segment the 3D peripancreatic arteries solely from one annotated 2D projection per training image with depth supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-arterial-segmentation-via-single-2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Domain Gap: Exploiting Subjectivity in Sketch-Based Person Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-domain-gap-exploiting-subjectivity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) Multi-perspective and multi-style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-domain-gap-exploiting-subjectivity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing the temporal dynamics of universal speech representations for generalizable deepfake detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-temporal-dynamics-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing deepfake speech detection systems lack generalizability to unseen attacks (i. e., samples generated by generative algorithms not seen during training).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-temporal-dynamics-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P-ROCKET: Pruning Random Convolution Kernels for Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-rocket-pruning-random-convolution-kernels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stage 1 of P-ROCKET employs group-wise regularization similarly to our initial ADMM-based Algorithm, but introduces dynamically varying penalties to greatly accelerate the process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-rocket-pruning-random-convolution-kernels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Failure Mode Classification: An Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-failure-mode</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present the first investigation into the effectiveness of Large Language Models (LLMs) for Failure Mode Classification (FMC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-failure-mode</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bayesian Approach to Robust Inverse Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-robust-inverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider a Bayesian approach to offline model-based inverse reinforcement learning (IRL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-robust-inverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICLEF: In-Context Learning with Expert Feedback for Explainable Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iclef-in-context-learning-with-expert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a framework to augment and improve a formality style transfer dataset with explanations via model distillation from ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iclef-in-context-learning-with-expert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Resolution Compression and Alignment for Efficient Video Classification and Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-resolution-compression-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose an efficient video representation network with Differentiable Resolution Compression and Alignment mechanism, which compresses non-essential information in the early stage of the network to reduce computational costs while maintaining consistent temporal correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-resolution-compression-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDCSR: Federated Cross-domain Sequential Recommendation via Disentangled Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddcsr-federated-cross-domain-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nonetheless, the sequence feature heterogeneity across different domains significantly impacts the overall performance of FL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddcsr-federated-cross-domain-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reward Engineering for Generating Semi-structured Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-engineering-for-generating-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-structured explanation depicts the implicit process of a reasoner with an explicit representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-engineering-for-generating-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-learning-powered data analysis in plankton ecology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-powered-data-analysis-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The implementation of deep learning algorithms has brought new perspectives to plankton ecology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-powered-data-analysis-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increasing diversity of omni-directional images generated from single image using cGAN based on MLPMixer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-diversity-of-omni-directional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, since a convolutional layer only processes a local area, it is difficult to propagate the information of an input snapshot picture embedded in the center of the omni-directional image to the edges of the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increasing-diversity-of-omni-directional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Nonnegative Matrix Factorization with Beta Divergences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-nonnegative-matrix-factorization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Nonnegative Matrix Factorization (deep NMF) has recently emerged as a valuable technique for extracting multiple layers of features across different scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-nonnegative-matrix-factorization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topological Node2vec: Enhanced Graph Embedding via Persistent Homology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-node2vec-enhanced-graph-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Node2vec is a graph embedding method that learns a vector representation for each node of a weighted graph while seeking to preserve relative proximity and global structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topological-node2vec-enhanced-graph-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Merge Conflicts!" Exploring the Impacts of External Distractors to Parametric Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merge-conflicts-exploring-the-impacts-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) acquire extensive knowledge during pre-training, known as their parametric knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merge-conflicts-exploring-the-impacts-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLMIA-SR: Speaker-Level Membership Inference Attacks against Speaker Recognition Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slmia-sr-speaker-level-membership-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our attack is versatile and can work in both white-box and black-box scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slmia-sr-speaker-level-membership-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Large-scale Building Attribute Mapping using Crowdsourced Images: Scene Text Recognition on Flickr and Problems to be Solved</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-large-scale-building-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work addresses the challenges in applying Scene Text Recognition (STR) in crowdsourced street-view images for building attribute mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-large-scale-building-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Padding Aware Neurons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padding-aware-neurons</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we identify Padding Aware Neurons (PANs), a type of filter that is found in most (if not all) convolutional models trained with static padding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padding-aware-neurons</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretability-Aware Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-aware-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, if ViTs are not properly trained with the given data and do not prioritize the region of interest, the {\it post hoc} methods would be less effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretability-aware-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiariST: Streaming Speech Translation with Speaker Diarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diarist-streaming-speech-translation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[End-to-end speech translation (ST) for conversation recordings involves several under-explored challenges such as speaker diarization (SD) without accurate word time stamps and handling of overlapping speech in a streaming fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diarist-streaming-speech-translation-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
