<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 21:09:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Compact Biomedical Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-compact-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models pre-trained on biomedical corpora, such as BioBERT, have recently shown promising results on downstream biomedical tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-compact-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Crowd Counting via Density Agency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-crowd-counting-via-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new agency-guided semi-supervised counting approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-crowd-counting-via-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KT-BT: A Framework for Knowledge Transfer Through Behavior Trees in Multi-Robot Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kt-bt-a-framework-for-knowledge-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We theoretically investigate the properties of the KT-BT framework in achieving homogeneity of high knowledge across the entire group compared to a heterogeneous system without the capability of sharing their knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kt-bt-a-framework-for-knowledge-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretations Steered Network Pruning via Amortized Inferred Saliency Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretations-steered-network-pruning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill in this gap, we propose to address the channel pruning problem from a novel perspective by leveraging the interpretations of a model to steer the pruning process, thereby utilizing information from both inputs and outputs of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretations-steered-network-pruning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv6: A Single-Stage Object Detection Framework for Industrial Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov6-a-single-stage-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The YOLO community has prospered overwhelmingly to enrich its use in a multitude of hardware platforms and abundant scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov6-a-single-stage-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Complementarity between Pre-Training and Random-Initialization for Resource-Rich Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-complementarity-between-pre-training-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-Training (PT) of text representations has been successfully applied to low-resource Neural Machine Translation (NMT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-complementarity-between-pre-training-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGStore: A Multimodal Extension to SPARQL for Querying RDF Scene Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgstore-a-multimodal-extension-to-sparql-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic Web technology has successfully facilitated many RDF models with rich data representation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vgstore-a-multimodal-extension-to-sparql-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Self-supervised Learning for Out-of-distribution Task via Auxiliary Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-learning-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Observing a strong relationship between rotation prediction (self-supervised) accuracy and semantic classification accuracy on OOD tasks, we introduce an additional auxiliary classification head in our multi-task network along with semantic classification and rotation prediction head.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-self-supervised-learning-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effects of Archive Size on Computation Time and Solution Quality for Multi-Objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effects-of-archive-size-on-computation-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we examine the effects of the archive size on three aspects: (i) the quality of the selected final solution set, (ii) the total computation time for the archive maintenance and the final solution set selection, and (iii) the required memory size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effects-of-archive-size-on-computation-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficulty-Net: Learning to Predict Difficulty for Long-Tailed Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-net-learning-to-predict-difficulty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-tailed datasets, where head classes comprise much more training samples than tail classes, cause recognition models to get biased towards the head classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difficulty-net-learning-to-predict-difficulty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morphology-preserving Autoregressive 3D Generative Modelling of the Brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphology-preserving-autoregressive-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Still, the ability to produce high-resolution 3D volumetric imaging data with correct anatomical morphology has been hampered by data scarcity and algorithmic and computational limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphology-preserving-autoregressive-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does a platypus look like? Generating customized prompts for zero-shot image classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-does-a-platypus-look-like-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional classification models, open vocabulary models classify among any arbitrary set of categories specified with natural language during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-does-a-platypus-look-like-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shifting Perspective to See Difference: A Novel Multi-View Method for Skeleton based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifting-perspective-to-see-difference-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our module can work seamlessly with the existing action classification model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shifting-perspective-to-see-difference-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSMDFusion: Fusing LiDAR and Camera at Multiple Scales with Multi-Depth Seeds for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msmdfusion-fusing-lidar-and-camera-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fusing LiDAR and camera information is essential for achieving accurate and reliable 3D object detection in autonomous driving systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msmdfusion-fusing-lidar-and-camera-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiFuse++: Self-supervised and Efficient Bi-projection Fusion for 360 Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifuse-self-supervised-and-efficient-bi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, state-of-the-art frameworks for monocular 360 depth estimation such as bi-projection fusion in BiFuse are proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bifuse-self-supervised-and-efficient-bi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Textured Shape Recovery with Learned Geometric Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-textured-shape-recovery-with-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D textured shape recovery from partial scans is crucial for many real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-textured-shape-recovery-with-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Engagement and Cryptocurrency Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-media-engagement-and-cryptocurrency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use this model to estimate engagement coefficients for 48 cryptocurrencies created between 2019 and 2021 using data from Twitter from the first month of the cryptocurrencies' existence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/social-media-engagement-and-cryptocurrency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VulCurator: A Vulnerability-Fixing Commit Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vulcurator-a-vulnerability-fixing-commit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-source software (OSS) vulnerability management process is important nowadays, as the number of discovered OSS vulnerabilities is increasing over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vulcurator-a-vulnerability-fixing-commit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Attention-based Multiple Instance Learning for Classification of Multi-Gigapixel Histology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-attention-based-multiple-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first attempt to predict LMP1 status on NPC using deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-attention-based-multiple-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantitative probing: Validating causal models using quantitative domain knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-probing-validating-causal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present quantitative probing as a model-agnostic framework for validating causal models in the presence of quantitative domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantitative-probing-validating-causal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Multimodal Variational Autoencoders: GeBiD Dataset and Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multimodal-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we present a synthetic bimodal dataset designed for a comprehensive evaluation of the joint generation and cross-generation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multimodal-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Speech Enhancement Using Burst Propagation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-speech-enhancement-using-burst</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes the MBURST, a novel multimodal solution for audio-visual speech enhancements that consider the most recent neurological discoveries regarding pyramidal cells of the prefrontal cortex and other brain regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-speech-enhancement-using-burst</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFACT: An Online Human Evaluation Framework for Conversational Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infact-an-online-human-evaluation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational recommender systems (CRS) are interactive agents that support their users in recommendation-related goals through multi-turn conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infact-an-online-human-evaluation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Data-dependent Approach for High Dimensional (Robust) Wasserstein Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-dependent-approach-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our framework is a "data-dependent" approach that has the complexity depending on the intrinsic dimension of the input data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-dependent-approach-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding Demographic un-fairness from Indian Names</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-demographic-un-fairness-from-indian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Demographic classification is essential in fairness assessment in recommender systems or in measuring unintended bias in online networks and voting systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-demographic-un-fairness-from-indian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPruner: Transformer-Based Call Graph Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopruner-transformer-based-call-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a call graph constructed by traditional static analysis tools, AutoPruner takes a Transformer-based approach to capture the semantic relationships between the caller and callee functions associated with each edge in the call graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopruner-transformer-based-call-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk of Bias in Chest X-ray Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-of-bias-in-chest-x-ray-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models are considered a breakthrough in all applications of AI, promising robust and reusable mechanisms for feature extraction, alleviating the need for large amounts of high quality training data for task-specific prediction models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-of-bias-in-chest-x-ray-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bag of Tricks for FGSM Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bag-of-tricks-for-fgsm-adversarial-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training (AT) with samples generated by Fast Gradient Sign Method (FGSM), also known as FGSM-AT, is a computationally simple method to train robust networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bag-of-tricks-for-fgsm-adversarial-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTSEFormer: Progressive Temporal-Spatial Enhanced TransFormer Towards Video Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptseformer-progressive-temporal-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The temporal information is introduced by the temporal feature aggregation model (TFAM), by conducting an attention mechanism between the context frames and the target frame (i. e., the frame to be detected).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptseformer-progressive-temporal-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpaired Image Translation via Vector Symbolic Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpaired-image-translation-via-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image-to-image translation has played an important role in enabling synthetic data for computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpaired-image-translation-via-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Restoration with a Deep Plug-and-Play Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-restoration-with-a-deep-plug-and-play</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under a Bayesian formalism, the method consists in using a deep convolutional denoising network in place of the proximal operator of the prior in an alternating optimization scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-restoration-with-a-deep-plug-and-play</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIND: A Drone Dataset at Signalized Intersection in China</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sind-a-drone-dataset-at-signalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, the behaviors of traffic light violations in SIND are recorded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sind-a-drone-dataset-at-signalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning: Fast and Slow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-fast-and-slow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this theory, we propose \emph{DualNets} (for Dual Networks), a general continual learning framework comprising a fast learning system for supervised learning of pattern-separated representation from specific tasks and a slow learning system for representation learning of task-agnostic general representation via Self-Supervised Learning (SSL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-fast-and-slow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XSimGCL: Towards Extremely Simple Graph Contrastive Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsimgcl-towards-extremely-simple-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning (CL) has recently been demonstrated critical in improving recommendation performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsimgcl-towards-extremely-simple-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASR2K: Speech Recognition for Around 2000 Languages without Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asr2k-speech-recognition-for-around-2000</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve 50% CER and 74% WER on the Wilderness dataset with Crubadan statistics only and improve them to 45% CER and 69% WER when using 10000 raw text utterances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asr2k-speech-recognition-for-around-2000</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USLN: A statistically guided lightweight network for underwater image enhancement via dual-statistic white balance and multi-color space stretch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usln-a-statistically-guided-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional statistic-based methods such as white balance and histogram stretching attempted to adjust the imbalance of color channels and narrow distribution of intensities a priori thus with limited performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usln-a-statistically-guided-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking The Memory Staleness Problem In Dynamics GNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-memory-staleness-problem-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The staleness problem is a well-known problem when working with dynamic data, due to the absence of events for a long time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-the-memory-staleness-problem-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk Aware Belief-dependent Constrained POMDP Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-belief-dependent-constrained-pomdp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Risk awareness is fundamental to an online operating agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-belief-dependent-constrained-pomdp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid dynamic speech imaging at 3 Tesla using combination of a custom vocal tract coil, variable density spirals and manifold regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-dynamic-speech-imaging-at-3-tesla-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit motion binning of the manifold scheme for both repetitive and fluent speaking tasks was demonstrated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-dynamic-speech-imaging-at-3-tesla-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient search of active inference policy spaces using k-means</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-search-of-active-inference-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop an approach to policy selection in active inference that allows us to efficiently search large policy spaces by mapping each policy to its embedding in a vector space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-search-of-active-inference-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViTKD: Practical Guidelines for ViT feature knowledge distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitkd-practical-guidelines-for-vit-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the way of feature-based distillation for ViT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitkd-practical-guidelines-for-vit-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Machine Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-machine-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent regulations require that private information about a user can be removed from computer systems in general and from ML models in particular upon request (e. g. the "right to be forgotten").]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-machine-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneEE: A One-Stage Framework for Fast Overlapping and Nested Event Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneee-a-one-stage-framework-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event extraction (EE) is an essential task of information extraction, which aims to extract structured event information from unstructured text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneee-a-one-stage-framework-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capsule Networks as Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capsule-networks-as-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Capsule networks are a neural network architecture specialized for visual scene recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capsule-networks-as-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Detection for Local Explainability in Evolving Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-detection-for-local-explainability-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we show that local attributions can become obsolete each time the predictive model is updated or concept drift alters the data generating distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/change-detection-for-local-explainability-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-Shot Document-Level Event Argument Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-document-level-event-argument</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event argument extraction (EAE) has been well studied at the sentence level but under-explored at the document level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-document-level-event-argument</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer or Representation Space: What makes BERT-based Evaluation Metrics Robust?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-or-representation-space-what-makes-bert</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of recent embedding-based evaluation metrics for text generation is primarily based on measuring their correlation with human evaluations on standard benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-or-representation-space-what-makes-bert</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Profiling Television Watching Behaviour Using Bayesian Hierarchical Joint Models for Time-to-Event and Count Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/profiling-television-watching-behaviour-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model drastically reduces the dimensionality of the data from thousands of observations per customer to 11 customer-level parameter estimates and random effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/profiling-television-watching-behaviour-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual and Cross-Domain Crisis Classification for Low-Resource Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-and-cross-domain-crisis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study the task of automatically classifying messages that are related to crisis events by leveraging cross-language and cross-domain labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-and-cross-domain-crisis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONCRETE: Improving Cross-lingual Fact-checking with Cross-lingual Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concrete-improving-cross-lingual-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the absence of cross-lingual information retrieval datasets with claim-like queries, we train the retriever with our proposed Cross-lingual Inverse Cloze Task (X-ICT), a self-supervised algorithm that creates training instances by translating the title of a passage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concrete-improving-cross-lingual-fact</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
