<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 09:17:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>KinDEL: DNA-Encoded Library Dataset for Kinase Inhibitors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kindel-dna-encoded-library-dataset-for-kinase</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DNA-Encoded Libraries (DEL) are combinatorial small molecule libraries that offer an efficient way to characterize diverse chemical spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kindel-dna-encoded-library-dataset-for-kinase</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SceneCraft: Layout-Guided 3D Scene Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scenecraft-layout-guided-3d-scene-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The creation of complex 3D scenes tailored to user specifications has been a tedious and challenging task with traditional 3D modeling tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scenecraft-layout-guided-3d-scene-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M$^3$-Impute: Mask-guided Representation Learning for Missing Value Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-impute-mask-guided-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing values are a common problem that poses significant challenges to data analysis and machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-impute-mask-guided-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of Surface Reflections in Maritime Obstacle Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-surface-reflections-in-maritime</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of maritime obstacle detection, the water surface can act like a mirror on certain circumstances, causing reflections on imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-surface-reflections-in-maritime</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language Induced Adversarial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-induced-adversarial-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose a natural language induced adversarial image attack method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-induced-adversarial-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVAM-Pose: Conditional Variational Autoencoder for Multi-Object Monocular Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvam-pose-conditional-variational-autoencoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed label-embedded pose regression strategy interprets the learnt latent space representations utilising continuous pose representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cvam-pose-conditional-variational-autoencoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Supertag Features into Neural Discontinuous Constituent Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-supertag-features-into-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An elegant proposal for a stack-free transition-based parser developed by Coavoux and Cohen (2019) successfully allows for the derivation of any discontinuous constituent tree over a sentence in worst-case quadratic time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integrating-supertag-features-into-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperCorrect: Supervising and Correcting Language Models with Error-Driven Insights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supercorrect-supervising-and-correcting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) like GPT-4, PaLM, and LLaMA have shown significant improvements in various reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supercorrect-supervising-and-correcting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representations of Instruments for Partial Identification of Treatment Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-instruments-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our contributions are three-fold: (1) We propose a novel approach for partial identification through a mapping of instruments to a discrete representation space so that we yield valid bounds on the CATE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-instruments-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bayesian Approach to Weakly-supervised Laparoscopic Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study weakly-supervised laparoscopic image segmentation with sparse annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bayesian-approach-to-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-shot Generative Domain Adaptation in 3D GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-generative-domain-adaptation-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper first considers a novel task known as One-shot 3D Generative Domain Adaptation (GDA), aimed at transferring a pre-trained 3D generator from one domain to a new one, relying solely on a single reference image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-generative-domain-adaptation-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmartPretrain: Model-Agnostic and Dataset-Agnostic Representation Learning for Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartpretrain-model-agnostic-and-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on multiple datasets demonstrate that SmartPretrain consistently improves the performance of state-of-the-art prediction models across datasets, data splits and main metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smartpretrain-model-agnostic-and-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QEFT: Quantization for Efficient Fine-Tuning of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qeft-quantization-for-efficient-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid growth in the use of fine-tuning for large language models (LLMs), optimizing fine-tuning while keeping inference efficient has become highly important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qeft-quantization-for-efficient-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baichuan-Omni Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baichuan-omni-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The salient multimodal capabilities and interactive experience of GPT-4o highlight its critical role in practical applications, yet it lacks a high-performing open-source counterpart.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baichuan-omni-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mentor-KD: Making Small Language Models Better Multi-step Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mentor-kd-making-small-language-models-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have displayed remarkable performances across various complex tasks by leveraging Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mentor-kd-making-small-language-models-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttnGCG: Enhancing Jailbreaking Attacks on LLMs with Attention Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attngcg-enhancing-jailbreaking-attacks-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the vulnerabilities of transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs) to jailbreaking attacks, focusing specifically on the optimization-based Greedy Coordinate Gradient (GCG) strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attngcg-enhancing-jailbreaking-attacks-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kaleidoscope: Learnable Masks for Heterogeneous Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaleidoscope-learnable-masks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL), parameter sharing is commonly employed to enhance sample efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kaleidoscope-learnable-masks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning of State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-of-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, LoRA remains effective for SSM-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-of-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look Gauss, No Pose: Novel View Synthesis using Gaussian Splatting without Accurate Pose Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-gauss-no-pose-novel-view-synthesis-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method enables fast reconstruction of 3D scenes without requiring accurate pose information by jointly optimizing geometry and camera poses, while achieving state-of-the-art results in novel-view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-gauss-no-pose-novel-view-synthesis-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Interaction-aware 3D Gaussian Splatting for One-shot Hand Avatars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-interaction-aware-3d-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce a novel two-stage interaction-aware GS framework that exploits cross-subject hand priors and refines 3D Gaussians in interacting areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-interaction-aware-3d-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning General Representation of 12-Lead Electrocardiogram with a Joint-Embedding Predictive architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-general-representation-of-12-lead</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a self-supervised learning method for 12-lead Electrocardiogram (ECG) analysis, named ECG Joint Embedding Predictive Architecture (ECG-JEPA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-general-representation-of-12-lead</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving Privacy Forward: Mitigating Information Leakage within Smart Vehicles through Synthetic Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-privacy-forward-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic data has emerged as a promising tool to address these privacy concerns, as it allows for the replication of real-world data relationships while minimising the risk of revealing sensitive information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/driving-privacy-forward-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond GFVC: A Progressive Face Video Compression Framework with Adaptive Visual Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-gfvc-a-progressive-face-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep generative models have greatly advanced the progress of face video coding towards promising rate-distortion performance and diverse application functionalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-gfvc-a-progressive-face-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAT: Dialogue-Aware Transformer with Modality-Group Fusion for Human Engagement Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dat-dialogue-aware-transformer-with-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Engagement estimation plays a crucial role in understanding human social behaviors, attracting increasing research interests in fields such as affective computing and human-computer interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dat-dialogue-aware-transformer-with-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retriever-and-Memory: Towards Adaptive Note-Enhanced Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retriever-and-memory-towards-adaptive-note</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) mitigates issues of the factual errors and hallucinated outputs generated by Large Language Models (LLMs) in open-domain question-answering tasks (OpenQA) via introducing external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retriever-and-memory-towards-adaptive-note</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeBiFormer: Vision Transformer with Deformable Agent Bi-level Routing Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiformer-vision-transformer-with-deformable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformers with various attention modules have demonstrated superior performance on vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiformer-vision-transformer-with-deformable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drama: Mamba-Enabled Model-Based Reinforcement Learning Is Sample and Parameter Efficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drama-mamba-enabled-model-based-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges we propose a state space model (SSM) based world model, specifically based on Mamba, that achieves $O(n)$ memory and computational complexity while effectively capturing long-term dependencies and facilitating the use of longer training sequences efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drama-mamba-enabled-model-based-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Score Distillation Sampling for Compositional Text-to-3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-score-distillation-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these challenges, we introduce a novel SDS approach, Semantic Score Distillation Sampling (SemanticSDS), designed to effectively improve the expressiveness and accuracy of compositional text-to-3D generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-score-distillation-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retraining-Free Merging of Sparse Mixture-of-Experts via Hierarchical Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retraining-free-merging-of-sparse-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose Hierarchical Clustering for Sparsely activated Mixture of Experts (HC-SMoE), a task-agnostic expert merging framework that reduces SMoE model parameters without retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retraining-free-merging-of-sparse-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>radarODE-MTL: A Multi-Task Learning Framework with Eccentric Gradient Alignment for Robust Radar-Based ECG Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radarode-mtl-a-multi-task-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Millimeter-wave radar is promising to provide robust and accurate vital sign monitoring in an unobtrusive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radarode-mtl-a-multi-task-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Bidirectional Interaction Model for Referring Remote Sensing Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-bidirectional-interaction-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, a language-guided feature aggregation (LGFA) module is introduced to integrate linguistic information into multi-scale visual features, incorporating an attention deficit compensation mechanism to enhance feature aggregation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-bidirectional-interaction-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain-of-Restoration: Multi-Task Image Restoration Models are Zero-Shot Step-by-Step Universal Image Restorers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-restoration-multi-task-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite previous works typically targeting isolated degradation types, recent research has increasingly focused on addressing composite degradations which involve a complex interplay of multiple different isolated degradations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-restoration-multi-task-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Unsupervised Dynamic MRI Reconstruction via Diffeo-Temporal Equivariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-unsupervised-dynamic-mri-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing dynamic MRI image sequences from undersampled accelerated measurements is crucial for faster and higher spatiotemporal resolution real-time imaging of cardiac motion, free breathing motion and many other applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-unsupervised-dynamic-mri-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MinorityPrompt: Text to Minority Image Generation via Prompt Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minorityprompt-text-to-minority-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the generation of minority samples using pretrained text-to-image (T2I) latent diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minorityprompt-text-to-minority-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Loop: Learning to Generate Writing Feedback via Language Model Simulated Student Revisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-loop-learning-to-generate-writing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, it remains unclear whether the feedback generated by these models is truly effective in enhancing the quality of student revisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closing-the-loop-learning-to-generate-writing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KV Prediction for Improved Time to First Token</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kv-prediction-for-improved-time-to-first</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our method, a small auxiliary model is used to process the prompt and produce an approximation of the KV cache used by a base model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kv-prediction-for-improved-time-to-first</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToMiE: Towards Modular Growth in Enhanced SMPL Skeleton for 3D Human with Animatable Garments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomie-towards-modular-growth-in-enhanced-smpl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we highlight a critical yet often overlooked factor in most 3D human tasks, namely modeling humans with complex garments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tomie-towards-modular-growth-in-enhanced-smpl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MELO: An Evaluation Benchmark for Multilingual Entity Linking of Occupations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melo-an-evaluation-benchmark-for-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Multilingual Entity Linking of Occupations (MELO) Benchmark, a new collection of 48 datasets for evaluating the linking of entity mentions in 21 languages to the ESCO Occupations multilingual taxonomy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/melo-an-evaluation-benchmark-for-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSGDN: Contrastive Signed Graph Diffusion Network for Predicting Crop Gene-Trait Associations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csgdn-contrastive-signed-graph-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positive and negative association preidiction between gene and trait help studies for crops to perform complex physiological functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csgdn-contrastive-signed-graph-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUS-Net: Social Bias Classification in Text with Generalizations, Unfairness, and Stereotypes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gus-net-social-bias-classification-in-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The detection of bias in natural language processing (NLP) is a critical challenge, particularly with the increasing use of large language models (LLMs) in various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gus-net-social-bias-classification-in-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable and Animatable Gaussian Head Avatar</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-and-animatable-gaussian-head</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Generalizable and Animatable Gaussian head Avatar (GAGAvatar) for one-shot animatable head avatar reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-and-animatable-gaussian-head</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noether's razor: Learning Conserved Quantities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noether-s-razor-learning-conserved-quantities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that our method correctly identifies the correct conserved quantities and U($n$) and SE($n$) symmetry groups, improving overall performance and predictive accuracy on test data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noether-s-razor-learning-conserved-quantities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal-Difference Variational Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-difference-variational-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate this, we propose new learning objectives that integrate the regularization effects of multiple previous posterior estimations, preventing individual errors from dominating future posterior updates and compounding over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-difference-variational-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thought2Text: Text Generation from EEG Signal using Large Language Models (LLMs)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thought2text-text-generation-from-eeg-signal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decoding and expressing brain activity in a comprehensible form is a challenging frontier in AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thought2text-text-generation-from-eeg-signal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-aware Simulation-based Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-aware-simulation-based-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simulation-based inference (SBI) is the preferred framework for estimating parameters of intractable models in science and engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-aware-simulation-based-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Window Function-less DFT with Reduced Noise and Latency for Real-Time Music Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/window-function-less-dft-with-reduced-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Music analysis applications demand algorithms that can provide both high time and frequency resolution while minimizing noise in an already-noisy signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/window-function-less-dft-with-reduced-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When and Where Did it Happen? An Encoder-Decoder Model to Identify Scenario Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-where-did-it-happen-an-encoder</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a neural architecture finetuned for the task of scenario context generation: The relevant location and time of an event or entity mentioned in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-where-did-it-happen-an-encoder</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning in Spectral Domain for Point Cloud Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-in-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PointGST freezes the pre-trained model and introduces a lightweight, trainable Point Cloud Spectral Adapter (PCSA) to fine-tune parameters in the spectral domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-in-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RayEmb: Arbitrary Landmark Detection in X-Ray Images Using Ray Embedding Subspace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rayemb-arbitrary-landmark-detection-in-x-ray</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anatomical landmarks pre-annotated in the CT volume can be detected in X-ray images to establish 2D-3D correspondences, which are then utilized for registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rayemb-arbitrary-landmark-detection-in-x-ray</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCoder2: Better Math Reasoning from Continued Pretraining on Model-translated Mathematical Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder2-better-math-reasoning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training several popular base models with this corpus significantly improves their mathematical abilities, leading to the creation of the MathCoder2 family of models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder2-better-math-reasoning-from</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
