<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 09:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Cognitive Backdoor Patterns within an Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-cognitive-backdoor-patterns-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments to show that CD can robustly detect a wide range of advanced backdoor attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-cognitive-backdoor-patterns-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train Hard, Fight Easy: Robust Meta Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-hard-fight-easy-robust-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that the former disappears in MRL, and address the latter via the novel Robust Meta RL algorithm (RoML).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/train-hard-fight-easy-robust-meta</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WL meet VC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-meet-vc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, when an upper bound on the graphs' order is known, we show a tight connection between the number of graphs distinguishable by the $1\text{-}\mathsf{WL}$ and GNNs' VC dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wl-meet-vc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Reasoning of Entities and Events in Procedural Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-of-entities-and-events-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entities and events have long been regarded as the crux of machine reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-reasoning-of-entities-and-events-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Language Model as Multi-task Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-language-model-as-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further propose multi-task molecular prefix tuning across several molecular generation tasks and different molecular domains (synthetic & natural products) with a self-feedback mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-language-model-as-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Regions of Counterfactual Explanations via Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-regions-of-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, our method provides a whole region of CEs allowing the user to choose a suitable recourse to obtain a desired outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-regions-of-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRaLay: A Multilingual and Multimodal Dataset for Long Range and Layout-Aware Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loralay-a-multilingual-and-multimodal-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text Summarization is a popular task and an active area of research for the Natural Language Processing community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loralay-a-multilingual-and-multimodal-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Temporal Modeling for CLIP-based Image-to-Video Knowledge Transferring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-temporal-modeling-for-clip-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, based on the CLIP model, we revisit temporal modeling in the context of image-to-video knowledge transferring, which is the key point for extending image-text pretrained models to the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-temporal-modeling-for-clip-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftMatch: Addressing the Quantity-Quality Trade-off in Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmatch-addressing-the-quantity-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The critical challenge of Semi-Supervised Learning (SSL) is how to effectively leverage the limited labeled data and massive unlabeled data to improve the model's generalization performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softmatch-addressing-the-quantity-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Experiences Are Influential for Your Agent? Policy Iteration with Turn-over Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-experiences-are-influential-for-your</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In reinforcement learning (RL) with experience replay, experiences stored in a replay buffer influence the RL agent's performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-experiences-are-influential-for-your</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Contrastive Learning for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-for-skeleton-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a graph contrastive learning framework for skeleton-based action recognition (\textit{SkeletonGCL}) to explore the \textit{global} context across all sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-learning-for-skeleton-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut and Learn for Unsupervised Object Detection and Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Cut-and-LEaRn (CutLER), a simple approach for training unsupervised object detection and segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact Transformer Tracker with Correlative Masked Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-transformer-tracker-with-correlative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer framework has been showing superior performances in visual object tracking for its great strength in information aggregation across the template and search image with the well-known attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-transformer-tracker-with-correlative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph-based Recommendation for Sparse and Heterogeneous User Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-recommendation-for-sparse-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a graph-based recommender model which utilizes heterogeneous interactions between users and content of different types and is able to operate well on small-scale datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-based-recommendation-for-sparse-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory-Aware Eligibility Traces for Off-Policy Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-aware-eligibility-traces-for-off</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Off-policy learning from multistep returns is crucial for sample-efficient reinforcement learning, but counteracting off-policy bias without exacerbating variance is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajectory-aware-eligibility-traces-for-off</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Model for All Domains: Collaborative Domain-Prefix Tuning for Cross-Domain NER</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-model-for-all-domains-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous typical solutions mainly obtain a NER model by pre-trained language models (PLMs) with data from a rich-resource domain and adapt it to the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-model-for-all-domains-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWING: Balancing Coverage and Faithfulness for Dialogue Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swing-balancing-coverage-and-faithfulness-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Missing information is a common issue of dialogue summarization where some information in the reference summaries is not covered in the generated summaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swing-balancing-coverage-and-faithfulness-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Tooth Mesh Segmentation with Simplified Mesh Cell Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-tooth-mesh-segmentation-with-simplified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summarizing of the mesh cell/triangle in this manner imposes an implicit structural constraint and makes it difficult to work with multiple resolutions which is done in many point cloud based deep learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-tooth-mesh-segmentation-with-simplified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Layers Play the Lottery, all Tickets Win at Initialization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-layers-play-the-lottery-all-tickets-win</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate LTH and pruning at initialization from the lens of layer pruning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-layers-play-the-lottery-all-tickets-win</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViDeBERTa: A powerful pre-trained language model for Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videberta-a-powerful-pre-trained-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ViDeBERTa, a new pre-trained monolingual language model for Vietnamese, with three versions - ViDeBERTa_xsmall, ViDeBERTa_base, and ViDeBERTa_large, which are pre-trained on a large-scale corpus of high-quality and diverse Vietnamese texts using DeBERTa architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videberta-a-powerful-pre-trained-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLPGradientFlow: going with the flow of multilayer perceptrons (and finding minima fast and accurately)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlpgradientflow-going-with-the-flow-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLPGradientFlow is a software package to solve numerically the gradient flow differential equation $\dot \theta = -\nabla \mathcal L(\theta; \mathcal D)$, where $\theta$ are the parameters of a multi-layer perceptron, $\mathcal D$ is some data set, and $\nabla \mathcal L$ is the gradient of a loss function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlpgradientflow-going-with-the-flow-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated multilingual detection of Pro-Kremlin propaganda in newspapers and Telegram posts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-multilingual-detection-of-pro</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The full-scale conflict between the Russian Federation and Ukraine generated an unprecedented amount of news articles and social media data reflecting opposing ideologies and narratives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-multilingual-detection-of-pro</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E(n)-equivariant Graph Neural Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-n-equivariant-graph-neural-cellular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cellular automata (CAs) are computational models exhibiting rich dynamics emerging from the local interaction of cells arranged in a regular lattice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-n-equivariant-graph-neural-cellular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Tenant Optimization For Few-Shot Task-Oriented FAQ Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-tenant-optimization-for-few-shot-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Business-specific Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ) retrieval in task-oriented dialog systems poses unique challenges vis-\`a-vis community based FAQs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-tenant-optimization-for-few-shot-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster DAN: Multi-target Queries with Document Positional Encoding for End-to-end Handwritten Document Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-dan-multi-target-queries-with-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in handwritten text recognition enabled to recognize whole documents in an end-to-end way: the Document Attention Network (DAN) recognizes the characters one after the other through an attention-based prediction process until reaching the end of the document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faster-dan-multi-target-queries-with-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact and rapid linear clustering of networks with dynamic programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-and-rapid-linear-clustering-of-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of clustering networks whose nodes have imputed or physical positions in a single dimension, such as prestige hierarchies or the similarity dimension of hyperbolic embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-and-rapid-linear-clustering-of-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Approximate Method for Online Convolutional Dictionary Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-approximate-method-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing convolutional dictionary learning (CDL) algorithms are based on batch learning, where the dictionary filters and the convolutional sparse representations are optimized in an alternating manner using a training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-approximate-method-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Control of Partial Differential Equations Using Convolutional Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-control-of-partial-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a convolutional framework which significantly reduces the complexity and thus, the computational effort for distributed reinforcement learning control of dynamical systems governed by partial differential equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-control-of-partial-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing Language Model-based Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-language-model-based-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build four new datasets: E-FB15k237, A-FB15k237, E-WN18RR, and A-WN18RR, and evaluate several knowledge editing baselines demonstrating the limited ability of previous models to handle the proposed challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editing-language-model-based-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HealthEdge: A Machine Learning-Based Smart Healthcare Framework for Prediction of Type 2 Diabetes in an Integrated IoT, Edge, and Cloud Computing System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthedge-a-machine-learning-based-smart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diabetes Mellitus has no permanent cure to date and is one of the leading causes of death globally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/healthedge-a-machine-learning-based-smart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Medical Image Segmentation with TransCeption: A Multi-Scale Feature Fusion Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-medical-image-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) In contrast to a bridge that only contains token-wise self-attention, we propose a Dual Transformer Bridge that also includes channel-wise self-attention to exploit correlations between scales at different stages from a dual perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-medical-image-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Consistent Deep Rigid MRI Motion Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-consistent-deep-rigid-mri-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion artifacts are a pervasive problem in MRI, leading to misdiagnosis or mischaracterization in population-level imaging studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-consistent-deep-rigid-mri-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salesforce CausalAI Library: A Fast and Scalable Framework for Causal Analysis of Time Series and Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salesforce-causalai-library-a-fast-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Salesforce CausalAI Library, an open-source library for causal analysis using observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salesforce-causalai-library-a-fast-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExaRanker: Explanation-Augmented Neural Ranker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaranker-explanation-augmented-neural-ranker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has shown that inducing a large language model (LLM) to generate explanations prior to outputting an answer is an effective strategy to improve performance on a wide range of reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaranker-explanation-augmented-neural-ranker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEJA VU: Continual Model Generalization For Unseen Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-continual-model-generalization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations of DA and DG in handling the Unfamiliar Period during continual domain shift, we propose RaTP, a framework that focuses on improving models' target domain generalization (TDG) capability, while also achieving effective target domain adaptation (TDA) capability right after training on certain domains and forgetting alleviation (FA) capability on past domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deja-vu-continual-model-generalization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Selection: Key to Enhance Node Classification with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-key-to-enhance-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graphs help to define the relationships between entities in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-key-to-enhance-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GePA*SE: Generalized Edge-Based Parallel A* for Slow Evaluations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gepa-se-generalized-edge-based-parallel-a-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in a number of robotics domains, the action space is heterogenous in the computational effort required to evaluate the cost of an action and its outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gepa-se-generalized-edge-based-parallel-a-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audience-Centric Natural Language Generation via Style Infusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audience-centric-natural-language-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing approaches demonstrate textual style transfer with large volumes of parallel or non-parallel data, we argue that grounding style on audience-independent external factors is innately limiting for two reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audience-centric-natural-language-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Super-Resolution using Efficient Striped Window Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-using-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further exploit the potential of the transformer, we propose a novel flexible window training strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-using-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a Waffle Iron for Automotive Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-waffle-iron-for-automotive-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation of point clouds in autonomous driving datasets requires techniques that can process large numbers of points over large field of views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-waffle-iron-for-automotive-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Reinforcement Learning for Dexterous Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-reinforcement-learning-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A potential way to address these limitations is to add constraints during learning that restrict and guide the robot's behavior during training as well as roll outs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-reinforcement-learning-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Distillation for Semi-Supervised Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-distillation-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a model well-trained with a large-scale base dataset, Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning (FSCIL) aims at incrementally learning novel classes from a few labeled samples by avoiding overfitting, without catastrophically forgetting all encountered classes previously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-distillation-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Agnostic Sample Reweighting for Out-of-Distribution Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-sample-reweighting-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The overfitting issue is addressed by considering a bilevel formulation to search for the sample reweighting, in which the generalization complexity depends on the search space of sample weights instead of the model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-sample-reweighting-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Data-Driven Optimization: From Context to Decision and Back Again</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-data-driven-optimization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-driven optimization uses contextual information and machine learning algorithms to find solutions to decision problems with uncertain parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-data-driven-optimization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Semantic Scholar Open Data Platform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-semantic-scholar-open-data-platform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The volume of scientific output is creating an urgent need for automated tools to help scientists keep up with developments in their field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-semantic-scholar-open-data-platform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation Alone Can Improve Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-alone-can-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation, which is effective at preventing overfitting in standard training, has been observed by many previous works to be ineffective in mitigating overfitting in adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-alone-can-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting the 2016-2017 Central Apennines Earthquake Sequence with a Neural Point Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-the-2016-2017-central-apennines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate whether these flexible point process models can be applied to short-term seismicity forecasting by extending an existing temporal neural model to the magnitude domain and we show how this model can forecast earthquakes above a target magnitude threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-the-2016-2017-central-apennines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Interactive Lung Lesion Segmentation: A Framework for Annotating PET/CT Images based on Physiological and Anatomical Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interactive-lung-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep learning enabled the accurate segmentation of various diseases in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interactive-lung-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViHOS: Hate Speech Spans Detection for Vietnamese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vihos-hate-speech-spans-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise in hateful and offensive language directed at other users is one of the adverse side effects of the increased use of social networking platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vihos-hate-speech-spans-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Same or Different? Diff-Vectors for Authorship Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/same-or-different-diff-vectors-for-authorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the effects on authorship identification tasks of a fundamental shift in how to conceive the vectorial representations of documents that are given as input to a supervised learner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/same-or-different-diff-vectors-for-authorship</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
