<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 21:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Value Decomposition with Greedy Marginal Contribution Computation for Cooperative Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-value-decomposition-with-greedy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first illustrate that the proposed value decomposition can consider the complicated interactions among agents and is feasible to learn in large-scale scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-value-decomposition-with-greedy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Anomaly Detection for Software Systems via Semi-supervised Cross-modal Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-anomaly-detection-for-software-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study demonstrates that logs and metrics can manifest system anomalies collaboratively and complementarily, and neither of them only is sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-anomaly-detection-for-software-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>simpleKT: A Simple But Tough-to-Beat Baseline for Knowledge Tracing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplekt-a-simple-but-tough-to-beat-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge tracing (KT) is the problem of predicting students' future performance based on their historical interactions with intelligent tutoring systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplekt-a-simple-but-tough-to-beat-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffFashion: Reference-based Fashion Design with Structure-aware Transfer by Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difffashion-reference-based-fashion-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on a new fashion design task, where we aim to transfer a reference appearance image onto a clothing image while preserving the structure of the clothing image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difffashion-reference-based-fashion-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team-DETR: Guide Queries as a Professional Team in Detection Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/team-detr-guide-queries-as-a-professional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent proposed DETR variants have made tremendous progress in various scenarios due to their streamlined processes and remarkable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/team-detr-guide-queries-as-a-professional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative State Value Estimation for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conservative-state-value-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Conservative State Value Estimation (CSVE), a new approach that learns conservative V-function via directly imposing penalty on OOD states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conservative-state-value-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Guidance for Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-guidance-for-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typical diffusion models are trained to accept a particular form of conditioning, most commonly text, and cannot be conditioned on other modalities without retraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-guidance-for-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lero: A Learning-to-Rank Query Optimizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lero-a-learning-to-rank-query-optimizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a learning to rank query optimizer, called Lero, which builds on top of the native query optimizer and continuously learns to improve query optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lero-a-learning-to-rank-query-optimizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKnow: A Unified Knowledge Protocol for Common-Sense Reasoning and Vision-Language Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uknow-a-unified-knowledge-protocol-for-common</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a unified knowledge protocol, called UKnow, which facilitates knowledge-based studies from the perspective of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uknow-a-unified-knowledge-protocol-for-common</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard-aware Instance Adaptive Self-training for Unsupervised Cross-domain Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-aware-instance-adaptive-self-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The divergence between labeled training data and unlabeled testing data is a significant challenge for recent deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hard-aware-instance-adaptive-self-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport for Change Detection on LiDAR Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-change-detection-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the DEM's interpolation step causes an information loss related to the height of the objects, affecting the detection capability of building changes, where the high resolution of LiDAR point clouds in the third dimension would be the most beneficial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-for-change-detection-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SwitchPrompt: Learning Domain-Specific Gated Soft Prompts for Classification in Low-Resource Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchprompt-learning-domain-specific-gated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompting pre-trained language models leads to promising results across natural language processing tasks but is less effective when applied in low-resource domains, due to the domain gap between the pre-training data and the downstream task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/switchprompt-learning-domain-specific-gated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOWOv2: A Stronger yet Efficient Multi-level Detection Framework for Real-time Spatio-temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yowov2-a-stronger-yet-efficient-multi-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Designing a real-time framework for the spatio-temporal action detection task is still a challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yowov2-a-stronger-yet-efficient-multi-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCONNA: A Stochastic Computing Based Optical Accelerator for Ultra-Fast, Energy-Efficient Inference of Integer-Quantized CNNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sconna-a-stochastic-computing-based-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To leverage the innate precision flexibility of stochastic computing, we invent an MRR-based optical stochastic multiplier (OSM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sconna-a-stochastic-computing-based-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Summarization Data to Help Text Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-summarization-data-to-help-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major problems with text simplification is the lack of high-quality data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-summarization-data-to-help-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Cross-system Shilling Attacks with Limited Access to Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-cross-system-shilling-attacks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the idea of Cross-system Attack, we design a Practical Cross-system Shilling Attack (PC-Attack) framework that requires little information about the victim RS model and the target RS data for conducting attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-cross-system-shilling-attacks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Complex Event Scenarios via Simple Entity-focused Questions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-event-scenarios-via-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event scenarios are often complex and involve multiple event sequences connected through different entity participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-complex-event-scenarios-via-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have become the de facto models of choice in machine learning, typically leading to impressive performance on many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EspalomaCharge: Machine learning-enabled ultra-fast partial charge assignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espalomacharge-machine-learning-enabled-ultra</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our hybrid approach couples a graph neural network to a streamlined charge equilibration approach in order to predict molecule-specific atomic electronegativity and hardness parameters, followed by analytical determination of optimal charge-equilibrated parameters that preserves total molecular charge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/espalomacharge-machine-learning-enabled-ultra</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightsolver challenges a leading deep learning solver for Max-2-SAT problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightsolver-challenges-a-leading-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maximum 2-satisfiability (MAX-2-SAT) is a type of combinatorial decision problem that is known to be NP-hard.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightsolver-challenges-a-leading-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Multi-source Active Learning for Natural Language Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-source-active-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that four popular active learning schemes fail to outperform random selection when applied to unlabelled pools comprised of multiple data sources on the task of natural language inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-multi-source-active-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A modern look at the relationship between sharpness and generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modern-look-at-the-relationship-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, we observe that sharpness does not correlate well with generalization but rather with some training parameters like the learning rate that can be positively or negatively correlated with generalization depending on the setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modern-look-at-the-relationship-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting long-term collective animal behavior with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-long-term-collective-animal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces a deep learning model for social interactions in the fish species Hemigrammus rhodostomus, and compares its results to experiments and to the results of a state-of-the-art analytical model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-long-term-collective-animal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPISODE: Episodic Gradient Clipping with Periodic Resampled Corrections for Federated Learning with Heterogeneous Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/episode-episodic-gradient-clipping-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we design EPISODE, the very first algorithm to solve FL problems with heterogeneous data in the nonconvex and relaxed smoothness setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/episode-episodic-gradient-clipping-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot Federated Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a conformal prediction method to construct prediction sets in a oneshot federated learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-federated-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Noise Filtering with Dynamic Sparse Training in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-noise-filtering-with-dynamic-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tomorrow's robots will need to distinguish useful information from noise when performing different tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-noise-filtering-with-dynamic-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Circuits That Know What They Don't Know</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-circuits-that-know-what-they</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to neural networks, they are often assumed to be well-calibrated and robust to out-of-distribution (OOD) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-circuits-that-know-what-they</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising the Cost of Malicious AI-Powered Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raising-the-cost-of-malicious-ai-powered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an approach to mitigating the risks of malicious image editing posed by large diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raising-the-cost-of-malicious-ai-powered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Hardware-Efficient Long Convolutions for Sequence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-hardware-efficient-long-convolutions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that a key requirement to achieving high performance is keeping the convolution kernels smooth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-hardware-efficient-long-convolutions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLIM: Sparsified Late Interaction for Multi-Vector Retrieval with Inverted Indexes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-sparsified-late-interaction-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among them, ColBERT is probably the most established method which is based on the late interaction of contextualized token embeddings of pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slim-sparsified-late-interaction-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comp2Comp: Open-Source Body Composition Assessment on Computed Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comp2comp-open-source-body-composition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting quantitative body composition measures manually from CT scans is a cumbersome and time-consuming task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comp2comp-open-source-body-composition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA-DepthNet: A Variational Approach to Single Image Depth Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/va-depthnet-a-variational-approach-to-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While state-of-the-art deep neural network methods for SIDP learn the scene depth from images in a supervised setting, they often overlook the invaluable invariances and priors in the rigid scene space, such as the regularity of the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/va-depthnet-a-variational-approach-to-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliability Assurance for Deep Neural Network Architectures Against Numerical Defects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-assurance-for-deep-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assure high reliability against numerical defects, in this paper, we propose the RANUM approach including novel techniques for three reliability assurance tasks: detection of potential numerical defects, confirmation of potential-defect feasibility, and suggestion of defect fixes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-assurance-for-deep-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Multivariate Time Series Classifiers through Self-Attention and Relative Positioning Infusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multivariate-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time Series Classification (TSC) is an important and challenging task for many visual computing applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-multivariate-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TIGER: Temporal Interaction Graph Embedding with Restarts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiger-temporal-interaction-graph-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to the entangled temporal and structural dependencies, existing methods have to process the sequence of events chronologically and consecutively to ensure node representations are up-to-date.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiger-temporal-interaction-graph-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AbLit: A Resource for Analyzing and Generating Abridged Versions of English Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablit-a-resource-for-analyzing-and-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset captures passage-level alignments between the original and abridged texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ablit-a-resource-for-analyzing-and-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Scale Multi-Lingual Multi-Modal Summarization Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-lingual-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant developments in techniques such as encoder-decoder models have enabled us to represent information comprising multiple modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-lingual-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishability Calibration to In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishability-calibration-to-in-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When using prompt-based learning for text classification, the goal is to use a pre-trained language model (PLM) to predict a missing token in a pre-defined template given an input text, which can be mapped to a class label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishability-calibration-to-in-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELEA -- Build your own Evolutionary Algorithm in your Browser</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elea-build-your-own-evolutionary-algorithm-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide an open source framework to experiment with evolutionary algorithms which we call "Experimenting and Learning toolkit for Evolutionary Algorithms (ELEA)".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elea-build-your-own-evolutionary-algorithm-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stitchable Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stitchable-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As each model family consists of pretrained models with diverse scales (e. g., DeiT-Ti/S/B), it naturally arises a fundamental question of how to effectively assemble these readily available models in a family for dynamic accuracy-efficiency trade-offs at runtime.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stitchable-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CholecTriplet2022: Show me a tool and tell me the triplet -- an endoscopic vision challenge for surgical action triplet detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cholectriplet2022-show-me-a-tool-and-tell-me</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the CholecTriplet2022 challenge, which extends surgical action triplet modeling from recognition to detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cholectriplet2022-show-me-a-tool-and-tell-me</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Arbitrary Shaped Clustering through Correlated Gaussian Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-arbitrary-shaped-clustering-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is no convincing evidence that backpropagation is a biologically plausible mechanism, and further studies of alternative learning methods are needed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-arbitrary-shaped-clustering-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preconditioned Score-based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preconditioned-score-based-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with the latest generative models (\eg, CLD-SGM, DDIM, and Analytic-DDIM), PDS can achieve the best sampling quality on CIFAR-10 at a FID score of 1. 99.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preconditioned-score-based-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniAdapter: Unified Parameter-Efficient Transfer Learning for Cross-modal Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniadapter-unified-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, on the MSRVTT retrieval task, UniAdapter achieves 49. 7% recall@1 with 2. 2% model parameters, outperforming the latest competitors by 2. 0%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniadapter-unified-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implications of the Convergence of Language and Vision Model Geometries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implications-of-the-convergence-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale pretrained language models (LMs) are said to ``lack the ability to connect [their] utterances to the world'' (Bender and Koller, 2020).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implications-of-the-convergence-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Anatomical Federated Network (Dafne): an open client/server framework for the continuous collaborative improvement of deep-learning-based medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-anatomical-federated-network-dafne-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation is a crucial step to extract quantitative information from medical (and, specifically, radiological) images to aid the diagnostic process, clinical follow-up.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-anatomical-federated-network-dafne-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Can't Discourse Parsing Generalize? A Thorough Investigation of the Impact of Data Diversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-can-t-discourse-parsing-generalize-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this study is the first to fully evaluate cross-corpus RST parsing generalizability on complete trees, examine between-genre degradation within an RST corpus, and investigate the impact of genre diversity in training data composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-can-t-discourse-parsing-generalize-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Recommendation Fairness via Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-fairness-via-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We augment imbalanced training data towards balanced data distribution to improve fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-recommendation-fairness-via-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contour Context: Abstract Structural Distribution for 3D LiDAR Loop Detection and Metric Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contour-context-abstract-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes \textit{Contour Context}, a simple, effective, and efficient topological loop closure detection pipeline with accurate 3-DoF metric pose estimation, targeting the urban utonomous driving scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contour-context-abstract-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GPT-3 Perform Statutory Reasoning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-perform-statutory-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By also posing the same questions when the synthetic statutes are written in sentence form, we find that some of GPT-3's poor performance results from difficulty in parsing the typical structure of statutes, containing subsections and paragraphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gpt-3-perform-statutory-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
