<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 09:14:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Convex Clustering through MM: An Efficient Algorithm to Perform Hierarchical Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-clustering-through-mm-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convex clustering is a modern method with both hierarchical and $k$-means clustering characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convex-clustering-through-mm-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Are Human-Level Prompt Engineers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-human-level-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By conditioning on natural language instructions, large language models (LLMs) have displayed impressive capabilities as general-purpose computers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-human-level-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single SMPC Invocation DPHelmet: Differentially Private Distributed Learning on a Large Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-smpc-invocation-dphelmet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that locally training support vector machines (SVMs) and computing their averages leads to a learning technique that is scalable to a large number of users, satisfies differential privacy, and is applicable to non-trivial tasks, such as CIFAR-10.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-smpc-invocation-dphelmet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crosslingual Generalization through Multitask Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslingual-generalization-through-multitask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find finetuning large multilingual language models on English tasks with English prompts allows for task generalization to non-English languages that appear only in the pretraining corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslingual-generalization-through-multitask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Few-shot Learning Without Using any Adversarial Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-few-shot-learning-without-using-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods rely on the generation of adversarial samples in every episode of training, which further adds a computational burden.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-few-shot-learning-without-using-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Argument Role Prediction for Event Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-argument-role-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we formulate the role prediction problem as an in-filling task and construct prompts for a pre-trained language model to generate candidate roles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-argument-role-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-free Defense of Black Box Models Against Adversarial Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-defense-of-black-box-models-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At test time, WNR combined with trained regenerator network is prepended to the black box network, resulting in a high boost in adversarial accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-free-defense-of-black-box-models-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Unsupervised Outlier Model Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unsupervised-outlier-model-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At its core, ELECT is based on meta-learning; transferring prior knowledge (e. g. model performance) on historical datasets that are similar to the new one to facilitate UOMS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unsupervised-outlier-model-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedTP: Federated Learning by Transformer Personalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedtp-federated-learning-by-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of using a vanilla personalization mechanism that maintains personalized self-attention layers of each client locally, we develop a learn-to-personalize mechanism to further encourage the cooperation among clients and to increase the scablability and generalization of FedTP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedtp-federated-learning-by-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the State-of-the-Art Language Modeling Methods and Data Augmentation Techniques for Multilingual Clause-Level Morphology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-state-of-the-art-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Transformer architectures with data augmentation and pipeline architectures achieved the best results for inflection and reinflection tasks, pipelines and prefix-tuning on mGPT received the highest results for the analysis task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-state-of-the-art-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair and Optimal Classification via Transports to Wasserstein-Barycenter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-and-optimal-classification-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our insight comes from the key observation that finding the optimal fair classifier is equivalent to solving a Wasserstein-barycenter problem under $\ell_1$-norm restricted to the vertices of the probability simplex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-and-optimal-classification-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and robust Bayesian Inference using Gaussian Processes with GPry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-bayesian-inference-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GPry does not need any pre-training, special hardware such as GPUs, and is intended as a drop-in replacement for traditional Monte Carlo methods for Bayesian inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-bayesian-inference-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning of Neural Machine Translation within Low Forgetting Risk Regions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-neural-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose two methods to search the low forgetting risk regions, which are based on the curvature of loss and the impacts of the parameters on the model output, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-of-neural-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Galaxy Image Deconvolution for Weak Gravitational Lensing with Physics-informed Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-image-deconvolution-for-weak</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Removing optical and atmospheric blur from galaxy images significantly improves galaxy shape measurements for weak gravitational lensing and galaxy evolution studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/galaxy-image-deconvolution-for-weak</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MALUNet: A Multi-Attention and Light-weight UNet for Skin Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/malunet-a-multi-attention-and-light-weight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a light-weight model to achieve competitive performances for skin lesion segmentation at the lowest cost of parameters and computational complexity so far.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/malunet-a-multi-attention-and-light-weight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Log-density gradient covariance and automatic metric tensors for Riemann manifold Monte Carlo methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/log-density-gradient-covariance-and-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When implemented in conjunction with a Riemann manifold variant of the recently proposed numerical generalized randomized Hamiltonian Monte Carlo processes, the proposed methodology is highly competitive, in particular for the more challenging target distributions associated with Bayesian hierarchical models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/log-density-gradient-covariance-and-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Spatially Sparse Inference for Conditional GANs and Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-spatially-sparse-inference-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With 1. 2%-area edited regions, our method reduces the computation of DDIM by 7. 5$\times$ and GauGAN by 18$\times$ while preserving the visual fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-spatially-sparse-inference-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterMPL: Momentum Pseudo-Labeling with Intermediate CTC Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intermpl-momentum-pseudo-labeling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents InterMPL, a semi-supervised learning method of end-to-end automatic speech recognition (ASR) that performs pseudo-labeling (PL) with intermediate supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intermpl-momentum-pseudo-labeling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying And Interpreting Neural Networks using Finite Automata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-and-interpreting-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Verifying properties and interpreting the behaviour of deep neural networks (DNN) is an important task given their ubiquitous use in applications, including safety-critical ones, and their blackbox nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-and-interpreting-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cluster-Based Autoencoders for Volumetric Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-based-autoencoders-for-volumetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoencoders allow to reconstruct a given input from a small set of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cluster-based-autoencoders-for-volumetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPM-Solver++: Fast Solver for Guided Sampling of Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpm-solver-fast-solver-for-guided-sampling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The commonly-used fast sampler for guided sampling is DDIM, a first-order diffusion ODE solver that generally needs 100 to 250 steps for high-quality samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpm-solver-fast-solver-for-guided-sampling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoneme Segmentation Using Self-Supervised Speech Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoneme-segmentation-using-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply transfer learning to the task of phoneme segmentation and demonstrate the utility of representations learned in self-supervised pre-training for the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/phoneme-segmentation-using-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynamicLight: Dynamically Tuning Traffic Signal Duration with DRL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamiclight-dynamically-tuning-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning (DRL) is becoming increasingly popular in implementing traffic signal control (TSC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamiclight-dynamically-tuning-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Embedding-based High-dimensional Batch Bayesian Optimization without Reconstruction Mappings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-embedding-based-high-dimensional-batch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate a simple alternative approach: tackling the problem in the original high-dimensional space using the information from the learned low-dimensional structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-embedding-based-high-dimensional-batch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insight into cloud processes from unsupervised classification with a rotationally invariant autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insight-into-cloud-processes-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clouds play a critical role in the Earth's energy budget and their potential changes are one of the largest uncertainties in future climate projections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insight-into-cloud-processes-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Auto-Augment with Label Preservation: A Representation Learning Principle Guided Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-auto-augment-with-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments, we show that our method consistently brings non-trivial improvements to the three aforementioned learning tasks from both efficiency and final performance, either or not combined with strong pre-defined augmentations, e. g., on medical images when domain knowledge is unavailable and the existing augmentation techniques perform poorly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-auto-augment-with-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Active Learning on Heteroskedastic Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-active-learning-on-heteroskedastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we demonstrate the catastrophic failure of these active learning algorithms on heteroskedastic distributions and propose a fine-tuning-based approach to mitigate these failures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-active-learning-on-heteroskedastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Multimodal Fusion for Generalizable Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-multimodal-fusion-for-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, in this paper, we propose DMF, a Deep Multimodal Fusion network for the general scenarios on person re-identification task, where rich semantic knowledge is introduced to assist in feature representation learning during the pre-training stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-multimodal-fusion-for-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PI is back! Switching Acquisition Functions in Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pi-is-back-switching-acquisition-functions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also compare this to a random schedule and round-robin selection of EI and PI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pi-is-back-switching-acquisition-functions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic SuperPoint: A Deep Semantic Descriptor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-superpoint-a-deep-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several SLAM methods benefit from the use of semantic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-superpoint-a-deep-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-end deep multi-score model for No-reference stereoscopic image quality assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-deep-multi-score-model-for-no-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike existing stereoscopic IQA measures which focus mainly on estimating a global human score, we suggest incorporating left, right, and stereoscopic objective scores to extract the corresponding properties of each view, and so forth estimating stereoscopic image quality without reference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-deep-multi-score-model-for-no-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WITT: A Wireless Image Transmission Transformer for Semantic Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/witt-a-wireless-image-transmission</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to redesign the vision Transformer (ViT) as a new backbone to realize semantic image transmission, termed wireless image transmission transformer (WITT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/witt-a-wireless-image-transmission</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive GAN for Semantic Unconditional Head Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-gan-for-semantic-unconditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the task of unconditional head motion generation to animate still human faces in a low-dimensional semantic space. Deviating from talking head generation conditioned on audio that seldom puts emphasis on realistic head motions, we devise a GAN-based architecture that allows obtaining rich head motion sequences while avoiding known caveats associated with GANs. Namely, the autoregressive generation of incremental outputs ensures smooth trajectories, while a multi-scale discriminator on input pairs drives generation toward better handling of high and low frequency signals and less mode collapse. We demonstrate experimentally the relevance of the proposed architecture and compare with models that showed state-of-the-art performances on similar tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-gan-for-semantic-unconditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new method for determining Wasserstein 1 optimal transport maps from Kantorovich potentials, with deep learning applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-method-for-determining-wasserstein-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In general, a Wasserstein 1 optimal transport map is not unique and is not computable from a potential alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-method-for-determining-wasserstein-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Deep Image Compression via Content-Adaptive Optimization with Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-deep-image-compression-via-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This task aims to compress images belonging to arbitrary domains, such as natural images, line drawings, and comics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-deep-image-compression-via-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias-Aware Face Mask Detection Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-aware-face-mask-detection-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel face mask detection dataset that contains images posted on Twitter during the pandemic from around the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-aware-face-mask-detection-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambiguity-Aware Multi-Object Pose Optimization for Visually-Assisted Robot Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguity-aware-multi-object-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tackling these limitations, we present an ambiguity-aware 6D object pose estimation network, PrimA6D++, as a generic uncertainty prediction method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambiguity-aware-multi-object-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADPTriage: Approximate Dynamic Programming for Bug Triage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adptriage-approximate-dynamic-programming-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we develop a Markov decision process (MDP) model for an online bug triage task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adptriage-approximate-dynamic-programming-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exponentially Converging Particle Method for the Mixed Nash Equilibrium of Continuous Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exponentially-converging-particle-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of computing mixed Nash equilibria of two-player zero-sum games with continuous sets of pure strategies and with first-order access to the payoff function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-exponentially-converging-particle-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference and Denoise: Causal Inference-based Neural Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-and-denoise-causal-inference-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study addresses the speech enhancement (SE) task within the causal inference paradigm by modeling the noise presence as an intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-and-denoise-causal-inference-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese CLIP: Contrastive Vision-Language Pretraining in Chinese</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinese-clip-contrastive-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The tremendous success of CLIP (Radford et al., 2021) has promoted the research and application of contrastive learning for vision-language pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinese-clip-contrastive-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing Utility and Fairness in Submodular Maximization (Technical Report)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-utility-and-fairness-in-submodular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, it requires finding a fixed-size solution to maximize the utility function, subject to the value of the fairness function not being below a threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balancing-utility-and-fairness-in-submodular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pop2Piano : Pop Audio-based Piano Cover Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pop2piano-pop-audio-based-piano-cover</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The piano cover of pop music is widely enjoyed by people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pop2piano-pop-audio-based-piano-cover</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Losses Can Be Blessings: Routing Self-Supervised Speech Representations Towards Efficient Multilingual and Multitask Speech Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/losses-can-be-blessings-routing-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe S$^3$-Router has provided a new perspective for practical deployment of speech SSL models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/losses-can-be-blessings-routing-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thunderstorm nowcasting with deep learning: a multi-hazard data fusion model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thunderstorm-nowcasting-with-deep-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this need, we present a deep learning model that can be adapted to different hazard types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thunderstorm-nowcasting-with-deep-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CircleSnake: Instance Segmentation with Circle Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circlesnake-instance-segmentation-with-circle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Circle representation has recently been introduced as a medical imaging optimized representation for more effective instance object detection on ball-shaped medical objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circlesnake-instance-segmentation-with-circle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Benefit of Dual-domain Denoising in a Self-supervised Low-dose CT Setting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-benefit-of-dual-domain-denoising-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present an end-to-end trainable CT reconstruction pipeline that contains denoising operators in both the projection and the image domain and that are optimized simultaneously without requiring ground-truth high-dose CT data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-benefit-of-dual-domain-denoising-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial-temporal recurrent reinforcement learning for autonomous ships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-recurrent-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper proposes a spatial-temporal recurrent neural network architecture for Deep $Q$-Networks to steer an autonomous ship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-temporal-recurrent-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Algebraic Framework for Stock &amp; Flow Diagrams and Dynamical Systems Using Category Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-algebraic-framework-for-stock-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stock & flow diagrams are widely used as broadly accessible building blocks for infectious disease modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-algebraic-framework-for-stock-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Better Out-of-Distribution Generalization of Neural Algorithmic Reasoning Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-out-of-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the OOD generalization of neural algorithmic reasoning tasks, where the goal is to learn an algorithm (e. g., sorting, breadth-first search, and depth-first search) from input-output pairs using deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-better-out-of-distribution</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
