<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 09:12:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FinalMLP: An Enhanced Two-Stream MLP Model for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finalmlp-an-enhanced-two-stream-mlp-model-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While multi-layer perceptron (MLP) serves as a core component in many deep CTR prediction models, it has been widely recognized that applying a vanilla MLP network alone is inefficient in learning multiplicative feature interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finalmlp-an-enhanced-two-stream-mlp-model-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combinatorial Optimization enriched Machine Learning to solve the Dynamic Vehicle Routing Problem with Time Windows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-enriched-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise of e-commerce and increasing customer requirements, logistics service providers face a new complexity in their daily planning, mainly due to efficiently handling same day deliveries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-enriched-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polytuplet Loss: A Reverse Approach to Training Reading Comprehension and Logical Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polytuplet-loss-a-reverse-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper examines the effectiveness of applying such a strategy to train transfer learning models to solve reading comprehension and logical reasoning questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polytuplet-loss-a-reverse-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Features Matter: Enhancing Few-shot CLIP with Adaptive Prior Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-features-matter-enhancing-few-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The popularity of Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP) has propelled its application to diverse downstream vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-features-matter-enhancing-few-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Multiplane Neural Radiance for 3D-Aware Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-multiplane-neural-radiance-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method to efficiently generate 3D-aware high-resolution images that are view-consistent across multiple target views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-multiplane-neural-radiance-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering and Explaining the Non-Causality of Deep Learning in SAR ATR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-and-explaining-the-non-causality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, the causes of the non-causality of deep learning in SAR ATR include data selection bias and model texture bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-and-explaining-the-non-causality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Instance Segmentation in an Open-World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-instance-segmentation-in-an-open-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-world formulation relaxes the close-world static-learning assumption as follows: (a) first, it distinguishes a set of known categories as well as labels an unknown object as `unknown' and then (b) it incrementally learns the class of an unknown as and when the corresponding semantic labels become available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-instance-segmentation-in-an-open-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Semantic Segmentation in the Wild: Learning Generalized Models for Adverse-Condition Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-semantic-segmentation-in-the-wild-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we design a domain randomization technique that alternatively randomizes the geometry styles of point clouds and aggregates their embeddings, ultimately leading to a generalizable model that can improve 3DSS under various adverse weather effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-semantic-segmentation-in-the-wild-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Integration of Discriminability and Robustness for Document-Level Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-integration-of-discriminability-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we introduce two new data regimes to mimic more realistic scenarios with annotation errors and evaluate our sampling strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-integration-of-discriminability-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring and Manipulating Knowledge Representations in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-manipulating-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tools for inspecting and modifying LM fact representations would be useful almost everywhere LMs are used: making it possible to update them when the world changes, to localize and remove sources of bias, and to identify errors in generated text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/measuring-and-manipulating-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Generalization for Crop Segmentation with Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-for-crop-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach provides a promising solution for domain generalization in crop segmentation and has the potential to enhance precision agriculture applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-generalization-for-crop-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HypLiLoc: Towards Effective LiDAR Pose Regression with Hyperbolic Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypliloc-towards-effective-lidar-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR relocalization plays a crucial role in many fields, including robotics, autonomous driving, and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypliloc-towards-effective-lidar-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPTQ: Reorder-based Post-training Quantization for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rptq-reorder-based-post-training-quantization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale language models (LLMs) have demonstrated outstanding performance on various tasks, but their deployment poses challenges due to their enormous model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rptq-reorder-based-post-training-quantization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeakTr: Exploring Plain Vision Transformer for Weakly-supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weaktr-exploring-plain-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus a novel weight-based method is proposed to end-to-end estimate the importance of attention heads, while the self-attention maps are adaptively fused for high-quality CAM results that tend to have more complete objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weaktr-exploring-plain-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinnWoodlands Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finnwoodlands-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides tree trunks, we also annotated "Obstacles" objects as instances as well as the semantic stuff classes "Lake", "Ground", and "Track".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finnwoodlands-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoctorGLM: Fine-tuning your Chinese Doctor is not a Herculean Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doctorglm-fine-tuning-your-chinese-doctor-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent progress of large language models (LLMs), including ChatGPT and GPT-4, in comprehending and responding to human instructions has been remarkable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doctorglm-fine-tuning-your-chinese-doctor-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperThumbnail: Real-time 6K Image Rescaling with Rate-distortion Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperthumbnail-real-time-6k-image-rescaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, an efficient frequency-aware decoder reconstructs a high-fidelity HR image from the LR one in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperthumbnail-real-time-6k-image-rescaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baize: An Open-Source Chat Model with Parameter-Efficient Tuning on Self-Chat Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baize-an-open-source-chat-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chat models, such as ChatGPT, have shown impressive capabilities and have been rapidly adopted across numerous domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baize-an-open-source-chat-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow Your Pose: Pose-Guided Text-to-Video Generation using Pose-Free Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-your-pose-pose-guided-text-to-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating text-editable and pose-controllable character videos have an imperious demand in creating various digital human.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-your-pose-pose-guided-text-to-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeGPR: Deep Guided Posterior Regularization for Multi-Class Cell Detection and Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degpr-deep-guided-posterior-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there exist multiple, general-purpose, deep learning-based object detection and counting methods, they may not readily transfer to detecting and counting cells in medical images, due to the limited data, presence of tiny overlapping objects, multiple cell types, severe class-imbalance, minute differences in size/shape of cells, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/degpr-deep-guided-posterior-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate Speech Targets Detection in Parler using BERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hate-speech-targets-detection-in-parler-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These platforms have become a district for hate speech against diverse targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hate-speech-targets-detection-in-parler-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Context Aggregation in Natural Image Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-context-aggregation-in-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For natural image matting, context information plays a crucial role in estimating alpha mattes especially when it is challenging to distinguish foreground from its background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-context-aggregation-in-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain-of-Thought Predictive Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-thought-predictive-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study generalizable policy learning from demonstrations for complex low-level control tasks (e. g., contact-rich object manipulations).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-thought-predictive-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective and Stable Role-Based Multi-Agent Collaboration by Structural Information Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-stable-role-based-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Role-based learning is a promising approach to improving the performance of Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-stable-role-based-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoLabel: CLIP-based framework for Open-set Video Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autolabel-clip-based-framework-for-open-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-set Unsupervised Video Domain Adaptation (OUVDA) deals with the task of adapting an action recognition model from a labelled source domain to an unlabelled target domain that contains "target-private" categories, which are present in the target but absent in the source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autolabel-clip-based-framework-for-open-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparDL: Distributed Deep Learning Training with Efficient Sparse Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spardl-distributed-deep-learning-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Top-$k$ sparsification has recently been widely used to reduce the communication volume in distributed deep learning; however, due to Gradient Accumulation (GA) dilemma, the performance of top-$k$ sparsification is still limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spardl-distributed-deep-learning-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoxelFormer: Bird's-Eye-View Feature Generation based on Dual-view Attention for Multi-view 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxelformer-bird-s-eye-view-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, transformer-based detectors have demonstrated remarkable performance in 2D visual perception tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxelformer-bird-s-eye-view-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint 2D-3D Multi-Task Learning on Cityscapes-3D: 3D Detection, Segmentation, and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-2d-3d-multi-task-learning-on-cityscapes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TaskPrompter introduces a new multi-task benchmark based on Cityscapes-3D dataset, which requires the multi-task model to concurrently generate predictions for monocular 3D vehicle detection, semantic segmentation, and monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-2d-3d-multi-task-learning-on-cityscapes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FANS: Fast Non-Autoregressive Sequence Generation for Item List Continuation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fans-fast-non-autoregressive-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Item list continuation is proposed to model the overall trend of a list and predict subsequent items.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fans-fast-non-autoregressive-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Pretraining Advances 3D Deep Learning on Chest CT Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-pretraining-advances-3d-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate video pretraining improves the average performance of seven 3D models on two chest CT datasets, regardless of finetuning dataset size, and that video pretraining allows 3D models to outperform 2D baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-pretraining-advances-3d-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LG-BPN: Local and Global Blind-Patch Network for Self-Supervised Real-World Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lg-bpn-local-and-global-blind-patch-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the significant results on synthetic noise under simplified assumptions, most self-supervised denoising methods fail under real noise due to the strong spatial noise correlation, including the advanced self-supervised blind-spot networks (BSNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lg-bpn-local-and-global-blind-patch-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PK-Chat: Pointer Network Guided Knowledge Driven Generative Dialogue Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pk-chat-pointer-network-guided-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the research of end-to-end dialogue systems, using real-world knowledge to generate natural, fluent, and human-like utterances with correct answers is crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pk-chat-pointer-network-guided-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Data-centric Framework for Improving Domain-specific Machine Reading Comprehension Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-centric-framework-for-improving-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We applied the proposed framework to four biomedical datasets and showed relative improvement of up to 33%/40% for fine-tuning of retrieval/reader models on the BioASQ dataset when using back translation to enhance the original dataset quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-centric-framework-for-improving-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Fantasy: Semantic-Aware Virtual Contrastive Constraint for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-fantasy-semantic-aware-virtual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in this work, we find that the CE loss is not ideal for the base session training as it suffers poor class separation in terms of representations, which further degrades generalization to novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-fantasy-semantic-aware-virtual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Multiview Point Cloud Registration with Reliable Pose Graph Initialization and History Reweighting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multiview-point-cloud-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous multiview registration methods rely on exhaustive pairwise registration to construct a densely-connected pose graph and apply Iteratively Reweighted Least Square (IRLS) on the pose graph to compute the scan poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-multiview-point-cloud-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedFTN: Personalized Federated Learning with Deep Feature Transformation Network for Multi-institutional Low-count PET Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedftn-personalized-federated-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous federated learning (FL) algorithms enable multi-institution collaborative training without the need of aggregating local data, addressing the large domain shift in the application of multi-institutional low-count PET denoising remains a challenge and is still highly under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedftn-personalized-federated-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Optimal Recovery of Graph Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-optimal-recovery-of-graph-signals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning a smooth graph signal from partially observed data is a well-studied task in graph-based machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-optimal-recovery-of-graph-signals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DropMAE: Masked Autoencoders with Spatial-Attention Dropout for Tracking Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropmae-masked-autoencoders-with-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we find that this simple baseline heavily relies on spatial cues while ignoring temporal relations for frame reconstruction, thus leading to sub-optimal temporal matching representations for VOT and VOS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropmae-masked-autoencoders-with-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PrefGen: Preference Guided Image Generation with Relative Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefgen-preference-guided-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using information from a sequence of query responses, we can estimate user preferences over a set of image attributes and perform preference-guided image editing and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prefgen-preference-guided-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Transformers with Mixed-Resolution Tokenization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-transformers-with-mixed-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we apply this approach to Vision Transformers by introducing a novel image tokenization scheme, replacing the standard uniform grid with a mixed-resolution sequence of tokens, where each token represents a patch of arbitrary size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-transformers-with-mixed-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Tensor Graph Neural Networks Through Reinforced Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-tensor-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, RTGNN first uses tensor decomposition to extract the graph structure features (GSFs) of each view in the common feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-tensor-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLT-T++: Global-Local Transformer for 3D Siamese Tracking with Ranking Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glt-t-global-local-transformer-for-3d-siamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incorporating this transformer-based voting scheme into 3D RPN, a novel Siamese method dubbed GLT-T is developed for 3D single object tracking on point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glt-t-global-local-transformer-for-3d-siamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applications of No-Collision Transportation Maps in Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applications-of-no-collision-transportation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate applications of no-collision transportation maps introduced in [Nurbekyan et.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/applications-of-no-collision-transportation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large language models can rate news outlet credibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-rate-news-outlet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although large language models (LLMs) have shown exceptional performance in various natural language processing tasks, they are prone to hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-can-rate-news-outlet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic High Resolution Wire Segmentation and Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-high-resolution-wire-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an automatic wire clean-up system that eases the process of wire segmentation and removal/inpainting to within a few seconds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-high-resolution-wire-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-scale Multi-instance Learning for Pathological Image Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-scale-multi-instance-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analyzing high resolution whole slide images (WSIs) with regard to information across multiple scales poses a significant challenge in digital pathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-scale-multi-instance-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to Hero: Convincing with Extremely Complicated Math</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-to-hero-convincing-with-extremely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, they end up as a researcher, writing boring, non-impressive papers all day long because they only rely on simple mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-zero-to-hero-convincing-with-extremely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Context Distribution Shift in Task Representation Learning for Offline Meta RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-context-distribution-shift-in-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we consider context-based OMRL, in particular, the issue of task representation learning for OMRL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-context-distribution-shift-in-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reusing Deep Neural Network Models through Model Re-engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reusing-deep-neural-network-models-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior approaches to DNN model reuse have two main limitations: 1) reusing the entire model, while only a small part of the model's functionalities (labels) are required, would cause much overhead (e. g., computational and time costs for inference), and 2) model reuse would inherit the defects and weaknesses of the reused model, and hence put the new system under threats of security attack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reusing-deep-neural-network-models-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Cold-start in The Serverless Cloud with Temporal Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/managing-cold-start-in-the-serverless-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A big threat to the serverless cloud's performance is cold-start, which is when the time of provisioning the needed cloud resource to serve customers' requests incurs unacceptable costs to the service providers and/or the customers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/managing-cold-start-in-the-serverless-cloud</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
