<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 09:13:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>\emph{MEnsA}: Mix-up Ensemble Average for Unsupervised Multi Target Domain Adaptation on 3D Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emph-mensa-mix-up-ensemble-average-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) addresses the problem of distribution shift between the unlabeled target domain and labelled source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emph-mensa-mix-up-ensemble-average-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCANet: Dual Convolutional Neural Network with Attention for Image Blind Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcanet-dual-convolutional-neural-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new dual convolutional neural network (CNN) with attention for image blind denoising, named as the DCANet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcanet-dual-convolutional-neural-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Blind Denoising Using Dual Convolutional Neural Network with Skip Connection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-blind-denoising-using-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed DCBDNet consists of a noise estimation network and a dual convolutional neural network (CNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-blind-denoising-using-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Level Contrastive Learning for Dense Prediction Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-contrastive-learning-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend our pretext task to supervised pre-training, which achieves a similar performance to self-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-contrastive-learning-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap between Model Explanations in Partially Annotated Multi-label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-model-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these findings, we propose to boost the attribution scores of the model trained with partial labels to make its explanation resemble that of the model trained with full labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-model-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGClass: Text Classification with Extremely Weak Supervision via Mutually-Enhancing Text Granularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megclass-text-classification-with-extremely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, MEGClass constructs class-oriented sentence and class representations based on keywords for performing a sentence-level confidence-weighted label ensemble in order to estimate a document's initial class distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megclass-text-classification-with-extremely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Convolutional Networks for Dense Water Flow Intensity Prediction in Swedish Catchment Areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-convolutional-networks-for-dense-water</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, we are the first to tackle the task of dense water flow intensity prediction; earlier works have considered predicting flow intensities at a sparse set of locations at a time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-convolutional-networks-for-dense-water</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Outlier Rejection for 3D Registration with Variational Bayes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-outlier-rejection-for-3d-registration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Embedded with the inlier/outlier label, the posterior feature distribution is label-dependent and discriminative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-outlier-rejection-for-3d-registration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form-NLU: Dataset for the Form Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/form-nlu-dataset-for-the-form-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to general document analysis tasks, form document structure understanding and retrieval are challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/form-nlu-dataset-for-the-form-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Degeneration Meets Label Evolution: Learning Infrared Small Target Detection with Single Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-degeneration-meets-label-evolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, during the training phase supervised by point labels, we discover that CNNs first learn to segment a cluster of pixels near the targets, and then gradually converge to predict groundtruth point labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-degeneration-meets-label-evolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modulated Few-shot Image Generation for Colorectal Tissue Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modulated-few-shot-image-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a few-shot colorectal tissue image generation method for addressing the scarcity of histopathological training data for rare cancer tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modulated-few-shot-image-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Supervision and Shuffle Data Augmentation for 3D Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-supervision-and-shuffle-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art 3D object detectors are usually trained on large-scale datasets with high-quality 3D annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-supervision-and-shuffle-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A differentiable programming framework for spin models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-differentiable-programming-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spin systems are a powerful tool for modeling a wide range of physical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-differentiable-programming-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against Patch-based Backdoor Attacks on Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-patch-based-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It was shown that an adversary can poison a small part of the unlabeled data so that when a victim trains an SSL model on it, the final model will have a backdoor that the adversary can exploit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-patch-based-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrhythmia Classifier Based on Ultra-Lightweight Binary Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arrhythmia-classifier-based-on-ultra</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of deep learning, numerous ECG classification algorithms based on deep learning have emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arrhythmia-classifier-based-on-ultra</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Aware Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aware-neural-architecture-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in the case of resource constrained Machine Learning, one single metric is not enough to evaluate a NN architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aware-neural-architecture-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Framework for Unsupervised Structure Preservation Medical Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-framework-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a framework for practical unsupervised medical image enhancement that includes (1) a non-reference objective evaluation of structure preservation for medical image enhancement tasks called Laplacian structural similarity index measure (LaSSIM), which is based on SSIM and the Laplacian pyramid, and (2) a novel unsupervised GAN-based method called Laplacian medical image enhancement (LaMEGAN) to support the improvement of both originality and quality from LQ images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-framework-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Adapters: An Adapter Family for Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-adapters-an-adapter-family-for-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable further research on PEFT methods of LLMs, this paper presents LLM-Adapters, an easy-to-use framework that integrates various adapters into LLMs and can execute these adapter-based PEFT methods of LLMs for different tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-adapters-an-adapter-family-for-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-BSN: Self-Supervised Image Denoising for Real-World with Multi-Mask based on Blind-Spot Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bsn-self-supervised-image-denoising-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our MM-BSN can be used to address the problem of large-noise denoising, which cannot be efficiently handled by other BSN methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bsn-self-supervised-image-denoising-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Avatar Stream: a cost-down approach to the Metaverse experience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-avatar-stream-a-cost-down-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Metaverse through VR headsets is a rapidly growing concept, but the high cost of entry currently limits access for many users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-avatar-stream-a-cost-down-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Comprehension: Language Models with Compiled Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-comprehension-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models have achieved impressive results in natural language processing tasks, but their ability to perform symbolic operations and arithmetic operations, remains limited, which attribute to their learn the rules implicitly from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-comprehension-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FakET: Simulating Cryo-Electron Tomograms with Neural Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faket-simulating-cryo-electron-tomograms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key shortcoming of these supervised learning methods is their need for large training data sets, typically generated from particle models in conjunction with complex numerical forward models simulating the physics of transmission electron microscopes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faket-simulating-cryo-electron-tomograms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Vision-Language Models for Imbalanced Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-vision-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, their performance on imbalanced dataset is relatively poor, where the distribution of classes in the training dataset is skewed, leading to poor performance in predicting minority classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-vision-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneShotSTL: One-Shot Seasonal-Trend Decomposition For Online Time Series Anomaly Detection And Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneshotstl-one-shot-seasonal-trend</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on real-world benchmark datasets for downstream time series anomaly detection and forecasting tasks demonstrate that OneShotSTL is from 10 to over 1, 000 times faster than the state-of-the-art methods, while still providing comparable or even better accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneshotstl-one-shot-seasonal-trend</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Improvement of Factual Knowledge in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-improvement-of-factual-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an approach for influencing MLM pretraining in a way that can improve language model performance on a variety of knowledge-intensive tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-improvement-of-factual-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned Tree Search for Long-Horizon Social Robot Navigation in Shared Airspace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-tree-search-for-long-horizon-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Social Robot Tree Search (SoRTS), an algorithm for the safe navigation of mobile robots in social domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-tree-search-for-long-horizon-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources and Few-shot Learners for In-context Learning in Slavic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resources-and-few-shot-learners-for-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid recent progress in creating accurate and compact in-context learners, most recent work focuses on in-context learning (ICL) for tasks in English.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resources-and-few-shot-learners-for-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GlueStick: Robust Image Matching by Sticking Points and Lines Together</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gluestick-robust-image-matching-by-sticking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Line segments are powerful features complementary to points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gluestick-robust-image-matching-by-sticking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-space-frequency feature Fusion for 3-channel motor imagery classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-space-frequency-feature-fusion-for-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TSFF-Net comprises four main components: time-frequency representation, time-frequency feature extraction, time-space feature extraction, and feature fusion and classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-space-frequency-feature-fusion-for-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AToMiC: An Image/Text Retrieval Test Collection to Support Multimedia Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-an-image-text-retrieval-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the AToMiC (Authoring Tools for Multimedia Content) dataset, designed to advance research in image/text cross-modal retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-an-image-text-retrieval-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EGC: Image Generation and Classification via a Single Energy-Based Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egc-image-generation-and-classification-via-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning image classification and image generation using the same set of network parameters is a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egc-image-generation-and-classification-via-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploration of Lightweight Single Image Denoising with Transformers and Truly Fair Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-lightweight-single-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As multimedia content often contains noise from intrinsic defects of digital devices, image denoising is an important step for high-level vision recognition tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-lightweight-single-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning with a Geometry-Adaptive Preconditioner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-a-geometry-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose Geometry-Adaptive Preconditioned gradient descent (GAP) that can overcome the limitations in MAML; GAP can efficiently meta-learn a preconditioner that is dependent on task-specific parameters, and its preconditioner can be shown to be a Riemannian metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-a-geometry-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VNE: An Effective Method for Improving Deep Representation by Manipulating Eigenvalue Distribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vne-an-effective-method-for-improving-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the introduction of deep learning, a wide scope of representation properties, such as decorrelation, whitening, disentanglement, rank, isotropy, and mutual information, have been studied to improve the quality of representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vne-an-effective-method-for-improving-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Learning on Graphs: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-learning-on-graphs-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the development of this promising direction, in this survey, we categorize and comprehensively review papers on graph counterfactual learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-learning-on-graphs-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thermal Spread Functions (TSF): Physics-guided Material Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-spread-functions-tsf-physics-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key observation is that the rate of heating and cooling of an object depends on the unique intrinsic properties of the material, namely the emissivity and diffusivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thermal-spread-functions-tsf-physics-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Guide for Practical Use of ADMG Causal Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-guide-for-practical-use-of-admg-causal-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation is essential when applying Machine Learning in small-data regimes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-guide-for-practical-use-of-admg-causal-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering and Explaining the Non-Causality of Deep Learning in SAR ATR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-and-explaining-the-non-causality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, the causes of the non-causality of deep learning in SAR ATR include data selection bias and model texture bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-and-explaining-the-non-causality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Instance Segmentation in an Open-World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-instance-segmentation-in-an-open-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-world formulation relaxes the close-world static-learning assumption as follows: (a) first, it distinguishes a set of known categories as well as labels an unknown object as `unknown' and then (b) it incrementally learns the class of an unknown as and when the corresponding semantic labels become available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-instance-segmentation-in-an-open-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective and Stable Role-Based Multi-Agent Collaboration by Structural Information Principles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-stable-role-based-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Role-based learning is a promising approach to improving the performance of Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-and-stable-role-based-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScandEval: A Benchmark for Scandinavian Natural Language Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scandeval-a-benchmark-for-scandinavian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a Scandinavian benchmarking platform, ScandEval, which can benchmark any pretrained model on four different tasks in the Scandinavian languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scandeval-a-benchmark-for-scandinavian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparDL: Distributed Deep Learning Training with Efficient Sparse Communication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spardl-distributed-deep-learning-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Top-$k$ sparsification has recently been widely used to reduce the communication volume in distributed deep learning; however, due to Gradient Accumulation (GA) dilemma, the performance of top-$k$ sparsification is still limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spardl-distributed-deep-learning-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinnWoodlands Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finnwoodlands-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides tree trunks, we also annotated "Obstacles" objects as instances as well as the semantic stuff classes "Lake", "Ground", and "Track".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finnwoodlands-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combinatorial Optimization enriched Machine Learning to solve the Dynamic Vehicle Routing Problem with Time Windows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-enriched-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise of e-commerce and increasing customer requirements, logistics service providers face a new complexity in their daily planning, mainly due to efficiently handling same day deliveries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinatorial-optimization-enriched-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HypLiLoc: Towards Effective LiDAR Pose Regression with Hyperbolic Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypliloc-towards-effective-lidar-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR relocalization plays a crucial role in many fields, including robotics, autonomous driving, and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypliloc-towards-effective-lidar-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Fine-tuning is All You Need for Source-free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-fine-tuning-is-all-you-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These limitations include a lack of principled ways to determine optimal hyperparameters and performance degradation when the unlabeled target data fail to meet certain requirements such as a closed-set and identical label distribution to the source data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-fine-tuning-is-all-you-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperThumbnail: Real-time 6K Image Rescaling with Rate-distortion Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperthumbnail-real-time-6k-image-rescaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, an efficient frequency-aware decoder reconstructs a high-fidelity HR image from the LR one in real time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperthumbnail-real-time-6k-image-rescaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeakTr: Exploring Plain Vision Transformer for Weakly-supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weaktr-exploring-plain-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus a novel weight-based method is proposed to end-to-end estimate the importance of attention heads, while the self-attention maps are adaptively fused for high-quality CAM results that tend to have more complete objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weaktr-exploring-plain-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint 2D-3D Multi-Task Learning on Cityscapes-3D: 3D Detection, Segmentation, and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-2d-3d-multi-task-learning-on-cityscapes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TaskPrompter introduces a new multi-task benchmark based on Cityscapes-3D dataset, which requires the multi-task model to concurrently generate predictions for monocular 3D vehicle detection, semantic segmentation, and monocular depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-2d-3d-multi-task-learning-on-cityscapes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-building Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-building-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare our proposed SBNN with traditional neural networks (NNs) over three classical control tasks from OpenAI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-building-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
