<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 09:11:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Attack Prompt Generation for Red Teaming and Defending Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attack-prompt-generation-for-red-teaming-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a defense framework that fine-tunes victim LLMs through iterative interactions with the attack framework to enhance their safety against red teaming attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attack-prompt-generation-for-red-teaming-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-World Lifelong Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-lifelong-graph-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of lifelong graph learning in an open-world scenario, where a model needs to deal with new tasks and potentially unknown classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-world-lifelong-graph-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quasi Manhattan Wasserstein Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quasi-manhattan-wasserstein-distance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Quasi Manhattan Wasserstein Distance (QMWD) is a metric designed to quantify the dissimilarity between two matrices by combining elements of the Wasserstein Distance with specific transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quasi-manhattan-wasserstein-distance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pretraining Language Models with Text-Attributed Heterogeneous Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-language-models-with-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many real-world scenarios (e. g., academic networks, social platforms), different types of entities are not only associated with texts but also connected by various relationships, which can be abstracted as Text-Attributed Heterogeneous Graphs (TAHGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pretraining-language-models-with-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting the Object Back into Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-the-object-back-into-video-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The object queries act as a high-level summary of the target object, while high-resolution feature maps are retained for accurate segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-the-object-back-into-video-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Similarity-Based Hierarchical Bayesian Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-similarity-based-hierarchical-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Common approaches for learning supervised models with heterogeneous datasets include learning a global model for the entire dataset, learning local models for each tasks' data, or utilising hierarchical, meta-learning and multi-task learning approaches to learn how to generalise from data pooled across multiple tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-similarity-based-hierarchical-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemantIC: Semantic Interference Cancellation Towards 6G Wireless Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-semantic-interference-cancellation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This letter proposes a novel anti-interference technique, semantic interference cancellation (SemantIC), for enhancing information quality towards the sixth-generation (6G) wireless networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-semantic-interference-cancellation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not Just Learning from Others but Relying on Yourself: A New Perspective on Few-Shot Segmentation in Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-just-learning-from-others-but-relying-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to prevent the co-existence of multiple classes in remote sensing scenes from exacerbating the collapse of FSS generalization, we also propose a new Known-class Meta Suppressor (KMS) module to suppress the activation of known-class objects in the sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-just-learning-from-others-but-relying-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-Aware Representation Learning for Time-Sensitive Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-aware-representation-learning-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model is trained to extract the answer span from the sentence that is both correct in time and context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-aware-representation-learning-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Locality and Symmetry of Positional Encodings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-locality-and-symmetry-of-positional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Positional Encodings (PEs) are used to inject word-order information into transformer-based language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-locality-and-symmetry-of-positional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing High-Resolution 3D Generation through Pixel-wise Gradient Clipping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-high-resolution-3d-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this framework, a significant challenge arises: To compute gradients for individual image pixels, it is necessary to backpropagate gradients from the designated latent space through the frozen components of the image model, such as the VAE encoder used within LDM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-high-resolution-3d-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Structural Concepts Universal in Transformer Language Models? Towards Interpretable Cross-Lingual Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-structural-concepts-universal-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose a meta-learning-based method to learn to align conceptual spaces of different languages, which facilitates zero-shot and few-shot generalization in concept classification and also offers insights into the cross-lingual in-context learning phenomenon.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-structural-concepts-universal-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DA-TransUNet: Integrating Spatial and Channel Dual Attention with Transformer U-Net for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-transunet-integrating-spatial-and-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a novel deep medical image segmentation framework, called DA-TransUNet, aiming to introduce the Transformer and dual attention block into the encoder and decoder of the traditional U-shaped architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/da-transunet-integrating-spatial-and-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frozen Transformers in Language Models Are Effective Visual Encoder Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frozen-transformers-in-language-models-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reveals that large language models (LLMs), despite being trained solely on textual data, are surprisingly strong encoders for purely visual tasks in the absence of language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frozen-transformers-in-language-models-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discretize Relaxed Solution of Spectral Clustering via a Non-Heuristic Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discretize-relaxed-solution-of-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, the goal of the existing methods is not to find a discrete solution that minimizes the original objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discretize-relaxed-solution-of-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Attribute Value Extraction using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/product-attribute-value-extraction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[E-commerce applications such as faceted product search or product comparison are based on structured product descriptions like attribute/value pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/product-attribute-value-extraction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Ovarian Cancer Treatment Response in Histopathology using Hierarchical Vision Transformers and Multiple Instance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-ovarian-cancer-treatment-response</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For some therapies, it is not possible to predict patients' responses, potentially exposing them to the adverse effects of treatment without any therapeutic benefit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-ovarian-cancer-treatment-response</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinEntity: Entity-level Sentiment Classification for Financial Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finentity-entity-level-sentiment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce an entity-level sentiment classification dataset, called \textbf{FinEntity}, that annotates financial entity spans and their sentiment (positive, neutral, and negative) in financial news.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finentity-entity-level-sentiment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe RLHF: Safe Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-rlhf-safe-reinforcement-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the inherent tension between the objectives of helpfulness and harmlessness presents a significant challenge during LLM training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-rlhf-safe-reinforcement-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Streaming Speech Translation for Code-Switched Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-streaming-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code-switching (CS), i. e. mixing different languages in a single sentence, is a common phenomenon in communication and can be challenging in many Natural Language Processing (NLP) settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-streaming-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Robust Adversarial Examples against Online Social Networks (OSNs)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-robust-adversarial-examples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim to design a new framework for generating robust AEs that can survive the OSN transmission; namely, the AEs before and after the OSN transmission both possess strong attack capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-robust-adversarial-examples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoMix: Automatically Mixing Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automix-automatically-mixing-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are now available in various sizes and configurations from cloud API providers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automix-automatically-mixing-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Improved Metarounding Algorithm via Frank-Wolfe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-improved-metarounding-algorithm-via-frank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Metarounding is an approach to convert an approximation algorithm for linear optimization over some combinatorial classes to an online linear optimization algorithm for the same class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-improved-metarounding-algorithm-via-frank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExtSwap: Leveraging Extended Latent Mapper for Generating High Quality Face Swapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extswap-leveraging-extended-latent-mapper-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel face swapping method using the progressively growing structure of a pre-trained StyleGAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extswap-leveraging-extended-latent-mapper-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Representational Capacity of Recurrent Neural Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-representational-capacity-of-recurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend the Turing completeness result to the probabilistic case, showing how a rationally weighted RLM with unbounded computation time can simulate any probabilistic Turing machine (PTM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-representational-capacity-of-recurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a student becomes a teacher: learning and forgetting through Spectral methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-a-student-becomes-a-teacher-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In theoretical ML, the teacher-student paradigm is often employed as an effective metaphor for real-life tuition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-a-student-becomes-a-teacher-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recoverable Privacy-Preserving Image Classification through Noise-like Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recoverable-privacy-preserving-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that 1) the classification accuracy of the classifier trained in the plaintext domain remains the same in both the ciphertext and plaintext domains; 2) the encrypted images can be recovered into their original form with an average PSNR of up to 51+ dB for the SVHN dataset and 48+ dB for the VGGFace2 dataset; 3) our system exhibits satisfactory generalization capability on the encryption, decryption and classification tasks across datasets that are different from the training one; and 4) a high-level of security is achieved against three potential threat models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recoverable-privacy-preserving-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Object Localization in the Era of Self-Supervised ViTs: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-object-localization-in-the-era</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose here a survey of unsupervised object localization methods that discover objects in images without requiring any manual annotation in the era of self-supervised ViTs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-object-localization-in-the-era</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Foundation Model Transparency Index</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-foundation-model-transparency-index</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We score 10 major foundation model developers (e. g. OpenAI, Google, Meta) against the 100 indicators to assess their transparency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-foundation-model-transparency-index</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Vertex Fitting for Jet Flavour Tagging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-vertex-fitting-for-jet-flavour</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a differentiable vertex fitting algorithm that can be used for secondary vertex fitting, and that can be seamlessly integrated into neural networks for jet flavour tagging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-vertex-fitting-for-jet-flavour</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representing and Computing Uncertainty in Phonological Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-and-computing-uncertainty-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the inherently fuzzy nature of reconstructions in historical linguistics, most scholars do not represent their uncertainty when proposing proto-forms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-and-computing-uncertainty-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating collective counterfactual explanations in score-based classification via mathematical optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-collective-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By means of novel Mathematical Optimization models, we provide a counterfactual explanation for each instance in a group of interest, so that the total cost of the perturbations is minimized under some linking constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-collective-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCSI -- An improved measure of cluster separability based on separation and connectedness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcsi-an-improved-measure-of-cluster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detailed evaluation on frequently used real-world data sets shows that DCSI can correctly identify touching or overlapping classes that do not form meaningful clusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcsi-an-improved-measure-of-cluster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Autoregressive Sentence Ordering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-sentence-ordering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing sentence ordering approaches generally employ encoder-decoder frameworks with the pointer net to recover the coherence by recurrently predicting each sentence step-by-step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-autoregressive-sentence-ordering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixing Histopathology Prototypes into Robust Slide-Level Representations for Cancer Subtyping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixing-histopathology-prototypes-into-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whole-slide image analysis via the means of computational pathology often relies on processing tessellated gigapixel images with only slide-level labels available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixing-histopathology-prototypes-into-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MolCA: Molecular Graph-Language Modeling with Cross-Modal Projector and Uni-Modal Adapter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molca-molecular-graph-language-modeling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MolCA enables an LM (e. g., Galactica) to understand both text- and graph-based molecular contents via the cross-modal projector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molca-molecular-graph-language-modeling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cousins Of The Vendi Score: A Family Of Similarity-Based Diversity Metrics For Science And Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cousins-of-the-vendi-score-a-family-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrary to many diversity metrics in ecology, the Vendi Score accounts for similarity and does not require knowledge of the prevalence of the categories in the collection to be evaluated for diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cousins-of-the-vendi-score-a-family-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representation Learning via Consistent Assignment of Views over Random Partitions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-via-consistent-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extensively ablate our method and demonstrate that our proposed random partition pretext task improves the quality of the learned representations by devising multiple random classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representation-learning-via-consistent-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co$^2$PT: Mitigating Bias in Pre-trained Language Models through Counterfactual Contrastive Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-2-pt-mitigating-bias-in-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained Language Models are widely used in many important real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-2-pt-mitigating-bias-in-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocXChain: A Powerful Open-Source Toolchain for Document Parsing and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docxchain-a-powerful-open-source-toolchain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we introduce DocXChain, a powerful open-source toolchain for document parsing, which is designed and developed to automatically convert the rich information embodied in unstructured documents, such as text, tables and charts, into structured representations that are readable and manipulable by machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docxchain-a-powerful-open-source-toolchain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning for Inference in Dialogue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-inference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference, especially those derived from inductive processes, is a crucial component in our conversation to complement the information implicitly or explicitly conveyed by a speaker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-inference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual estimation of political-party positioning: From label aggregation to long-input Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-estimation-of-political-party</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We carry out the analysis of the Comparative Manifestos Project dataset across 41 countries and 27 languages and find that the task can be efficiently solved by state-of-the-art models, with label aggregation producing the best results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-estimation-of-political-party</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAC Prediction Sets Under Label Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pac-prediction-sets-under-label-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel algorithm for constructing prediction sets with PAC guarantees in the label shift setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pac-prediction-sets-under-label-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lidar Panoptic Segmentation and Tracking without Bells and Whistles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-panoptic-segmentation-and-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our network is modular by design and optimized for all aspects of both the panoptic segmentation and tracking task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-panoptic-segmentation-and-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICU: Conquering Language Barriers in Vision-and-Language Modeling by Dividing the Tasks into Image Captioning and Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icu-conquering-language-barriers-in-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most multilingual vision-and-language (V&L) research aims to accomplish multilingual and multimodal capabilities within one model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icu-conquering-language-barriers-in-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Motion Prediction via Heterogeneous Polyline Transformer with Relative Pose Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-motion-prediction-via-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The real-world deployment of an autonomous driving system requires its components to run on-board and in real-time, including the motion prediction module that predicts the future trajectories of surrounding traffic participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-motion-prediction-via-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing the Consistency of Performance Scores Reported for Binary Classification Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-the-consistency-of-performance-scores</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce numerical techniques to assess the consistency of reported performance scores and the assumed experimental setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/testing-the-consistency-of-performance-scores</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SalUn: Empowering Machine Unlearning via Gradient-based Weight Saliency in Both Image Classification and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salun-empowering-machine-unlearning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resultant method that we call saliency unlearning (SalUn) narrows the performance gap with 'exact' unlearning (model retraining from scratch after removing the forgetting dataset).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salun-empowering-machine-unlearning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt Injection Attacks and Defenses in LLM-Integrated Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-injection-attacks-and-defenses-in-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a result, the literature lacks a systematic understanding of prompt injection attacks and their defenses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-injection-attacks-and-defenses-in-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival of the Most Influential Prompts: Efficient Black-Box Prompt Search via Clustering and Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-of-the-most-influential-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt-based learning has been an effective paradigm for large pretrained language models (LLM), enabling few-shot or even zero-shot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/survival-of-the-most-influential-prompts</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
