<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Light Coreference Resolution for Russian with Hierarchical Discourse Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-coreference-resolution-for-russian-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our best model employing rhetorical distance between mentions has ranked 1st on the development set (74. 6% F1) and 2nd on the test set (73. 3% F1) of the Shared Task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-coreference-resolution-for-russian-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Objective Population Based Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-population-based-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Population Based Training (PBT) is an efficient hyperparameter optimization algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-objective-population-based-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Partially Annotated Data: Example-aware Creation of Gap-filling Exercises for Language Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-partially-annotated-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since performing exercises (including, e. g., practice tests) forms a crucial component of learning, and creating such exercises requires non-trivial effort from the teacher.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-partially-annotated-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAIA Search: Hugging Face and Pyserini Interoperability for NLP Training Data Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaia-search-hugging-face-and-pyserini</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss how Pyserini - a widely used toolkit for reproducible IR research can be integrated with the Hugging Face ecosystem of open-source AI libraries and artifacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaia-search-hugging-face-and-pyserini</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture Proportion Estimation Beyond Irreducibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-proportion-estimation-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of mixture proportion estimation (MPE) is to estimate the weight of a component distribution in a mixture, given observations from both the component and mixture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-proportion-estimation-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-View Geometry Scoring Without Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-view-geometry-scoring-without-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a remedy, we propose the Fundamental Scoring Network (FSNet), which infers a score for a pair of overlapping images and any proposed fundamental matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-view-geometry-scoring-without-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoCoOp: Few-Shot Out-of-Distribution Detection via Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locoop-few-shot-out-of-distribution-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CLIP's local features have a lot of ID-irrelevant nuisances (e. g., backgrounds), and by learning to push them away from the ID class text embeddings, we can remove the nuisances in the ID class text embeddings and enhance the separation between ID and OOD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locoop-few-shot-out-of-distribution-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Importance of Frequency versus Compositionality for Subword-based Tokenization in NMT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-importance-of-frequency-versus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subword tokenization is the de facto standard for tokenization in neural language models and machine translation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-importance-of-frequency-versus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at the Adversarial Robustness of Deep Equilibrium Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-adversarial-robustness-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep equilibrium models (DEQs) refrain from the traditional layer-stacking paradigm and turn to find the fixed point of a single layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-the-adversarial-robustness-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Efficient Language-Specific Models for Cross-Lingual Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-efficient-language-specific-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we use a two-phase distillation approach, termed BiStil: (i) the first phase distils a general bilingual model from the MMT, while (ii) the second, task-specific phase sparsely fine-tunes the bilingual "student" model using a task-tuned variant of the original MMT as its "teacher".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-efficient-language-specific-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Style Transfer Back-Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-style-transfer-back-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose Text Style Transfer Back Translation (TST BT), which uses a style transfer model to modify the source side of BT data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-style-transfer-back-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Popularity Bias in Recommender Systems through AUC-Optimal Negative Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-popularity-bias-in-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To achieve this win-win situation, we propose to intervene in model training through negative sampling thereby modifying model predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-popularity-bias-in-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-concept-bottleneck-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To provide a reliable interpretation against this ambiguity, we propose Probabilistic Concept Bottleneck Models (ProbCBM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-concept-bottleneck-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything in High Quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-in-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HQ-SAM is only trained on the introduced detaset of 44k masks, which takes only 4 hours on 8 GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-in-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MutateNN: Mutation Testing of Image Recognition Models Deployed on Hardware Accelerators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutatenn-mutation-testing-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the research advancement of Artificial Intelligence in the last years, there are new opportunities to mitigate real-world problems and advance technologically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutatenn-mutation-testing-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HomE: Homography-Equivariant Video Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/home-homography-equivariant-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel method for representation learning of multi-view videos, where we explicitly model the representation space to maintain Homography Equivariance (HomE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/home-homography-equivariant-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Source-free Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation via Importance-aware and Prototype-contrast Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-source-free-domain-adaptive-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It utilizes a well-trained source model and unlabeled target data to achieve adaptation in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-source-free-domain-adaptive-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameters in Reinforcement Learning and How To Tune Them</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameters-in-reinforcement-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to improve reproducibility, deep reinforcement learning (RL) has been adopting better scientific practices such as standardized evaluation metrics and reporting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameters-in-reinforcement-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Conditional Normalizing Flow for Accelerated Multi-Coil MR Imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-conditional-normalizing-flow-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accelerated magnetic resonance (MR) imaging attempts to reduce acquisition time by collecting data below the Nyquist rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-conditional-normalizing-flow-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BabySLM: language-acquisition-friendly benchmark of self-supervised spoken language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/babyslm-language-acquisition-friendly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised techniques for learning speech representations have been shown to develop linguistic competence from exposure to speech without the need for human labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/babyslm-language-acquisition-friendly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Adversarial Robustness of DEQs with Explicit Regulations Along the Neural Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adversarial-robustness-of-deqs-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we interpret DEQs through the lens of neural dynamics and find that AT under-regulates intermediate states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-adversarial-robustness-of-deqs-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THiFLY Research at SemEval-2023 Task 7: A Multi-granularity System for CTR-based Textual Entailment and Evidence Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thifly-research-at-semeval-2023-task-7-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The NLI4CT task aims to entail hypotheses based on Clinical Trial Reports (CTRs) and retrieve the corresponding evidence supporting the justification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thifly-research-at-semeval-2023-task-7-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NNMobile-Net: Rethinking CNN Design for Deep Learning-Based Retinopathy Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnmobile-net-rethinking-cnn-design-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we argue that a channel-aware and well-calibrated CNN model may overcome these problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnmobile-net-rethinking-cnn-design-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Feature Reuse Framework with Texture-adaptive Aggregation for Reference-based Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-reuse-framework-with-texture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a feature reuse framework that guides the step-by-step texture reconstruction process through different stages, reducing the negative impacts of perceptual and adversarial loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-reuse-framework-with-texture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Multi-step Reasoning from Arithmetic Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-step-reasoning-from-arithmetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematical reasoning is regarded as a necessary ability for Language Models (LMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-multi-step-reasoning-from-arithmetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing CLIP with CLIP: Exploring Pseudolabeling for Limited-Label Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-clip-with-clip-exploring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that (1) unexplored prompt tuning strategies that iteratively refine pseudolabels consistently improve CLIP accuracy, by 19. 5 points in semi-supervised learning, by 28. 4 points in transductive zero-shot learning, and by 15. 2 points in unsupervised learning, and (2) unlike conventional semi-supervised pseudolabeling, which exacerbates model biases toward classes with higher-quality pseudolabels, prompt tuning leads to a more equitable distribution of per-class accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-clip-with-clip-exploring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group channel pruning and spatial attention distilling for object detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-channel-pruning-and-spatial-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, for the object detection network we introduce a three-stage model compression method: dynamic sparse training, group channel pruning, and spatial attention distilling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-channel-pruning-and-spatial-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepScribe: Localization and Classification of Elamite Cuneiform Signs Via Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepscribe-localization-and-classification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The end-to-end pipeline achieves a top-5 classification accuracy of 0. 80.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepscribe-localization-and-classification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Multi-Sequence Stochastic Approximation with Local Hypergradient Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-multi-sequence-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic approximation with multiple coupled sequences (MSA) has found broad applications in machine learning as it encompasses a rich class of problems including bilevel optimization (BLO), multi-level compositional optimization (MCO), and reinforcement learning (specifically, actor-critic methods).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-multi-sequence-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resolving Interference When Merging Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-interference-when-merging-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose our method, TrIm, Elect Sign & Merge (TIES-Merging), which introduces three novel steps when merging models: (1) resetting parameters that only changed a small amount during fine-tuning, (2) resolving sign conflicts, and (3) merging only the parameters that are in alignment with the final agreed-upon sign.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resolving-interference-when-merging-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Differential Recurrent Neural Network with Adaptive Time Steps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-differential-recurrent-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an RNN-based model, called RNN-ODE-Adap, that uses a neural ODE to represent the time development of the hidden states, and we adaptively select time steps based on the steepness of changes of the data over time so as to train the model more efficiently for the "spike-like" time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-differential-recurrent-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Reinforcement Learning Framework for Thoracic Diseases Classification via Prior Knowledge Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The chest X-ray is often utilized for diagnosing common thoracic diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoising Diffusion Semantic Segmentation with Mask Prior Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to ameliorate the semantic segmentation quality of existing discriminative approaches with a mask prior modeled by a recently-developed denoising diffusion generative model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoising-diffusion-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collect-and-Distribute Transformer for 3D Point Cloud Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collect-and-distribute-transformer-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new transformer architecture equipped with a collect-and-distribute mechanism to communicate short- and long-range contexts of point clouds, which we refer to as CDFormer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collect-and-distribute-transformer-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Message Quantization and Parallelization for Distributed Full-graph GNN Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-message-quantization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distributed full-graph training of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) over large graphs is bandwidth-demanding and time-consuming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-message-quantization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-LRFusion: Bi-Directional LiDAR-Radar Fusion for 3D Dynamic Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-lrfusion-bi-directional-lidar-radar-fusion-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LiDAR and Radar are two complementary sensing approaches in that LiDAR specializes in capturing an object's 3D shape while Radar provides longer detection ranges as well as velocity hints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-lrfusion-bi-directional-lidar-radar-fusion-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affinity Clustering Framework for Data Debiasing Using Pairwise Distribution Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affinity-clustering-framework-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents MASC, a data augmentation approach that leverages affinity clustering to balance the representation of non-protected and protected groups of a target dataset by utilizing instances of the same protected attributes from similar datasets that are categorized in the same cluster as the target dataset by sharing instances of the protected attribute.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affinity-clustering-framework-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Signed Distance Functions from Noisy 3D Point Clouds via Noise to Noise Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-signed-distance-functions-from-noisy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, without ground truth signed distances, point normals or clean point clouds, current methods still struggle from learning SDFs from noisy point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-signed-distance-functions-from-noisy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does it pay to optimize AUC?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-it-pay-to-optimize-auc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better understand the value of optimizing for AUC, we present an efficient algorithm, namely AUC-opt, to find the provably optimal AUC linear classifier in $\mathbb{R}^2$, which runs in $\mathcal{O}(n_+ n_- \log (n_+ n_-))$ where $n_+$ and $n_-$ are the number of positive and negative samples respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-it-pay-to-optimize-auc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Reasoning over Entities and Numerical Values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-reasoning-over-entities-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the difference between entities and numerical values, we also propose the framework of Number Reasoning Network (NRN) for alternatively encoding entities and numerical values into separate encoding structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-reasoning-over-entities-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Data-Driven Measure of Relative Uncertainty for Misclassification Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-measure-of-relative-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Misclassification detection is an important problem in machine learning, as it allows for the identification of instances where the model's predictions are unreliable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-driven-measure-of-relative-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Conceptual Coverage in Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-conceptual-coverage-in-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose "Conceptual Coverage Across Languages" (CoCo-CroLa), a technique for benchmarking the degree to which any generative text-to-image system provides multilingual parity to its training language in terms of tangible nouns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-conceptual-coverage-in-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMNI: Open-endedness via Models of human Notions of Interestingness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-open-endedness-via-models-of-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-ended algorithms aim to learn new, interesting behaviors forever.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omni-open-endedness-via-models-of-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoteTRANS: Detecting Adversarial Text without Training by Voting on Hard Labels of Transformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votetrans-detecting-adversarial-text-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, VoteTRANS detects adversarial text by comparing the hard labels of input text and its transformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votetrans-detecting-adversarial-text-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilevel Fast Scene Adaptation for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilevel-fast-scene-adaptation-for-low-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A bilevel learning framework is constructed to endow the scene-irrelevant generality of the encoder towards diverse scenes (i. e., freezing the encoder in the adaptation and testing phases).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilevel-fast-scene-adaptation-for-low-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DistilXLSR: A Light Weight Cross-Lingual Speech Representation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilxlsr-a-light-weight-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual self-supervised speech representation models have greatly enhanced the speech recognition performance for low-resource languages, and the compression of these huge models has also become a crucial prerequisite for their industrial application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilxlsr-a-light-weight-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved DeepFake Detection Using Whisper Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-deepfake-detection-using-whisper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a recent influx of voice generation methods, the threat introduced by audio DeepFake (DF) is ever-increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-deepfake-detection-using-whisper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LyricSIM: A novel Dataset and Benchmark for Similarity Detection in Spanish Song LyricS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyricsim-a-novel-dataset-and-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new dataset and benchmark tailored to the task of semantic similarity in song lyrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyricsim-a-novel-dataset-and-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Paraphrasing of Multiword Expressions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-paraphrasing-of-multiword</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an unsupervised approach to paraphrasing multiword expressions (MWEs) in context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-paraphrasing-of-multiword</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Adversarial Contrastive Learning for Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-adversarial-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To avoid the negative impact of adversarial perturbations on context-dependent data, we design a contextual adversarial training strategy to learn more diverse features from context and enhance the model's context robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-adversarial-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
