<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 21:06:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging AI to improve human planning in large partially observable environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-ai-to-improve-human-planning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we developed the first metareasoning algorithm for discovering resource-rational strategies for human planning in partially observable environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-ai-to-improve-human-planning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Survival Forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-survival-forests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel federated algorithm for survival analysis based on one of the most successful survival models, the random survival forest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-survival-forests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Lexical Simplification for English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-lexical-simplification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning Transformer-based approaches have recently shown exciting results on sentence simplification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-lexical-simplification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP: Memory-aware Automated Intra-op Parallel Training For Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-memory-aware-automated-intra-op-parallel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, finding an efficient distributed execution plan not only requires fine-grained model statistics, such as memory and computing overhead of each operator but also is a labor-intensive task even for an expert in the field of distributed training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-memory-aware-automated-intra-op-parallel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Indexing Variational Bayes: Interpretable Domain Index for Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-indexing-variational-bayes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous studies have shown that leveraging domain index can significantly boost domain adaptation performance \cite{arXiv:2007. 01807, arXiv:2202. 03628}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-indexing-variational-bayes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust, but Verify: Using Self-Supervised Probing to Improve Trustworthiness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-using-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Trustworthy machine learning is of primary importance to the practical deployment of deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trust-but-verify-using-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Representations of Bi-Level Knowledge Graphs for Reasoning beyond Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-bi-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define a bi-level knowledge graph that consists of the base-level and the higher-level triplets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-representations-of-bi-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-based Out-of-Distribution Detection for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-out-of-distribution-detection-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paves a way for a simple, powerful and efficient OOD detection model for GNN-based learning on graphs, which we call GNNSafe.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-out-of-distribution-detection-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic Contrastive Learning Recovers the Correct Aleatoric Uncertainty of Ambiguous Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-contrastive-learning-recovers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that these distributions recover the correct posteriors of the data-generating process, including its level of aleatoric uncertainty, up to a rotation of the latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-contrastive-learning-recovers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INCREASE: Inductive Graph Representation Learning for Spatio-Temporal Kriging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increase-inductive-graph-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It aims to infer knowledge for (the things at) unobserved locations using the data from (the things at) observed locations during a given time period of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/increase-inductive-graph-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide the Learner: Controlling Product of Experts Debiasing Method Based on Token Attribution Similarities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-the-learner-controlling-product-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A popular workaround is to train a robust model by re-weighting training examples based on a secondary biased model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guide-the-learner-controlling-product-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport Guided Unsupervised Learning for Enhancing low-quality Retinal Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-guided-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we proposed a simple but effective end-to-end framework for enhancing poor-quality retinal fundus images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-guided-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoFT: Enhancing Faithfulness and Diversity for Table-to-Text Generation via Logic Form Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loft-enhancing-faithfulness-and-diversity-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Logical Table-to-Text (LT2T) generation is tasked with generating logically faithful sentences from tables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loft-enhancing-faithfulness-and-diversity-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixFormer: End-to-End Tracking with Iterative Mixed Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixformer-end-to-end-tracking-with-iterative-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our core design is to utilize the flexibility of attention operations, and propose a Mixed Attention Module (MAM) for simultaneous feature extraction and target information integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixformer-end-to-end-tracking-with-iterative-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Collapse Inspired Feature-Classifier Alignment for Few-Shot Class Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we deal with this misalignment dilemma in FSCIL inspired by the recently discovered phenomenon named neural collapse, which reveals that the last-layer features of the same class will collapse into a vertex, and the vertices of all classes are aligned with the classifier prototypes, which are formed as a simplex equiangular tight frame (ETF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution for PSG competition with ECCV'22 SenseHuman Workshop</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-psg-competition-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Panoptic Scene Graph (PSG) generation aims to generate scene graph representations based on panoptic segmentation instead of rigid bounding boxes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-for-psg-competition-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchDCT: Patch Refinement for High Quality Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchdct-patch-refinement-for-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further refine masks obtained by compressed vectors, we propose for the first time a compressed vector based multi-stage refinement framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchdct-patch-refinement-for-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TR3D: Towards Real-Time Indoor 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tr3d-towards-real-time-indoor-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model with early feature fusion, which we refer to as TR3D+FF, outperforms existing 3D object detection approaches on the SUN RGB-D dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tr3d-towards-real-time-indoor-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHiLS: Zero-Shot Image Classification with Hierarchical Label Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chils-zero-shot-image-classification-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open vocabulary models (e. g.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chils-zero-shot-image-classification-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-Down Beats Bottom-Up in 3D Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-down-beats-bottom-up-in-3d-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most 3D instance segmentation methods exploit a bottom-up strategy, typically including resource-exhaustive post-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-down-beats-bottom-up-in-3d-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Large Kernel Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-large-kernel-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies indicate that kernel machines can often perform similarly or better than deep neural networks (DNNs) on small datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-large-kernel-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perception Datasets for Anomaly Detection in Autonomous Driving: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-datasets-for-anomaly-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNN) which are employed in perception systems for autonomous driving require a huge amount of data to train on, as they must reliably achieve high performance in all kinds of situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perception-datasets-for-anomaly-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuG: A Multimodal Classification Benchmark on Game Data with Tabular, Textual, and Visual Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mug-a-multimodal-classification-benchmark-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal learning has attracted the interest of the machine learning community due to its great potential in a variety of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mug-a-multimodal-classification-benchmark-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Target-based Surrogates for Stochastic Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-based-surrogates-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our target optimization framework uses the (expensive) gradient computation to construct surrogate functions in a target space (e. g. the logits output by a linear model for classification) that can be minimized efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/target-based-surrogates-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropout Injection at Test Time for Post Hoc Uncertainty Quantification in Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-injection-at-test-time-for-post-hoc</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among Bayesian methods, Monte-Carlo dropout provides principled tools for evaluating the epistemic uncertainty of neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dropout-injection-at-test-time-for-post-hoc</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Control-Oriented Dynamical Structure from Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-control-oriented-dynamical-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even for known nonlinear dynamical systems, feedback controller synthesis is a difficult problem that often requires leveraging the particular structure of the dynamics to induce a stable closed-loop system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-control-oriented-dynamical-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLSbench: Domain Adaptation Under Relaxed Label Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlsbench-domain-adaptation-under-relaxed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, popular deep domain adaptation heuristics tend to falter when faced with shifts in label proportions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlsbench-domain-adaptation-under-relaxed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the True Potential of Sequence-to-Sequence Models for Sequence Tagging and Structure Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-true-potential-of-sequence-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequence-to-Sequence (S2S) models have achieved remarkable success on various text generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-true-potential-of-sequence-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Robust Generalization for Wireless Channel Estimation Neural Networks by Designed Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-robust-generalization-for-wireless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method to design the training data that can support robust generalization of trained neural networks to unseen channels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-robust-generalization-for-wireless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hatemongers ride on echo chambers to escalate hate speech diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatemongers-ride-on-echo-chambers-to-escalate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze more than 32 million posts from over 6. 8 million users across three popular online social networks to investigate the interrelations between hateful behavior, information dissemination, and polarised organization mediated by echo chambers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hatemongers-ride-on-echo-chambers-to-escalate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrast with Reconstruct: Contrastive 3D Representation Learning Guided by Generative Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-with-reconstruct-contrastive-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This motivates us to learn 3D representations by sharing the merits of both paradigms, which is non-trivial due to the pattern difference between the two paradigms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrast-with-reconstruct-contrastive-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample Dropout: A Simple yet Effective Variance Reduction Technique in Deep Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-dropout-a-simple-yet-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent success in Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) methods has shown that policy optimization with respect to an off-policy distribution via importance sampling is effective for sample reuse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-dropout-a-simple-yet-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FastPillars: A Deployment-friendly Pillar-based 3D Detector</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastpillars-a-deployment-friendly-pillar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deployment of 3D detectors strikes one of the major challenges in real-world self-driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fastpillars-a-deployment-friendly-pillar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyramid Self-attention Polymerization Learning for Semi-supervised Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-self-attention-polymerization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most semi-supervised skeleton-based action recognition approaches aim to learn the skeleton action representations only at the joint level, but neglect the crucial motion characteristics at the coarser-grained body (e. g., limb, trunk) level that provide rich additional semantic information, though the number of labeled data is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramid-self-attention-polymerization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving Reality to Imagination: Robust Classification via Generated Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leaving-reality-to-imagination-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that Imagenet classifiers trained on real data augmented with generated data achieve higher accuracy and effective robustness than standard training and popular augmentation strategies in the presence of natural distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leaving-reality-to-imagination-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Discriminative vs. Generative Classifiers: Theory and Implications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-discriminative-vs-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically, the paper considers the surrogate loss instead of the zero-one loss in analyses and generalizes the classical results from binary cases to multiclass ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-discriminative-vs-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TempEL: Linking Dynamically Evolving and Newly Emerging Entities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tempel-linking-dynamically-evolving-and-newly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For that study, we introduce TempEL, an entity linking dataset that consists of time-stratified English Wikipedia snapshots from 2013 to 2022, from which we collect both anchor mentions of entities, and these target entities' descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tempel-linking-dynamically-evolving-and-newly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Role of Contrastive Representation Learning in Adversarial Robustness: An Empirical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-role-of-contrastive-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, adversarial fine-tuning is not very effective for supervised contrastive learning and supervised learning schemes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-role-of-contrastive-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run-Off Election: Improved Provable Defense against Data Poisoning Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/run-off-election-improved-provable-defense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we propose Run-Off Election (ROE), a novel aggregation method based on a two-round election across the base models: In the first round, models vote for their preferred class and then a second, Run-Off election is held between the top two classes in the first round.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/run-off-election-improved-provable-defense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaranteed Tensor Recovery Fused Low-rankness and Smoothness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guaranteed-tensor-recovery-fused-low-rankness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research have made significant progress by adopting two insightful tensor priors, i. e., global low-rankness (L) and local smoothness (S) across different tensor modes, which are always encoded as a sum of two separate regularization terms into the recovery models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guaranteed-tensor-recovery-fused-low-rankness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Image Deblurring with an Efficient ConvNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-image-deblurring-with-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a unified lightweight CNN network that features a large effective receptive field (ERF) and demonstrates comparable or even better performance than Transformers while bearing less computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-image-deblurring-with-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Many and Which Training Points Would Need to be Removed to Flip this Prediction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-many-and-which-training-points-would-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first work in to investigate the problem of identifying a minimal training set necessary to flip a given prediction in the context of machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-many-and-which-training-points-would-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REaLTabFormer: Generating Realistic Relational and Tabular Data using Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realtabformer-generating-realistic-relational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It first creates a parent table using an autoregressive GPT-2 model, then generates the relational dataset conditioned on the parent table using a sequence-to-sequence (Seq2Seq) model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realtabformer-generating-realistic-relational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Time Series Analysis with Fourier Transform: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-time-series-analysis-with-fourier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, although increasing attention has been attracted and research is flourishing in this emerging area, there lacks a systematic review of the variety of existing studies in the area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-time-series-analysis-with-fourier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Collaborative Filtering for Cold-Start Item Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-collaborative-filtering-for-cold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel model called Contrastive Collaborative Filtering for Cold-start item Recommendation (CCFCRec), which capitalizes on the co-occurrence collaborative signals in warm training data to alleviate the issue of blurry collaborative embeddings for cold-start item recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-collaborative-filtering-for-cold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Image Demoireing on Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-image-demoireing-on-mobile-devices</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we launch the first study on accelerating demoireing networks and propose a dynamic demoireing acceleration method (DDA) towards a real-time deployment on mobile devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-image-demoireing-on-mobile-devices</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A neural operator-based surrogate solver for free-form electromagnetic inverse design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-operator-based-surrogate-solver-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural operators have emerged as a powerful tool for solving partial differential equations in the context of scientific machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-operator-based-surrogate-solver-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient End-to-End Video Question Answering with Pyramidal Multimodal Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-end-to-end-video-question-answering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new method for end-to-end Video Question Answering (VideoQA), aside from the current popularity of using large-scale pre-training with huge feature extractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-end-to-end-video-question-answering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Box Detection Unifies End-to-End Multi-Person Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-box-detection-unifies-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel end-to-end framework with Explicit box Detection for multi-person Pose estimation, called ED-Pose, where it unifies the contextual learning between human-level (global) and keypoint-level (local) information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-box-detection-unifies-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShadowFormer: Global Context Helps Image Shadow Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowformer-global-context-helps-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is still challenging for the deep shadow removal model to exploit the global contextual correlation between shadow and non-shadow regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadowformer-global-context-helps-image</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
