<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Dec 2023 09:12:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Code Ownership in Open-Source AI Software Security</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-ownership-in-open-source-ai-software</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As open-source AI software projects become an integral component in the AI software development, it is critical to develop a novel methods to ensure and measure the security of the open-source projects for developers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/code-ownership-in-open-source-ai-software</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-latency Space-time Supersampling for Real-time Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-space-time-supersampling-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise of real-time rendering and the evolution of display devices, there is a growing demand for post-processing methods that offer high-resolution content in a high frame rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-space-time-supersampling-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoupled Knowledge with Ensemble Learning for Online Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-knowledge-with-ensemble-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To obtain early decoupled knowledge, an initialization scheme for the teacher is devised, and a 2D geometry-based analysis experiment is conducted under ideal conditions to showcase the effectiveness of this scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoupled-knowledge-with-ensemble-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Whole-slide Image to Biomarker Prediction: A Protocol for End-to-End Deep Learning in Computational Pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-whole-slide-image-to-biomarker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hematoxylin- and eosin (H&E) stained whole-slide images (WSIs) are the foundation of diagnosis of cancer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-whole-slide-image-to-biomarker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-ARK: Knowledge Graph Reasoning Using Large Language Models via Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-ark-knowledge-graph-reasoning-using-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the absence of Knowledge Graph (KG) environment awareness and the challenge of engineering viable optimization mechanisms for intermediary reasoning processes, constrict the performance of LLMs on KG reasoning tasks compared to smaller models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-ark-knowledge-graph-reasoning-using-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling agency: trade-offs between regional and integrated energy systems design flexibility</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-agency-trade-offs-between-regional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Europe as a whole as well as individual countries have many distinct pathways to net carbon neutrality by 2050.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-agency-trade-offs-between-regional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Discrete-Time Major-Minor Mean Field Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-discrete-time-major-minor-mean-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel discrete time version of major-minor MFGs (M3FGs), along with a learning algorithm based on fictitious play and partitioning the probability simplex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-discrete-time-major-minor-mean-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DistilVPR: Cross-Modal Knowledge Distillation for Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilvpr-cross-modal-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The utilization of multi-modal sensor data in visual place recognition (VPR) has demonstrated enhanced performance compared to single-modal counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilvpr-cross-modal-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Label Classification of COVID-Tweets Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-classification-of-covid-tweets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vaccination is important to minimize the risk and spread of various diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-classification-of-covid-tweets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperPIE: Hyperparameter Information Extraction from Scientific Publications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperpie-hyperparameter-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We create a labeled data set covering publications from a variety of computer science disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperpie-hyperparameter-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Student is Better Than Expected: Adaptive Teacher-Student Collaboration for Text-Conditional Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-student-is-better-than-expected-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While several powerful distillation methods were recently proposed, the overall quality of student samples is typically lower compared to the teacher ones, which hinders their practical usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-student-is-better-than-expected-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-directional Adapter for Multi-modal Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-adapter-for-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To handle this problem, we propose a novel multi-modal visual prompt tracking model based on a universal bi-directional adapter, cross-prompting multiple modalities mutually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-adapter-for-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-Euclidean Spatial Graph Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-euclidean-spatial-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, existing spatial network representation learning methods can only consider networks embedded in Euclidean space, and can not well exploit the rich geometric information carried by irregular and non-uniform non-Euclidean space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-euclidean-spatial-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wikiformer: Pre-training with Structured Information of Wikipedia for Ad-hoc Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikiformer-pre-training-with-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of deep learning and natural language processing techniques, pre-trained language models have been widely used to solve information retrieval (IR) problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikiformer-pre-training-with-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bengali License Plate Recognition: Unveiling Clarity with CNN and GFP-GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bengali-license-plate-recognition-unveiling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automated License Plate Recognition(ALPR) is a system that automatically reads and extracts data from vehicle license plates using image processing and computer vision techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bengali-license-plate-recognition-unveiling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M3DBench: Let's Instruct Large Models with Multi-modal 3D Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3dbench-let-s-instruct-large-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we establish a new benchmark for assessing the performance of large models in understanding multi-modal 3D prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m3dbench-let-s-instruct-large-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking Deepfake Faces from Videos Using An Explainable Cost-Sensitive Deep Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-deepfake-faces-from-videos-using-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To create a reliable deepfake detection system, four pre-trained Convolutional Neural Network (CNN) models: XceptionNet, InceptionResNetV2, EfficientNetV2S, and EfficientNetV2M were used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-deepfake-faces-from-videos-using-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarks for Physical Reasoning AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarks-for-physical-reasoning-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we aim to offer an overview of existing benchmarks and their solution approaches and propose a unified perspective for measuring the physical reasoning capacity of AI systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarks-for-physical-reasoning-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing Networks: Understanding Effective Teacher Practices in AI-Supported Classrooms using Transmodal Ordered Network Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-networks-understanding-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Taken together, offering early conceptual support to students with low learning rates could make classroom practice with AI tutors more effective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revealing-networks-understanding-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traffic Incident Database with Multiple Labels Including Various Perspective Environmental Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-incident-database-with-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[V-TIDB is constructed by collecting many videos from the Internet and annotating them with appropriate environmental information. In our experiments, we compare the performance of traffic accident recognition when only labels related to the presence or absence of traffic accidents are trained and when environmental information is added as a multi-label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/traffic-incident-database-with-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Detection in Long-Tailed Recognition with Calibrated Outlier Class Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-in-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a novel calibrated outlier class learning (COCL) approach, in which 1) a debiased large margin learning method is introduced in the outlier class learning to distinguish OOD samples from both head and tail classes in the representation space and 2) an outlier-class-aware logit calibration method is defined to enhance the long-tailed classification confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-in-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Learning in Multilingual Scene Text Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-learning-in-multilingual-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to find the condition that exploits knowledge from high-resource languages for improving performance in low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-learning-in-multilingual-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-Training Quantization for Re-parameterization via Coarse &amp; Fine Weight Splitting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-quantization-for-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although neural networks have made remarkable advancements in various applications, they require substantial computational and memory resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/post-training-quantization-for-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E2E-AT: A Unified Framework for Tackling Uncertainty in Task-aware End-to-end Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2e-at-a-unified-framework-for-tackling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful machine learning involves a complete pipeline of data, model, and downstream applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e2e-at-a-unified-framework-for-tackling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mathematical perspective on Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mathematical-perspective-on-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers play a central role in the inner workings of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-mathematical-perspective-on-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Compact 3D Representations via Point Feature Enhancement Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-compact-3d-representations-via-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, to learn more compact features, a share-parameter Transformer encoder is introduced to extract point features from the global and local unmasked patches obtained by global random and local block mask strategies, followed by a specific decoder to reconstruct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-compact-3d-representations-via-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAME: Sample Reconstruction Against Model Extraction Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/same-sample-reconstruction-against-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep learning models have shown significant performance across various domains, their deployment needs extensive resources and advanced computing infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/same-sample-reconstruction-against-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Multi-Robot Coverage Path Planning via Local Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-robot-coverage-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing graph-based MCPP algorithms first compute a tree cover on $G$ -- a forest of multiple trees that cover all vertices -- and then employ the Spanning Tree Coverage (STC) paradigm to generate coverage paths on the decomposed graph $D$ of the terrain graph $G$ by circumnavigating the edges of the computed trees, aiming to optimize the makespan (i. e., the maximum coverage path cost among all robots).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-robot-coverage-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>p-Laplacian Adaptation for Generative Pre-trained Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-laplacian-adaptation-for-generative-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel modeling framework that recasts adapter tuning after attention as a graph message passing process on attention graphs, where the projected query and value features and attention matrix constitute the node features and the graph adjacency matrix, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-laplacian-adaptation-for-generative-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Conditioning Bias in Binary Decision Trees and Random Forests and Its Elimination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-conditioning-bias-in-binary-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed techniques successfully mitigate the bias, compared to the worst-case scenario, statistically significant improvements of up to 0. 1-0. 2 percentage points of AUC and $r^2$ scores were achieved and the improvement of 1. 5 percentage points of $r^2$ score was measured in the most sensitive case of random forest regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-conditioning-bias-in-binary-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding Concerns: Multi-label Classification of Vaccine Sentiments in Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-concerns-multi-label-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of public health, vaccination stands as the cornerstone for mitigating disease risks and controlling their proliferation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-concerns-multi-label-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Optimization in RLHF: The Impact of Out-of-preference Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-optimization-in-rlhf-the-impact-of-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These methods, either explicitly or implicitly, learn a reward model from preference data and differ in the data used for policy optimization to unlock the generalization ability of the reward model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-optimization-in-rlhf-the-impact-of-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amortized Reparametrization: Efficient and Scalable Variational Inference for Latent SDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-reparametrization-efficient-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of inferring latent stochastic differential equations (SDEs) with a time and memory cost that scales independently with the amount of data, the total length of the time series, and the stiffness of the approximate differential equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amortized-reparametrization-efficient-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers in Unsupervised Structure-from-Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-in-unsupervised-structure-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have revolutionized deep learning based computer vision with improved performance as well as robustness to natural corruptions and adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-in-unsupervised-structure-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIGHT: Retrieval-augmented Generation for Mainstream Hashtag Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/right-retrieval-augmented-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic mainstream hashtag recommendation aims to accurately provide users with concise and popular topical hashtags before publication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/right-retrieval-augmented-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SA$^2$VP: Spatially Aligned-and-Adapted Visual Prompt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-2-vp-spatially-aligned-and-adapted-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Typical methods for visual prompt tuning follow the sequential modeling paradigm stemming from NLP, which represents an input image as a flattened sequence of token embeddings and then learns a set of unordered parameterized tokens prefixed to the sequence representation as the visual prompts for task adaptation of large vision models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sa-2-vp-spatially-aligned-and-adapted-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PETDet: Proposal Enhancement for Two-Stage Fine-Grained Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/petdet-proposal-enhancement-for-two-stage</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-grained object detection (FGOD) extends object detection with the capability of fine-grained recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/petdet-proposal-enhancement-for-two-stage</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Similar Entities have Similar Embeddings?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-similar-entities-have-similar-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper challenges the prevailing assumption that entity similarity in the graph is inherently mirrored in the embedding space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-similar-entities-have-similar-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One step closer to unbiased aleatoric uncertainty estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-closer-to-unbiased-aleatoric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks are powerful tools in various applications, and quantifying their uncertainty is crucial for reliable decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-closer-to-unbiased-aleatoric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepArt: A Benchmark to Advance Fidelity Research in AI-Generated Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepart-a-benchmark-to-advance-fidelity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the image synthesis capabilities of GPT-4, a leading multi-modal large language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepart-a-benchmark-to-advance-fidelity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deriving Rewards for Reinforcement Learning from Symbolic Behaviour Descriptions of Bipedal Walking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deriving-rewards-for-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating physical movement behaviours from their symbolic description is a long-standing challenge in artificial intelligence (AI) and robotics, requiring insights into numerical optimization methods as well as into formalizations from symbolic AI and reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deriving-rewards-for-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Image-level Classification Improves Open-vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-image-level-classification-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This limits their capability in detecting hard objects of small, blurred, or occluded appearance from novel/base categories, whose detection heavily relies on contextual information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-image-level-classification-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Restoration Through Generalized Ornstein-Uhlenbeck Bridge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-restoration-through-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models possess powerful generative capabilities enabling the mapping of noise to data using reverse stochastic differential equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-restoration-through-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPIDSG: A Privacy-Preserving Image Distribution Sharing Scheme with GAN in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppidsg-a-privacy-preserving-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, a privacy-preserving image distribution sharing scheme with GAN (PPIDSG) is proposed, which consists of a block scrambling-based encryption algorithm, an image distribution sharing method, and local classification training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppidsg-a-privacy-preserving-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Causal Impact of Credit Lines on Spending Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-causal-impact-of-credit-lines-on-spending</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consumer credit services offered by e-commerce platforms provide customers with convenient loan access during shopping and have the potential to stimulate sales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-causal-impact-of-credit-lines-on-spending</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPT: Fine-Tuning Transformer-based Language Models Efficiently with Sparsification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spt-fine-tuning-transformer-based-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we design the sparse MHA module, which computes and stores only large attention weights to reduce memory consumption, and the routed FFN module, which dynamically activates a subset of model parameters for each token to reduce computation cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spt-fine-tuning-transformer-based-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Environment Robustness of Deep Reinforcement Learning Approaches for Autonomous Racing Using Bayesian Optimization-based Curriculum Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-environment-robustness-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning (RL) approaches have been broadly applied to a large number of robotics tasks, such as robot manipulation and autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-environment-robustness-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opara: Exploiting Operator Parallelism for Expediting DNN Inference on GPUs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opara-exploiting-operator-parallelism-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GPUs have become the defacto hardware devices to accelerate Deep Neural Network (DNN) inference in deep learning(DL) frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opara-exploiting-operator-parallelism-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalization Analysis of Policy Networks: An Example of Double-Integrator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-analysis-of-policy-networks-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive utilization of deep reinforcement learning (DRL) policy networks in diverse continuous control tasks has raised questions regarding performance degradation in expansive state spaces where the input state norm is larger than that in the training environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalization-analysis-of-policy-networks-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Bayesian Optimization with Unknown Continuous Context Distribution via Kernel Density Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-bayesian-optimization-with-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that the estimated PDF may have high estimation error when the true distribution is complicated, we further propose the second algorithm that optimizes the distributionally robust objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-bayesian-optimization-with-unknown</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
