<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 21:09:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Thought2Text: Text Generation from EEG Signal using Large Language Models (LLMs)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thought2text-text-generation-from-eeg-signal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decoding and expressing brain activity in a comprehensible form is a challenging frontier in AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thought2text-text-generation-from-eeg-signal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Window Function-less DFT with Reduced Noise and Latency for Real-Time Music Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/window-function-less-dft-with-reduced-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Music analysis applications demand algorithms that can provide both high time and frequency resolution while minimizing noise in an already-noisy signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/window-function-less-dft-with-reduced-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneRef: Unified One-tower Expression Grounding and Segmentation with Mask Referring Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneref-unified-one-tower-expression-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Simultaneously, the current mask visual language modeling (MVLM) fails to capture the nuanced referential relationship between image-text in referring tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oneref-unified-one-tower-expression-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poison-splat: Computation Cost Attack on 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poison-splat-computation-cost-attack-on-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in this work, we reveal a significant security vulnerability that has been largely overlooked in 3DGS: the computation cost of training 3DGS could be maliciously tampered by poisoning the input data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poison-splat-computation-cost-attack-on-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Reasoning Networks: Efficient Interpretable Neural Networks With Automatic Textual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-reasoning-networks-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in machine learning have led to a surge in adoption of neural networks for various tasks, but lack of interpretability remains an issue for many others in which an understanding of the features influencing the prediction is necessary to ensure fairness, safety, and legal compliance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-reasoning-networks-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable and Animatable Gaussian Head Avatar</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-and-animatable-gaussian-head</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Generalizable and Animatable Gaussian head Avatar (GAGAvatar) for one-shot animatable head avatar reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-and-animatable-gaussian-head</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoPESD: A Multi-Level Surgical Motion Dataset for Training Large Vision-Language Models to Co-Pilot Endoscopic Submucosal Dissection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copesd-a-multi-level-surgical-motion-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we design a hierarchical decomposition of ESD motion granularity and introduce a multi-level surgical motion dataset (CoPESD) for training LVLMs as the robotic \textbf{Co}-\textbf{P}ilot of \textbf{E}ndoscopic \textbf{S}ubmucosal \textbf{D}issection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copesd-a-multi-level-surgical-motion-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reward-Augmented Data Enhances Direct Preference Alignment of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-augmented-data-enhances-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset is easily integrated with existing direct alignment algorithms and is applicable to any preference dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reward-augmented-data-enhances-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrackSegDiff: Diffusion Probability Model-based Multi-modal Crack Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cracksegdiff-diffusion-probability-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental evaluation on the three-class crack image segmentation tasks within the FIND dataset demonstrates that CrackSegDiff outperforms state-of-the-art methods, particularly excelling in the detection of shallow cracks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cracksegdiff-diffusion-probability-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QCircuitNet: A Large-Scale Hierarchical Dataset for Quantum Algorithm Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qcircuitnet-a-large-scale-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce QCircuitNet, the first benchmark and test dataset designed to evaluate AI's capability in designing and implementing quantum algorithms in the form of quantum circuit codes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qcircuitnet-a-large-scale-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Dictionary Learning with Switch Sparse Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-dictionary-learning-with-switch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present experiments comparing Switch SAEs with other SAE architectures, and find that Switch SAEs deliver a substantial Pareto improvement in the reconstruction vs. sparsity frontier for a given fixed training compute budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-dictionary-learning-with-switch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Up Your Kernels: Large Kernel Design in ConvNets towards Universal Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-your-kernels-large-kernel-design</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes the paradigm of large convolutional kernels in designing modern Convolutional Neural Networks (ConvNets).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-your-kernels-large-kernel-design</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Diffusion Distillation for Efficient Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-diffusion-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, many training-free sampling methods have been proposed to reduce the number of sampling steps required for diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-diffusion-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistically-Informed Multilingual Instruction Tuning: Is There an Optimal Set of Languages to Tune?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistically-informed-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All resources, including the code for language selection and multilingual instruction tuning, are made available in our official repository at https://github. com/GGLAB-KU/ling-informed-mit enabling reproducibility and further research in this area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistically-informed-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent S: An Open Agentic Framework that Uses Computers Like a Human</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-s-an-open-agentic-framework-that-uses</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Agent S, an open agentic framework that enables autonomous interaction with computers through a Graphical User Interface (GUI), aimed at transforming human-computer interaction by automating complex, multi-step tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-s-an-open-agentic-framework-that-uses</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StepTool: A Step-grained Reinforcement Learning Framework for Tool Learning in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steptool-a-step-grained-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite having powerful reasoning and inference capabilities, Large Language Models (LLMs) still need external tools to acquire real-time information retrieval or domain-specific expertise to solve complex tasks, which is referred to as tool learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steptool-a-step-grained-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-VLM: Post-training Quantization for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-vlm-post-training-quantization-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the contrary, we mine the cross-layer dependency that significantly influences discretization errors of the entire vision-language model, and embed this dependency into optimal quantization strategy searching with low search cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-vlm-post-training-quantization-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Learning at Test-Time: Active Fine-Tuning of LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-learning-at-test-time-active-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce SIFT, a data selection algorithm designed to reduce uncertainty about the model's response given a prompt, which unifies ideas from retrieval and active learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-learning-at-test-time-active-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching-Inspired Integrated Prompting Framework: A Novel Approach for Enhancing Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-inspired-integrated-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments are conducted on nine benchmarks which demonstrates that our approach improves the reasoning accuracy of LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-inspired-integrated-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DelTA: An Online Document-Level Translation Agent Based on Multi-Level Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delta-an-online-document-level-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have achieved reasonable quality improvements in machine translation (MT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delta-an-online-document-level-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reversible Decoupling Network for Single Image Reflection Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversible-decoupling-network-for-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep-learning-based approaches to single-image reflection removal have shown promising advances, primarily for two reasons: 1) the utilization of recognition-pretrained features as inputs, and 2) the design of dual-stream interaction networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reversible-decoupling-network-for-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning Integration in Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning for Advanced Task Complexity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-integration-in-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we integrate meta-learning into HRL to enhance the agent's ability to learn and adapt hierarchical policies swiftly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-integration-in-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IncEventGS: Pose-Free Gaussian Splatting from a Single Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inceventgs-pose-free-gaussian-splatting-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To recover the 3D scene representation incrementally, we exploit the tracking and mapping paradigm of conventional SLAM pipelines for IncEventGS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inceventgs-pose-free-gaussian-splatting-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LADIMO: Face Morph Generation through Biometric Template Inversion with Latent Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladimo-face-morph-generation-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Face morphing attacks pose a severe security threat to face recognition systems, enabling the morphed face image to be verified against multiple identities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladimo-face-morph-generation-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deconstructing equivariant representations in molecular systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-equivariant-representations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we report on a set of experiments using a simple equivariant graph convolution model on the QM9 dataset, focusing on correlating quantitative performance with the resulting molecular graph embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-equivariant-representations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal-State Dynamics Estimation for Physics-based Human Motion Capture from Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-state-dynamics-estimation-for-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a control loop as a meta-PD controller to predict internal joint torques and external reaction forces, followed by a physics-based motion simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-state-dynamics-estimation-for-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at Machine Unlearning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-machine-unlearning-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the behavior that untargeted unlearning attempts to approximate is unpredictable and may involve hallucinations, and existing regularization is insufficient for targeted unlearning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-machine-unlearning-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RayEmb: Arbitrary Landmark Detection in X-Ray Images Using Ray Embedding Subspace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rayemb-arbitrary-landmark-detection-in-x-ray</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anatomical landmarks pre-annotated in the CT volume can be detected in X-ray images to establish 2D-3D correspondences, which are then utilized for registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rayemb-arbitrary-landmark-detection-in-x-ray</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packing Analysis: Packing Is More Appropriate for Large Models or Datasets in Supervised Fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/packing-analysis-packing-is-more-appropriate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although it has demonstrated effectiveness during pre-training, there remains a lack of comprehensive analysis for the supervised fine-tuning (SFT) stage on the following points: (1) whether packing can effectively enhance training efficiency while maintaining performance, (2) the suitable size of the model and dataset for fine-tuning with the packing method, and (3) whether packing unrelated or related training samples might cause the model to either excessively disregard or over-rely on the context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/packing-analysis-packing-is-more-appropriate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNN-PAR: Energy Efficient Pedestrian Attribute Recognition via Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snn-par-energy-efficient-pedestrian-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, in this paper, we propose a Spiking Neural Network (SNN) based framework for energy-efficient attribute recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snn-par-energy-efficient-pedestrian-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameTraversalBenchmark: Evaluating Planning Abilities Of Large Language Models Through Traversing 2D Game Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gametraversalbenchmark-evaluating-planning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have recently demonstrated great success in generating and understanding natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gametraversalbenchmark-evaluating-planning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning in Spectral Domain for Point Cloud Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-in-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PointGST freezes the pre-trained model and introduces a lightweight, trainable Point Cloud Spectral Adapter (PCSA) to fine-tune parameters in the spectral domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-in-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCoder2: Better Math Reasoning from Continued Pretraining on Model-translated Mathematical Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder2-better-math-reasoning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training several popular base models with this corpus significantly improves their mathematical abilities, leading to the creation of the MathCoder2 family of models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder2-better-math-reasoning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firzen: Firing Strict Cold-Start Items with Frozen Heterogeneous and Homogeneous Graphs for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/firzen-firing-strict-cold-start-items-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation models utilizing unique identities (IDs) to represent distinct users and items have dominated the recommender systems literature for over a decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/firzen-firing-strict-cold-start-items-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MotionGS: Exploring Explicit Motion Guidance for Deformable 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motiongs-exploring-explicit-motion-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first introduce an optical flow decoupling module that decouples optical flow into camera flow and motion flow, corresponding to camera movement and object motion respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motiongs-exploring-explicit-motion-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Correlated Prompting for Visual Recognition with Missing Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-correlated-prompting-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Plentiful ablations are further given to show the generalizability and reliability of our method upon different modality-missing ratios and types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-correlated-prompting-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReIFE: Re-evaluating Instruction-Following Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reife-re-evaluating-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automatic evaluation of instruction following typically involves using large language models (LLMs) to assess response quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reife-re-evaluating-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity Prevails: Rethinking Negative Preference Optimization for LLM Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicity-prevails-rethinking-negative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we address the problem of large language model (LLM) unlearning, aiming to remove unwanted data influences and associated model capabilities (e. g., copyrighted data or harmful content generation) while preserving essential model utilities, without the need for retraining from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicity-prevails-rethinking-negative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking GS: Towards High-Accuracy and Low-Cost Surface Reconstruction via Spiking Neuron-based Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-gs-towards-high-accuracy-and-low-cost</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in improving surface reconstruction accuracy, the reconstructed results still exhibit bias and suffer from inefficiency in storage and training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-gs-towards-high-accuracy-and-low-cost</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Legal Case Retrieval via Scaling High-quality Synthetic Query-Candidate Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-legal-case-retrieval-via-scaling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, the construction method can also be applied to civil cases and achieve promising results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-legal-case-retrieval-via-scaling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Readiness of Prominent Small Language Models for the Democratization of Financial Literacy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-readiness-of-prominent-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of small language models (SLMs), herein defined as models with less than three billion parameters, is increasing across various domains and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-readiness-of-prominent-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting the Best Sequential Transfer Path for Medical Image Segmentation with Limited Labeled Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-the-best-sequential-transfer-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this, we select appropriate source tasks and develop an effective sequential transfer strategy by incorporating intermediate source tasks to gradually narrow the domain discrepancy and minimize the transfer cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-the-best-sequential-transfer-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>En masse scanning and automated surfacing of small objects using Micro-CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/en-masse-scanning-and-automated-surfacing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern archaeological methods increasingly utilize 3D virtual representations of objects, computationally intensive analyses, high resolution scanning, large datasets, and machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/en-masse-scanning-and-automated-surfacing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principal Orthogonal Latent Components Analysis (POLCA Net)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principal-orthogonal-latent-components</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Representation learning is a pivotal area in the field of machine learning, focusing on the development of methods to automatically discover the representations or features needed for a given task from raw data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principal-orthogonal-latent-components</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suppress Content Shift: Better Diffusion Features via Off-the-Shelf Generation Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suppress-content-shift-better-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We locate the cause of content shift as one inherent characteristic of diffusion models, which suggests the broad existence of this phenomenon in diffusion feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suppress-content-shift-better-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Positive-Augmented Contrastive Learning for Vision-and-Language Evaluation and Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-augmented-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Metrics can indeed play a key role in the fine-tuning stage of captioning models, ultimately enhancing the quality of the generated captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/positive-augmented-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyEmo: Scaling down Emotional Reasoning via Metric Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyemo-scaling-down-emotional-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach features: (1) a synthetic emotional instruct dataset for both pre-training and fine-tuning stages, (2) a Metric Projector that delegates classification from the language model allowing for more efficient training and inference, (3) a multi-modal large language model (MM-LLM) for emotional reasoning, and (4) a semi-automated framework for bias detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyemo-scaling-down-emotional-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HFH-Font: Few-shot Chinese Font Synthesis with Higher Quality, Faster Speed, and Higher Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hfh-font-few-shot-chinese-font-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using our method, for the first time, large-scale Chinese vector fonts of a quality comparable to those manually created by professional font designers can be automatically generated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hfh-font-few-shot-chinese-font-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLE-bench: Evaluating Machine Learning Agents on Machine Learning Engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mle-bench-evaluating-machine-learning-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MLE-bench, a benchmark for measuring how well AI agents perform at machine learning engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mle-bench-evaluating-machine-learning-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixtral 12B</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixtral-12b</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike many open-source models, Pixtral is also a cutting-edge text model for its size, and does not compromise on natural language performance to excel in multimodal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixtral-12b</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
