<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:09:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mathador-LM: A Dynamic Benchmark for Mathematical Reasoning on Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathador-lm-a-dynamic-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Mathador-LM, a new benchmark for evaluating the mathematical reasoning on large language models (LLMs), combining ruleset interpretation, planning, and problem-solving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathador-lm-a-dynamic-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Fusion By Evolving Weights of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-fusion-by-evolving-weights-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning pre-trained language models, particularly large language models, demands extensive computing resources and can result in varying performance outcomes across different domains and datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-fusion-by-evolving-weights-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A data-centric approach for assessing progress of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-centric-approach-for-assessing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we define homophily and Cross-Class Neighborhood Similarity for multi-label classification and investigate $9$ collected multi-label datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-data-centric-approach-for-assessing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSI-Bench: Benchmarking Time Series Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsi-bench-benchmarking-time-series-imputation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the development of numerous deep learning algorithms for time series imputation, the community lacks standardized and comprehensive benchmark platforms to effectively evaluate imputation performance across different settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsi-bench-benchmarking-time-series-imputation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Transparency of Machine Generated Fact Checking Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-transparency-of-machine-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the impact of human-curated vs. machine-selected evidence for explanation generation using large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-transparency-of-machine-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Efficient Randomized Exploration for Reinforcement Learning via Approximate Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-randomized-exploration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirically, we show that in tasks where deep exploration is necessary, our proposed algorithms that combine FGTS and approximate sampling perform significantly better compared to other strong baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-efficient-randomized-exploration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCIE_LAM Solution for Ego4D Looking At Me Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcie-lam-solution-for-ego4d-looking-at-me</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report presents our team's 'PCIE_LAM' solution for the Ego4D Looking At Me Challenge at CVPR2024.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcie-lam-solution-for-ego4d-looking-at-me</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Preferences via Multi-Objective Reward Modeling and Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-preferences-via-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The trained RM serves as a proxy for human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-preferences-via-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Slow Generating: An Empirical Study on Large and Small Language Models Collaborative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-slow-generating-an-empirical-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Collaborative decoding between large and small language models (SLMs) offers a novel approach to address these challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-slow-generating-an-empirical-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPEval: A Bilingual Intellectual Property Agency Consultation Evaluation Benchmark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ipeval-a-bilingual-intellectual-property</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of Large Language Models (LLMs) in vertical domains, including intellectual property (IP), lacks a specific evaluation benchmark for assessing their understanding, application, and reasoning abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ipeval-a-bilingual-intellectual-property</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AITTI: Learning Adaptive Inclusive Token for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aitti-learning-adaptive-inclusive-token-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the core of our method is a lightweight adaptive mapping network, which can customize the inclusive tokens for the concepts to be de-biased, making the tokens generalizable to unseen concepts regardless of their original bias distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aitti-learning-adaptive-inclusive-token-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OlympicArena: Benchmarking Multi-discipline Cognitive Reasoning for Superintelligent AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olympicarena-benchmarking-multi-discipline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We delve into the models' cognitive reasoning abilities, their performance across different modalities, and their outcomes in process-level evaluations, which are vital for tasks requiring complex reasoning with lengthy solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olympicarena-benchmarking-multi-discipline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCIE_EgoHandPose Solution for EgoExo4D Hand Pose Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcie-egohandpose-solution-for-egoexo4d-hand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach achieved the 1st position in the Hand Pose challenge with 25. 51 MPJPE and 8. 49 PA-MPJPE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcie-egohandpose-solution-for-egoexo4d-hand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CollabStory: Multi-LLM Collaborative Story Generation and Authorship Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collabstory-multi-llm-collaborative-story</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, there have not been efforts to explore such collaborative writing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collabstory-multi-llm-collaborative-story</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSI-Bench: Benchmarking Time Series Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsi-bench-benchmarking-time-series-imputation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the development of numerous deep learning algorithms for time series imputation, the community lacks standardized and comprehensive benchmark platforms to effectively evaluate imputation performance across different settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tsi-bench-benchmarking-time-series-imputation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealth edits for provably fixing or attacking large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stealth-edits-for-provably-fixing-or</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We reveal new methods and the theoretical foundations of techniques for editing large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stealth-edits-for-provably-fixing-or</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Prompting Taxonomy: A Universal Evaluation Framework for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-prompting-taxonomy-a-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Hierarchical Prompting Taxonomy (HPT), a taxonomy that employs a Hierarchical Prompt Framework (HPF) composed of five unique prompting strategies, arranged from the simplest to the most complex, to assess LLMs more precisely and to offer a clearer perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-prompting-taxonomy-a-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlanRAG: A Plan-then-Retrieval Augmented Generation for Generative Large Language Models as Decision Makers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planrag-a-plan-then-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct a study to utilize LLMs as a solution for decision making that requires complex data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planrag-a-plan-then-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the Veil: An Investigation into Concept Ablation for Privacy and Copyright Protection in Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-the-veil-an-investigation-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the study of concept ablation within pre-trained models as introduced in 'Ablating Concepts in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models' by (Kumari et al., 2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unmasking-the-veil-an-investigation-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Attacks on Multimodal Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-attacks-on-multimodal-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our attacks use adversarial text strings to guide gradient-based perturbation over one trigger image in the environment: (1) our captioner attack attacks white-box captioners if they are used to process images into captions as additional inputs to the VLM; (2) our CLIP attack attacks a set of CLIP models jointly, which can transfer to proprietary VLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-attacks-on-multimodal-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Preserving Federated Learning in Medical Imaging with Uncertainty Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-federated-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, FL, while robust in privacy preservation, faces several challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-federated-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoBench: Benchmarking and Analyzing Monocular Geometry Estimation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geobench-benchmarking-and-analyzing-monocular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While discriminative monocular geometry estimation methods rely on large-scale fine-tuning data to achieve zero-shot generalization, several generative-based paradigms show the potential of achieving impressive generalization performance on unseen scenes by leveraging pre-trained diffusion models and fine-tuning on even a small scale of synthetic training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geobench-benchmarking-and-analyzing-monocular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Multi-Image Understanding in Vision and Language Models: Perception, Knowledge, Reasoning, and Multi-Hop Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multi-image-understanding-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advancement of large language models (LLMs) has significantly broadened the scope of applications in natural language processing, with multi-modal LLMs extending these capabilities to integrate and interpret visual data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-multi-image-understanding-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Density-Peaks Clustering via Matrix Computations on MPI Parallelization System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-density-peaks-clustering-via-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Density peaks clustering (DP) has the ability of detecting clusters of arbitrary shape and clustering non-Euclidean space data, but its quadratic complexity in both computing and storage makes it difficult to scale for big data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-density-peaks-clustering-via-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebCanvas: Benchmarking Web Agents in Online Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webcanvas-benchmarking-web-agents-in-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce WebCanvas, an innovative online evaluation framework for web agents that effectively addresses the dynamic nature of web interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/webcanvas-benchmarking-web-agents-in-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RS-GPT4V: A Unified Multimodal Instruction-Following Dataset for Remote Sensing Image Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rs-gpt4v-a-unified-multimodal-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under the new LaGD paradigm, the old datasets, which have led to advances in RSI intelligence understanding in the last decade, are no longer suitable for fire-new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rs-gpt4v-a-unified-multimodal-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talk With Human-like Agents: Empathetic Dialogue Through Perceptible Acoustic Reception and Reaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talk-with-human-like-agents-empathetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This oversight can lead to misinterpretations of speakers' intentions, resulting in inconsistent or even contradictory responses within dialogues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/talk-with-human-like-agents-empathetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Column Generation Approach to the Vehicle Routing Problem with Two-Dimensional Loading and Last-In-First-Out Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-column-generation-approach-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The vehicle routing problem with two-dimensional loading constraints (2L-CVRP) and the last-in-first-out (LIFO) rule presents significant practical and algorithmic challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-column-generation-approach-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetric Multi-Similarity Loss for EPIC-KITCHENS-100 Multi-Instance Retrieval Challenge 2024</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-multi-similarity-loss-for-epic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present our champion solution for EPIC-KITCHENS-100 Multi-Instance Retrieval Challenge in CVPR 2024.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-multi-similarity-loss-for-epic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Generating Narrative-Style Radiology Reports from Volumetric CT Images; a Proof of Concept</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-generating-narrative-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces a deep learning-based proof of concept model to accurately identify abnormalities in volumetric CT data and generate narrative-style reports.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-generating-narrative-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRSBench: A Versatile Vision-Language Benchmark Dataset for Remote Sensing Image Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrsbench-a-versatile-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new benchmark designed to advance the development of general-purpose, large-scale vision-language models for remote sensing images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrsbench-a-versatile-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem-Solving in Language Model Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solving-in-language-model-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these methods enhance performance, the application of collective intelligence-based approaches to complex network structures and the dynamics of agent interactions remain underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solving-in-language-model-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>News Without Borders: Domain Adaptation of Multilingual Sentence Embeddings for Cross-lingual News Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/news-without-borders-domain-adaptation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rapidly growing numbers of multilingual news consumers pose an increasing challenge to news recommender systems in terms of providing customized recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/news-without-borders-domain-adaptation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holmes-VAD: Towards Unbiased and Explainable Video Anomaly Detection via Multi-modal LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holmes-vad-towards-unbiased-and-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train a lightweight temporal sampler to select frames with high anomaly response and fine-tune a multimodal large language model (LLM) to generate explanatory content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holmes-vad-towards-unbiased-and-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying the Recency Heuristic in Temporal-Difference Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-the-recency-heuristic-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recency heuristic in reinforcement learning is the assumption that stimuli that occurred closer in time to an acquired reward should be more heavily reinforced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demystifying-the-recency-heuristic-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic benchmarking of large multimodal models via iterative experiment programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-benchmarking-of-large-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, the LLM refines the report, presenting the results to the user in natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-benchmarking-of-large-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask-before-Plan: Proactive Language Agents for Real-World Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-before-plan-proactive-language-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce a new task, Proactive Agent Planning, which requires language agents to predict clarification needs based on user-agent conversation and agent-environment interaction, invoke external tools to collect valid information, and generate a plan to fulfill the user's demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ask-before-plan-proactive-language-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViDSOD-100: A New Dataset and a Baseline Model for RGB-D Video Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidsod-100-a-new-dataset-and-a-baseline-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the existing salient object detection (SOD) works only focus on either static RGB-D images or RGB videos, ignoring the collaborating of RGB-D and video information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidsod-100-a-new-dataset-and-a-baseline-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TroL: Traversal of Layers for Large Language and Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trol-traversal-of-layers-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language and vision models (LLVMs) have been driven by the generalization power of large language models (LLMs) and the advent of visual instruction tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trol-traversal-of-layers-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LayerMerge: Neural Network Depth Compression through Layer Pruning and Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layermerge-neural-network-depth-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing depth compression methods remove redundant non-linear activation functions and merge the consecutive convolution layers into a single layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layermerge-neural-network-depth-compression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Ceiling of the LLM Community by Treating Token Generation as a Classification for Ensembling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-ceiling-of-the-llm-community-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we treat the Generation of each token by LLMs as a Classification (GaC) for ensembling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/breaking-the-ceiling-of-the-llm-community-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Source Web Service with Morphological Dictionary-Supplemented Deep Learning for Morphosyntactic Analysis of Czech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-web-service-with-morphological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an open-source web service for Czech morphosyntactic analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-web-service-with-morphological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Resource Machine Translation through the Lens of Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-resource-machine-translation-through-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new approach based on the Personalized Federated Learning algorithm MeritFed that can be applied to Natural Language Tasks with heterogeneous data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-resource-machine-translation-through-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIOSCAN-5M: A Multimodal Dataset for Insect Biodiversity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioscan-5m-a-multimodal-dataset-for-insect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose three benchmark experiments to demonstrate the impact of the multi-modal data types on the classification and clustering accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioscan-5m-a-multimodal-dataset-for-insect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Heterophilic Snowflake Hypothesis: Training and Empowering GNNs for Heterophilic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-heterophilic-snowflake-hypothesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on observations, we innovatively introduce the Heterophily Snowflake Hypothesis and provide an effective solution to guide and facilitate research on heterophilic graphs and beyond.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-heterophilic-snowflake-hypothesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insect Identification in the Wild: The AMI Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insect-identification-in-the-wild-the-ami</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Insects represent half of all global biodiversity, yet many of the world's insects are disappearing, with severe implications for ecosystems and agriculture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insect-identification-in-the-wild-the-ami</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cephalometric Landmark Detection across Ages with Prototypical Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cephalometric-landmark-detection-across-ages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first effort toward developing a unified solution and dataset for cephalometric landmark detection across age groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cephalometric-landmark-detection-across-ages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning with a Single Shared Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-a-single-shared-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, in this paper, we introduce a new method that improves this knowledge distillation method to only rely on a single shared image between clients and server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-with-a-single-shared-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaMDA: Large Model Fine-Tuning via Spectrally Decomposed Low-Dimensional Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamda-large-model-fine-tuning-via-spectrally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LaMDA freezes a first projection matrix (PMA) in the adaptation path while introducing a low-dimensional trainable square matrix, resulting in substantial reductions in trainable parameters and peak GPU memory usage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamda-large-model-fine-tuning-via-spectrally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HumanSplat: Generalizable Single-Image Human Gaussian Splatting with Structure Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humansplat-generalizable-single-image-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advancements in high-fidelity human reconstruction techniques, the requirements for densely captured images or time-consuming per-instance optimization significantly hinder their applications in broader scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humansplat-generalizable-single-image-human</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
