<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 21:06:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Inducing Systematicity in Transformers by Attending to Structurally Quantized Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducing-systematicity-in-transformers-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers generalize to novel compositions of structures and entities after being trained on a complex dataset, but easily overfit on datasets of insufficient complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inducing-systematicity-in-transformers-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing facade details using MLS point clouds and Bag-of-Words approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-facade-details-using-mls-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new approach for the reconstruction of 3D fa\c{c}ade details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-facade-details-using-mls-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM-Math: Open Math Large Language Models Toward Verifiable Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-math-open-math-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further explore how to use LEAN to solve math problems and study its performance under the setting of multi-task learning which shows the possibility of using LEAN as a unified platform for solving and proving in math.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-math-open-math-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding hardness reductions automatically using SAT solvers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-hardness-reductions-automatically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we show that the completion problem, i. e. the decision problem whether a partial structure can be completed to a full structure, is NP-complete for many combinatorial structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-hardness-reductions-automatically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Node-wise Propagation for Large-scale Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-node-wise-propagation-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, (i) Most scalable GNNs tend to treat all nodes in graphs with the same propagation rules, neglecting their topological uniqueness; (ii) Existing node-wise propagation optimization strategies are insufficient on web-scale graphs with intricate topology, where a full portrayal of nodes' local properties is required.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-node-wise-propagation-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classifying point clouds at the facade-level using geometric features and deep learning networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifying-point-clouds-at-the-facade-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D building models with facade details are playing an important role in many applications now.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classifying-point-clouds-at-the-facade-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deceptive Path Planning via Reinforcement Learning with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deceptive-path-planning-via-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deceptive path planning (DPP) is the problem of designing a path that hides its true goal from an outside observer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deceptive-path-planning-via-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExaRanker-Open: Synthetic Explanation for IR using Open-Source LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaranker-open-synthetic-explanation-for-ir</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ExaRanker recently introduced an approach to training information retrieval (IR) models, incorporating natural language explanations as additional labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exaranker-open-synthetic-explanation-for-ir</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieve, Merge, Predict: Augmenting Tables with Data Lakes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieve-merge-predict-augmenting-tables-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present an in-depth analysis of data discovery in data lakes, focusing on table augmentation for given machine learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieve-merge-predict-augmenting-tables-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Sentence Completion with a Parser-Driven Rhetorical Control Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-sentence-completion-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controlled text generation (CTG) seeks to guide large language model (LLM) output to produce text that conforms to desired criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-sentence-completion-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Particle Denoising Diffusion Sampler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-denoising-diffusion-sampler</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising diffusion models have become ubiquitous for generative modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-denoising-diffusion-sampler</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The boundary of neural network trainability is fractal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-boundary-of-neural-network-trainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some fractals -- for instance those associated with the Mandelbrot and quadratic Julia sets -- are computed by iterating a function, and identifying the boundary between hyperparameters for which the resulting series diverges or remains bounded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-boundary-of-neural-network-trainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Weakness of Large Language Model Agents within a Complex Android Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-weakness-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These challenges motivate AndroidArena, an environment and benchmark designed to evaluate LLM agents on a modern operating system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-the-weakness-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal estimation of Gaussian (poly)trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-estimation-of-gaussian-poly-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop optimal algorithms for learning undirected Gaussian trees and directed Gaussian polytrees from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-estimation-of-gaussian-poly-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Editing with Canonical Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-editing-with-canonical-examples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Backpack defines a large bank of sense vectors--a decomposition of the different uses of each word--which are weighted and summed to form the output logits of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-editing-with-canonical-examples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Annotator: A framework for efficiently building video classifiers using vision-language models and active learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-annotator-a-framework-for-efficiently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-quality and consistent annotations are fundamental to the successful development of robust machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-annotator-a-framework-for-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where is the Truth? The Risk of Getting Confounded in a Continual World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-is-the-truth-the-risk-of-getting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A dataset is confounded if it is most easily solved via a spurious correlation which fails to generalize to new data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/where-is-the-truth-the-risk-of-getting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferring facade labels between point clouds with semantic octrees while considering change detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferring-facade-labels-between-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point clouds and high-resolution 3D data have become increasingly important in various fields, including surveying, construction, and virtual reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferring-facade-labels-between-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe Guaranteed Exploration for Non-linear Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-guaranteed-exploration-for-non-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this framework we propose an efficient algorithm, SageMPC, SAfe Guaranteed Exploration using Model Predictive Control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-guaranteed-exploration-for-non-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImplicitDeepfake: Plausible Face-Swapping through Implicit Deepfake Generation using NeRF and Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicitdeepfake-plausible-face-swapping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[NeRFs encode the object's shape and color in neural network weights using a handful of images with known camera positions to generate novel views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicitdeepfake-plausible-face-swapping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Contrastive Feature Representations for Facial Action Unit Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-contrastive-feature-representations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenge posed by noisy AU labels, we augment the supervised signal through the introduction of a self-supervised signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-contrastive-feature-representations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural SPH: Improved Neural Modeling of Lagrangian Fluid Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-sph-improved-neural-modeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Smoothed particle hydrodynamics (SPH) is omnipresent in modern engineering and scientific disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-sph-improved-neural-modeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Efficacy of Eviction Policy for Key-Value Constrained Generative Language Model Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-eviction-policy-for-key</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the recent success associated with Large Language Models~(LLMs), they are notably cost-prohibitive to deploy in resource-constrained environments due to their excessive memory and computational demands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-efficacy-of-eviction-policy-for-key</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Interpretable Data-Driven Models for Early Prediction of Antimicrobial Multidrug Resistance Using Multivariate Time-Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interpretable-data-driven-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electronic health records (EHR) is an inherently multimodal register of the patient's health status characterized by static data and multivariate time series (MTS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interpretable-data-driven-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Adversarial Bayesian Optimization for Surrogate Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-adversarial-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose generative adversarial Bayesian optimization (GABO) using adaptive source critic regularization, a task-agnostic framework for Bayesian optimization that employs a Lipschitz-bounded source critic model to constrain the optimization trajectory to regions where the surrogate function is reliable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-adversarial-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Membership Inference Attacks and Defenses in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-membership-inference-attacks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, combining model information from multiple communication rounds (Multi-temporal) enhances the overall effectiveness of MIAs compared to utilizing model information from a single epoch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-membership-inference-attacks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSearchAgent: A Lightweight Collaborative Search Agent with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosearchagent-a-lightweight-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hence, to better support the research in collaborative search, in this demo, we propose CoSearchAgent, a lightweight collaborative search agent powered by LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosearchagent-a-lightweight-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metamodeling and Control of Medical Digital Twins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamodeling-and-control-of-medical-digital</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical digital twins, computational models that integrate a wide range of health-related data about a person and can be dynamically updated, are a key technology that can help guide medical decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamodeling-and-control-of-medical-digital</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptCrypt: Prompt Encryption for Secure Communication with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptcrypt-prompt-encryption-for-secure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these models offer substantial benefits in terms of accessibility and functionality, they also introduce significant privacy concerns: the transmission and storage of user data in cloud infrastructures pose substantial risks of data breaches and unauthorized access to sensitive information; even if the transmission and storage of data is encrypted, the LLM service provider itself still knows the real contents of the data, preventing individuals or entities from confidently using such LLM services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptcrypt-prompt-encryption-for-secure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checking the Sufficiently Scattered Condition using a Global Non-Convex Optimization Software</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/checking-the-sufficiently-scattered-condition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this condition is NP-hard to check in general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/checking-the-sufficiently-scattered-condition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPHINX-X: Scaling Data and Parameters for a Family of Multi-modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sphinx-x-scaling-data-and-parameters-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SPHINX-X, an extensive Multimodality Large Language Model (MLLM) series developed upon SPHINX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sphinx-x-scaling-data-and-parameters-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everybody Prune Now: Structured Pruning of LLMs with only Forward Passes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-prune-now-structured-pruning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the generational gap in available hardware between lay practitioners and the most endowed institutions, LLMs are becoming increasingly inaccessible as they grow in size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/everybody-prune-now-structured-pruning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ordinal Regression Framework for a Deep Learning Based Severity Assessment for Chest Radiographs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ordinal-regression-framework-for-a-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the application of ordinal regression methods for categorizing disease severity in chest radiographs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ordinal-regression-framework-for-a-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Token-Based World Models with Parallel Observation Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-token-based-world-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We incorporate POP in a novel TBWM agent named REM (Retentive Environment Model), showcasing a 15. 4x faster imagination compared to prior TBWMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-token-based-world-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftEDA: Rethinking Rule-Based Data Augmentation with Soft Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softeda-rethinking-rule-based-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Rule-based text data augmentation is widely used for NLP tasks due to its simplicity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softeda-rethinking-rule-based-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIGC: Multi-Instance Generation Controller for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/migc-multi-instance-generation-controller-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, we aggregate all the shaded instances to provide the necessary information for accurately generating multiple instances in stable diffusion (SD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/migc-multi-instance-generation-controller-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum neural network with ensemble learning to mitigate barren plateaus and cost function concentration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-neural-network-with-ensemble-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of quantum computers promises transformative impacts across diverse fields of science and technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-neural-network-with-ensemble-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Sensitive Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning in Network Aggregative Markov Games</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-multi-agent-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under a set of assumptions, we prove the convergence of the algorithm to a subjective notion of Markov perfect Nash equilibrium in NAMGs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-sensitive-multi-agent-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing for ROC Curves on Class-Imbalanced Data by Training over a Family of Loss Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-for-roc-curves-on-class-imbalanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although binary classification is a well-studied problem in computer vision, training reliable classifiers under severe class imbalance remains a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-for-roc-curves-on-class-imbalanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLAPT: Protein-Ligand Binding Affinity Prediction Using Pretrained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plapt-protein-ligand-binding-affinity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding protein-ligand binding affinity is crucial for drug discovery, enabling the identification of promising drug candidates efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plapt-protein-ligand-binding-affinity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anfinsen Goes Neural: a Graphical Model for Conditional Antibody Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anfinsen-goes-neural-a-graphical-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Antibody design plays a pivotal role in advancing therapeutics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anfinsen-goes-neural-a-graphical-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking Neural Network Enhanced Hand Gesture Recognition Using Low-Cost Single-photon Avalanche Diode Array</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-network-enhanced-hand-gesture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a compact spiking convolutional neural network (SCNN) and spiking multilayer perceptron (SMLP) to recognize ten different gestures in dark and bright light environments, using a $9. 6 single-photon avalanche diode (SPAD) array.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-neural-network-enhanced-hand-gesture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Timescale Ensemble Q-learning for Markov Decision Process Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-timescale-ensemble-q-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning (RL) is a classical tool to solve network control or policy optimization problems in unknown environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-timescale-ensemble-q-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid Optimization for Jailbreaking LLMs via Subconscious Exploitation and Echopraxia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-optimization-for-jailbreaking-llms-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have become prevalent across diverse sectors, transforming human life with their extraordinary reasoning and comprehension abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rapid-optimization-for-jailbreaking-llms-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate LoRA-Finetuning Quantization of LLMs via Information Retention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-lora-finetuning-quantization-of-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel IR-QLoRA for pushing quantized LLMs with LoRA to be highly accurate through information retention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-lora-finetuning-quantization-of-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Function Aligned Regression: A Method Explicitly Learns Functional Derivatives from Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/function-aligned-regression-a-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regression is a fundamental task in machine learning that has garnered extensive attention over the past decades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/function-aligned-regression-a-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining Gender and Racial Bias in Large Vision-Language Models Using a Novel Dataset of Parallel Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-gender-and-racial-bias-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Following on recent advances in large language models (LLMs) and subsequent chat models, a new wave of large vision-language models (LVLMs) has emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-gender-and-racial-bias-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Contrastive Alignment of Language Models with Explicit Rewards</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-contrastive-alignment-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing alignment methods, such as Direct Preference Optimization (DPO), are mainly tailored for pairwise preference data where rewards are implicitly defined rather than explicitly given.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-contrastive-alignment-of-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sandwiched Compression: Repurposing Standard Codecs with Neural Network Wrappers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sandwiched-compression-repurposing-standard</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through a variety of examples, we apply the sandwich architecture to sources with different numbers of channels, higher resolution, higher dynamic range, and perceptual distortion measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sandwiched-compression-repurposing-standard</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Need One Color Space: An Efficient Network for Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-need-one-color-space-an-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we design a novel Color and Intensity Decoupling Network (CIDNet) with two branches dedicated to processing the decoupled image brightness and color in the HVI space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-need-one-color-space-an-efficient</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
