<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 09:16:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Semantic-Guided Image Smoothing Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-semantic-guided-image-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image smoothing is a fundamental low-level vision task that aims to preserve salient structures of an image while removing insignificant details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-semantic-guided-image-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Aligned Simple German Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-aligned-simple-german-corpus</link>
      <description><![CDATA["Leichte Sprache", the German counterpart to Simple English, is a regulated language aiming to facilitate complex written language that would otherwise stay inaccessible to different groups of people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-aligned-simple-german-corpus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact-Tolerant Clustering-Guided Contrastive Embedding Learning for Ophthalmic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-tolerant-clustering-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ophthalmic images and derivatives such as the retinal nerve fiber layer (RNFL) thickness map are crucial for detecting and monitoring ophthalmic diseases (e. g., glaucoma).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-tolerant-clustering-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-Preserving Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-graph-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel Structure-Preserving Graph Representation Learning (SPGRL) method, to fully capture the structure information of graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-graph-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"More Than Words": Linking Music Preferences and Moral Values Through Lyrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-than-words-linking-music-preferences-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the association between music preferences and moral values by applying text analysis techniques to lyrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/more-than-words-linking-music-preferences-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-modal Contrastive Representation Learning for Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-contrastive-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal entity alignment aims to identify equivalent entities between two different multi-modal knowledge graphs, which consist of structural triples and images associated with entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-contrastive-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Pretrained Biochemical Language Models for Targeted Drug Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pretrained-biochemical-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, large amounts of unlabeled protein sequences and chemical compounds are available and have been used to train language models that learn useful representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pretrained-biochemical-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighborhood-aware Scalable Temporal Network Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighborhood-aware-scalable-temporal-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a temporal network, the joint neighborhood of a set of nodes often provides crucial structural information on predicting whether they may interact at a certain time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neighborhood-aware-scalable-temporal-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Learning Stages and Accuracy-Efficiency Tradeoff of Restricted Boltzmann Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-learning-stages-and-accuracy-efficiency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Restricted Boltzmann Machines (RBMs) offer a versatile architecture for unsupervised machine learning that can in principle approximate any target probability distribution with arbitrary accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/three-learning-stages-and-accuracy-efficiency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exact Decomposition of Quantum Channels for Non-IID Quantum Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-decomposition-of-quantum-channels-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning refers to the task of performing machine learning with decentralized data from multiple clients while protecting data security and privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exact-decomposition-of-quantum-channels-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time 3D Single Object Tracking with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-3d-single-object-tracking-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PTT module in the voting stage could model the interactions among point patches, which learns context-dependent features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-3d-single-object-tracking-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nnOOD: A Framework for Benchmarking Self-supervised Anomaly Localisation Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnood-a-framework-for-benchmarking-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is also difficult to assess whether a task generalises well for universal anomaly detection, as they are often only tested on a limited range of anomalies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nnood-a-framework-for-benchmarking-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiducial Marker Detection in Multi-Viewpoint Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fiducial-marker-detection-in-multi-viewpoint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Especially, LiDARTag requires a specific marker placement and Intensity Image-based LiDAR Fiducial Marker demands that the point cloud is sampled from one viewpoint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fiducial-marker-detection-in-multi-viewpoint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOLIO: Natural Language Reasoning with First-Order Logic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/folio-natural-language-reasoning-with-first</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present FOLIO, a human-annotated, open-domain, and logically complex and diverse dataset for reasoning in natural language (NL), equipped with first order logic (FOL) annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/folio-natural-language-reasoning-with-first</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Adaptation from Scratch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-from-scratch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this setup, we aim to efficiently annotate data from a set of source domains such that the trained model performs well on a sensitive target domain from which data is unavailable for annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-adaptation-from-scratch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural Bias for Aspect Sentiment Triplet Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-bias-for-aspect-sentiment-triplet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, a natural question arises: Is structural bias still a necessity in the context of PLMs?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-bias-for-aspect-sentiment-triplet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STDEN: Towards Physics-Guided Neural Networks for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stden-towards-physics-guided-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-performance traffic flow prediction model designing, a core technology of Intelligent Transportation System, is a long-standing but still challenging task for industrial and academic communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stden-towards-physics-guided-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hidden Author Bias in Book Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-author-bias-in-book-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that popular books are mainly written by US citizens in the dataset, and that these books tend to be recommended disproportionally by popular collaborative filtering algorithms compared to the users' profiles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hidden-author-bias-in-book-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Tree Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-tree-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous graph neural networks (HGNNs) have attracted increasing research interest in recent three years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-tree-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Imaging Projection Cloud Scattering Tomography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-imaging-projection-cloud-scattering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper is the first to demonstrate CT of a real cloud using empirical data directly in a DNN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-imaging-projection-cloud-scattering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning correspondences of cardiac motion from images using biomechanics-informed modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-correspondences-of-cardiac-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning spatial-temporal correspondences in cardiac motion from images is important for understanding the underlying dynamics of cardiac anatomical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-correspondences-of-cardiac-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-Guided Curriculum Learning for Spoken Video Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-guided-curriculum-learning-for-spoken</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To rectify the discriminative phonemes and extract video-related information from noisy audio, we develop a novel video-guided curriculum learning (VGCL) during the audio pre-training process, which can make use of the vital visual perceptions to help understand the spoken language and suppress the external noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-guided-curriculum-learning-for-spoken</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi Camera Unsupervised Domain Adaptation Pipeline for Object Detection in Cultural Sites through Adversarial Learning and Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection algorithms allow to enable many interesting applications which can be implemented in different devices, such as smartphones and wearable devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-camera-unsupervised-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensembling Neural Networks for Improved Prediction and Privacy in Early Diagnosis of Sepsis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-neural-networks-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ensembling neural networks is a long-standing technique for improving the generalization error of neural networks by combining networks with orthogonal properties via a committee decision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-neural-networks-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProCo: Prototype-aware Contrastive Learning for Long-tailed Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proco-prototype-aware-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The overall framework, namely as Prototype-aware Contrastive learning (ProCo), is unified as a single-stage pipeline in an end-to-end manner to alleviate the imbalanced problem in medical image classification, which is also a distinct progress than existing works as they follow the traditional two-stage pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proco-prototype-aware-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointCLM: A Contrastive Learning-based Framework for Multi-instance Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointclm-a-contrastive-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-instance point cloud registration is the problem of estimating multiple poses of source point cloud instances within a target point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointclm-a-contrastive-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-Channel Next POI Recommendation Framework with Multi-Granularity Check-in Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-channel-next-poi-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being equipped with three modules (i. e., global user behavior encoder, local multi-channel encoder, and region-aware weighting strategy), MCMG is capable of capturing both fine- and coarse-grained sequential regularities as well as exploring the dynamic impact of multi-channel by differentiating the region check-in patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-channel-next-poi-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SketchBetween: Video-to-Video Synthesis for Sprite Animation via Sketches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketchbetween-video-to-video-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a problem formulation that more closely adheres to the standard workflow of animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sketchbetween-video-to-video-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Neural Process Family: Survey, Applications and Perspectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-neural-process-family-survey-applications</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We shed light on their potential to bring several recent advances in other deep learning domains under one umbrella.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-neural-process-family-survey-applications</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negation detection in Dutch clinical texts: an evaluation of rule-based and machine learning methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negation-detection-in-dutch-clinical-texts-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As structured data are often insufficient, labels need to be extracted from free text in electronic health records when developing models for clinical information retrieval and decision support systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/negation-detection-in-dutch-clinical-texts-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Models and Benchmarks for Representation Learning of Partially Observed Subgraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/models-and-benchmarks-for-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subgraphs are rich substructures in graphs, and their nodes and edges can be partially observed in real-world tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/models-and-benchmarks-for-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed MTA-UNet: Prediction of Thermal Stress and Thermal Deformation of Satellites</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-mta-unet-prediction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid analysis of thermal stress and deformation plays a pivotal role in the thermal control measures and optimization of the structural design of satellites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-mta-unet-prediction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Transferable Multi-stage Model with Cycling Discrepancy Learning for Lithium-ion Battery State of Health Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transferable-multi-stage-model-with-cycling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A transferable multi-stage SOH estimation model is proposed to perform TL across batteries in the same stage, consisting of four steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-transferable-multi-stage-model-with-cycling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HistoSeg : Quick attention with multi-loss function for multi-structure segmentation in digital histology images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histoseg-quick-attention-with-multi-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation assists in computer-aided diagnosis, surgeries, and treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histoseg-quick-attention-with-multi-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemSegDepth: A Combined Model for Semantic Segmentation and Depth Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semsegdepth-a-combined-model-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Holistic scene understanding is pivotal for the performance of autonomous machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semsegdepth-a-combined-model-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers are Sample Efficient World Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-sample-efficient-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning agents are notoriously sample inefficient, which considerably limits their application to real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-sample-efficient-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Chemical Space Exploration Using Active Learning Based on Marginalized Graph Kernel: an Application for Predicting the Thermodynamic Properties of Alkanes with Molecular Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-chemical-space-exploration-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an explorative active learning (AL) algorithm based on Gaussian process regression and marginalized graph kernel (GPR-MGK) to explore chemical space with minimum cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-chemical-space-exploration-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hermes: Accelerating Long-Latency Load Requests via Perceptron-Based Off-Chip Load Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-accelerating-long-latency-load</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a new technique called Hermes, whose key idea is to: 1) accurately predict which load requests might go off-chip, and 2) speculatively fetch the data required by the predicted off-chip loads directly from the main memory, while also concurrently accessing the cache hierarchy for such loads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hermes-accelerating-long-latency-load</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AccoMontage2: A Complete Harmonization and Accompaniment Arrangement System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accomontage2-a-complete-harmonization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose AccoMontage2, a system capable of doing full-length song harmonization and accompaniment arrangement based on a lead melody.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accomontage2-a-complete-harmonization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Prioritized Experience Replay</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actor-prioritized-experience-replay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A widely-studied deep reinforcement learning (RL) technique known as Prioritized Experience Replay (PER) allows agents to learn from transitions sampled with non-uniform probability proportional to their temporal-difference (TD) error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actor-prioritized-experience-replay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holomorphic Equilibrium Propagation Computes Exact Gradients Through Finite Size Oscillations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holomorphic-equilibrium-propagation-computes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equilibrium propagation (EP) is an alternative to backpropagation (BP) that allows the training of deep neural networks with local learning rules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holomorphic-equilibrium-propagation-computes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Sparse Conformer for Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-sparse-conformer-for-speech-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A deep normalization strategy is utilized when performing residual connections to ensure our training of hundred-level Conformer blocks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-sparse-conformer-for-speech-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Pretraining for 2D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-2d-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we elaborate and analyse the effectiveness of supervised and self-supervised pretraining approaches on downstream medical image segmentation, focusing on convergence and data efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-2d-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataset for Detecting Real-World Environmental Claims</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-detecting-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce an expert-annotated dataset for detecting real-world environmental claims made by listed companies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-detecting-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audiogram Digitization Tool for Audiological Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogram-digitization-tool-for-audiological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A number of private and public insurers compensate workers whose hearing loss can be directly attributed to excessive exposure to noise in the workplace.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audiogram-digitization-tool-for-audiological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2BiVQA: Double Bi-LSTM based Video Quality Assessment of UGC Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2bivqa-double-bi-lstm-based-video-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the growing popularity of mobile devices as well as video sharing platforms (e. g., YouTube, Facebook, TikTok, and Twitch), User-Generated Content (UGC) videos have become increasingly common and now account for a large portion of multimedia traffic on the internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2bivqa-double-bi-lstm-based-video-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contextualized language models for semantic change detection: lessons learned</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualized-language-models-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that contextualized methods can often predict high change scores for words which are not undergoing any real diachronic semantic shift in the lexicographic sense of the term (or at least the status of these shifts is questionable).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextualized-language-models-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stationary Kernels and Gaussian Processes on Lie Groups and their Homogeneous Spaces I: the Compact Case</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stationary-kernels-and-gaussian-processes-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The invariance of a Gaussian process' covariance to such symmetries gives rise to the most natural generalization of the concept of stationarity to such spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stationary-kernels-and-gaussian-processes-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-Space NeRF: Learning Animatable Avatars and Scene Lighting in Separate Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-nerf-learning-animatable-avatars</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous methods alleviate the inconsistency of lighting by learning a per-frame embedding, but this operation does not generalize to unseen poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-space-nerf-learning-animatable-avatars</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARMA Cell: A Modular and Effective Approach for Neural Autoregressive Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arma-cell-a-modular-and-effective-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce the ARMA cell, a simpler, modular, and effective approach for time series modeling in neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arma-cell-a-modular-and-effective-approach</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
