<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 21:08:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Quantum Creep In: Designing Quantum Neural Network Models by Gradually Swapping Out Classical Components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-quantum-creep-in-designing-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To provide a more fine-grained characterisation of the impact of quantum components on the performance of neural networks, we propose a framework where classical neural network layers are gradually replaced by quantum layers that have the same type of input and output while keeping the flow of information between layers unchanged, different from most current research in quantum neural network, which favours an end-to-end quantum model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-quantum-creep-in-designing-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving logical and functional dependencies in synthetic tabular data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-logical-and-functional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the existing notion of functional dependencies, we introduce the notion of logical dependencies among the attributes in this article.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-logical-and-functional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Banking Dataset: Understanding Client Needs through Event Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-banking-dataset-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Financial organizations collect a huge amount of data about clients that typically has a temporal (sequential) structure and is collected from various sources (modalities).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-banking-dataset-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Shortest Plank: Vulnerability-Aware Adversarial Training for Robust Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-shortest-plank-vulnerability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging these insights, we introduce the Vulnerability-aware Adversarial Training (VAT), designed to defend against poisoning attacks in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-shortest-plank-vulnerability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explanation Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-bottleneck-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent concept-based interpretable models have succeeded in providing meaningful explanations by pre-defined concept sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explanation-bottleneck-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightAvatar: Efficient Head Avatar as Dynamic Neural Light Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightavatar-efficient-head-avatar-as-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have shown that neural radiance fields (NeRFs) on top of parametric models have reached SOTA quality to build photorealistic head avatars from a monocular video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightavatar-efficient-head-avatar-as-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowTurbo: Towards Real-time Flow-Based Image Generation with Velocity Refiner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowturbo-towards-real-time-flow-based-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating FlowTurbo into different flow-based models, we obtain an acceleration ratio of 53. 1%$\sim$58. 3% on class-conditional generation and 29. 8%$\sim$38. 5% on text-to-image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowturbo-towards-real-time-flow-based-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting Affect Aggregates from Longitudinal Social Media Data with Temporal Adapters for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-affect-aggregates-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work enables new approaches towards the longitudinal analysis of social media data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extracting-affect-aggregates-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisit Anything: Visual Place Recognition via Image Segment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-anything-visual-place-recognition-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This poses a fundamental challenge in matching two images of the same place captured from different camera viewpoints: "the similarity of what overlaps can be dominated by the dissimilarity of what does not overlap".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-anything-visual-place-recognition-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Deep Ensemble Uncertainty for Enhanced Medical Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-ensemble-uncertainty-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we propose D2UE, a Diversified Dual-space Uncertainty Estimation framework for medical anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-deep-ensemble-uncertainty-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E.T. Bench: Towards Open-Ended Event-Level Video-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-t-bench-towards-open-ended-event-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bench (Event-Level & Time-Sensitive Video Understanding Benchmark), a large-scale and high-quality benchmark for open-ended event-level video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-t-bench-towards-open-ended-event-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-intensity knowledge distillation for robust medical image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-intensity-knowledge-distillation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to incorporate joint shape-intensity prior information into the segmentation network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-intensity-knowledge-distillation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Control Industrial Automation System with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-industrial-automation-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a framework for integrating LLMs to achieve end-to-end control of industrial automation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/control-industrial-automation-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototype based Masked Audio Model for Self-Supervised Learning of Sound Event Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-masked-audio-model-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant challenge in sound event detection (SED) is the effective utilization of unlabeled data, given the limited availability of labeled data due to high annotation costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototype-based-masked-audio-model-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Modeling of Molecular Dynamics Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-molecular-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce generative modeling of molecular trajectories as a paradigm for learning flexible multi-task surrogate models of MD from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-of-molecular-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskLLM: Learnable Semi-Structured Sparsity for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskllm-learnable-semi-structured-sparsity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach facilitates end-to-end training on large-scale datasets and offers two notable advantages: 1) High-quality Masks - our method effectively scales to large datasets and learns accurate masks; 2) Transferability - the probabilistic modeling of mask distribution enables the transfer learning of sparsity across domains or tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maskllm-learnable-semi-structured-sparsity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Open-Set Domain Generalization Using Evidential Bi-Level Hardest Domain Scheduler</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-open-set-domain-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe that an adaptive domain scheduler benefits more in OSDG compared with prefixed sequential and random domain schedulers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-open-set-domain-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGN: The RNN's New Successor is Effective for Long-Range Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgn-the-rnn-s-new-successor-is-effective-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The other branch employs patches to capture short-term information and aggregate the global representation of the series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgn-the-rnn-s-new-successor-is-effective-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DarkSAM: Fooling Segment Anything Model to Segment Nothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darksam-fooling-segment-anything-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the spatial domain, we disrupt the semantics of both the foreground and background in the image to confuse SAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/darksam-fooling-segment-anything-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting Regression Models for Conditional Uncertainty Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-regression-models-for-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal Prediction methods have finite-sample distribution-free marginal coverage guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adjusting-regression-models-for-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Hierarchy and Temporal Attention Guided Cross Masking for Self-supervised Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-hierarchy-and-temporal-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In self-supervised skeleton-based action recognition, the mask reconstruction paradigm is gaining interest in enhancing model refinement and robustness through effective masking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-hierarchy-and-temporal-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Pretraining for Cardiovascular Magnetic Resonance Cine Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, short-axis cine stacks of 296 subjects (90618 2D slices) were used for unlabeled pretraining with four SSP methods; SimCLR, positional contrastive learning, DINO, and masked image modeling (MIM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-pretraining-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Rhinos without Finding Rhinos: Active Learning with Multimodal Imagery of South African Rhino Habitats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/find-rhinos-without-finding-rhinos-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much of Earth's charismatic megafauna is endangered by human activities, particularly the rhino, which is at risk of extinction due to the poaching crisis in Africa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/find-rhinos-without-finding-rhinos-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Preference Optimization: Enhance Your Language Model with Preference Degree Awareness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-preference-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there has been significant interest in replacing the reward model in Reinforcement Learning with Human Feedback (RLHF) methods for Large Language Models (LLMs), such as Direct Preference Optimization (DPO) and its variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-preference-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Proportion Detection for Optimized Data Management for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-proportion-detection-for-optimized-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated exceptional performance across a wide range of tasks and domains, with data preparation playing a critical role in achieving these results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-proportion-detection-for-optimized-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upper-Body Pose-based Gaze Estimation for Privacy-Preserving 3D Gaze Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-body-pose-based-gaze-estimation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach to tackle this problem by utilizing the person's upper-body pose and available depth maps to extract a 3D gaze direction and employing a multi-stage or an end-to-end pipeline to predict the gazed target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upper-body-pose-based-gaze-estimation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Time Series is Worth Five Experts: Heterogeneous Mixture of Experts for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-five-experts-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate traffic prediction faces significant challenges, necessitating a deep understanding of both temporal and spatial cues and their complex interactions across multiple variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-five-experts-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming Diffusion Prior for Image Super-Resolution with Domain Shift SDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-prior-for-image-super</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present DoSSR, a Domain Shift diffusion-based SR model that capitalizes on the generative powers of pretrained diffusion models while significantly enhancing efficiency by initiating the diffusion process with low-resolution (LR) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taming-diffusion-prior-for-image-super</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimVG: A Simple Framework for Visual Grounding with Decoupled Multi-modal Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvg-a-simple-framework-for-visual-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual grounding is a common vision task that involves grounding descriptive sentences to the corresponding regions of an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simvg-a-simple-framework-for-visual-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaViLS, a Benchmark Dataset for Video-to-Slide Alignment, Assessing Baseline Accuracy with a Multimodal Alignment Algorithm Leveraging Speech, OCR, and Visual Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mavils-a-benchmark-dataset-for-video-to-slide</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a benchmark dataset for aligning lecture videos with corresponding slides and introduces a novel multimodal algorithm leveraging features from speech, text, and images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mavils-a-benchmark-dataset-for-video-to-slide</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HazeSpace2M: A Dataset for Haze Aware Single Image Dehazing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hazespace2m-a-dataset-for-haze-aware-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results underscore the significance of HazeSpace2M and our proposed framework in addressing atmospheric haze in multimedia processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hazespace2m-a-dataset-for-haze-aware-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress Detection from Photoplethysmography in a Virtual Reality Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stress-detection-from-photoplethysmography-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized virtual reality exposure therapy is a therapeutic practice that can adapt to an individual patient, leading to better health outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stress-detection-from-photoplethysmography-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTQ4RIS: Post-Training Quantization for Referring Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptq4ris-post-training-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first conduct an in-depth analysis of the root causes of performance degradation in RIS model quantization and propose dual-region quantization (DRQ) and reorder-based outlier-retained quantization (RORQ) to address the quantization difficulties in visual and text encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptq4ris-post-training-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Representation Learning for Real-Time UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-representation-learning-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, PRL-Track is divided into coarse representation learning and fine representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-representation-learning-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MorphoSeg: An Uncertainty-Aware Deep Learning Method for Biomedical Segmentation of Complex Cellular Morphologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphoseg-an-uncertainty-aware-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel benchmark dataset of Ntera-2 (NT2) cells, a pluripotent carcinoma cell line, exhibiting diverse morphologies across multiple stages of differentiation, capturing the intricate and heterogeneous cellular structures that complicate segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/morphoseg-an-uncertainty-aware-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Comic Generation: Integrating Visual Narrative Theories with AI Models for Enhanced Creativity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-comic-generation-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our system combines human creativity with AI models to support parts of the generative process, providing a collaborative platform for creating comic content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-comic-generation-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitQ: Tailoring Block Floating Point Precision for Improved DNN Efficiency on Resource-Constrained Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitq-tailoring-block-floating-point-precision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) are powerful for cognitive tasks such as image classification, object detection, and scene segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitq-tailoring-block-floating-point-precision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statewide Visual Geolocalization in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statewide-visual-geolocalization-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a method that is able to predict the geolocation of a street-view photo taken in the wild within a state-sized search region by matching against a database of aerial reference imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statewide-visual-geolocalization-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model aggregation: minimizing empirical variance outperforms minimizing empirical error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-aggregation-minimizing-empirical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is non-intrusive - treating models as black-box functions - model-agnostic, requires minimal assumptions, and can combine outputs from a wide range of models, including those from machine learning and numerical solvers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-aggregation-minimizing-empirical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>data2lang2vec: Data Driven Typological Features Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data2lang2vec-data-driven-typological</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language typology databases enhance multi-lingual Natural Language Processing (NLP) by improving model adaptability to diverse linguistic structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data2lang2vec-data-driven-typological</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-trained Language Models Return Distinguishable Probability Distributions to Unfaithfully Hallucinated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-language-models-return</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show the pre-trained language models return distinguishable generation probability and uncertainty distribution to unfaithfully hallucinated texts, regardless of their size and structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-trained-language-models-return</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WasteGAN: Data Augmentation for Robotic Waste Sorting through Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wastegan-data-augmentation-for-robotic-waste</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this issue, we introduce a data augmentation method based on a novel GAN architecture called wasteGAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wastegan-data-augmentation-for-robotic-waste</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMIT- Event-Based Masked Auto Encoding for Irregular Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emit-event-based-masked-auto-encoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Irregular time series, where data points are recorded at uneven intervals, are prevalent in healthcare settings, such as emergency wards where vital signs and laboratory results are captured at varying times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emit-event-based-masked-auto-encoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Language Models to Win Debates with Self-Play Improves Judge Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-win-debates-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We test the robustness of debate as a method of scalable oversight by training models to debate with data generated via self-play.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-to-win-debates-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game4Loc: A UAV Geo-Localization Benchmark from Game Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game4loc-a-uav-geo-localization-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent deep learning based methods attribute this as the task of image matching and retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/game4loc-a-uav-geo-localization-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EventHallusion: Diagnosing Event Hallucinations in Video LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventhallusion-diagnosing-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, we also propose a simple yet effective method, called Temporal Contrastive Decoding (TCD), to tackle the hallucination problems of VideoLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventhallusion-diagnosing-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Neural Representations for Simultaneous Reduction and Continuous Reconstruction of Multi-Altitude Climate Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representations-for-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The world is moving towards clean and renewable energy sources, such as wind energy, in an attempt to reduce greenhouse gas emissions that contribute to global warming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-neural-representations-for-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General Detection-based Text Line Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-detection-based-text-line-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a general detection-based approach to text line recognition, be it printed (OCR) or handwritten (HTR), with Latin, Chinese, or ciphered characters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-detection-based-text-line-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicitly Modeling Pre-Cortical Vision with a Neuro-Inspired Front-End Improves CNN Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-modeling-pre-cortical-vision-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While convolutional neural networks (CNNs) excel at clean image classification, they struggle to classify images corrupted with different common corruptions, limiting their real-world applicability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicitly-modeling-pre-cortical-vision-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards General Text-guided Image Synthesis for Customized Multimodal Brain MRI Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-text-guided-image-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we present TUMSyn, a Text-guided Universal MR image Synthesis generalist model, which can flexibly generate brain MR images with demanded imaging metadata from routinely acquired scans guided by text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-general-text-guided-image-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
