<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 21:07:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Constructing Multilingual Code Search Dataset Using Neural Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-multilingual-code-search-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code search is a task to find programming codes that semantically match the given natural language queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constructing-multilingual-code-search-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Re] Double Sampling Randomized Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is a contribution to the reproducibility challenge in the field of machine learning, specifically addressing the issue of certifying the robustness of neural networks (NNs) against adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re-double-sampling-randomized-smoothing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Detection in Networks via Score-Based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Node outlier detection in attributed graphs is a challenging problem for which there is no method that would work well across different datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-detection-in-networks-via-score-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Annealed Importance Sampling with Constant Rate Progress</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm relies on a sequence of interpolating distributions bridging the target to an initial tractable distribution such as the well-known geometric mean path of unnormalized distributions which is assumed to be suboptimal in general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-annealed-importance-sampling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Meta-analytical Comparison of Naive Bayes and Random Forest for Software Defect Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-analytical-comparison-of-naive-bayes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conducted a systematic literature review by establishing criteria to search and choose papers, resulting in five studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-meta-analytical-comparison-of-naive-bayes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-class systems seamlessly fit in the forward-forward algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-systems-seamlessly-fit-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The forward-forward algorithm presents a new method of training neural networks by updating weights during an inference, performing parameter updates for each layer individually.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-class-systems-seamlessly-fit-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Client Reactions in Online Mental Health Counseling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-client-reactions-in-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communication success relies heavily on reading participants' reactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-client-reactions-in-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellViT: Vision Transformers for Precise Cell Segmentation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-vision-transformers-for-precise-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nuclei detection and segmentation in hematoxylin and eosin-stained (H&E) tissue images are important clinical tasks and crucial for a wide range of applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellvit-vision-transformers-for-precise-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Pseudo Future Contexts for Emotion Recognition in Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-future-contexts-for-emotion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, for an utterance, we generate its future context with pre-trained language models, potentially containing extra beneficial knowledge in a conversational form homogeneous with the historical ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-pseudo-future-contexts-for-emotion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIMIC: Masked Image Modeling with Image Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-masked-image-modeling-with-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unfortunately, the effective pretraining datasets are those with multi-view scenes and have only been curated using annotated 3D meshes, point clouds, and camera parameters from simulated environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimic-masked-image-modeling-with-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symphonize 3D Semantic Scene Completion with Contextual Instance Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symphonize-3d-semantic-scene-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the queries as the instance feature representations within the scene, Symphonies dynamically encodes the instance-centric semantics to interact with the image and volume features while avoiding the dense voxel-wise modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symphonize-3d-semantic-scene-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyBADS: Fast and robust black-box optimization in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pybads-fast-and-robust-black-box-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PyBADS is a Python implementation of the Bayesian Adaptive Direct Search (BADS) algorithm for fast and robust black-box optimization (Acerbi and Ma 2017).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pybads-fast-and-robust-black-box-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPA-v2: Scaling CLIP Training with 81.1% Zero-shot ImageNet Accuracy within a \$10,000 Budget; An Extra \$4,000 Unlocks 81.8% Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipa-v2-scaling-clip-training-with-81-1-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent work CLIPA presents an inverse scaling law for CLIP training -- whereby the larger the image/text encoders used, the shorter the sequence length of image/text tokens that can be applied in training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clipa-v2-scaling-clip-training-with-81-1-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transferability Metrics for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-metrics-for-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our experiments, we compare TLogME to state-of-the-art metrics in the estimation of transfer performance of the Faster-RCNN object detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transferability-metrics-for-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Truss Design with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-truss-design-with-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Directly applying end-to-end reinforcement learning (RL) methods to truss layout design is infeasible either, since only a tiny portion of the entire layout space is valid under the physical constraints, leading to particularly sparse rewards for RL training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-truss-design-with-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PANet: LiDAR Panoptic Segmentation with Sparse Instance Proposal and Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panet-lidar-panoptic-segmentation-with-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we propose a non-learning Sparse Instance Proposal (SIP) module with the ``sampling-shifting-grouping" scheme to directly group thing points into instances from the raw point cloud efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panet-lidar-panoptic-segmentation-with-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GroundNLQ @ Ego4D Natural Language Queries Challenge 2023</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groundnlq-ego4d-natural-language-queries</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this, we leverage a two-stage pre-training strategy to train egocentric feature extractors and the grounding model on video narrations, and further fine-tune the model on annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/groundnlq-ego4d-natural-language-queries</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShuttleSet22: Benchmarking Stroke Forecasting with Stroke-Level Badminton Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset22-benchmarking-stroke-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also hold a challenge, Track 2: Forecasting Future Turn-Based Strokes in Badminton Rallies, at CoachAI Badminton Challenge 2023 to boost researchers to tackle this problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shuttleset22-benchmarking-stroke-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KnowPrefix-Tuning: A Two-Stage Prefix-Tuning Framework for Knowledge-Grounded Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Knowledgeable Prefix Tuning (KnowPrefix-Tuning), a two-stage tuning framework, bypassing the retrieval process in a knowledge-grounded conversation system by injecting prior knowledge into the lightweight knowledge prefix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowprefix-tuning-a-two-stage-prefix-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Inferential Structure in Neural Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Processes (NPs) are appealing due to their ability to perform fast adaptation based on a context set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inferential-structure-in-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDOL: Indicator-oriented Logic Pre-training for Logical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idol-indicator-oriented-logic-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[IDOL achieves state-of-the-art performance on ReClor and LogiQA, the two most representative benchmarks in logical reasoning MRC, and is proven to be capable of generalizing to different pre-trained models and other types of MRC benchmarks like RACE and SQuAD 2. 0 while keeping competitive general language understanding ability through testing on tasks in GLUE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/idol-indicator-oriented-logic-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shikra: Unleashing Multimodal LLM's Referential Dialogue Magic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shikra-unleashing-multimodal-llm-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referential dialogue is a superset of various vision-language (VL) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shikra-unleashing-multimodal-llm-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC-RS: Elevate LiDAR Semantic Scene Completion with Representation Separation and BEV Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssc-rs-elevate-lidar-semantic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, how to effectively exploit the relationships between the semantic context in semantic segmentation and geometric structure in scene completion remains under exploration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssc-rs-elevate-lidar-semantic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D-Speaker: A Large-Scale Multi-Device, Multi-Distance, and Multi-Dialect Corpus for Speech Representation Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-speaker-a-large-scale-multi-device-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Disentangling uncorrelated information in speech utterances is a crucial research topic within speech community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-speaker-a-large-scale-multi-device-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeanDojo: Theorem Proving with Retrieval-Augmented Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leandojo-theorem-proving-with-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this data, we develop ReProver (Retrieval-Augmented Prover): the first LLM-based prover that is augmented with retrieval for selecting premises from a vast math library.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leandojo-theorem-proving-with-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Can Mask More For Extremely Low-Bitrate Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-can-mask-more-for-extremely-low-bitrate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments have demonstrated that our approach outperforms recent state-of-the-art methods in R-D performance, visual quality, and downstream applications, at very low bitrates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-can-mask-more-for-extremely-low-bitrate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube-ASL: A Large-Scale, Open-Domain American Sign Language-English Parallel Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/youtube-asl-a-large-scale-open-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning for sign languages is bottlenecked by data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/youtube-asl-a-large-scale-open-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCID: Deep Canonical Information Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Canonical Correlation Analysis (CCA)-based methods have traditionally been used to identify shared variables, however, they were designed for multivariate targets and only offer trivial solutions for univariate cases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcid-deep-canonical-information-decomposition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a MESS: Multi-Domain Evaluation of Zero-Shot Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-a-mess-multi-domain-evaluation-of-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, zero-shot semantic segmentation makes use of large self-supervised vision-language models, allowing zero-shot transfer to unseen classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-a-mess-multi-domain-evaluation-of-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Annotation of Direct Speech in Written French Narratives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automatic annotation of direct speech (AADS) in written text has been often used in computational narrative understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-annotation-of-direct-speech-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating counterfactuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-counterfactuals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual inference considers a hypothetical intervention in a parallel world that shares some evidence with the factual world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-counterfactuals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Component Separation for Targeted Signal Recovery in Noisy Mixtures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-component-separation-for-targeted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the case of 1), we show that our method better recovers the descriptors of the target data than a standard denoising method in most situations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-component-separation-for-targeted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art of Embedding Fusion: Optimizing Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-art-of-embedding-fusion-optimizing-hate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hate speech detection is a challenging natural language processing task that requires capturing linguistic and contextual nuances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-art-of-embedding-fusion-optimizing-hate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond dynamic programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-dynamic-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of our approach by applying it to nonlinear optimal control problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-dynamic-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontology Enrichment from Texts: A Biomedical Dataset for Concept Discovery and Placement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-enrichment-from-texts-a-biomedical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mentions of new concepts appear regularly in texts and require automated approaches to harvest and place them into Knowledge Bases (KB), e. g., ontologies and taxonomies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-enrichment-from-texts-a-biomedical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Query Network for Multi-Modal Product Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-query-network-for-multi-modal-product</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Product image segmentation is vital in e-commerce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-query-network-for-multi-modal-product</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Effective Baseline for Attentional Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-baseline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthesising a text-to-image model of high-quality images by guiding the generative model through the Text description is an innovative and challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-effective-baseline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-Device Evaluation Toolkit for Machine Learning on Heterogeneous Low-Power System-on-Chip</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-device-evaluation-toolkit-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide an open source implementation of U-TOE and we demonstrate its use to experimentally evaluate the performance of a wide variety of models, on a wide variety of low-power boards, based on popular microcontroller architectures (ARM Cortex-M and RISC-V).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-device-evaluation-toolkit-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SugarCrepe: Fixing Hackable Benchmarks for Vision-Language Compositionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sugarcrepe-fixing-hackable-benchmarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the last year alone, a surge of new benchmarks to measure compositional understanding of vision-language models have permeated the machine learning ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sugarcrepe-fixing-hackable-benchmarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Modulate pre-trained Models in RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-modulate-pre-trained-models-in-rl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, fine-tuning a pre-trained model often suffers from catastrophic forgetting, that is, the performance on the pre-training tasks deteriorates when fine-tuning on new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-modulate-pre-trained-models-in-rl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn over Past, Evolve for Future: Forecasting Temporal Trends for Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-over-past-evolve-for-future-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we observe that the appearances of news events on the same topic may display discernible patterns over time, and posit that such patterns can assist in selecting training instances that could make the model adapt better to future data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-over-past-evolve-for-future-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How About Kind of Generating Hedges using End-to-End Neural Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-about-kind-of-generating-hedges-using-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hedging is a strategy for softening the impact of a statement in conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-about-kind-of-generating-hedges-using-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PTVD: A Large-Scale Plot-Oriented Multimodal Dataset Based on Television Dramas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptvd-a-large-scale-plot-oriented-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Art forms such as movies and television (TV) dramas are reflections of the real world, which have attracted much attention from the multimodal learning community recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ptvd-a-large-scale-plot-oriented-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CST-YOLO: A Novel Method for Blood Cell Detection Based on Improved YOLOv7 and CNN-Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst-yolo-a-novel-method-for-blood-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Blood cell detection is a typical small-scale object detection problem in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cst-yolo-a-novel-method-for-blood-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Item-attribute Graph Pre-training for Strict Cold-start Item Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-item-attribute-graph-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the role of the fine-grained item attributes in bridging the gaps between the existing and the SCS items and pre-train a knowledgeable item-attribute graph for SCS item recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-item-attribute-graph-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FunQA: Towards Surprising Video Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funqa-towards-surprising-video-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprising videos, e. g., funny clips, creative performances, or visual illusions, attract significant attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funqa-towards-surprising-video-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Sparsification of Brain Graphs: Better Practices and Effective Designs for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-sparsification-of-brain-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these insights, we propose a new model, Interpretable Graph Sparsification (IGS), which enhances graph classification performance by up to 5. 1% with 55. 0% fewer edges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-sparsification-of-brain-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video object detection for privacy-preserving patient monitoring in intensive care</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-object-detection-for-privacy-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new method for exploiting information in the temporal succession of video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-object-detection-for-privacy-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design from Policies: Conservative Test-Time Adaptation for Offline Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-from-policies-conservative-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Naturally, such a paradigm raises three core questions that are \textit{not} fully answered by prior non-iterative offline RL counterparts like reward-conditioned policy: Q1) What information should we transfer from the inner-level to the outer-level?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/design-from-policies-conservative-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Scalable Unpaired Image Translation via Latent Space Anchoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-scalable-unpaired-image-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, given a UNIT model trained on certain domains, it is difficult for current methods to incorporate new domains because they often need to train the full model on both existing and new domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-scalable-unpaired-image-translation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
