<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 21:05:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>K-Planes: Explicit Radiance Fields in Space, Time, and Appearance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-planes-explicit-radiance-fields-in-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce k-planes, a white-box model for radiance fields in arbitrary dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-planes-explicit-radiance-fields-in-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a Waffle Iron for Automotive Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-waffle-iron-for-automotive-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation of point clouds in autonomous driving datasets requires techniques that can process large numbers of points over large field of views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-a-waffle-iron-for-automotive-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WEASEL 2.0 -- A Random Dilated Dictionary Transform for Fast, Accurate and Memory Constrained Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weasel-2-0-a-random-dilated-dictionary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series classification (TSC) is the task of assigning a time series to one of a set of predefined classes, usually based on a model learned from examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weasel-2-0-a-random-dilated-dictionary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model soups to increase inference without increasing compute time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-soups-to-increase-inference-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we compare Model Soups performances on three different models (ResNet, ViT and EfficientNet) using three Soup Recipes (Greedy Soup Sorted, Greedy Soup Random and Uniform soup) from arXiv:2203. 05482, and reproduce the results of the authors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-soups-to-increase-inference-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Constrained Reinforcement Learning for Dexterous Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-reinforcement-learning-for-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A potential way to address these limitations is to add constraints during learning that restrict and guide the robot's behavior during training as well as roll outs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/constrained-reinforcement-learning-for-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Agnostic Sample Reweighting for Out-of-Distribution Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-sample-reweighting-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The overfitting issue is addressed by considering a bilevel formulation to search for the sample reweighting, in which the generalization complexity depends on the search space of sample weights instead of the model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-sample-reweighting-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planar Object Tracking via Weighted Optical Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planar-object-tracking-via-weighted-optical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose WOFT -- a novel method for planar object tracking that estimates a full 8 degrees-of-freedom pose, i. e. the homography w. r. t.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planar-object-tracking-via-weighted-optical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffMotion: Speech-Driven Gesture Synthesis Using Denoising Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmotion-speech-driven-gesture-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech-driven gesture synthesis is a field of growing interest in virtual human creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffmotion-speech-driven-gesture-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LDMIC: Learning-based Distributed Multi-view Image Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ldmic-learning-based-distributed-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-view image compression plays a critical role in 3D-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ldmic-learning-based-distributed-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Distillation for Semi-Supervised Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-distillation-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a model well-trained with a large-scale base dataset, Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning (FSCIL) aims at incrementally learning novel classes from a few labeled samples by avoiding overfitting, without catastrophically forgetting all encountered classes previously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-distillation-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RD-NAS: Enhancing One-shot Supernet Ranking Ability via Ranking Distillation from Zero-cost Proxies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rd-nas-enhancing-one-shot-supernet-ranking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Ranking Distillation one-shot NAS (RD-NAS) to enhance ranking consistency, which utilizes zero-cost proxies as the cheap teacher and adopts the margin ranking loss to distill the ranking knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rd-nas-enhancing-one-shot-supernet-ranking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Augmentation Alone Can Improve Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-alone-can-improve</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation, which is effective at preventing overfitting in standard training, has been observed by many previous works to be ineffective in mitigating overfitting in adversarial training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-augmentation-alone-can-improve</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Super-Resolution using Efficient Striped Window Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-using-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further exploit the potential of the transformer, we propose a novel flexible window training strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-super-resolution-using-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting the 2016-2017 Central Apennines Earthquake Sequence with a Neural Point Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-the-2016-2017-central-apennines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate whether these flexible point process models can be applied to short-term seismicity forecasting by extending an existing temporal neural model to the magnitude domain and we show how this model can forecast earthquakes above a target magnitude threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-the-2016-2017-central-apennines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Interactive Lung Lesion Segmentation: A Framework for Annotating PET/CT Images based on Physiological and Anatomical Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interactive-lung-lesion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, deep learning enabled the accurate segmentation of various diseases in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-interactive-lung-lesion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Patcher: One Mistake worth One Neuron</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-patcher-one-mistake-worth-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method outperforms previous fine-tuning and HyperNetwork-based methods and achieves state-of-the-art performance for Sequential Model Editing (SME).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-patcher-one-mistake-worth-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Adaptive Unfolding Network for Hyperspectral Image Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-adaptive-unfolding-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a simple, efficient, and scalable unfolding network, SAUNet, to simplify the network design with an adaptive alternate optimization framework for hyperspectral image (HSI) reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-adaptive-unfolding-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-based method for segmenting epithelial layer of tubules in histopathological images of testicular tissue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-method-for-segmenting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pretrained ResNet-34 in the encoder and attention block suggested in the decoder result in better segmentation and generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-method-for-segmenting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleGAN-T: Unlocking the Power of GANs for Fast Large-Scale Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylegan-t-unlocking-the-power-of-gans-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image synthesis has recently seen significant progress thanks to large pretrained language models, large-scale training data, and the introduction of scalable model families such as diffusion and autoregressive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylegan-t-unlocking-the-power-of-gans-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimising Event-Driven Spiking Neural Network with Regularisation and Cutoff</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-event-driven-spiking-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two novel optimisation techniques are presented to achieve AOI-SNNs: a regularisation and a cutoff.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-event-driven-spiking-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WDC Products: A Multi-Dimensional Entity Matching Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wdc-products-a-multi-dimensional-entity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The difficulty of an entity matching task depends on a combination of multiple factors such as the amount of corner-case pairs, the fraction of entities in the test set that have not been seen during training, and the size of the development set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wdc-products-a-multi-dimensional-entity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoder-based Joint Communication and Sensing of Multiple Targets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-joint-communication-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foremost, we develop a suitable encoding scheme for the training of the AE and for targeting a fixed false alarm rate of the target detection during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoencoder-based-joint-communication-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Mean Discrepancy Kernels for Predictive and Prognostic Modeling of Whole Slide Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-mean-discrepancy-kernels-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How similar are two images?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximum-mean-discrepancy-kernels-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Active 3D Object Detection from a Generalization Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-active-3d-object-detection-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate the high annotation cost in LiDAR-based 3D object detection, active learning is a promising solution that learns to select only a small portion of unlabeled data to annotate, without compromising model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-active-3d-object-detection-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StockEmotions: Discover Investor Emotions for Financial Sentiment Analysis and Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stockemotions-discover-investor-emotions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There has been growing interest in applying NLP techniques in the financial domain, however, resources are extremely limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stockemotions-discover-investor-emotions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prediction-Powered Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-powered-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce prediction-powered inference $\unicode{x2013}$ a framework for performing valid statistical inference when an experimental data set is supplemented with predictions from a machine-learning system such as AlphaFold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prediction-powered-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensemaking About Contraceptive Methods Across Online Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensemaking-about-contraceptive-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selecting a birth control method is a complex healthcare decision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensemaking-about-contraceptive-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Non-deterministic Human Behaviors in Discrete Food Choices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-deterministic-human-behaviors-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We establish a non-deterministic model that predicts a user's food preferences from their demographic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-non-deterministic-human-behaviors-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Expressive Power of Geometric Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-geometric-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The expressive power of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) has been studied extensively through the Weisfeiler-Leman (WL) graph isomorphism test.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-expressive-power-of-geometric-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triplet Contrastive Learning for Unsupervised Vehicle Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-contrastive-learning-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the inter-class instance, a hybrid contrastive loss (HCL) re-defines the sample correlations by approaching the positive cluster features and leaving the all negative instance features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-contrastive-learning-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ddml: Double/debiased machine learning in Stata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddml-double-debiased-machine-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the package ddml for Double/Debiased Machine Learning (DDML) in Stata.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddml-double-debiased-machine-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-tail Detection with Effective Class-Margins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tail-detection-with-effective-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale object detection and instance segmentation face a severe data imbalance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tail-detection-with-effective-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully transformer-based biomarker prediction from colorectal cancer histology: a large-scale multicentric study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-transformer-based-biomarker-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: In this study, we developed a new fully transformer-based pipeline for end-to-end biomarker prediction from pathology slides.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-transformer-based-biomarker-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Training Under Limited Resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-under-limited-resources</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training time budget and size of the dataset are among the factors affecting the performance of a Deep Neural Network (DNN).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-under-limited-resources</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Injecting the BM25 Score as Text Improves BERT-Based Re-rankers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecting-the-bm25-score-as-text-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we propose a novel approach for combining first-stage lexical retrieval models and Transformer-based re-rankers: we inject the relevance score of the lexical model as a token in the middle of the input of the cross-encoder re-ranker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/injecting-the-bm25-score-as-text-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRIMEQA: The Prime Repository for State-of-the-Art MultilingualQuestion Answering Research and Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primeqa-the-prime-repository-for-state-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of Question Answering (QA) has made remarkable progress in recent years, thanks to the advent of large pre-trained language models, newer realistic benchmark datasets with leaderboards, and novel algorithms for key components such as retrievers and readers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/primeqa-the-prime-repository-for-state-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexi: Self-Supervised Learning of the UI Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexi-self-supervised-learning-of-the-ui</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along with text, these resources include visual content such as UI screenshots and images of application icons referenced in the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexi-self-supervised-learning-of-the-ui</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Data Selection for TTS: Using Arabic Broadcast News as a Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-data-selection-for-tts-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Several high-resource Text to Speech (TTS) systems currently produce natural, well-established human-like speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-data-selection-for-tts-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bidirectional Propagation for Cross-Modal 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-propagation-for-cross-modal-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have revealed the superiority of feature-level fusion for cross-modal 3D object detection, where fine-grained feature propagation from 2D image pixels to 3D LiDAR points has been widely adopted for performance improvement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bidirectional-propagation-for-cross-modal-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champion Solution for the WSDM2023 Toloka VQA Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/champion-solution-for-the-wsdm2023-toloka-vqa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present our champion solution to the WSDM2023 Toloka Visual Question Answering (VQA) Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/champion-solution-for-the-wsdm2023-toloka-vqa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPEC5G: A Dataset for 5G Cellular Network Protocol Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec5g-a-dataset-for-5g-cellular-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[5G is the 5th generation cellular network protocol.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spec5g-a-dataset-for-5g-cellular-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing the Cloze Task in Sequential Recommendation with Bidirectional Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-the-cloze-task-in-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most common approach to mitigating exposure bias in recommendation has been Inverse Propensity Scoring (IPS), which consists of down-weighting the interacted predictions in the loss function in proportion to their propensities of exposure, yielding a theoretically unbiased learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-the-cloze-task-in-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Metrics to Measure Representational Harms in Pre-Trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-metrics-to-measure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale Pre-Trained Language Models (PTLMs) capture knowledge from massive human-written data which contains latent societal biases and toxic contents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-metrics-to-measure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy Prediction using Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-prediction-using-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we demonstrate the viability of using federated learning to successfully predict energy consumption as well as solar production for all households within a certain network using low-power and low-space consuming embedded devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-prediction-using-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LF-checker: Machine Learning Acceleration of Bounded Model Checking for Concurrency Verification (Competition Contribution)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lf-checker-machine-learning-acceleration-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe and evaluate LF-checker, a metaverifier tool based on machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lf-checker-machine-learning-acceleration-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propagation of Linear Uncertainties through Multiline Thru-Reflect-Line Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagation-of-linear-uncertainties-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a linear approach for propagating uncertainties in the multiline thru-reflect-line (TRL) calibration method for vector network analyzers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagation-of-linear-uncertainties-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-Supervised Questions for Zero-Shot Relation Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-questions-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-Shot Relation Extraction (ZRE) is the task of Relation Extraction where the training and test sets have no shared relation types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-questions-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adapting a Language Model While Preserving its General Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-a-language-model-while-preserving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper shows that the existing methods are suboptimal and proposes a novel method to perform a more informed adaptation of the knowledge in the LM by (1) soft-masking the attention heads based on their importance to best preserve the general knowledge in the LM and (2) contrasting the representations of the general and the full (both general and domain knowledge) to learn an integrated representation with both general and domain-specific knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapting-a-language-model-while-preserving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Deep Regression with Ordinal Entropy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-deep-regression-with-ordinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In computer vision, it is often observed that formulating regression problems as a classification task often yields better performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-deep-regression-with-ordinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tier Balancing: Towards Dynamic Fairness over Underlying Causal Factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-balancing-towards-dynamic-fairness-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pursuit of long-term fairness involves the interplay between decision-making and the underlying data generating process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tier-balancing-towards-dynamic-fairness-over</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
