<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 09:15:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying Emergence in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-emergence-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results show that (1) our method gives consistent measurements which align with existing observations based on performance metrics, validating the effectiveness of our emergence quantification; (2) our proposed metric uncovers novel emergence patterns such as the correlations between the variance of our metric and the number of ``shots'' in ICL, which further suggests a new way of interpreting hallucinations in LLMs; (3) we offer a potential solution towards estimating the emergence of larger and closed-resource LMs via smaller LMs like GPT-2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-emergence-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of cosmological likelihood-based inference: accelerated high-dimensional parameter estimation and model comparison</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-future-of-cosmological-likelihood-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standard nested sampling techniques are simply not feasible in this high-dimensional setting, requiring a projected 12 years of compute time on 48 CPU cores; on the other hand, the proposed approach only requires 8 days of compute time on 24 GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-future-of-cosmological-likelihood-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPL: Empirical Prototype Learning for Deep Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epl-empirical-prototype-learning-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When the prototypes are updated using the facial sample feature gradients in the model training, they are prone to being pulled away from the class center by the hard samples, resulting in decreased overall model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epl-empirical-prototype-learning-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SirLLM: Streaming Infinite Retentive LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sirllm-streaming-infinite-retentive-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the one-off input of overly long texts is limited, as studies have shown that when input lengths exceed the LLMs' pre-trained text length, there is a dramatic decline in text generation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sirllm-streaming-infinite-retentive-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalize Polyp Segmentation via Inpainting across Diverse Backgrounds and Pseudo-Mask Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalize-polyp-segmentation-via-inpainting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inpainting lesions within different normal backgrounds is a potential method of addressing the generalization problem, which is crucial for polyp segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalize-polyp-segmentation-via-inpainting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-RSCC: Diffusion Probabilistic Model for Change Captioning in Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rscc-diffusion-probabilistic-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In training process, we construct a noise predictor conditioned on cross modal features to learn the distribution from the real caption distribution to the standard Gaussian distribution under the Markov chain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-rscc-diffusion-probabilistic-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retrieval-Augmented Language Model for Extreme Multi-Label Knowledge Graph Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments demonstrate that (1) KGs with different characteristics require different augmenting strategies, and (2) augmenting the language model's input with textual data improves task performance significantly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrieval-augmented-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topic Modelling Case Law Using a Large Language Model and a New Taxonomy for UK Law: AI Insights into Summary Judgment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topic-modelling-case-law-using-a-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses a critical gap in legal analytics by developing and applying a novel taxonomy for topic modelling summary judgment cases in the United Kingdom.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topic-modelling-case-law-using-a-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Modality-Agnostic Pre-Training of Swin Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-modality-agnostic-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised pre-training has emerged as a transformative paradigm, displaying remarkable advancements in various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-modality-agnostic-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMFD: Distillation via Adaptive Multimodal Fusion for Multispectral Pedestrian Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amfd-distillation-via-adaptive-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This increased inference time has hindered the widespread employment of multispectral pedestrian detection in embedded devices for autonomous systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amfd-distillation-via-adaptive-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Universal Polynomial Bases Enhance Spectral Graph Neural Networks: Heterophily, Over-smoothing, and Over-squashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-universal-polynomial-bases-enhance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our extensive experiments, conducted on a diverse range of real-world and synthetic datasets with varying degrees of heterophily, support the superiority of UniFilter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-universal-polynomial-bases-enhance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Treat Noisy Labels as Accurate?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-treat-noisy-labels-as-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of focusing on label correction, EchoAlign treats noisy labels ($\tilde{Y}$) as accurate and modifies corresponding instance features ($X$) to achieve better alignment with $\tilde{Y}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-treat-noisy-labels-as-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearest is Not Dearest: Towards Practical Defense against Quantization-conditioned Backdoor Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearest-is-not-dearest-towards-practical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model quantization is widely used to compress and accelerate deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearest-is-not-dearest-towards-practical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FFAM: Feature Factorization Activation Map for Explanation of 3D Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffam-feature-factorization-activation-map-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a feature factorization activation map (FFAM) to generate high-quality visual explanations for 3D detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ffam-feature-factorization-activation-map-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Video Retrieval with Global-Local Semantic Consistent Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-video-retrieval-with-global-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we devise a shared local interaction module that employs several learnable queries to capture latent semantic concepts for learning fine-grained alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-video-retrieval-with-global-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProtT3: Protein-to-Text Generation for Text-based Protein Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prott3-protein-to-text-generation-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ProtT3 empowers an LM to understand protein sequences of amino acids by incorporating a PLM as its protein understanding module, enabling effective protein-to-text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prott3-protein-to-text-generation-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLAPH: Improving Factuality in Biomedical Long-form Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olaph-improving-factuality-in-biomedical-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We highlight that, even on evaluation metrics not used during training, LLMs trained with our OLAPH framework demonstrate significant performance improvement in factuality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olaph-improving-factuality-in-biomedical-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wav-KAN: Wavelet Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wav-kan-wavelet-kolmogorov-arnold-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper , we introduce Wav-KAN, an innovative neural network architecture that leverages the Wavelet Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks (Wav-KAN) framework to enhance interpretability and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wav-kan-wavelet-kolmogorov-arnold-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLM4Traj: Cognizing Movement Patterns and Travel Purposes from Trajectories with Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plm4traj-cognizing-movement-patterns-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, PLM4Traj introduces a novel trajectory prompt that integrates movement patterns and travel purposes into PLMs, while also allowing the model to adapt to various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plm4traj-cognizing-movement-patterns-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A machine learning framework for interpretable predictions in patient pathways: The case of predicting ICU admission for patients with symptoms of sepsis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-machine-learning-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Proactive analysis of patient pathways helps healthcare providers anticipate treatment-related risks, identify outcomes, and allocate resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-machine-learning-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pytorch-Wildlife: A Collaborative Deep Learning Framework for Conservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-wildlife-a-collaborative-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Opossum model achieves 98% accuracy, and the Amazon model has 92% recognition accuracy for 36 animals in 90% of the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-wildlife-a-collaborative-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Neighbors Together Makes it Easy: Jointly Comparing Multiple Candidates for Efficient and Effective Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-neighbors-together-makes-it-easy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, when integrated with another retriever, CMC reranking can function as a virtually enhanced retriever.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-neighbors-together-makes-it-easy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni-Mol Docking V2: Towards Realistic and Accurate Binding Pose Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-docking-v2-towards-realistic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, machine learning (ML) methods have emerged as promising alternatives for molecular docking, offering the potential for high accuracy without incurring prohibitive computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni-mol-docking-v2-towards-realistic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathBench: Evaluating the Theory and Application Proficiency of LLMs with a Hierarchical Mathematics Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbench-evaluating-the-theory-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MathBench spans a wide range of mathematical disciplines, offering a detailed evaluation of both theoretical understanding and practical problem-solving skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathbench-evaluating-the-theory-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Token-wise Influential Training Data Retrieval for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-wise-influential-training-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a Large Language Model (LLM) generation, how can we identify which training data led to this generation?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/token-wise-influential-training-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highway Graph to Accelerate Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highway-graph-to-accelerate-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on improving the training efficiency of RL algorithms by improving the efficiency of the value learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highway-graph-to-accelerate-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Versatile Teacher: A Class-aware Teacher-student Framework for Cross-domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-teacher-a-class-aware-teacher</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing the challenge of domain shift between datasets is vital in maintaining model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/versatile-teacher-a-class-aware-teacher</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAME-MT Dataset: Formality Awareness Made Easy for Machine Translation Purposes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fame-mt-dataset-formality-awareness-made-easy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People use language for various purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fame-mt-dataset-formality-awareness-made-easy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-of-Distribution Detection with a Single Unconditional Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-a-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, we introduce our method, Diffusion Paths, (DiffPath) in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-a-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning by Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the SMAC benchmark demonstrate that MAZero outperforms model-free approaches in terms of sample efficiency and provides comparable or better performance than existing model-based methods in terms of both sample and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-agent-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenRLHF: An Easy-to-use, Scalable and High-performance RLHF Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openrlhf-an-easy-to-use-scalable-and-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, unlike pretraining or fine-tuning a single model, scaling reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF) for training large language models poses coordination challenges across four models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openrlhf-an-easy-to-use-scalable-and-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Temporal Kernels with Orthogonal Polynomials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-temporal-kernels-with-orthogonal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a class of models named PLEIADES (PoLynomial Expansion In Adaptive Distributed Event-based Systems), which contains temporal convolution kernels generated from orthogonal polynomial basis functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-temporal-kernels-with-orthogonal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSTA: CNN-based Spatiotemporal Attention for Video Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csta-cnn-based-spatiotemporal-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video summarization aims to generate a concise representation of a video, capturing its essential content and key moments while reducing its overall length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csta-cnn-based-spatiotemporal-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Cartography-Based Curriculum Learning Method Applied on RoNLI: The First Romanian Natural Language Inference Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-cartography-based-curriculum-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language inference (NLI), the task of recognizing the entailment relationship in sentence pairs, is an actively studied topic serving as a proxy for natural language understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-cartography-based-curriculum-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bangladeshi Native Vehicle Detection in Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bangladeshi-native-vehicle-detection-in-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To advance terrestrial object detection research, this paper proposes a native vehicle detection dataset for the most commonly appeared vehicle classes in Bangladesh.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bangladeshi-native-vehicle-detection-in-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mammo-CLIP: A Vision Language Foundation Model to Enhance Data Efficiency and Robustness in Mammography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mammo-clip-a-vision-language-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of large and diverse training data on Computer-Aided Diagnosis (CAD) in breast cancer detection has been one of the concerns that impedes the adoption of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mammo-clip-a-vision-language-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feasibility Consistent Representation Learning for Safe Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasibility-consistent-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key obstacle in this endeavor is the estimation of safety constraints, which is typically more difficult than estimating a reward metric due to the sparse nature of the constraint signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasibility-consistent-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoRA: High-Rank Updating for Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mora-high-rank-updating-for-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Low-rank adaptation is a popular parameter-efficient fine-tuning method for large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mora-high-rank-updating-for-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QComp: A QSAR-Based Data Completion Framework for Drug Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qcomp-a-qsar-based-data-completion-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In drug discovery, in vitro and in vivo experiments reveal biochemical activities related to the efficacy and toxicity of compounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qcomp-a-qsar-based-data-completion-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling User Fatigue for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-user-fatigue-for-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to model user Fatigue in interest learning for sequential Recommendations (FRec).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-user-fatigue-for-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fennec: Fine-grained Language Model Evaluation and Correction Extended through Branching and Bridging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fennec-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large language models has given rise to a plethora of applications across a myriad of real-world tasks, mainly centered on aligning with human intent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fennec-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Contamination Calibration for Black-box LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-contamination-calibration-for-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancements of Large Language Models (LLMs) tightly associate with the expansion of the training data size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-contamination-calibration-for-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheet Music Transformer ++: End-to-End Full-Page Optical Music Recognition for Pianoform Sheet Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sheet-music-transformer-end-to-end-full-page</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the Sheet Music Transformer++, an end-to-end model that is able to transcribe full-page polyphonic music scores without the need of a previous Layout Analysis step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sheet-music-transformer-end-to-end-full-page</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomedical Entity Linking for Dutch: Fine-tuning a Self-alignment BERT Model on an Automatically Generated Wikipedia Corpus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-entity-linking-for-dutch-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use MedRoBERTa. nl as base model and perform second-phase pretraining through self-alignment on a Dutch biomedical ontology extracted from the UMLS and Dutch SNOMED.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-entity-linking-for-dutch-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Multi-Center CT and MRI Segmentation of Pancreas with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-center-ct-and-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also collected CT scans of 1, 350 patients from publicly available sources for benchmarking purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-multi-center-ct-and-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imp: Highly Capable Large Multimodal Models for Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imp-highly-capable-large-multimodal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By harnessing the capabilities of large language models (LLMs), recent large multimodal models (LMMs) have shown remarkable versatility in open-world multimodal understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imp-highly-capable-large-multimodal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Data Attribution via Approximate Unrolled Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-data-attribution-via-approximate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While being computationally efficient compared to unrolling-based approaches, Source is suitable in cases where implicit-differentiation-based approaches struggle, such as in non-converged models and multi-stage training pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-data-attribution-via-approximate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling citation worthiness by using attention-based bidirectional long short-term memory networks and interpretable models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-citation-worthiness-by-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This opens the door for our model to check documents during pre-submission and pre-archival procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-citation-worthiness-by-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULL: PU-Learning-based Accurate Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pull-pu-learning-based-accurate-link</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given an edge-incomplete graph, how can we accurately find the missing links?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pull-pu-learning-based-accurate-link</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PT43D: A Probabilistic Transformer for Generating 3D Shapes from Single Highly-Ambiguous RGB Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pt43d-a-probabilistic-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments demonstrate that our model outperforms state of the art in both scenarios]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pt43d-a-probabilistic-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
