<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 21:08:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GaraMoSt: Parallel Multi-Granularity Motion and Structural Modeling for Efficient Multi-Frame Interpolation in DSA Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/garamost-parallel-multi-granularity-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that GaraMoSt achieves the SOTA performance in accuracy, robustness, visual effects, and noise suppression, comprehensively surpassing MoSt-DSA and other natural scene VFI methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/garamost-parallel-multi-granularity-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAG-RewardBench: Benchmarking Reward Models in Retrieval Augmented Generation for Preference Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-rewardbench-benchmarking-reward-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the significant progress made by existing retrieval augmented language models (RALMs) in providing trustworthy responses and grounding in reliable sources, they often overlook effective alignment with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rag-rewardbench-benchmarking-reward-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIIS: Visible and Infrared Information Synthesis for Severe Low-light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viis-visible-and-infrared-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose a novel task, dubbed visible and infrared information synthesis (VIIS), which aims to achieve both information enhancement and fusion of the two modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viis-visible-and-infrared-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modality-Independent Graph Neural Networks with Global Transformers for Multimodal Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-independent-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results indicate that the optimal $K$ for certain modalities on specific datasets can be as low as 1 or 2, which may restrict the GNNs' capacity to capture global information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-independent-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Fuzzy-oriented Multi-Modal Meta-Learning for Fine-grained Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-fuzzy-oriented-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing FER methods face three key challenges in real-world applications: (i) they rely on large amounts of continuously annotated data to ensure accuracy since emotions are complex and ambiguous in reality, which is costly and time-consuming; (ii) they cannot capture the temporal heterogeneity caused by changing emotion patterns, because they usually assume that the temporal correlation within sampling periods is the same; (iii) they do not consider the spatial heterogeneity of different FER scenarios, that is, the distribution of emotion information in different data may have bias or interference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-fuzzy-oriented-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mix-LN: Unleashing the Power of Deeper Layers by Combining Pre-LN and Post-LN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mix-ln-unleashing-the-power-of-deeper-layers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, Post-Layer Normalization (Post-LN) preserves larger gradient norms in deeper layers but suffers from vanishing gradients in earlier layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mix-ln-unleashing-the-power-of-deeper-layers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics Reasoner: Knowledge-Augmented Reasoning for Solving Physics Problems with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-reasoner-knowledge-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics problems constitute a significant aspect of reasoning, necessitating complicated reasoning ability and abundant physics knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-reasoner-knowledge-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEKE: Specialised Experts for Keyword Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seke-specialised-experts-for-keyword</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relying on the insight that real-world keyword detection often requires handling of diverse content, we propose a novel supervised keyword extraction approach based on the mixture of experts (MoE) technique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seke-specialised-experts-for-keyword</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsyDT: Using LLMs to Construct the Digital Twin of Psychological Counselor with Personalized Counseling Style for Psychological Counseling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psydt-using-llms-to-construct-the-digital</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results indicate that our proposed PsyDT framework can synthesize multi-turn dialogues that closely resemble real-world counseling cases and demonstrate better performance compared to other baselines, thereby show that our framework can effectively construct the digital twin of psychological counselor with a specific counseling style.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psydt-using-llms-to-construct-the-digital</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Steerable Alignment: Adapting Rewards and LLM Policies with Neural Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-steerable-alignment-adapting-rewards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) become increasingly embedded in everyday applications, ensuring their alignment with the diverse preferences of individual users has become a critical challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-steerable-alignment-adapting-rewards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nullu: Mitigating Object Hallucinations in Large Vision-Language Models via HalluSpace Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nullu-mitigating-object-hallucinations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By orthogonalizing the model weights, input features will be projected into the Null space of the HalluSpace to reduce OH, based on which we name our method Nullu.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nullu-mitigating-object-hallucinations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FarExStance: Explainable Stance Detection for Farsi</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/farexstance-explainable-stance-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare the performance of a fine-tuned multilingual RoBERTa model to several large language models in zero-shot, few-shot, and parameter-efficient fine-tuned settings on our new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/farexstance-explainable-stance-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnySat: An Earth Observation Model for Any Resolutions, Scales, and Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anysat-an-earth-observation-model-for-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Geospatial models must adapt to the diversity of Earth observation data in terms of resolutions, scales, and modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anysat-an-earth-observation-model-for-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mesoscopic Insights: Orchestrating Multi-scale &amp; Hybrid Architecture for Image Manipulation Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesoscopic-insights-orchestrating-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this, our paper explores how to simultaneously construct mesoscopic representations of micro and macro information for IML and introduces the Mesorch architecture to orchestrate both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mesoscopic-insights-orchestrating-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EscapeBench: Pushing Language Models to Think Outside the Box</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escapebench-pushing-language-models-to-think</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language model agents excel in long-session planning and reasoning, but existing benchmarks primarily focus on goal-oriented tasks with explicit objectives, neglecting creative adaptation in unfamiliar environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escapebench-pushing-language-models-to-think</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CA-Edit: Causality-Aware Condition Adapter for High-Fidelity Local Facial Attribute Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ca-edit-causality-aware-condition-adapter-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For efficient and high-fidelity local facial attribute editing, most existing editing methods either require additional fine-tuning for different editing effects or tend to affect beyond the editing regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ca-edit-causality-aware-condition-adapter-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking and Improving Large Vision-Language Models for Fundamental Visual Graph Understanding and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-improving-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study the reason behind these limitations, we propose VGCure, a comprehensive benchmark covering 22 tasks for examining the fundamental graph understanding and reasoning capacities of LVLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-and-improving-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient and Explainable Hate Speech Detection via Model Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-explainable-hate-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic detection of hate and abusive language is essential to combat its online spread.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-explainable-hate-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QueryCDR: Query-based Controllable Distortion Rectification Network for Fisheye Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/querycdr-query-based-controllable-distortion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Query-based Controllable Distortion Rectification network for fisheye images (QueryCDR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/querycdr-query-based-controllable-distortion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment faking in large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-faking-in-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explaining this gap, in almost all cases where the model complies with a harmful query from a free user, we observe explicit alignment-faking reasoning, with the model stating it is strategically answering harmful queries in training to preserve its preferred harmlessness behavior out of training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-faking-in-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAD-Recode: Reverse Engineering CAD Code from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad-recode-reverse-engineering-cad-code-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Taking advantage of the exposure of pre-trained Large Language Models (LLMs) to Python code, we leverage a relatively small LLM as a decoder for CAD-Recode and combine it with a lightweight point cloud projector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad-recode-reverse-engineering-cad-code-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Gap in Entity Knowledge Extraction Across Modalities in Vision Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-gap-in-entity-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language models (VLMs) excel at extracting and reasoning about information from images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-gap-in-entity-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Lingual Transfer of Debiasing and Detoxification in Multilingual LLMs: An Extensive Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-transfer-of-debiasing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate the impact of different finetuning methods on the model's bias and toxicity, but also on its ability to produce fluent and diverse text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-lingual-transfer-of-debiasing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Enhanced Recommender Systems: Taxonomy, Trend, Application and Future</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-enhanced-recommender</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Model (LLM) has transformative potential in various domains, including recommender systems (RS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-enhanced-recommender</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedCoT: Medical Chain of Thought via Hierarchical Expert</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medcot-medical-chain-of-thought-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence has advanced in Medical Visual Question Answering (Med-VQA), but prevalent research tends to focus on the accuracy of the answers, often overlooking the reasoning paths and interpretability, which are crucial in clinical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medcot-medical-chain-of-thought-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-VEval: A Versatile Metric for Evaluating Image and Video Captions Using GPT-4o</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-veval-a-versatile-metric-for-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose MSVD-Eval, a new dataset for video captioning evaluation, to establish a more transparent and consistent framework for both human experts and evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-veval-a-versatile-metric-for-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-Based Adversarial Attack on Near-Infrared Human Detector for Nighttime Surveillance Camera Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-based-adversarial-attack-on-near</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many surveillance cameras switch between daytime and nighttime modes based on illuminance levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-based-adversarial-attack-on-near</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memorizing SAM: 3D Medical Segment Anything Model with Memorizing Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorizing-sam-3d-medical-segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate whether introducing the memory mechanism as a plug-in, specifically the ability to memorize and recall internal representations of past inputs, can improve the performance of SAM with limited computation cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorizing-sam-3d-medical-segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphAvatar: Compact Head Avatars with GNN-Generated 3D Gaussians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphavatar-compact-head-avatars-with-gnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a method called GraphAvatar that utilizes Graph Neural Networks (GNN) to generate 3D Gaussians for the head avatar.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphavatar-compact-head-avatars-with-gnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructSeg: Unifying Instructed Visual Segmentation with Multi-modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructseg-unifying-instructed-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Boosted by Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs), text-guided universal segmentation models for the image and video domains have made rapid progress recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructseg-unifying-instructed-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Data-Free Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-data-free-knowledge-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the student distillation module, we explore a data inflation strategy to properly utilize a blend of real and synthetic data to train the student network via a classifier-sharing-based feature alignment technique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-data-free-knowledge-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Long-form Story Using Dynamic Hierarchical Outlining with Memory-Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-long-form-story-using-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-form story generation task aims to produce coherent and sufficiently lengthy text, essential for applications such as novel writingand interactive storytelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-long-form-story-using-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Registration in 30 Years: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-registration-in-30-years-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D point cloud registration is a fundamental problem in computer vision, computer graphics, robotics, remote sensing, and etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-registration-in-30-years-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuLTSF: Long-Term Time Series Forecasting with Quantum Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qultsf-long-term-time-series-forecasting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-term time series forecasting (LTSF) involves predicting a large number of future values of a time series based on the past values and is an essential task in a wide range of domains including weather forecasting, stock market analysis, disease outbreak prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qultsf-long-term-time-series-forecasting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Efficient Data-Free Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-data-free-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method, Inhibited Synthetic PostFilter (ISPF), to tackle this challenge from two perspectives: First, the Inhibited Synthetic, by reducing the synthesized forgetting information; Second, the PostFilter, by fully utilizing the retaining-related information in synthesized samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-efficient-data-free-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Forecasting of PM2.5 via Spatial-Diffusion guided Encoder-Decoder Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-forecasting-of-pm2-5-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One such example is forecasting the concentration of fine particulate matter (PM2. 5) in the atmosphere which is influenced by many complex factors, the most important ones being diffusion due to meteorological factors as well as transport across vast distances over a period of time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-forecasting-of-pm2-5-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of Multimodal Explainable Artificial Intelligence: Past, Present and Future</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-multimodal-explainable-artificial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence (AI) has rapidly developed through advancements in computational power and the growth of massive datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-multimodal-explainable-artificial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Algorithm-Centric Quantum Processor Topology Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-powered-algorithm-centric-quantum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method marks a significant departure from previous methods that have been constrained to mapping circuits onto a fixed processor topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-powered-algorithm-centric-quantum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency of Compositional Generalization across Multiple Levels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-of-compositional-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compositional generalization is the capability of a model to understand novel compositions composed of seen concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-of-compositional-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemiDFL: A Semi-Supervised Paradigm for Decentralized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semidfl-a-semi-supervised-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose SemiDFL, the first semi-supervised DFL method that enhances DFL performance in SSL scenarios by establishing a consensus in both data and model spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semidfl-a-semi-supervised-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashVTG: Feature Layering and Adaptive Score Handling Network for Video Temporal Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashvtg-feature-layering-and-adaptive-score</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For short-moment retrieval, FlashVTG increases mAP to 125% of previous SOTA performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashvtg-feature-layering-and-adaptive-score</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RadField3D: A Data Generator and Data Format for Deep Learning in Radiation-Protection Dosimetry for Medical Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radfield3d-a-data-generator-and-data-format</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research work, we present our open-source Geant4-based Monte-Carlo simulation application, called RadField3D, for generating threedimensional radiation field datasets for dosimetry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radfield3d-a-data-generator-and-data-format</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MATCHED: Multimodal Authorship-Attribution To Combat Human Trafficking in Escort-Advertisement Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matched-multimodal-authorship-attribution-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human trafficking (HT) remains a critical issue, with traffickers increasingly leveraging online escort advertisements (ads) to advertise victims anonymously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matched-multimodal-authorship-attribution-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Should We Prefer State-to-Visual DAgger Over Visual Reinforcement Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-should-we-prefer-state-to-visual-dagger</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual reinforcement learning is a promising approach that directly trains policies from visual observations, although it faces challenges in sample efficiency and computational costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-should-we-prefer-state-to-visual-dagger</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking in Space: How Multimodal Large Language Models See, Remember, and Recall Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-in-space-how-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans possess the visual-spatial intelligence to remember spaces from sequential visual observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-in-space-how-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidential Deep Learning for Probabilistic Modelling of Extreme Storm Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidential-deep-learning-for-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evidential Deep Learning (EDL) is an uncertainty-aware deep learning approach designed to provide confidence about its predictions using only one forecast.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidential-deep-learning-for-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Co-pilot for Screening of Organic Molecular Additives for Perovskite Solar Cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-co-pilot-for-screening-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning (ML) has been extensively employed in planar perovskite photovoltaics to screen effective organic molecular additives, while encountering predictive biases for novel materials due to small datasets and reliance on predefined descriptors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-co-pilot-for-screening-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Granularity Open Intent Classification via Adaptive Granular-Ball Decision Boundary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-open-intent-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we propose a Multi-granularity Open intent classification method via adaptive Granular-Ball decision boundary (MOGB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-open-intent-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASCO (PArallel Structured COarsening): an overlay to speed up graph clustering algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasco-parallel-structured-coarsening-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering the nodes of a graph is a cornerstone of graph analysis and has been extensively studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasco-parallel-structured-coarsening-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cultivating Archipelago of Forests: Evolving Robust Decision Trees through Island Coevolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cultivating-archipelago-of-forests-evolving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The algorithm operates on multiple islands, each containing populations of decision trees and adversarial perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cultivating-archipelago-of-forests-evolving</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
