<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Enhanced Autoregressive Prediction: Pay Less Attention to Learn More</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-enhanced-autoregressive-prediction-pay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose Mask-Enhanced Autoregressive Prediction (MEAP), a simple yet effective training paradigm that seamlessly integrates Masked Language Modeling (MLM) into Next-Token Prediction (NTP) to enhance the latter's in-context retrieval capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-enhanced-autoregressive-prediction-pay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jakiro: Boosting Speculative Decoding with Decoupled Multi-Head via MoE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jakiro-boosting-speculative-decoding-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speculative decoding (SD) accelerates large language model inference by using a smaller draft model to predict multiple tokens, which are then verified in parallel by the larger target model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jakiro-boosting-speculative-decoding-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-preserving contrastive learning for spatial time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, this study suggests that higher similarity structure preservation indicates more informative and useful representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAVE: Self-Attention on Visual Embedding for Zero-Shot Generic Object Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/save-self-attention-on-visual-embedding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Zero-shot counting is a subcategory of Generic Visual Object Counting, which aims to count objects from an arbitrary class in a given image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/save-self-attention-on-visual-embedding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Potential of Pre-Trained Diffusion Models for Generalizable Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method integrates a discriminative and contrastive Re-ID model with a pre-trained diffusion model through a correlation-aware conditioning scheme.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-potential-of-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neumann eigenmaps for landmark embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neumann-eigenmaps-for-landmark-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Neumann eigenmaps (NeuMaps), a novel approach for enhancing the standard diffusion map embedding using landmarks, i. e distinguished samples within the dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neumann-eigenmaps-for-landmark-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Vision-Language Models on Optical Character Recognition in Dynamic Video Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-vision-language-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces an open-source benchmark for evaluating Vision-Language Models (VLMs) on Optical Character Recognition (OCR) tasks in dynamic video environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-vision-language-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Language Models for Social Deduction with Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-for-social-deduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Communicating in natural language is a powerful tool in multi-agent settings, as it enables independent agents to share information in partially observable settings and allows zero-shot coordination with humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-language-models-for-social-deduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving 77% of the Parameters in Large Language Models Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saving-77-of-the-parameters-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report demonstrates that large language models (LLMs) can maintain their learning capacity while reducing their non-embedding parameters by up to 77%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saving-77-of-the-parameters-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Global Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-global-neural-architecture-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural architecture search (NAS) has shown promise towards automating neural network design for a given task, but it is computationally demanding due to training costs associated with evaluating a large number of architectures to find the optimal one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-global-neural-architecture-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ELMTEX: Fine-Tuning Large Language Models for Structured Clinical Information Extraction. A Case Study on Clinical Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elmtex-fine-tuning-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Europe's healthcare systems require enhanced interoperability and digitalization, driving a demand for innovative solutions to process legacy clinical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elmtex-fine-tuning-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Supported Natural Language to Bash Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-supported-natural-language-to-bash</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we present a novel functional equivalence heuristic that combines command execution with LLM evaluation of command outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-supported-natural-language-to-bash</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Symbolic World Models via Test-time Scaling of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-symbolic-world-models-via-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solving complex planning problems requires Large Language Models (LLMs) to explicitly model the state transition to avoid rule violations, comply with constraints, and ensure optimality-a task hindered by the inherent ambiguity of natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-symbolic-world-models-via-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuEST: Stable Training of LLMs with 1-Bit Weights and Activations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quest-stable-training-of-llms-with-1-bit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While post-training compression methods are very popular, the question of obtaining even more accurate compressed models by directly training over such representations, i. e., Quantization-Aware Training (QAT), is still open: for example, a recent study (arXiv:2411. 04330v2) put the "optimal" bit-width at which models can be trained using QAT, while staying accuracy-competitive with standard FP16/BF16 precision, at 8-bits weights and activations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quest-stable-training-of-llms-with-1-bit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlightForge: Advancing UAV Research with Procedural Generation of High-Fidelity Simulation and Integrated Autonomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flightforge-advancing-uav-research-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing simulators often lack high-level autonomy, hindering their immediate applicability to complex tasks such as autonomous navigation in unknown environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flightforge-advancing-uav-research-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNNs Getting ComFy: Community and Feature Similarity Guided Rewiring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnns-getting-comfy-community-and-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Maximizing the spectral gap through graph rewiring has been proposed to enhance the performance of message-passing graph neural networks (GNNs) by addressing over-squashing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnns-getting-comfy-community-and-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling up Test-Time Compute with Latent Reasoning: A Recurrent Depth Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-test-time-compute-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We scale a proof-of-concept model to 3. 5 billion parameters and 800 billion tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-test-time-compute-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARR: Question Answering with Large Language Models via Analyzing, Retrieving, and Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arr-question-answering-with-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces ARR, an intuitive and effective zero-shot prompting method that explicitly incorporates three key steps in QA solving: analyzing the intent of the question, retrieving relevant information, and reasoning step by step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arr-question-answering-with-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable and externally validated machine learning for neuropsychiatric diagnosis via electrocardiograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-externally-validated-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant predictive performance was observed for conditions within the neurological and psychiatric groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-externally-validated-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory Capacity of Nonlinear Recurrent Networks: Is it Informative?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-capacity-of-nonlinear-recurrent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The total memory capacity (MC) of linear recurrent neural networks (RNNs) has been proven to be equal to the rank of the corresponding Kalman controllability matrix, and it is almost surely maximal for connectivity and input weight matrices drawn from regular distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-capacity-of-nonlinear-recurrent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Graph of Thoughts: Test-Time Adaptive Reasoning Unifying Chain, Tree, and Graph Structures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-graph-of-thoughts-test-time-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive reasoning capabilities, yet their performance is highly dependent on the prompting strategy and model scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-graph-of-thoughts-test-time-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LR0.FM: Low-Resolution Zero-shot Classification Benchmark For Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lr0-fm-low-resolution-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LR0. FM, a comprehensive benchmark evaluating the impact of low resolution on the zero-shot classification performance of 10 FM(s) across 66 backbones and 15 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lr0-fm-low-resolution-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Retrospective Systematic Study on Hierarchical Sparse Query Transformer-assisted Ultrasound Screening for Early Hepatocellular Carcinoma</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-retrospective-systematic-study-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) ranks as the third leading cause of cancer-related mortality worldwide, with early detection being crucial for improving patient survival rates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-retrospective-systematic-study-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Models Think Alike and this Undermines AI Oversight</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/great-models-think-alike-and-this-undermines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study how model similarity affects both aspects of AI oversight by proposing a probabilistic metric for LM similarity based on overlap in model mistakes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/great-models-think-alike-and-this-undermines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Randomized Experiments Using Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-randomized-experiments-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical results across several randomized experiments show that our estimator offers substantial precision gains, equivalent to a reduction of up to 20% in the sample size needed to match the same precision as the standard estimator based on experimental data alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-randomized-experiments-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STURM-Flood: a curated dataset for deep learning-based flood extent mapping leveraging Sentinel-1 and Sentinel-2 imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sturm-flood-a-curated-dataset-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Flooding is a major global natural disaster exacerbated by climate change and urbanization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sturm-flood-a-curated-dataset-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Meta Coordination Graphs for Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-meta-coordination-graphs-for-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents deep meta coordination graphs (DMCG) for learning cooperative policies in multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-meta-coordination-graphs-for-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMoE: Fast Carving of Mixture-of-Experts for Efficient LLM Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmoe-fast-carving-of-mixture-of-experts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) achieve impressive performance by scaling model parameters, but this comes with significant inference overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmoe-fast-carving-of-mixture-of-experts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FE-UNet: Frequency Domain Enhanced U-Net with Segment Anything Capability for Versatile Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fe-unet-frequency-domain-enhanced-u-net-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further emulate the human visual system, we introduce the Frequency Domain Enhanced Receptive Field Block (FE-RFB), which integrates WSPM to extract enriched features from the frequency domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fe-unet-frequency-domain-enhanced-u-net-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Circuit Design using a Progressive Widening Monte Carlo Tree Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-circuit-design-using-a-progressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The performance of Variational Quantum Algorithms (VQAs) strongly depends on the choice of the parameterized quantum circuit to optimize.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-circuit-design-using-a-progressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Uniformly Rotated Mondrian Kernel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-uniformly-rotated-mondrian-kernel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First proposed by Rahimi and Recht, random features are used to decrease the computational cost of kernel machines in large-scale problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-uniformly-rotated-mondrian-kernel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZISVFM: Zero-Shot Object Instance Segmentation in Indoor Robotic Environments with Vision Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zisvfm-zero-shot-object-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Service robots operating in unstructured environments must effectively recognize and segment unknown objects to enhance their functionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zisvfm-zero-shot-object-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSTARLab: Open Approach for Spatio-Temporal Agent Data Analysis in Soccer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstarlab-open-approach-for-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenSTARLab includes the Pre-processing Package that standardizes event and tracking data through Unified and Integrated Event Data and State-Action-Reward formats, the Event Modeling Package that implements deep learning-based event prediction, alongside the RLearn Package for reinforcement learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openstarlab-open-approach-for-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinically-Inspired Hierarchical Multi-Label Classification of Chest X-rays with a Penalty-Based Loss Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinically-inspired-hierarchical-multi-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel approach to multi-label chest X-ray (CXR) image classification that enhances clinical interpretability while maintaining a streamlined, single-model, single-run training pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinically-inspired-hierarchical-multi-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rule-based Evolving Fuzzy System for Time Series Forecasting: New Perspectives Based on Type-2 Fuzzy Sets Measures Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-based-evolving-fuzzy-system-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the existing methods to deal with this type of data is the use of the evolving Fuzzy Systems (eFSs), which have been proven to be a powerful class of models for time series forecasting, due to their autonomy to handle the data and highly complex problems in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rule-based-evolving-fuzzy-system-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Large Language Model Benchmarks Test Reliability?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-model-benchmarks-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate a wide range of models on these platinum benchmarks and find that, indeed, frontier LLMs still exhibit failures on simple tasks such as elementary-level math word problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-large-language-model-benchmarks-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kozax: Flexible and Scalable Genetic Programming in JAX</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kozax-flexible-and-scalable-genetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Genetic programming is an optimization algorithm inspired by natural selection which automatically evolves the structure of computer programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kozax-flexible-and-scalable-genetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackout DIFUSCO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackout-difusco</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work represents the first application of Blackout Diffusion to combinatorial optimization, providing a foundation for further advancements in this domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blackout-difusco</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIMO: Less is More for Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limo-less-is-more-for-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While conventional wisdom suggests that sophisticated reasoning tasks demand extensive training data (>100, 000 examples), we demonstrate that complex mathematical reasoning abilities can be effectively elicited with surprisingly few examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limo-less-is-more-for-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Guidance of Flow Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-guidance-of-flow-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From this framework, we derive a family of guidance techniques that can be applied to general flow matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-guidance-of-flow-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EFKAN: A KAN-Integrated Neural Operator For Efficient Magnetotelluric Forward Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efkan-a-kan-integrated-neural-operator-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural operators (NOs) have been effectively used for rapid MT forward modeling, demonstrating their promising performance in solving the MT forward modeling-related partial differential equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efkan-a-kan-integrated-neural-operator-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diff9D: Diffusion-Based Domain-Generalized Category-Level 9-DoF Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff9d-diffusion-based-domain-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our motivation is to leverage the latent generalization ability of the diffusion model to address the domain generalization challenge in object pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diff9d-diffusion-based-domain-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event-aided Semantic Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-aided-semantic-scene-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Semantic Scene Completion (SSC) for autonomous driving underscore the limitations of RGB-based approaches, which struggle under motion blur, poor lighting, and adverse weather.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-aided-semantic-scene-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Dimensionality Hurts: The Role of LLM Embedding Compression for Noisy Regression Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-dimensionality-hurts-the-role-of-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable success in language modelling due to scaling laws found in model size and the hidden dimension of the model's text representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-dimensionality-hurts-the-role-of-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimBEV: A Synthetic Multi-Task Multi-Sensor Driving Data Generation Tool and Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simbev-a-synthetic-multi-task-multi-sensor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bird's-eye view (BEV) perception for autonomous driving has garnered significant attention in recent years, in part because BEV representation facilitates the fusion of multi-sensor data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simbev-a-synthetic-multi-task-multi-sensor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Circular Microalgae-Based Carbon Control for Net Zero</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circular-microalgae-based-carbon-control-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, to compensate for carbon emissions we show that a cultivation of microalgae with a volume 625 times bigger than the one of the carbon emitter is required.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/circular-microalgae-based-carbon-control-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMER: Crafting Interactive Extended Reality Worlds with JSON Data Generated by Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmer-crafting-interactive-extended-reality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike prior approaches focusing on coding script generation, LLMER translates natural language inputs into JSON data, significantly reducing the likelihood of application crashes and processing latency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmer-crafting-interactive-extended-reality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QLASS: Boosting Language Agent Inference via Q-Guided Stepwise Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlass-boosting-language-agent-inference-via-q</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the stepwise guidance, we propose a Q-guided generation strategy to enable language agents to better adapt to long-term value, resulting in significant performance improvement during model inference on complex interactive agent tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlass-boosting-language-agent-inference-via-q</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Ensemble Learning for Cross-View Isolated Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-ensemble-learning-for-cross-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our solution to the Cross-View Isolated Sign Language Recognition (CV-ISLR) challenge held at WWW 2025.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-ensemble-learning-for-cross-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-Aware Driving Scenario Analysis with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-driving-scenario-analysis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) can capture nuanced contextual relationships, reasoning, and complex problem-solving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-aware-driving-scenario-analysis-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
