<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 21:08:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AI Opportunistic Coronary Calcium Screening at Veterans Affairs Hospitals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-opportunistic-coronary-calcium-screening</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusions This nongated CT CAC algorithm was developed across a national health care system and shows strong performance in evaluation against paired gated CT scans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-opportunistic-coronary-calcium-screening</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning on a Budget: Miniaturizing DeepSeek R1 with SFT-GRPO Alignment for Instruction-Tuned LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-on-a-budget-miniaturizing-deepseek</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a modular, low-cost replication of the DeepSeek-R1 training methodology using Qwen2. 5-0. 5B-Instruct (a compact instruction-tuned LLM) optimized via a two-stage pipeline: Supervised Fine-Tuning (SFT) and Group Relative Policy Optimization (GRPO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-on-a-budget-miniaturizing-deepseek</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LDIR: Low-Dimensional Dense and Interpretable Text Embeddings with Relative Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ldir-low-dimensional-dense-and-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic text representation is a fundamental task in the field of natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ldir-low-dimensional-dense-and-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Scalable Gradient-Based Optimization Framework for Sparse Minimum-Variance Portfolio Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-scalable-gradient-based-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Portfolio optimization involves selecting asset weights to minimize a risk-reward objective, such as the portfolio variance in the classical minimum-variance framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-scalable-gradient-based-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Nonlinear Dynamics in Physical Modelling Synthesis using Neural Ordinary Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-dynamics-in-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we examine how modal decomposition can be combined with neural ordinary differential equations for modelling distributed musical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-dynamics-in-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating brain-inspired mechanisms for multimodal learning in artificial intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-brain-inspired-mechanisms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this biological mechanism, we explore the relationship between multimodal output and information from individual modalities, proposing an inverse effectiveness driven multimodal fusion (IEMF) strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-brain-inspired-mechanisms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring entropy production in many-body systems using nonequilibrium MaxEnt</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-entropy-production-in-many-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method for inferring entropy production (EP) in high-dimensional stochastic systems, including many-body systems and non-Markovian systems with long memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-entropy-production-in-many-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-Stage Generative Model for Intracranial Aneurysm Meshes with Morphological Marker Conditioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-generative-model-for-intracranial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing shape generation methods struggle to capture realistic IA features and ignore the relationship between IA pouches and parent vessels, limiting physiological realism and their generation cannot be controlled to have specific morphological measurements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-stage-generative-model-for-intracranial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deconstructing Subset Construction -- Reducing While Determinizing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-subset-construction-reducing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel perspective on the NFA canonization problem, which introduces intermediate minimization steps to reduce the exploration space on-the-fly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deconstructing-subset-construction-reducing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid Strategy for Aggregated Probabilistic Forecasting and Energy Trading in HEFTCom2024</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-strategy-for-aggregated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Obtaining accurate probabilistic energy forecasts and making effective decisions amid diverse uncertainties are routine challenges in future energy systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-strategy-for-aggregated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction to Discrete Variational Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-introduction-to-discrete-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we provide a rigorous, yet practical, introduction to discrete variational autoencoders -- specifically, VAEs in which the latent space is made up of latent variables that follow a categorical distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-introduction-to-discrete-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CheXGenBench: A Unified Benchmark For Fidelity, Privacy and Utility of Synthetic Chest Radiographs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexgenbench-a-unified-benchmark-for-fidelity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we release a high-quality, synthetic dataset, SynthCheX-75K, comprising 75K radiographs generated by the top-performing model (Sana 0. 6B) in our benchmark to support further research in this critical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chexgenbench-a-unified-benchmark-for-fidelity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Trade-off to Synergy: A Versatile Symbiotic Watermarking Framework for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-trade-off-to-synergy-a-versatile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hybrid framework adaptively embeds watermarks using token entropy and semantic entropy, optimizing the balance between detectability, robustness, text quality, and security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-trade-off-to-synergy-a-versatile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Robustness of Deep Reinforcement Learning for Autonomous Surface Vehicle Control in Field Tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-robustness-of-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant advancements in Deep Reinforcement Learning (DRL) for Autonomous Surface Vehicles (ASVs), their robustness in real-world conditions, particularly under external disturbances, remains insufficiently explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-robustness-of-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond 'Aha!': Toward Systematic Meta-Abilities Alignment in Large Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-aha-toward-systematic-meta-abilities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large reasoning models (LRMs) already possess a latent capacity for long chain-of-thought reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-aha-toward-systematic-meta-abilities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSPENet: Contour-Aware and Saliency Priors Embedding Network for Infrared Small Target Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cspenet-contour-aware-and-saliency-priors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this, we propose a dual-branch priors embedding architecture (DBPEA) that establishes differentiated feature fusion pathways, embedding these two priors at optimal network positions to achieve performance enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cspenet-contour-aware-and-saliency-priors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WorldPM: Scaling Human Preference Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/worldpm-scaling-human-preference-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by scaling laws in language modeling that demonstrate how test loss scales as a power law with model and dataset sizes, we find that similar laws exist in preference modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/worldpm-scaling-human-preference-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Questions to Clinical Recommendations: Large Language Models Driving Evidence-Based Clinical Decision Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-questions-to-clinical-recommendations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical evidence, derived from rigorous research and data analysis, provides healthcare professionals with reliable scientific foundations for informed decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-questions-to-clinical-recommendations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuXAI: Explainers for Hybrid Quantum Machine Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quxai-explainers-for-hybrid-quantum-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of hybrid quantum-classical machine learning (HQML) models opens new horizons of computational intelligence but their fundamental complexity frequently leads to black box behavior that undermines transparency and reliability in their application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quxai-explainers-for-hybrid-quantum-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDFP: Data-dependent Frequency Prompt for Source Free Domain Adaptation of Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddfp-data-dependent-frequency-prompt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance adaptation, we employ a style-related layer fine-tuning strategy, specifically designed for SFDA, to train the target model using the prompted target domain images and pseudo-labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddfp-data-dependent-frequency-prompt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIG: Privacy Jailbreak Attack on LLMs via Gradient-based Iterative In-Context Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pig-privacy-jailbreak-attack-on-llms-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate PIG and existing jailbreak methods using two privacy-related datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pig-privacy-jailbreak-attack-on-llms-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can You Really Trust Code Copilots? Evaluating Large Language Models from a Code Security Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-you-really-trust-code-copilots-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first propose CoV-Eval, a multi-task benchmark covering various tasks such as code completion, vulnerability repair, vulnerability detection and classification, for comprehensive evaluation of LLM code security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-you-really-trust-code-copilots-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Document Refinement for Long-context Retrieval-augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-document-refinement-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world RAG applications often encounter long-context input scenarios, where redundant information and noise results in higher inference costs and reduced performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-document-refinement-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Prompt Optimizers: From Prompt Merits to Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-prompt-optimizers-from-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to limited downward compatibility, verbose, instruction-heavy prompts from advanced LLMs can overwhelm lightweight inference models and degrade response quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-prompt-optimizers-from-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaptCLIP: Adapting CLIP for Universal Visual Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptclip-adapting-clip-for-universal-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Universal visual anomaly detection aims to identify anomalies from novel or unseen vision domains without additional fine-tuning, which is critical in open scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptclip-adapting-clip-for-universal-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MathCoder-VL: Bridging Vision and Code for Enhanced Multimodal Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-vl-bridging-vision-and-code-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language image-caption datasets, widely used for training Large Multimodal Models, mainly focus on natural scenarios and overlook the intricate details of mathematical figures that are critical for problem-solving, hindering the advancement of current LMMs in multimodal mathematical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mathcoder-vl-bridging-vision-and-code-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HWA-UNETR: Hierarchical Window Aggregate UNETR for 3D Multimodal Gastric Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwa-unetr-hierarchical-window-aggregate-unetr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal medical image segmentation faces significant challenges in the context of gastric cancer lesion analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hwa-unetr-hierarchical-window-aggregate-unetr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSCI: Addressing CLIP's Inherent Limitations for Compositional Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msci-addressing-clip-s-inherent-limitations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a Multi-Stage Cross-modal Interaction (MSCI) model that effectively explores and utilizes intermediate-layer information from CLIP's visual encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msci-addressing-clip-s-inherent-limitations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Exploration-Exploitation Strategies of LLMs and Humans: Insights from Standard Multi-armed Bandit Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-exploration-exploitation-strategies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In simple stationary tasks, reasoning-enabled LLMs exhibit similar levels of random and directed exploration compared to humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-exploration-exploitation-strategies</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADHMR: Aligning Diffusion-based Human Mesh Recovery via Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adhmr-aligning-diffusion-based-human-mesh</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose ADHMR, a framework that Aligns a Diffusion-based HMR model in a preference optimization manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adhmr-aligning-diffusion-based-human-mesh</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MFogHub: Bridging Multi-Regional and Multi-Satellite Data for Global Marine Fog Detection and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfoghub-bridging-multi-regional-and-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning approaches for marine fog detection and forecasting have outperformed traditional methods, demonstrating significant scientific and practical importance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mfoghub-bridging-multi-regional-and-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Radiance Field for Dynamic Scene: From Neural Field to Gaussian Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-radiance-field-for-dynamic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This survey presents a systematic analysis of over 200 papers focused on dynamic scene representation using radiance field, spanning the spectrum from implicit neural representations to explicit Gaussian primitives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-radiance-field-for-dynamic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of SMT and MILP for the Nurse Rostering Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-smt-and-milp-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On real-world inspired problems containing a more varied set of shifts and personnel, the SMT solver excels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-smt-and-milp-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASS: Multi-Agent Simulation Scaling for Portfolio Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-multi-agent-simulation-scaling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM-based multi-agent has gained significant attention for their potential in simulation and enhancing performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mass-multi-agent-simulation-scaling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Repetition Problems of LLMs in Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-repetition-problems-of-llms-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, RPG first leverages grammar rules to identify repetition problems during code generation, and then strategically decays the likelihood of critical tokens that contribute to repetitions, thereby mitigating them in code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-repetition-problems-of-llms-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Deep Fusion of Large Language Models and Diffusion Transformers for Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-deep-fusion-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper does not describe a new method; instead, it provides a thorough exploration of an important yet understudied design space related to recent advances in text-to-image synthesis -- specifically, the deep fusion of large language models (LLMs) and diffusion transformers (DiTs) for multi-modal generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-deep-fusion-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalizing Large Language Models using Retrieval Augmented Generation and Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-large-language-models-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of large language models (LLMs) has allowed numerous applications, including the generation of queried responses, to be leveraged in chatbots and other conversational assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalizing-large-language-models-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Agnostic Augmentations for Unknown Variations: Out-of-Distribution Generalisation in MRI Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-agnostic-augmentations-for-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation models are often trained on curated datasets, leading to performance degradation when deployed in real-world clinical settings due to mismatches between training and test distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-agnostic-augmentations-for-unknown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-driven identification of repetitions in multi-variate time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-driven-identification-of-repetitions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many multi-variate time series obtained in the natural sciences and engineering possess a repetitive behavior, as for instance state-space trajectories of industrial machines in discrete automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-driven-identification-of-repetitions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Feasibility Matter? Understanding the Impact of Feasibility on Synthetic Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-feasibility-matter-understanding-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, mixing feasible and infeasible images in training datasets does not significantly impact performance compared to using purely feasible or infeasible datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-feasibility-matter-understanding-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAL: Searching Expandable Architectures for Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-searching-expandable-architectures-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incremental learning is a machine learning paradigm where a model learns from a sequential stream of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-searching-expandable-architectures-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Implicit Visual Misunderstandings in Multimodal Large Language Models through Attention Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-implicit-visual-misunderstandings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements have enhanced the capability of Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) to comprehend multi-image information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-implicit-visual-misunderstandings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMRL++: Parameter-Efficient and Interaction-Aware Representation Learning for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrl-parameter-efficient-and-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During training, both class and representation features are jointly optimized: a trainable projection layer is applied to representation tokens for task adaptation, while the projection layer for class token remains frozen to retain pre-trained knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrl-parameter-efficient-and-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified and Scalable Membership Inference Method for Visual Self-supervised Encoder via Part-aware Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-and-scalable-membership-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this setting, considering that self-supervised model could be trained by completely different self-supervised paradigms, e. g., masked image modeling and contrastive learning, with complex training details, we propose a unified membership inference method called PartCrop.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-and-scalable-membership-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Wireless Localization Model (LWLM): A Foundation Model for Positioning in 6G Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-wireless-localization-model-lwlm-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate and robust localization is a critical enabler for emerging 5G and 6G applications, including autonomous driving, extended reality (XR), and smart manufacturing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-wireless-localization-model-lwlm-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Model Explanations without Ground Truth</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-model-explanations-without-ground</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current explanation evaluation frameworks measure quality by comparing against ideal "ground-truth" explanations, or by verifying model sensitivity to important inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-model-explanations-without-ground</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIPHEI-ViT: Multiplex Immunofluorescence Prediction from H&amp;E Images using ViT Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miphei-vit-multiplex-immunofluorescence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results indicate that our model effectively captures the complex relationships between nuclear morphologies in their tissue context, as visible in H&E images and molecular markers defining specific cell types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miphei-vit-multiplex-immunofluorescence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRSplat: Fast and Robust Gaussian Splatting for Virtual Reality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrsplat-fast-and-robust-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, 3DGS faces key challenges in virtual reality (VR): (1) temporal artifacts, such as popping during head movements, (2) projection-based distortions that result in disturbing and view-inconsistent floaters, and (3) reduced framerates when rendering large numbers of Gaussians, falling below the critical threshold for VR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vrsplat-fast-and-robust-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoPentest: Enhancing Vulnerability Management With Autonomous LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopentest-enhancing-vulnerability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent area of increasing research is the use of Large Language Models (LLMs) in penetration testing, which promises to reduce costs and thus allow for higher frequency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autopentest-enhancing-vulnerability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing LLM Text Annotation Skills: A Study on Human Rights Violations in Social Media Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-llm-text-annotation-skills-a-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the era of increasingly sophisticated natural language processing (NLP) systems, large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable potential for diverse applications, including tasks requiring nuanced textual understanding and contextual reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-llm-text-annotation-skills-a-study</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
