<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 21:07:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Connecting the Dots: Floorplan Reconstruction Using Two-Level Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-the-dots-floorplan-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we formulate floorplan reconstruction as a single-stage structured prediction task: find a variable-size set of polygons, which in turn are variable-length sequences of ordered vertices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-the-dots-floorplan-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Invariance: Test-Time Label-Shift Adaptation for Distributions with "Spurious" Correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-invariance-test-time-label-shift</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spurious correlations, or correlations that change across domains where a model can be deployed, present significant challenges to real-world applications of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-invariance-test-time-label-shift</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to design without prior data: Discovering generalizable design strategies using deep learning and tree search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-design-without-prior-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ultimate goal for a design agent is the ability to learn generalizable design behavior in a problem space without having seen it before.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-design-without-prior-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning-free Plug-and-Play Hyperspectral Image Deconvolution with Deep Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-free-plug-and-play-hyperspectral-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deconvolution is a widely used strategy to mitigate the blurring and noisy degradation of hyperspectral images~(HSI) generated by the acquisition devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-free-plug-and-play-hyperspectral-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperFusion: Multilevel LiDAR-Camera Fusion for Long-Range HD Map Generation and Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superfusion-multilevel-lidar-camera-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel network named SuperFusion, exploiting the fusion of LiDAR and camera data at multiple levels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superfusion-multilevel-lidar-camera-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically generating question-answer pairs for assessing basic reading comprehension in Swedish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-generating-question-answer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an evaluation of the quality of automatically generated reading comprehension questions from Swedish text, using the Quinductor method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatically-generating-question-answer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantile Constrained Reinforcement Learning: A Reinforcement Learning Framework Constraining Outage Probability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-constrained-reinforcement-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a framework, named Quantile Constrained RL (QCRL), to constrain the quantile of the distribution of the cumulative sum cost that is a necessary and sufficient condition to satisfy the outage constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-constrained-reinforcement-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An adaptive shortest-solution guided decimation approach to sparse high-dimensional linear regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-shortest-solution-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-dimensional linear regression model is the most popular statistical model for high-dimensional data, but it is quite a challenging task to achieve a sparse set of regression coefficients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-adaptive-shortest-solution-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Visual Feature Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-visual-feature-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many visualization techniques have been created to help explain the behavior of convolutional neural networks (CNNs), but they largely consist of static diagrams that convey limited information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-visual-feature-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refined Semantic Enhancement towards Frequency Diffusion for Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refined-semantic-enhancement-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel Refined Semantic enhancement method towards Frequency Diffusion (RSFD), a captioning model that constantly perceives the linguistic representation of the infrequent tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refined-semantic-enhancement-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MicroAST: Towards Super-Fast Ultra-Resolution Arbitrary Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microast-towards-super-fast-ultra-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The style encoder, coupled with a modulator, encodes the style image into learnable dual-modulation signals that modulate both intermediate features and convolutional filters of the decoder, thus injecting more sophisticated and flexible style signals to guide the stylizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/microast-towards-super-fast-ultra-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Dense Object Descriptors from Multiple Views for Low-shot Category Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dense-object-descriptors-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A hallmark of the deep learning era for computer vision is the successful use of large-scale labeled datasets to train feature representations for tasks ranging from object recognition and semantic segmentation to optical flow estimation and novel view synthesis of 3D scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dense-object-descriptors-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Category Discovery with Decoupled Prototypical Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-category-discovery-with-decoupled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the coupled training approach prevents these models transferring category-specific knowledge explicitly from labeled data to unlabeled data, which can lose high-level semantic information and impair model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-category-discovery-with-decoupled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Representation of Asymmetrical Distances with Interval Quasimetric Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-representation-of-asymmetrical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Asymmetrical distance structures (quasimetrics) are ubiquitous in our lives and are gaining more attention in machine learning applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-representation-of-asymmetrical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-analysis of individualized treatment rules via sign-coherency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-analysis-of-individualized-treatment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical treatments tailored to a patient's baseline characteristics hold the potential of improving patient outcomes while reducing negative side effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-analysis-of-individualized-treatment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Task-Aware Asynchronous Multi-Task Model with Class Incremental Contrastive Learning for Surgical Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-aware-asynchronous-multi-task-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conclusion: The proposed multi-task model was able to adapt to domain shifts, incorporate novel instruments in the target domain, and perform tool-tissue interaction detection and report generation on par with single-task models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/task-aware-asynchronous-multi-task-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Critical Analysis of Classifier Selection in Learned Bloom Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-critical-analysis-of-classifier-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learned Bloom Filters, i. e., models induced from data via machine learning techniques and solving the approximate set membership problem, have recently been introduced with the aim of enhancing the performance of standard Bloom Filters, with special focus on space occupancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-critical-analysis-of-classifier-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MixFairFace: Towards Ultimate Fairness via MixFair Adapter in Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixfairface-towards-ultimate-fairness-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose MixFairFace framework to improve the fairness in face recognition models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixfairface-towards-ultimate-fairness-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DQ-DETR: Dual Query Detection Transformer for Phrase Extraction and Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dq-detr-dual-query-detection-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As phrase extraction can be regarded as a $1$D text segmentation problem, we formulate PEG as a dual detection problem and propose a novel DQ-DETR model, which introduces dual queries to probe different features from image and text for object prediction and phrase mask prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dq-detr-dual-query-detection-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed neural networks with unknown measurement noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-with-unknown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) constitute a flexible approach to both finding solutions and identifying parameters of partial differential equations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-with-unknown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Mirror Detection via Multi-level Heterogeneous Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mirror-detection-via-multi-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present HetNet (Multi-level \textbf{Het}erogeneous \textbf{Net}work), a highly efficient mirror detection network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-mirror-detection-via-multi-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Learning for Multi-modal Medical Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-learning-for-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an effective graph-based framework called HetMed (Heterogeneous Graph Learning for Multi-modal Medical Data Analysis) for fusing the multi-modal medical data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-learning-for-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Effectiveness of Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to choose the tunable parameters?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-effectiveness-of-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Dynamic Patterns from Spatiotemporal Data with Time-Varying Low-Rank Autoregression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-dynamic-patterns-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the temporal context, the complex time-varying system behaviors can be revealed by the temporal modes in the proposed model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-dynamic-patterns-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Exclusivity Training and Primitive Augmentation to Induce Compositionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-exclusivity-training-and-primitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent datasets expose the lack of the systematic generalization ability in standard sequence-to-sequence models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-exclusivity-training-and-primitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Interspecies Face Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-interspecies-face-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are three main obstacles for interspecies face understanding: (1) lack of animal data compared to human, (2) ambiguous connection between faces of various animals, and (3) extreme shape and style variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-interspecies-face-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study of Representational Properties of Unsupervised Anomaly Detection in Brain MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-representational-properties-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly detection in MRI is of high clinical value in imaging and diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-of-representational-properties-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easy Begun is Half Done: Spatial-Temporal Graph Modeling with ST-Curriculum Dropout</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easy-begun-is-half-done-spatial-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatial-temporal (ST) graph modeling, such as traffic speed forecasting and taxi demand prediction, is an important task in deep learning area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easy-begun-is-half-done-spatial-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recent Advances in RecBole: Extensions with more Practical Considerations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-recbole-extensions-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to show the recent update in RecBole, we write this technical report to introduce our latest improvements on RecBole.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recent-advances-in-recbole-extensions-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceive, Ground, Reason, and Act: A Benchmark for General-purpose Visual Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceive-ground-reason-and-act-a-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current computer vision models, unlike the human visual system, cannot yet achieve general-purpose visual understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceive-ground-reason-and-act-a-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-SNARF: A Fast Deformer for Articulated Neural Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-snarf-a-fast-deformer-for-articulated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge in making such methods applicable to articulated objects, such as the human body, is to model the deformation of 3D locations between the rest pose (a canonical space) and the deformed space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-snarf-a-fast-deformer-for-articulated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactive Robot Assistance via Spatio-Temporal Object Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactive-robot-assistance-via-spatio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Proactive robot assistance enables a robot to anticipate and provide for a user's needs without being explicitly asked.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proactive-robot-assistance-via-spatio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Sample Complexity of Representation Learning in Multi-task Bandits with Global and Local structure</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-sample-complexity-of-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Arms consist of two components: one that is shared across tasks (that we call representation) and one that is task-specific (that we call predictor).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-sample-complexity-of-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepAngle: Fast calculation of contact angles in tomography images using deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepangle-fast-calculation-of-contact-angles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeepAngle is a machine learning-based method to determine the contact angles of different phases in the tomography images of porous materials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepangle-fast-calculation-of-contact-angles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imperceptible Adversarial Attack via Invertible Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imperceptible-adversarial-attack-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adding perturbations via utilizing auxiliary gradient information or discarding existing details of the benign images are two common approaches for generating adversarial examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imperceptible-adversarial-attack-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shielding in Resource-Constrained Goal POMDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shielding-in-resource-constrained-goal-pomdps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider partially observable Markov decision processes (POMDPs) modeling an agent that needs a supply of a certain resource (e. g., electricity stored in batteries) to operate correctly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shielding-in-resource-constrained-goal-pomdps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGFN: Magnitude-Contrastive Glance-and-Focus Network for Weakly-Supervised Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgfn-magnitude-contrastive-glance-and-focus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly supervised detection of anomalies in surveillance videos is a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgfn-magnitude-contrastive-glance-and-focus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Recommendations from User Actions in the Item-poor Insurance Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-recommendations-from-user-actions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we present a recurrent neural network recommendation model that uses past user sessions as signals for learning recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-recommendations-from-user-actions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Multimodal Entity-Relation Extraction Based on Edge-enhanced Graph Alignment Network and Word-pair Relation Tagging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multimodal-entity-relation-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper is the first to propose jointly performing MNER and MRE as a joint multimodal entity-relation extraction task (JMERE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-multimodal-entity-relation-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G^3: Geolocation via Guidebook Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-3-geolocation-via-guidebook-grounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose the task of Geolocation via Guidebook Grounding that uses a dataset of StreetView images from a diverse set of locations and an associated textual guidebook for GeoGuessr, a popular interactive geolocation game.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-3-geolocation-via-guidebook-grounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weight Predictor Network with Feature Selection for Small Sample Tabular Biomedical Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weight-predictor-network-with-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tabular biomedical data is often high-dimensional but with a very small number of samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weight-predictor-network-with-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Adaptive Network Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-adaptive-network-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive evaluation and multiple comparisons on a variety of benchmarks, including standard and long-tailed image classification, semantic segmentation, and text classification, demonstrate the superiority of the proposed method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-adaptive-network-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Global Sensing Quality Maximization: A Configuration Optimization Scheme for Camera Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-global-sensing-quality-maximization-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we form a single quantity that measures the sensing quality of the targets by the camera network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-global-sensing-quality-maximization-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Sparse Regression Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-sparse-regression-trees</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regression trees are one of the oldest forms of AI models, and their predictions can be made without a calculator, which makes them broadly useful, particularly for high-stakes applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-sparse-regression-trees</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who is Gambling? Finding Cryptocurrency Gamblers Using Multi-modal Retrieval Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-is-gambling-finding-cryptocurrency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, decentralized applications have also attracted intense attention from the online gambling community, with more and more decentralized gambling platforms created through the help of smart contracts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/who-is-gambling-finding-cryptocurrency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Discrete Diffusion for Simultaneous Vision-Language Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-discrete-diffusion-for-simultaneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently developed discrete diffusion models perform extraordinarily well in the text-to-image task, showing significant promise for handling the multi-modality signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-discrete-diffusion-for-simultaneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Font Rasterization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-font-rasterization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning techniques and applications have revolutionized artistic creation and manipulation in many domains (text, images, music); however, fonts have not yet been integrated with deep learning architectures in a manner that supports their multi-scale nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-font-rasterization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Image Segmentation Review: The success of U-Net</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-review-the-success</link>
      <description><![CDATA[U-Net is the most widespread image segmentation architecture due to its flexibility, optimized modular design, and success in all medical image modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-image-segmentation-review-the-success</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAR: Physics-Principled Building Environment for Control and Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bear-physics-principled-building-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in reinforcement learning algorithms have opened doors for researchers to operate and optimize building energy management systems autonomously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bear-physics-principled-building-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Time Series is Worth 64 Words: Long-term Forecasting with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-64-words-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our channel-independent patch time series Transformer (PatchTST) can improve the long-term forecasting accuracy significantly when compared with that of SOTA Transformer-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-time-series-is-worth-64-words-long-term</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
