<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 09:16:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptation of uncertainty-penalized Bayesian information criterion for parametric partial differential equation discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-uncertainty-penalized-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-driven discovery of partial differential equations (PDEs) has emerged as a promising approach for deriving governing physics when domain knowledge about observed data is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-uncertainty-penalized-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximally Permissive Reward Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximally-permissive-reward-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that learning using such "maximally permissive" reward machines results in higher rewards than learning using RMs based on a single plan.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maximally-permissive-reward-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAIR: Hypernetworks-based All-in-One Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hair-hypernetworks-based-all-in-one-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be more specific, the Classifier is a simple image classification network which is used to generate a Global Information Vector (GIV) that contains the degradation information of the input image; And the HSNs can be seen as a simple Fully-connected Neural Network that receive the GIV and output parameters for the corresponding modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hair-hypernetworks-based-all-in-one-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snuffy: Efficient Whole Slide Image Classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snuffy-efficient-whole-slide-image-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our sparsity pattern is tailored for pathology and is theoretically proven to be a universal approximator with the tightest probabilistic sharp bound on the number of layers for sparse transformers, to date.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snuffy-efficient-whole-slide-image-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Normalized AOPC: Fixing Misleading Faithfulness Metrics for Feature Attribution Explainability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalized-aopc-fixing-misleading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural network predictions are notoriously difficult to interpret.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/normalized-aopc-fixing-misleading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IIU: Independent Inference Units for Knowledge-based Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iiu-independent-inference-units-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Independent Inference Units (IIU) for fine-grained multi-modal reasoning to decompose intra-modal information by the functionally independent units.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iiu-independent-inference-units-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Part Discovery via Dual Representation Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-part-discovery-via-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object parts serve as crucial intermediate representations in various downstream tasks, but part-level representation learning still has not received as much attention as other vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-part-discovery-via-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InVAErt networks for amortized inference and identifiability analysis of lumped parameter hemodynamic models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invaert-networks-for-amortized-inference-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimation of cardiovascular model parameters from electronic health records (EHR) poses a significant challenge primarily due to lack of identifiability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invaert-networks-for-amortized-inference-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Fairness Analytics: Quantifying Fairness in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-fairness-analytics-quantifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated Learning (FL) is a privacy-enhancing technology for distributed ML.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-fairness-analytics-quantifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Medical Anomaly Detection in Brain MRI: An Image Quality Assessment Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-medical-anomaly-detection-in-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstruction-based methods, particularly those leveraging autoencoders, have been widely adopted to perform anomaly detection in brain MRI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-medical-anomaly-detection-in-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FuseChat: Knowledge Fusion of Chat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusechat-knowledge-fusion-of-chat-models-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new framework for the knowledge fusion of chat LLMs through two main stages, resulting in FuseChat.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusechat-knowledge-fusion-of-chat-models-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArabLegalEval: A Multitask Benchmark for Assessing Arabic Legal Knowledge in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arablegaleval-a-multitask-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the evaluation of LLMs' legal knowledge, particularly in non-English languages such as Arabic, remains under-explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arablegaleval-a-multitask-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved transferability of self-supervised learning models through batch normalization finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-transferability-of-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At a cost of extra training of only 0. 16% model parameters, in case of ResNet-50, we acquire a proxy task that (i) has a stronger correlation with end-to-end finetuned performance, (ii) improves the linear probing performance in the many- and few-shot learning regimes and (iii) in some cases, outperforms both linear probing and end-to-end finetuning, reaching the state-of-the-art performance on a pathology dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-transferability-of-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-driven identification of latent port-Hamiltonian systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-identification-of-latent-port</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this space, a linear pH system, that satisfies the pH properties per construction, is parameterized by the weights of a neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-identification-of-latent-port</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining an Agent's Future Beliefs through Temporally Decomposing Future Reward Estimators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-an-agent-s-future-beliefs-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Future reward estimation is a core component of reinforcement learning agents; i. e., Q-value and state-value functions, predicting an agent's sum of future rewards.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-an-agent-s-future-beliefs-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLCA++: Unleash the Power of Sequential Fine-tuning for Continual Learning with Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slca-unleash-the-power-of-sequential-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that the overly fast representation learning and the biased classification layer constitute this particular problem, we introduce the advanced Slow Learner with Classifier Alignment (SLCA++) framework to unleash the power of Seq FT, serving as a strong baseline approach for CLPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slca-unleash-the-power-of-sequential-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of Comprehensive Data Preprocessing on Predictive Modelling of COVID-19 Mortality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-comprehensive-data-preprocessing-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study evaluates the impact of a custom data preprocessing pipeline on ten machine learning models predicting COVID-19 mortality using data from Our World in Data (OWID).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-comprehensive-data-preprocessing-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery from Time-Series Data with Short-Term Invariance-Based Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-from-time-series-data-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal discovery from time-series data aims to capture both intra-slice (contemporaneous) and inter-slice (time-lagged) causality between variables within the temporal chain, which is crucial for various scientific disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-from-time-series-data-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CatalogBank: A Structured and Interoperable Catalog Dataset with a Semi-Automatic Annotation Tool (DocumentLabeler) for Engineering System Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catalogbank-a-structured-and-interoperable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of document engineering and Natural Language Processing (NLP), the integration of digitally born catalogs into product design processes presents a novel avenue for enhancing information extraction and interoperability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catalogbank-a-structured-and-interoperable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Language Models' Worldview for Fiction Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-language-models-worldview-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We highlight the limitations of current LLMs in fiction writing and advocate for future research to test and create story worlds for LLMs to reside in.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-language-models-worldview-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOReloc: Graph-based Object-Level Relocalization for Visual SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goreloc-graph-based-object-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It determines the pose of a camera sensor by robustly associating the object detections in the current frame with 3D objects in a lightweight object-level map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goreloc-graph-based-object-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColorMamba: Towards High-quality NIR-to-RGB Spectral Translation with Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colormamba-towards-high-quality-nir-to-rgb</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explore global long-range dependencies and local context for efficient spectral translation, we introduce learnable padding tokens to enhance the distinction of image boundaries and prevent potential confusion within the sequence model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colormamba-towards-high-quality-nir-to-rgb</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating High-Fidelity Waveform Generation via Adversarial Flow Matching Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-high-fidelity-waveform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces PeriodWave-Turbo, a high-fidelity and high-efficient waveform generation model via adversarial flow matching optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-high-fidelity-waveform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persistence Image from 3D Medical Image: Superpixel and Optimized Gaussian Coefficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistence-image-from-3d-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topological data analysis (TDA) uncovers crucial properties of objects in medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistence-image-from-3d-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIVE: Towards Descriptive and Diverse Visual Commonsense Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-towards-descriptive-and-diverse-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towards human-level visual understanding, visual commonsense generation has been introduced to generate commonsense inferences beyond images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-towards-descriptive-and-diverse-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treat Stillness with Movement: Remote Sensing Change Detection via Coarse-grained Temporal Foregrounds Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treat-stillness-with-movement-remote-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a motion augmented strategy that leverages motion cues as an additional output to aggregate with the spatial features for improved results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treat-stillness-with-movement-remote-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Evaluation of 3D Reconstruction Methods for Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-evaluation-of-3d-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to answer this question by proposing a novel benchmark for measuring the impact of 3D reconstruction quality on pose estimation accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-evaluation-of-3d-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multi-task Adversarial Attack Against Face Authentication</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-adversarial-attack-against-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a multi-task adversarial attack algorithm called MTADV that are adaptable for multiple users or systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multi-task-adversarial-attack-against-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MambaMIM: Pre-training Mamba with State Space Token-interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamim-pre-training-mamba-with-state-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we introduce a generative self-supervised learning method for Mamba (MambaMIM) based on Selective Structure State Space Sequence Token-interpolation (S6T), a general-purpose pre-training method for arbitrary Mamba architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mambamim-pre-training-mamba-with-state-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monte Carlo Path Tracing and Statistical Event Detection for Event Camera Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-path-tracing-and-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel event camera simulation system fully based on physically based Monte Carlo path tracing with adaptive path sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monte-carlo-path-tracing-and-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Vision Model Compression Techniques for Embedded Systems: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-vision-model-compression-techniques</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks have consistently represented the state of the art in most computer vision problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computer-vision-model-compression-techniques</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Category-Prompt Refined Feature Learning for Long-Tailed Multi-Label Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-prompt-refined-feature-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world data consistently exhibits a long-tailed distribution, often spanning multiple categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/category-prompt-refined-feature-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Causal Reasoning Benchmark: Challenging Vision Large Language Models to Infer Causal Links Between Siamese Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-causal-reasoning-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, will these causalities remain straightforward for Vision Large Language Models (VLLMs) when only visual hints are provided?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-causal-reasoning-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum-inspired Interpretable Deep Learning Architecture for Text Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-inspired-interpretable-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text has become the predominant form of communication on social media, embedding a wealth of emotional nuances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-inspired-interpretable-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Model Interpretability with Local Attribution over Global Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-model-interpretability-with-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The LA algorithm comprises both targeted and untargeted exploration phases, which are designed to effectively generate intermediate states for attribution that thoroughly encompass the local space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-model-interpretability-with-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved 3D Whole Heart Geometry from Sparse CMR Slices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-3d-whole-heart-geometry-from-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we explore the combination of Slice Shifting Algorithm (SSA), Spatial Transformer Network (STN), and Label Transformer Network (LTN) to: 1) correct respiratory motion between segmented slices, and 2) transform sparse segmentation data into dense segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-3d-whole-heart-geometry-from-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-time Video Compressive Sensing on Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-video-compressive-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fast evolving mobile devices and existing high-performance video SCI reconstruction algorithms motivate us to develop mobile reconstruction methods for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-video-compressive-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAPLe: Backdoor Attacks on Medical Foundational Models using Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baple-backdoor-attacks-on-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the latest developments in learnable prompts, this work introduces a method to embed a backdoor into the medical foundation model during the prompt learning phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baple-backdoor-attacks-on-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sum-Product-Set Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sum-product-set-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily internet communication relies heavily on tree-structured graphs, embodied by popular data formats such as XML and JSON.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sum-product-set-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BadMerging: Backdoor Attacks Against Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badmerging-backdoor-attacks-against-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that a merged model may incorporate tasks from different domains, BadMerging can jointly compromise the tasks provided by the adversary (on-task attack) and other contributors (off-task attack) and solve the corresponding unique challenges with novel attack designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badmerging-backdoor-attacks-against-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Semi-supervised Multimodal Medical Image Segmentation via Cross Modality Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semi-supervised-multimodal-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a channel-wise semantic consistency loss, our framework ensures alignment of modality-independent information from a feature-wise perspective across modalities, thereby fortifying it against misalignments in multimodal scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semi-supervised-multimodal-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Distillation with Refined Logits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-with-refined-logits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research on knowledge distillation has increasingly focused on logit distillation because of its simplicity, effectiveness, and versatility in model compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-with-refined-logits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pattern-Matching Dynamic Memory Network for Dual-Mode Traffic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pattern-matching-dynamic-memory-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PM-DMNet employs a novel dynamic memory network to capture traffic pattern features with only O(N) complexity, significantly reducing computational overhead while achieving excellent performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pattern-matching-dynamic-memory-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Gradient Flows of MMD Functionals with Distance Kernel and Cauchy Problems on Quantile Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-gradient-flows-of-mmd-functionals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We give a comprehensive description of Wasserstein gradient flows of maximum mean discrepancy (MMD) functionals $\mathcal F_\nu := \text{MMD}_K^2(\cdot, \nu)$ towards given target measures $\nu$ on the real line, where we focus on the negative distance kernel $K(x, y) := -|x-y|$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-gradient-flows-of-mmd-functionals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spitting Image: Modular Superpixel Tokenization in Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spitting-image-modular-superpixel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformer (ViT) architectures traditionally employ a grid-based approach to tokenization independent of the semantic content of an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spitting-image-modular-superpixel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge in Superposition: Unveiling the Failures of Lifelong Knowledge Editing for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-in-superposition-unveiling-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, this is the first study to investigate knowledge editing from the perspective of superposition and provides a comprehensive observation of superposition across numerous real-world language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-in-superposition-unveiling-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SigmaRL: A Sample-Efficient and Generalizable Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning Framework for Motion Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sigmarl-a-sample-efficient-and-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most RL agents exhibit a limited capacity to generalize, often focusing narrowly on specific scenarios, and are usually evaluated in similar or even the same scenarios seen during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sigmarl-a-sample-efficient-and-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesion-aware network for diabetic retinopathy diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-network-for-diabetic-retinopathy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a CNN-based DR diagnosis network with attention mechanism involved, termed lesion-aware network, to better capture lesion information from imbalanced data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-network-for-diabetic-retinopathy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitening Consistently Improves Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whitening-consistently-improves-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose incorporating ZCA whitening as the final layer of the encoder in self-supervised learning to enhance the quality of learned features by normalizing and decorrelating them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whitening-consistently-improves-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRFormer: Grouped Residual Self-Attention for Lightweight Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grformer-grouped-residual-self-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The code is available at \url{https://github. com/sisrformer/GRFormer}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grformer-grouped-residual-self-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
