<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 09:16:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multilook Coherent Imaging: Theoretical Guarantees and Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilook-coherent-imaging-theoretical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study both the theoretical and algorithmic aspects of likelihood-based approaches for multilook coherent imaging, providing a rigorous framework for analysis and method development.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilook-coherent-imaging-theoretical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EmergentTTS-Eval: Evaluating TTS Models on Complex Prosodic, Expressiveness, and Linguistic Challenges Using Model-as-a-Judge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergenttts-eval-evaluating-tts-models-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-Speech (TTS) benchmarks often fail to capture how well models handle nuanced and semantically complex text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergenttts-eval-evaluating-tts-models-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computational Algebra with Attention: Transformer Oracles for Border Basis Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-algebra-with-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solving systems of polynomial equations, particularly those with finitely many solutions, is a crucial challenge across many scientific fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computational-algebra-with-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Descriptor Is All You Need: Accurate Machine Learning of Nonadiabatic Coupling Vectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-descriptor-is-all-you-need-accurate-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the efficiency and robustness of our approach on a prototypical example of fully ML-driven FSSH simulations of fulvene targeting the SA-2-CASSCF(6, 6) electronic structure level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-descriptor-is-all-you-need-accurate-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeNRe: A French Gender-Neutral Rewriting System Using Collective Nouns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genre-a-french-gender-neutral-rewriting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A significant portion of the textual data used in the field of Natural Language Processing (NLP) exhibits gender biases, particularly due to the use of masculine generics (masculine words that are supposed to refer to mixed groups of men and women), which can perpetuate and amplify stereotypes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genre-a-french-gender-neutral-rewriting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impromptu VLA: Open Weights and Open Data for Driving Vision-Language-Action Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impromptu-vla-open-weights-and-open-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-Language-Action (VLA) models for autonomous driving show promise but falter in unstructured corner case scenarios, largely due to a scarcity of targeted benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impromptu-vla-open-weights-and-open-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-to-Dashboard: Multi-Agent LLM Framework for Insightful Visualization in Enterprise Analytics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-to-dashboard-multi-agent-llm-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of LLMs has led to the creation of diverse agentic systems in data analysis, utilizing LLMs' capabilities to improve insight generation and visualization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-to-dashboard-multi-agent-llm-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZIPA: A family of efficient models for multilingual phone recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipa-a-family-of-efficient-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ZIPA, a family of efficient speech models that advances the state-of-the-art performance of crosslinguistic phone recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipa-a-family-of-efficient-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Transferring Transferability: Towards a Theory for Size Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-transferring-transferability-towards-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many modern learning tasks require models that can take inputs of varying sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-transferring-transferability-towards-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Neural Scaling Laws Extrapolation with Prior-Fitted Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-neural-scaling-laws-extrapolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods mostly rely on point estimation and do not quantify uncertainty, which is crucial for real-world applications involving decision-making problems such as determining the expected performance improvements achievable by investing additional computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-neural-scaling-laws-extrapolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table-R1: Inference-Time Scaling for Table Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/table-r1-inference-time-scaling-for-table</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop and evaluate two post-training strategies to enable inference-time scaling: distillation from frontier model reasoning traces and reinforcement learning with verifiable rewards (RLVR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/table-r1-inference-time-scaling-for-table</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probability-Consistent Preference Optimization for Enhanced LLM Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probability-consistent-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in preference optimization have demonstrated significant potential for improving mathematical reasoning capabilities in large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probability-consistent-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProDiff: Prototype-Guided Diffusion for Minimal Information Trajectory Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodiff-prototype-guided-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing imputation methods rely on sparse trajectory or travel information, such as velocity, to infer missing points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodiff-prototype-guided-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$K^2$VAE: A Koopman-Kalman Enhanced Variational AutoEncoder for Probabilistic Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-2-vae-a-koopman-kalman-enhanced-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Probabilistic Time Series Forecasting (PTSF) plays a crucial role in decision-making across various fields, including economics, energy, and transportation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-2-vae-a-koopman-kalman-enhanced-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGD as Free Energy Minimization: A Thermodynamic View on Neural Network Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgd-as-free-energy-minimization-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UP models consistently follow free energy minimization, with temperature increasing monotonically with LR, while for OP models, the temperature effectively drops to zero at low LRs, causing SGD to minimize the loss directly and converge to an optimum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgd-as-free-energy-minimization-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWE-bench Goes Live!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-bench-goes-live</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While SWE-bench and its variants have become standard in this domain, they suffer from key limitations: they have not been updated since their initial releases, cover a narrow set of repositories, and depend heavily on manual effort for instance construction and environment setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swe-bench-goes-live</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafeScientist: Toward Risk-Aware Scientific Discoveries by LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safescientist-toward-risk-aware-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language model (LLM) agents have significantly accelerated scientific discovery automation, yet concurrently raised critical ethical and safety concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safescientist-toward-risk-aware-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Guidance Is a Controllable Policy Improvement Operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-guidance-is-a-controllable-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting framework, CFGRL, is trained with the simplicity of supervised learning, yet can further improve on the policies in the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-guidance-is-a-controllable-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Interpretable PDEs: Harmonizing Fourier Insights with Attention for Scalable and Interpretable Physics Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-interpretable-pdes-harmonizing-fourier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attention mechanisms have emerged as transformative tools in core AI domains such as natural language processing and computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-interpretable-pdes-harmonizing-fourier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised feature learning for cardiac Cine MR image reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-feature-learning-for-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a self-supervised feature learning assisted reconstruction (SSFL-Recon) framework for MRI reconstruction to address the limitation of existing supervised learning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-feature-learning-for-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisit CP Tensor Decomposition: Statistical Optimality and Fast Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-cp-tensor-decomposition-statistical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we revisit CP tensor decomposition from a statistical perspective and provide a comprehensive theoretical analysis of ALS under a signal-plus-noise model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-cp-tensor-decomposition-statistical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Generation and Latent Projection Denoising of Rim Lesions in Multiple Sclerosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-generation-and-latent-projection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We produce synthetic quantitative susceptibility maps of paramagnetic rim lesions and show that inclusion of such synthetic data improves classifier performance and provide a multi-channel extension to generate accompanying contrasts and probabilistic segmentation maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-generation-and-latent-projection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Refusal in Language Models with Sparse Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-refusal-in-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Refusal is a key safety behavior in aligned language models, yet the internal mechanisms driving refusals remain opaque.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-refusal-in-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Knowledge to Noise: CTIM-Rover and the Pitfalls of Episodic Memory in Software Engineering Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-knowledge-to-noise-ctim-rover-and-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce CTIM-Rover, an AI agent for Software Engineering (SE) built on top of AutoCodeRover (Zhang et al., 2024) that extends agentic reasoning frameworks with an episodic memory, more specifically, a general and repository-level Cross-Task-Instance Memory (CTIM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-knowledge-to-noise-ctim-rover-and-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-based HSE Compliance Assessment: Benchmark, Performance, and Advancements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-based-hse-compliance-assessment-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Health, Safety, and Environment (HSE) compliance assessment demands dynamic real-time decision-making under complicated regulations and complex human-machine-environment interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-based-hse-compliance-assessment-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Panaceas for Improving Low-Rank Decomposition in Communication-Efficient Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-panaceas-for-improving-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the training efficiency of federated learning (FL), previous research has employed low-rank decomposition techniques to reduce communication overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-panaceas-for-improving-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threading the Needle: Reweaving Chain-of-Thought Reasoning to Explain Human Label Variation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threading-the-needle-reweaving-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent rise of reasoning-tuned Large Language Models (LLMs)--which generate chains of thought (CoTs) before giving the final answer--has attracted significant attention and offers new opportunities for gaining insights into human label variation, which refers to plausible differences in how multiple annotators label the same data instance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threading-the-needle-reweaving-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Warmup Dilemma: How Learning Rate Strategies Impact Speech-to-Text Model Convergence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-warmup-dilemma-how-learning-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large-scale models presents challenges not only in terms of resource requirements but also in terms of their convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-warmup-dilemma-how-learning-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muddit: Liberating Generation Beyond Text-to-Image with a Unified Discrete Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muddit-liberating-generation-beyond-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike prior unified diffusion models trained from scratch, Muddit integrates strong visual priors from a pretrained text-to-image backbone with a lightweight text decoder, enabling flexible and high-quality multimodal generation under a unified architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muddit-liberating-generation-beyond-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spoken Language Modeling with Duration-Penalized Self-Supervised Units</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoken-language-modeling-with-duration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate SLM performance as we vary codebook size and unit coarseness using the simple duration-penalized dynamic programming (DPDP) method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spoken-language-modeling-with-duration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merge-Friendly Post-Training Quantization for Multi-Target Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merge-friendly-post-training-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In practical scenarios, quantization is often applied to target-specific data, but this process restricts the domain of interest and introduces discretization effects, making model merging highly non-trivial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merge-friendly-post-training-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDR-Agent: Intelligent Selection and Execution of Clinical Decision Rules Using Large Language Model Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdr-agent-intelligent-selection-and-execution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clinical decision-making is inherently complex and fast-paced, particularly in emergency departments (EDs) where critical, rapid and high-stakes decisions are made.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cdr-agent-intelligent-selection-and-execution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ML-Agent: Reinforcing LLM Agents for Autonomous Machine Learning Engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ml-agent-reinforcing-llm-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Focusing on this, for the first time, we explore the paradigm of learning-based agentic ML, where an LLM agent learns through interactive experimentation on ML tasks using online reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ml-agent-reinforcing-llm-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DyePack: Provably Flagging Test Set Contamination in LLMs Using Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyepack-provably-flagging-test-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For open-ended generation tasks, it generalizes well and identifies all contaminated models on Alpaca with a guaranteed false positive rate of just 0. 127% using six backdoors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dyepack-provably-flagging-test-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo Multi-Source Domain Generalization: Bridging the Gap Between Single and Multi-Source Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-multi-source-domain-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose Pseudo Multi-source Domain Generalization (PMDG), a novel framework that enables the application of sophisticated MDG algorithms in more practical Single-source Domain Generalization (SDG) settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-multi-source-domain-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document-Level Text Generation with Minimum Bayes Risk Decoding using Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-text-generation-with-minimum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although MBR decoding is shown to be effective in a wide range of sentence-level text generation tasks, its performance on document-level text generation tasks is limited as many of the utility functions are designed for evaluating the utility of sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-text-generation-with-minimum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Access Diffusion Fisher: Within the Outer Product Span Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-access-diffusion-fisher-within</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the outer-product structure, we develop two efficient approximation algorithms to access the trace and matrix-vector multiplication of DF, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-access-diffusion-fisher-within</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrossLinear: Plug-and-Play Cross-Correlation Embedding for Time Series Forecasting with Exogenous Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslinear-plug-and-play-cross-correlation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series forecasting with exogenous variables is a critical emerging paradigm that presents unique challenges in modeling dependencies between variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crosslinear-plug-and-play-cross-correlation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallo4: High-Fidelity Dynamic Portrait Animation via Direct Preference Optimization and Temporal Motion Modulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallo4-high-fidelity-dynamic-portrait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating highly dynamic and photorealistic portrait animations driven by audio and skeletal motion remains challenging due to the need for precise lip synchronization, natural facial expressions, and high-fidelity body motion dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallo4-high-fidelity-dynamic-portrait</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VAU-R1: Advancing Video Anomaly Understanding via Reinforcement Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vau-r1-advancing-video-anomaly-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video Anomaly Understanding (VAU) is essential for applications such as smart cities, security surveillance, and disaster alert systems, yet remains challenging due to its demand for fine-grained spatio-temporal perception and robust reasoning under ambiguity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vau-r1-advancing-video-anomaly-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jigsaw-R1: A Study of Rule-based Visual Reinforcement Learning with Jigsaw Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jigsaw-r1-a-study-of-rule-based-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although these observations are based on jigsaw puzzles and may vary across other visual tasks, this research contributes a valuable piece of jigsaw to the larger puzzle of collective understanding rule-based visual RL and its potential in multimodal learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jigsaw-r1-a-study-of-rule-based-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen Look Again: Guiding Vision-Language Reasoning Models to Re-attention Visual Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-look-again-guiding-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference time scaling drives extended reasoning to enhance the performance of Vision-Language Models (VLMs), thus forming powerful Vision-Language Reasoning Models (VLRMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-look-again-guiding-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGREF: Masked Guidance for Any-Reference Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magref-masked-guidance-for-any-reference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video generation has made substantial strides with the emergence of deep generative models, especially diffusion-based approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magref-masked-guidance-for-any-reference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLDTracker: A Comprehensive Language Description for Visual Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cldtracker-a-comprehensive-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge these gaps and unlock the full potential of VLMs for VOT, we propose CLDTracker, a novel Comprehensive Language Description framework for robust visual Tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cldtracker-a-comprehensive-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VF-Eval: Evaluating Multimodal LLMs for Generating Feedback on AIGC Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vf-eval-evaluating-multimodal-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MLLMs have been widely studied for video question answering recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vf-eval-evaluating-multimodal-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreRA: A Frequency-Refined Augmentation for Contrastive Learning on Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frera-a-frequency-refined-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fully utilize the three properties, we propose the lightweight yet effective Frequency Refined Augmentation (FreRA) tailored for time series contrastive learning on classification tasks, which can be seamlessly integrated with contrastive learning frameworks in a plug-and-play manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frera-a-frequency-refined-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenUni: A Simple Baseline for Unified Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openuni-a-simple-baseline-for-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present OpenUni, a simple, lightweight, and fully open-source baseline for unifying multimodal understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openuni-a-simple-baseline-for-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subgraph Gaussian Embedding Contrast for Self-Supervised Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subgraph-gaussian-embedding-contrast-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach introduces a subgraph Gaussian embedding module, which adaptively maps subgraphs to a structured Gaussian space, ensuring the preservation of input subgraph characteristics while generating subgraphs with a controlled distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subgraph-gaussian-embedding-contrast-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D-AR: Diffusion via Autoregressive Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-ar-diffusion-via-autoregressive-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Diffusion via Autoregressive models (D-AR), a new paradigm recasting the image diffusion process as a vanilla autoregressive procedure in the standard next-token-prediction fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d-ar-diffusion-via-autoregressive-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepChest: Dynamic Gradient-Free Task Weighting for Effective Multi-Task Learning in Chest X-ray Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepchest-dynamic-gradient-free-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Multi-Task Learning (MTL) offers inherent advantages in complex domains such as medical imaging by enabling shared representation learning, effectively balancing task contributions remains a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepchest-dynamic-gradient-free-task</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
