<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 21:07:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Language as Polices: Reasoning for Coordinate-Level Embodied Control with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-as-polices-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate experimental results with LLMs that address robotics action planning problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-as-polices-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Ordering of Divergences for Variational Inference with Factorized Gaussian Approximations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ordering-of-divergences-for-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis covers the KL divergence, the R\'enyi divergences, and a score-based divergence that compares $\nabla\log p$ and $\nabla\log q$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ordering-of-divergences-for-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Diffusion Models to Real-World 3D LiDAR Scene Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-diffusion-models-to-real-world-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental evaluation shows that our method can complete the scene given a single LiDAR scan as input, producing a scene with more details compared to state-of-the-art scene completion methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-diffusion-models-to-real-world-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding Spatial Relations in Text-Only Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-spatial-relations-in-text-only</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper shows that text-only Language Models (LM) can learn to ground spatial relations like "left of" or "below" if they are provided with explicit location information of objects and they are properly trained to leverage those locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-spatial-relations-in-text-only</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nellie: Automated organelle segmentation, tracking, and hierarchical feature extraction in 2D/3D live-cell microscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nellie-automated-organelle-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The analysis of dynamic organelles remains a formidable challenge, though key to understanding biological processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nellie-automated-organelle-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RewardBench: Evaluating Reward Models for Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewardbench-evaluating-reward-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present RewardBench, a benchmark dataset and code-base for evaluation, to enhance scientific understanding of reward models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewardbench-evaluating-reward-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversity-aware Channel Pruning for StyleGAN Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-aware-channel-pruning-for-stylegan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, by assessing channel importance based on their sensitivities to latent vector perturbations, our method enhances the diversity of samples in the compressed model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversity-aware-channel-pruning-for-stylegan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LlamaFactory: Unified Efficient Fine-Tuning of 100+ Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamafactory-unified-efficient-fine-tuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient fine-tuning is vital for adapting large language models (LLMs) to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamafactory-unified-efficient-fine-tuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Point Learning and Refining for Category-Agnostic Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-point-learning-and-refining-for-category</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods only rely on the features extracted at support keypoints to predict or refine the keypoints on query image, but a few support feature vectors are local and inadequate for CAPE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-point-learning-and-refining-for-category</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H-vmunet: High-order Vision Mamba UNet for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-vmunet-high-order-vision-mamba-unet-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of medical image segmentation, variant models based on Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) and Visual Transformers (ViTs) as the base modules have been very widely developed and applied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h-vmunet-high-order-vision-mamba-unet-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Class-Agnostic Motion Prediction with Spatial and Temporal Consistency Regularizations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-class-agnostic-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we explore the feasibility of self-supervised motion prediction with only unlabeled LiDAR point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-class-agnostic-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical End-to-End Optical Music Recognition for Pianoform Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-end-to-end-optical-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(c) We train and fine-tune an end-to-end model to serve as a baseline on the dataset and employ the TEDn metric to evaluate the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-end-to-end-optical-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuzzleVQA: Diagnosing Multimodal Reasoning Challenges of Language Models with Abstract Visual Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzlevqa-diagnosing-multimodal-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As recognizing patterns and abstracting concepts are key to general intelligence, we introduce PuzzleVQA, a collection of puzzles based on abstract patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzlevqa-diagnosing-multimodal-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mora: Enabling Generalist Video Generation via A Multi-Agent Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mora-enabling-generalist-video-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sora is the first large-scale generalist video generation model that garnered significant attention across society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mora-enabling-generalist-video-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MTP: Advancing Remote Sensing Foundation Model via Multi-Task Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtp-advancing-remote-sensing-foundation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, transferring the pretrained models to downstream tasks may encounter task discrepancy due to their formulation of pretraining as image classification or object discrimination tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mtp-advancing-remote-sensing-foundation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sampling-based Framework for Hypothesis Testing on Large Attributed Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sampling-based-framework-for-hypothesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on real datasets demonstrate the ability of our framework to leverage common graph sampling methods for hypothesis testing, and the superiority of hypothesis-aware sampling in terms of accuracy and time efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sampling-based-framework-for-hypothesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arcee's MergeKit: A Toolkit for Merging Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcee-s-mergekit-a-toolkit-for-merging-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid expansion of the open-source language model landscape presents an opportunity to merge the competencies of these model checkpoints by combining their parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arcee-s-mergekit-a-toolkit-for-merging-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty quantification for data-driven weather models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-for-data-driven-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a case study on medium-range forecasts of selected weather variables over Europe, the probabilistic forecasts obtained by using the Pangu-Weather model in concert with uncertainty quantification methods show promising results and provide improvements over ensemble forecasts from the physics-based ensemble weather model of the European Centre for Medium-Range Weather Forecasts for lead times of up to 5 days.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-for-data-driven-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Reward Adjustment in Multi-Reward Reinforcement Learning for Counselor Reflection Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-reward-adjustment-in-multi-reward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of multi-reward reinforcement learning to jointly optimize for multiple text qualities for natural language generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-reward-adjustment-in-multi-reward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retina Vision Transformer (RetinaViT): Introducing Scaled Patches into Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retina-vision-transformer-retinavit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans see low and high spatial frequency components at the same time, and combine the information from both to form a visual scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retina-vision-transformer-retinavit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESIRE-ME: Domain-Enhanced Supervised Information REtrieval using Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desire-me-domain-enhanced-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-domain question answering requires retrieval systems able to cope with the diverse and varied nature of questions, providing accurate answers across a broad spectrum of query types and topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desire-me-domain-enhanced-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable and Stable Finetuning of Pretrained Language Models on Low-Resource Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-and-stable-finetuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained Language Models (PLMs) have advanced Natural Language Processing (NLP) tasks significantly, but finetuning PLMs on low-resource datasets poses significant challenges such as instability and overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-and-stable-finetuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Spatial-Temporal Aggregation for Skeleton-Aware Sign Language Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-spatial-temporal-aggregation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current methods utilize spatial graph modules and temporal modules to capture spatial and temporal features, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-spatial-temporal-aggregation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedFisher: Leveraging Fisher Information for One-Shot Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfisher-leveraging-fisher-information-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standard federated learning (FL) algorithms typically require multiple rounds of communication between the server and the clients, which has several drawbacks, including requiring constant network connectivity, repeated investment of computational resources, and susceptibility to privacy attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedfisher-leveraging-fisher-information-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Shift It: Test-Time Prototype Shifting for Zero-Shot Generalization with Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-shift-it-test-time-prototype-shifting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advancements in vision-language models (VLMs) have propelled the field of computer vision, particularly in the zero-shot learning setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-shift-it-test-time-prototype-shifting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowerFormer: Empowering Neural Architecture Encoding using a Flow-aware Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowerformer-empowering-neural-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of a specific neural network architecture is closely tied to the dataset and task it tackles; there is no one-size-fits-all solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowerformer-empowering-neural-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserving Face Recognition Using Trainable Feature Subtraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-face-recognition-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizable identity features within the image are encouraged by co-training a recognition model on its high-dimensional feature representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-face-recognition-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Optimization of Model Merging Recipes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-optimization-of-model-merging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, our Japanese Math LLM achieved state-of-the-art performance on a variety of established Japanese LLM benchmarks, even surpassing models with significantly more parameters, despite not being explicitly trained for such tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-optimization-of-model-merging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Non-negative Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-negative-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Non-negative Contrastive Learning (NCL), a renaissance of Non-negative Matrix Factorization (NMF) aimed at deriving interpretable features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/non-negative-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FRESCO: Spatial-Temporal Correspondence for Zero-Shot Video Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fresco-spatial-temporal-correspondence-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce FRESCO, intra-frame correspondence alongside inter-frame correspondence to establish a more robust spatial-temporal constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fresco-spatial-temporal-correspondence-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Consistency Trajectory Models for Image Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-consistency-trajectory-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion-based generative models excel in unconditional generation, as well as on applied tasks such as image editing and restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-consistency-trajectory-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inter- and intra-uncertainty based feature aggregation model for semi-supervised histopathology image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inter-and-intra-uncertainty-based-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we first propose a novel inter- and intra-uncertainty regularization method to measure and constrain both inter- and intra-inconsistencies in the teacher-student architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inter-and-intra-uncertainty-based-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confusing Pair Correction Based on Category Prototype for Domain Adaptation under Noisy Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confusing-pair-correction-based-on-category</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address unsupervised domain adaptation under noisy environments, which is more challenging and practical than traditional domain adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confusing-pair-correction-based-on-category</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VQ-NeRV: A Vector Quantized Neural Representation for Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vq-nerv-a-vector-quantized-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This block incorporates a codebook mechanism to discretize the network's shallow residual features and inter-frame residual information effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vq-nerv-a-vector-quantized-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equity through Access: A Case for Small-scale Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equity-through-access-a-case-for-small-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advances in deep learning (DL) have been accelerated by access to large-scale data and compute.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equity-through-access-a-case-for-small-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy Bifurcation in Safe Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-bifurcation-in-safe-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safe reinforcement learning (RL) offers advanced solutions to constrained optimal control problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-bifurcation-in-safe-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra-High-Resolution Image Synthesis with Pyramid Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-image-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Pyramid Diffusion Model (PDM), a novel architecture designed for ultra-high-resolution image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ultra-high-resolution-image-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You Only Sample Once: Taming One-Step Text-To-Image Synthesis by Self-Cooperative Diffusion GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-sample-once-taming-one-step-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce YOSO, a novel generative model designed for rapid, scalable, and high-fidelity one-step image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/you-only-sample-once-taming-one-step-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FouriScale: A Frequency Perspective on Training-Free High-Resolution Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fouriscale-a-frequency-perspective-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we delve into the generation of high-resolution images from pre-trained diffusion models, addressing persistent challenges, such as repetitive patterns and structural distortions, that emerge when models are applied beyond their trained resolutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fouriscale-a-frequency-perspective-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class and Region-Adaptive Constraints for Network Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-and-region-adaptive-constraints-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we present a formulation that integrates class and region-wise constraints into the learning objective, with multiple penalty weights to account for class and region differences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-and-region-adaptive-constraints-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERASE: Benchmarking Feature Selection Methods for Deep Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erase-benchmarking-feature-selection-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, the existing literature's lack of detailed analysis on selection attributes, based on large-scale datasets and a thorough comparison among selection techniques and DRS backbones, restricts the generalizability of findings and impedes deployment on DRS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/erase-benchmarking-feature-selection-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characteristic AI Agents via Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristic-ai-agents-via-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to this research gap, we create a benchmark for the characteristic AI agents task, including dataset, techniques, and evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristic-ai-agents-via-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Predictive planning and counterfactual learning in active inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-predictive-planning-and-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the rapid advancement of artificial intelligence, understanding the foundations of intelligent behaviour is increasingly important.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-predictive-planning-and-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-FLAN: Designing Data and Methods of Effective Agent Tuning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-flan-designing-data-and-methods-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-sourced Large Language Models (LLMs) have achieved great success in various NLP tasks, however, they are still far inferior to API-based models when acting as agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-flan-designing-data-and-methods-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPLUG-DocOwl 1.5: Unified Structure Learning for OCR-free Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-docowl-1-5-unified-structure-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we emphasize the importance of structure information in Visual Document Understanding and propose the Unified Structure Learning to boost the performance of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-docowl-1-5-unified-structure-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Generated Data Always Help Contrastive Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-generated-data-always-help-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive Learning (CL) has emerged as one of the most successful paradigms for unsupervised visual representation learning, yet it often depends on intensive manual data augmentations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-generated-data-always-help-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-Efficient and Secure DNN Inference on TrustZone-enabled Consumer IoT Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-and-secure-dnn-inference-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We design a memory-efficient management method to support memory-demanding inference in TEEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-efficient-and-secure-dnn-inference-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Explanation Faithfulness between Multilingual and Monolingual Fine-tuned Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-explanation-faithfulness-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous studies have explored how different factors affect faithfulness, mainly in the context of monolingual English models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-explanation-faithfulness-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructing Large Language Models to Identify and Ignore Irrelevant Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructing-large-language-models-to-identify</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly it instructs the LLMs with the verification on relevant and irrelevant conditions to avoid confusion and improve reasoning paths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructing-large-language-models-to-identify</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding the Missing Data: A BERT-inspired Approach Against Package Loss in Wireless Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-the-missing-data-a-bert-inspired</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the development of various deep learning methods for Wi-Fi sensing, package loss often results in noncontinuous estimation of the Channel State Information (CSI), which negatively impacts the performance of the learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-the-missing-data-a-bert-inspired</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
