<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 21:07:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GPT as Knowledge Worker: A Zero-Shot Evaluation of (AI)CPA Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-as-knowledge-worker-a-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global economy is increasingly dependent on knowledge workers to meet the needs of public and private organizations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-as-knowledge-worker-a-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AdaPoinTr: Diverse Point Cloud Completion with Adaptive Geometry-Aware Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapointr-diverse-point-cloud-completion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new method that reformulates point cloud completion as a set-to-set translation problem and design a new model, called PoinTr, which adopts a Transformer encoder-decoder architecture for point cloud completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapointr-diverse-point-cloud-completion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scanner Canine Cutaneous Squamous Cell Carcinoma Histopathology Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scanner-canine-cutaneous-squamous-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, to quantify the inherent scanner-induced domain shift, we train a tumor segmentation network on each scanner subset and evaluate the performance both in- and cross-domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scanner-canine-cutaneous-squamous-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Tri-stream Clustering Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-tri-stream-clustering-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive deep clustering has recently gained significant attention with its ability of joint contrastive learning and clustering via deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-tri-stream-clustering-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tieval: An Evaluation Framework for Temporal Information Extraction Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tieval-an-evaluation-framework-for-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[All in all, these problems have limited the fair comparison between approaches and consequently, the development of temporal extraction systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tieval-an-evaluation-framework-for-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deep into Modes of Fact Hallucinations in Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-deep-into-modes-of-fact-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge Graph(KG) grounded conversations often use large pre-trained models and usually suffer from fact hallucination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diving-deep-into-modes-of-fact-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WuYun: Exploring hierarchical skeleton-guided melody generation using knowledge-enhanced deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuyun-exploring-hierarchical-skeleton-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning has revolutionized music generation, existing methods for structured melody generation follow an end-to-end left-to-right note-by-note generative paradigm and treat each note equally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wuyun-exploring-hierarchical-skeleton-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyHD: Efficient Video Saliency Prediction with Heterogeneous Decoders using Hierarchical Maps Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyhd-efficient-video-saliency-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video saliency prediction has recently attracted attention of the research community, as it is an upstream task for several practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyhd-efficient-video-saliency-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ClimaBench: A Benchmark Dataset For Climate Change Text Understanding in English</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climabench-a-benchmark-dataset-for-climate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The topic of Climate Change (CC) has received limited attention in NLP despite its real world urgency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climabench-a-benchmark-dataset-for-climate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Inverse Cloze Task for Knowledge-based Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-inverse-cloze-task-for-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new pre-training method, Multimodal Inverse Cloze Task, for Knowledge-based Visual Question Answering about named Entities (KVQAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-inverse-cloze-task-for-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning under Heterogeneous and Correlated Client Availability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-heterogeneous-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this purpose, CA-Fed dynamically adapts the weight given to each client and may ignore clients with low availability and large correlation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-under-heterogeneous-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Kinodynamic Planning on the Constraint Manifold with Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-kinodynamic-planning-on-the-constraint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motion planning is a mature area of research in robotics with many well-established methods based on optimization or sampling the state space, suitable for solving kinematic motion planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-kinodynamic-planning-on-the-constraint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LENet: Lightweight And Efficient LiDAR Semantic Segmentation Using Multi-Scale Convolution Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lenet-lightweight-and-efficient-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose LENet, a lightweight and efficient projection-based LiDAR semantic segmentation network, which has an encoder-decoder architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lenet-lightweight-and-efficient-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A prediction and behavioural analysis of machine learning methods for modelling travel mode choice</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prediction-and-behavioural-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The answer to this question goes beyond simple predictive performance, and is instead a balance of many factors, including behavioural interpretability and explainability, computational complexity, and data efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-prediction-and-behavioural-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast spline detection in high density microscopy data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-spline-detection-in-high-density</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer-aided analysis of biological microscopy data has seen a massive improvement with the utilization of general-purpose deep learning techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-spline-detection-in-high-density</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic data generation method for data-free knowledge distillation in regression neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-method-for-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge distillation is the technique of compressing a larger neural network, known as the teacher, into a smaller neural network, known as the student, while still trying to maintain the performance of the larger neural network as much as possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-generation-method-for-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Online Multi-Task Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-online-multi-task-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove a minimax lower bound of $\Omega(K\sqrt{DSAH})$ on the regret of any learning algorithm and an instance-specific lower bound of $\Omega(\frac{K}{\lambda^2})$ in sample complexity for a class of uniformly-good cluster-then-learn algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-online-multi-task-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head-Free Lightweight Semantic Segmentation with Linear Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-free-lightweight-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the ADE20K dataset, our model achieves 41. 8 mIoU and 4. 6 GFLOPs, which is 4. 4 mIoU higher than Segformer, with 45% less GFLOPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/head-free-lightweight-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from What is Already Out There: Few-shot Sign Language Recognition with Online Dictionaries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-what-is-already-out-there-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset represents the actual distribution and characteristics of available online sign language data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-what-is-already-out-there-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hint assisted reinforcement learning: an application in radio astronomy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hint-assisted-reinforcement-learning-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, the construction of a dynamics model in model based reinforcement learning has increased complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hint-assisted-reinforcement-learning-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Data Scientists Review the Scholarly Literature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-data-scientists-review-the-scholarly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keeping up with the research literature plays an important role in the workflow of scientists - allowing them to understand a field, formulate the problems they focus on, and develop the solutions that they contribute, which in turn shape the nature of the discipline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-data-scientists-review-the-scholarly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with minimal effort: leveraging in silico labeling for cell and nucleus segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-minimal-effort-leveraging-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning provides us with powerful methods to perform nucleus or cell segmentation with unprecedented quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-minimal-effort-leveraging-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Semantic Segmentation with Inter-Frame Feature Fusion and Inner-Frame Feature Refinement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-semantic-segmentation-with-inter-frame</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to tackle the misalignment issue, we propose a spatial-temporal fusion (STF) module to model dense pairwise relationships among multi-frame features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-semantic-segmentation-with-inter-frame</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Human Identity Anonymization using Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-human-identity-anonymization-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many outdoor autonomous mobile platforms require more human identity anonymized data to power their data-driven algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-human-identity-anonymization-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Grained Encoder for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-grained-encoder-for-vision-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a Dynamic Grained Encoder for vision transformers, which can adaptively assign a suitable number of queries to each spatial region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-grained-encoder-for-vision-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Hateful Discussions on Reddit using Graph Transformer Networks and Communal Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-hateful-discussions-on-reddit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a system to predict harmful discussions on social media platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-hateful-discussions-on-reddit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Drifters Deployment Strategy to Evaluate Water Current Velocity Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-drifters-deployment-strategy-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider a common approach for water current prediction that uses Lagrangian floaters for water current prediction by interpolating the trajectory of the elements to reflect the velocity field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-drifters-deployment-strategy-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There is No Big Brother or Small Brother: Knowledge Infusion in Language Models for Link Prediction and Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/there-is-no-big-brother-or-small-brother</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this context, we infuse knowledge in large and small language models and study their performance, and find the performance to be similar.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/there-is-no-big-brother-or-small-brother</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Does Localization Inform Editing? Surprising Differences in Causality-Based Localization vs. Knowledge Editing in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-localization-inform-editing-surprising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we find that we can change how a fact is stored in a model by editing weights that are in a different location than where existing methods suggest that the fact is stored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/does-localization-inform-editing-surprising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look Beyond Bias with Entropic Adversarial Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-beyond-bias-with-entropic-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks do not discriminate between spurious and causal patterns, and will only learn the most predictive ones while ignoring the others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/look-beyond-bias-with-entropic-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROBUSfT: Robust Real-Time Shape-from-Template, a C++ Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robusft-robust-real-time-shape-from-template</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking the 3D shape of a deforming object using only monocular 2D vision is a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robusft-robust-real-time-shape-from-template</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Conversational Search Behavior For Domain Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-conversational-search-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational search has evolved as a new information retrieval paradigm, marking a shift from traditional search systems towards interactive dialogues with intelligent search agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-conversational-search-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RedMule: A Mixed-Precision Matrix-Matrix Operation Engine for Flexible and Energy-Efficient On-Chip Linear Algebra and TinyML Training Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redmule-a-mixed-precision-matrix-matrix</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing interest in TinyML, i. e., near-sensor machine learning on power budgets of a few tens of mW, is currently pushing toward enabling TinyML-class training as opposed to inference only.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/redmule-a-mixed-precision-matrix-matrix</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why People Skip Music? On Predicting Music Skips using Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-people-skip-music-on-predicting-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the utility of users' historical data for the task of sequentially predicting users' skipping behaviour.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-people-skip-music-on-predicting-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Transferability of Machine-Learned Force Fields for Material Property Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-transferability-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine-learned force fields have generated significant interest in recent years as a tool for molecular dynamics (MD) simulations, with the aim of developing accurate and efficient models that can replace classical interatomic potentials.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-transferability-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Mandarin-Cantonese Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-mandarin-cantonese-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advancements in unsupervised machine translation have enabled the development of machine translation systems that can translate between languages for which there is not an abundance of parallel data available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-mandarin-cantonese-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Voxelization and Classification for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-voxelization-and-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main challenge in 3D object detection from LiDAR point clouds is achieving real-time performance without affecting the reliability of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-voxelization-and-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERNIE 3.0 Tiny: Frustratingly Simple Method to Improve Task-Agnostic Distillation Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-3-0-tiny-frustratingly-simple-method-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate that our method yields a student with much better generalization, significantly outperforms existing baselines, and establishes a new state-of-the-art result on in-domain, out-domain, and low-resource datasets in the setting of task-agnostic distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-3-0-tiny-frustratingly-simple-method-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing BERT for Convolutional Networks: Sparse and Hierarchical Masked Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-bert-for-convolutional-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is the first use of sparse convolution for 2D masked modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-bert-for-convolutional-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDebug: Systematic Debugging for Federated Learning Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddebug-systematic-debugging-for-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When a global model's performance deteriorates, finding the round and the clients responsible is a major pain point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddebug-systematic-debugging-for-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Discovery using Natural Language Questions via a Self-Supervised Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-discovery-using-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a self-supervised approach to assemble training datasets and train learned discovery systems without human intervention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-discovery-using-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution Cloud Removal with Multi-Modal and Multi-Resolution Data Fusion: A New Baseline and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-cloud-removal-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Planet-CR, a benchmark dataset for high-resolution cloud removal with multi-modal and multi-resolution data fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-cloud-removal-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color Me Intrigued: Quantifying Usage of Colors in Fiction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-me-intrigued-quantifying-usage-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present preliminary results in quantitative analyses of color usage in selected authors' works from LitBank.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-me-intrigued-quantifying-usage-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyRSM++: Hybrid Relation Guided Temporal Set Matching for Few-shot Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyrsm-hybrid-relation-guided-temporal-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To be specific, HyRSM++ consists of two key components, a hybrid relation module and a temporal set matching metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyrsm-hybrid-relation-guided-temporal-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Open-Set Video Domain Adaptation with Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-open-set-video-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we address a more realistic scenario, called open-set video domain adaptation (OUVDA), where the target dataset contains "unknown" semantic categories that are not shared with the source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-open-set-video-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doc2Query--: When Less is More</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doc2query-when-less-is-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Doc2Query -- the process of expanding the content of a document before indexing using a sequence-to-sequence model -- has emerged as a prominent technique for improving the first-stage retrieval effectiveness of search engines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/doc2query-when-less-is-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances in Medical Image Analysis with Vision Transformers: A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-medical-image-analysis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The remarkable performance of the Transformer architecture in natural language processing has recently also triggered broad interest in Computer Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-in-medical-image-analysis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Shape Perception Integrates Intuitive Physics and Analysis-by-Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-shape-perception-integrates-intuitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many surface cues support three-dimensional shape perception, but people can sometimes still see shape when these features are missing -- in extreme cases, even when an object is completely occluded, as when covered with a draped cloth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-shape-perception-integrates-intuitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Functional Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-functional-connectivity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most generally, dynamic functional connectivity (FC) refers to the non-instantaneous couplings across timeseries from a set of brain areas, here as measured by fMRI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-functional-connectivity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-Time Panoptic Narrative Grounding by an End-to-End Grounding Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-panoptic-narrative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on the PNG benchmark dataset demonstrate the effectiveness and efficiency of our method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-panoptic-narrative</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
