<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 09:12:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Neural Net with Dynamic Neuron Addition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-net-with-dynamic-neuron-addition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[X as the input matrix with dimensions(m, n), where m is the number of samples (batch size), and n is the number of input features, W as the weight matrix for the layer with dimensions (n, k), where k is the number of neurons in the layer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-net-with-dynamic-neuron-addition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DifAttack: Query-Efficient Black-Box Attack via Disentangled Feature Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difattack-query-efficient-black-box-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, due to the avoidance of using surrogate models' gradient information when optimizing AEs for black-box models, our proposed DifAttack inherently possesses better attack capability in the open-set scenario, where the training dataset of the victim model is unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/difattack-query-efficient-black-box-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrepancy Matters: Learning from Inconsistent Decoder Features for Consistent Semi-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrepancy-matters-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised learning (SSL) has been proven beneficial for mitigating the issue of limited labeled data especially on the task of volumetric medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrepancy-matters-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPEFlow: Multimodal Fusion of RGB-PointCloud-Event for Joint Optical Flow and Scene Flow Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rpeflow-multimodal-fusion-of-rgb-pointcloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, the RGB images and point clouds fusion methods have been proposed to jointly estimate 2D optical flow and 3D scene flow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rpeflow-multimodal-fusion-of-rgb-pointcloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearest Neighbor Guidance for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearest-neighbor-guidance-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting out-of-distribution (OOD) samples are crucial for machine learning models deployed in open-world environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearest-neighbor-guidance-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training-free Image Manipulation Localization through Non-Mutually Exclusive Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-free-image-manipulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that contrastive learning is more suitable to tackle the data insufficiency problem for IML.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-free-image-manipulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Test-Time Adaptation: Tri-Net Self-Training with Balanced Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-test-time-adaptation-tri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-Time Adaptation aims to adapt source domain model to testing data at inference stage with success demonstrated in adapting to unseen corruptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-test-time-adaptation-tri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactively Learning Social Media Representations Improves News Source Factuality Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactively-learning-social-media</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of social media has enabled the widespread propagation of fake news, text that is published with an intent to spread misinformation and sway beliefs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactively-learning-social-media</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearest Neighbor Guidance for Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearest-neighbor-guidance-for-out-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting out-of-distribution (OOD) samples are crucial for machine learning models deployed in open-world environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nearest-neighbor-guidance-for-out-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unidirectional brain-computer interface: Artificial neural network encoding natural images to fMRI response in the visual cortex</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidirectional-brain-computer-interface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While significant advancements in artificial intelligence (AI) have catalyzed progress across various domains, its full potential in understanding visual perception remains underexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidirectional-brain-computer-interface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Source Domain Adaptation for Object Detection with Prototype-based Mean-teacher</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-domain-adaptation-for-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of the use of prototypes, the parameter size of our method does not increase significantly with the number of source domains, thus reducing memory issues and possible overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-domain-adaptation-for-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Discontinuity Design: With an Application to the Economic Effects of Internet Shutdowns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-discontinuity-design-with-an-application</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thresholds in treatment assignments can produce discontinuities in outcomes, revealing causal insights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-discontinuity-design-with-an-application</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Invariant Transformation for better Adversarial Transferability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-invariant-transformation-for-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we find that the existing input transformation based attacks transform the input image globally, resulting in limited diversity of the transformed images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-invariant-transformation-for-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Text to Video Model via Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-text-to-video-model-via-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since both text and video are sequential data, we encode both texts and images into the same hidden space, which are further fed into Transformer to capture the temporal consistency and then decoder to generate either text or images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-text-to-video-model-via-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Stream-based Visual Object Tracking: A High-Resolution Benchmark Dataset and A Novel Baseline</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-stream-based-visual-object-tracking-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tracking using bio-inspired event cameras has drawn more and more attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-stream-based-visual-object-tracking-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Study of Population-Graph Construction Methods and Graph Neural Networks for Brain Age Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-population-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude that static graph construction approaches are potentially insufficient for the task of brain age estimation and make recommendations for alternative research directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-study-of-population-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Incremental Learning via Likelihood Ratio Based Task Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-learning-via-likelihood</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An emerging theoretically justified and effective approach is to train a task-specific model for each task in a shared network for all tasks based on a task-incremental learning (TIL) method to deal with forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-learning-via-likelihood</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RankVicuna: Zero-Shot Listwise Document Reranking with Open-Source Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankvicuna-zero-shot-listwise-document</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers have successfully applied large language models (LLMs) such as ChatGPT to reranking in an information retrieval context, but to date, such work has mostly been built on proprietary models hidden behind opaque API endpoints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankvicuna-zero-shot-listwise-document</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide and Conquer in Video Anomaly Detection: A Comprehensive Review and New Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-in-video-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video anomaly detection is a complex task, and the principle of "divide and conquer" is often regarded as an effective approach to tackling intricate issues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-in-video-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Sequential DeepFake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sequential-deepfake-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods only focus on detecting one-step facial manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sequential-deepfake-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QA-LoRA: Quantization-Aware Low-Rank Adaptation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qa-lora-quantization-aware-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently years have witnessed a rapid development of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qa-lora-quantization-aware-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFORM: Removing False Correlation in Multi-level Interaction for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reform-removing-false-correlation-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a CTR prediction framework that removes false correlation in multi-level feature interaction, termed REFORM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reform-removing-false-correlation-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Analysis of Quantum State Learning Process in Quantum Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-analysis-of-quantum-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a quantum analog of probability distribution learning, quantum state learning is theoretically and practically essential in quantum machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-analysis-of-quantum-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Multi-Agent Deep Reinforcement Learning Control with Relative Entropy Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-agent-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It alleviates the inconsistency of multiple agents' policy updates by introducing the relative entropy regularization to the Centralized Training with Decentralized Execution (CTDE) framework with the Actor-Critic (AC) structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-multi-agent-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDC-Scene: Boost Monocular 3D Semantic Scene Completion in Normalized Device Coordinates Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ndc-scene-boost-monocular-3d-semantic-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular 3D Semantic Scene Completion (SSC) has garnered significant attention in recent years due to its potential to predict complex semantics and geometry shapes from a single image, requiring no 3D inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ndc-scene-boost-monocular-3d-semantic-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Human-generated Demonstrations Necessary for In-context Learning?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-human-generated-demonstrations-necessary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we raise the fundamental question that whether human-generated demonstrations are necessary for ICL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-human-generated-demonstrations-necessary</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Text-To-Image Customization:From LyCORIS Fine-Tuning to Model Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-text-to-image-customization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generative models have garnered immense attention for their ability to produce high-fidelity images from text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-text-to-image-customization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Label Feature Selection Using Adaptive and Transformed Relevance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-feature-selection-using-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-label learning has emerged as a crucial paradigm in data analysis, addressing scenarios where instances are associated with multiple class labels simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-label-feature-selection-using-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Communication and Computation Framework for Goal-Oriented Semantic Communication with Distortion Rate Resilience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-communication-and-computation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research efforts on semantic communication have mostly considered accuracy as a main problem for optimizing goal-oriented communication systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-communication-and-computation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM-XComposer: A Vision-Language Large Model for Advanced Text-image Comprehension and Composition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer-a-vision-language-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose InternLM-XComposer, a vision-language large model that enables advanced image-text comprehension and composition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer-a-vision-language-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIP-Adapter: Parameter-Efficient Transfer Learning for Mobile Screenshot Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-adapter-parameter-efficient-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study aims to explore efficient tuning methods for the screenshot captioning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-adapter-parameter-efficient-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Post-training Quantization with FP8 Formats</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-post-training-quantization-with-fp8</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in deep learning methods such as LLMs and Diffusion models have created a need for improved quantization methods that can meet the computational demands of these modern architectures while maintaining accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-post-training-quantization-with-fp8</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReMasker: Imputing Tabular Data with Masked Autoencoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remasker-imputing-tabular-data-with-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ReMasker, a new method of imputing missing values in tabular data by extending the masked autoencoding framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/remasker-imputing-tabular-data-with-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRiSM: Enhancing Low-Resource Document-Level Relation Extraction with Relation-Aware Score Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-enhancing-low-resource-document-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Document-level relation extraction (DocRE) aims to extract relations of all entity pairs in a document.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prism-enhancing-low-resource-document-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperTrack: Neural Combinatorics for High Energy Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypertrack-neural-combinatorics-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial inverse problems in high energy physics span enormous algorithmic challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypertrack-neural-combinatorics-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An AI Chatbot for Explaining Deep Reinforcement Learning Decisions of Service-oriented Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ai-chatbot-for-explaining-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to earlier work on natural-language explanations using classical software-based dialogue systems, using an AI chatbot eliminates the need for eliciting and defining potential questions and answers up-front.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-ai-chatbot-for-explaining-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHuman: Harnessing Multi-Source Data for High-Resolution Human Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitedhuman-harnessing-multi-source-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A holistic human dataset inevitably has insufficient and low-resolution information on local parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitedhuman-harnessing-multi-source-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VidChapters-7M: Video Chapters at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidchapters-7m-video-chapters-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we present VidChapters-7M, a dataset of 817K user-chaptered videos including 7M chapters in total.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidchapters-7m-video-chapters-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AsymFormer: Asymmetrical Cross-Modal Representation Learning for Mobile Platform Real-Time RGB-D Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymformer-asymmetrical-cross-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose AsymFormer, a novel network for real-time RGB-D semantic segmentation, which targets the minimization of superfluous parameters by optimizing the distribution of computational resources and introduces an asymmetrical backbone to allow for the effective fusion of multimodal features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asymformer-asymmetrical-cross-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepACO: Neural-enhanced Ant Systems for Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepaco-neural-enhanced-ant-systems-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a Neural Combinatorial Optimization method, DeepACO performs better than or on par with problem-specific methods on canonical routing problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepaco-neural-enhanced-ant-systems-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting large collections of time series: feature-based methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-large-collections-of-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In economics and many other forecasting domains, the real world problems are too complex for a single model that assumes a specific data generation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forecasting-large-collections-of-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linked shrinkage to improve estimation of interaction effects in regression models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-shrinkage-to-improve-estimation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We empirically show that borrowing strength between the amount of shrinkage for main effects and their interactions can strongly improve estimation of the regression coefficients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linked-shrinkage-to-improve-estimation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beam Enumeration: Probabilistic Explainability For Sample Efficient Self-conditioned Molecular Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beam-enumeration-probabilistic-explainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative molecular design has moved from proof-of-concept to real-world applicability, as marked by the surge in very recent papers reporting experimental validation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beam-enumeration-probabilistic-explainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Indoor Instance Segmentation in an Open-World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-indoor-instance-segmentation-in-an-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that such a closed-world assumption is restrictive and explore for the first time 3D indoor instance segmentation in an open-world setting, where the model is allowed to distinguish a set of known classes as well as identify an unknown object as unknown and then later incrementally learning the semantic category of the unknown when the corresponding category labels are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-indoor-instance-segmentation-in-an-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Q-Bench: A Benchmark for General-Purpose Foundation Models on Low-level Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-bench-a-benchmark-for-general-purpose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we present Q-Bench, a holistic benchmark crafted to systematically evaluate potential abilities of MLLMs on three realms: low-level visual perception, low-level visual description, and overall visual quality assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-bench-a-benchmark-for-general-purpose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-Bloom: Zero-Shot Text-to-Video Generator with LLM Director and LDM Animator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-bloom-zero-shot-text-to-video-generator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-video is a rapidly growing research area that aims to generate a semantic, identical, and temporal coherence sequence of frames that accurately align with the input text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-bloom-zero-shot-text-to-video-generator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoIR: Box-Supervised Instance Representation for Multi-Person Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boir-box-supervised-instance-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our new instance embedding loss provides a learning signal on the entire area of the image with bounding box annotations, achieving globally consistent and disentangled instance representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boir-box-supervised-instance-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate and Interactive Visual-Inertial Sensor Calibration with Next-Best-View and Next-Best-Trajectory Suggestion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-interactive-visual-inertial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual-Inertial (VI) sensors are popular in robotics, self-driving vehicles, and augmented and virtual reality applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-interactive-visual-inertial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCF-Crime Annotation: A Benchmark for Surveillance Video-and-Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucf-crime-annotation-a-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we benchmark the state-of-the-art models of multiple multimodal tasks on this newly created dataset, including temporal sentence grounding in videos, video captioning, and dense video captioning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ucf-crime-annotation-a-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projected Randomized Smoothing for Certified Adversarial Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projected-randomized-smoothing-for-certified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Randomized smoothing is the current state-of-the-art method for producing provably robust classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/projected-randomized-smoothing-for-certified</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
