<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 21:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>An Incremental Learning Approach for Sustainable Region Isolation and Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-incremental-learning-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we mimic partitioned learning and memory replay in the human brain and propose an incremental learning approach named SRII, short for sustainable regional isolation and integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-incremental-learning-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghost-free High Dynamic Range Imaging via Hybrid CNN-Transformer and Structure Tensor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghost-free-high-dynamic-range-imaging-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this letter, we present a hybrid model consisting of a convolutional encoder and a Transformer decoder to generate ghost-free HDR images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghost-free-high-dynamic-range-imaging-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principled Multi-Aspect Evaluation Measures of Rankings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-multi-aspect-evaluation-measures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information Retrieval evaluation has traditionally focused on defining principled ways of assessing the relevance of a ranked list of documents with respect to a query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-multi-aspect-evaluation-measures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomedical NER for the Enterprise with Distillated BERN2 and the Kazu Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-ner-for-the-enterprise-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to assist the drug discovery/development process, pharmaceutical companies often apply biomedical NER and linking techniques over internal and public corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-ner-for-the-enterprise-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Impact of Music Recommendation Diversity on Listeners: A Longitudinal Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-impact-of-music-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the results of a 12-week longitudinal user study wherein the participants, 110 subjects from Southern Europe, received on a daily basis Electronic Music (EM) diversified recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-impact-of-music-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Commonsense-Infused Language-Agnostic Learning Framework for Enhancing Prediction of Political Polarity in Multilingual News Headlines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-commonsense-infused-language-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With attended knowledge in our framework, the same model show an increase in 2. 2% accuracy and F1, and 3. 6% jaccard score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-commonsense-infused-language-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrannGAN: Graph annotation generative adversarial networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granngan-graph-annotation-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model we propose tackles the problem of generating the data features constrained by the specific graph structure of each data point by splitting the task into two phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granngan-graph-annotation-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Representations Reveal Distinct Modes of Class Fitting in Residual Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-representations-reveal-distinct-modes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we estimate class-conditional density models for representations learned by deep ResNets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-representations-reveal-distinct-modes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Linear and Iterative Combinations of Patches for Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-linear-and-iterative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a parametric view of non-local two-step denoisers, for which BM3D is a major representative, where quadratic risk minimization is leveraged for unsupervised optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-linear-and-iterative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperbolic Contrastive Learning for Visual Representations beyond Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-contrastive-learning-for-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To exploit such a structure, we propose a contrastive learning framework where a Euclidean loss is used to learn object representations and a hyperbolic loss is used to encourage representations of scenes to lie close to representations of their constituent objects in a hyperbolic space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-contrastive-learning-for-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FoPro: Few-Shot Guided Robust Webly-Supervised Prototypical Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fopro-few-shot-guided-robust-webly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing methods focus on learning noise-robust models from web images while neglecting the performance drop caused by the differences between web domain and real-world domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fopro-few-shot-guided-robust-webly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable Artificial Intelligence for Improved Modeling of Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-artificial-intelligence-for-8</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, Machine Learning (ML) benefits from the vast amount of data available and can deal with high-dimensional sources, yet it has rarely been applied to being used in processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-artificial-intelligence-for-8</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prasatul Matrix: A Direct Comparison Approach for Analyzing Evolutionary Optimization Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prasatul-matrix-a-direct-comparison-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, a direct comparison approach is proposed to analyze the performance of evolutionary optimization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prasatul-matrix-a-direct-comparison-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AC-Band: A Combinatorial Bandit-Based Approach to Algorithm Configuration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ac-band-a-combinatorial-bandit-based-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the algorithm configuration (AC) problem, in which one seeks to find an optimal parameter configuration of a given target algorithm in an automated way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ac-band-a-combinatorial-bandit-based-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-CLEVR: A Virtual Benchmark to Diagnose Domain Robustness in Visual Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-clevr-a-virtual-benchmark-to-diagnose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Question Answering (VQA) models often perform poorly on out-of-distribution data and struggle on domain generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-clevr-a-virtual-benchmark-to-diagnose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRRGN: An Implicit Relational Reasoning Graph Network for Multi-turn Response Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrgn-an-implicit-relational-reasoning-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[URR aims to implicitly extract dependencies between utterances, as well as utterances and options, and make reasoning with relational graph convolutional networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrgn-an-implicit-relational-reasoning-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finetune like you pretrain: Improved finetuning of zero-shot vision models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetune-like-you-pretrain-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In total, these benchmarks establish contrastive finetuning as a simple, intuitive, and state-of-the-art approach for supervised finetuning of image-text models like CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finetune-like-you-pretrain-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unbiased Heterogeneous Scene Graph Generation with Relation-aware Message Passing Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-heterogeneous-scene-graph-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent scene graph generation (SGG) frameworks have focused on learning complex relationships among multiple objects in an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unbiased-heterogeneous-scene-graph-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIZZA: A new benchmark for complex end-to-end task-oriented parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pizza-a-new-benchmark-for-complex-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much recent work in task-oriented parsing has focused on finding a middle ground between flat slots and intents, which are inexpressive but easy to annotate, and powerful representations such as the lambda calculus, which are expressive but costly to annotate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pizza-a-new-benchmark-for-complex-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Selective Similarity Integration for Drug-Target Interaction Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-selective-similarity-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the availability of abundant heterogeneous biological information from diverse data sources, computational methods have been able to leverage multiple drug and target similarities to boost the performance of DTI prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-selective-similarity-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Document Cross-Lingual Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-document-cross-lingual-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-Lingual Summarization (CLS) aims at generating summaries in one language for the given documents in another language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-document-cross-lingual-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGTANet: Encoding Sequential LiDAR Points Using Long Short-Term Motion-Guided Temporal Attention for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtanet-encoding-sequential-lidar-points</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While conventional 3D object detectors use a set of unordered LiDAR points acquired over a fixed time interval, recent studies have revealed that substantial performance improvement can be achieved by exploiting the spatio-temporal context present in a sequence of LiDAR point sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtanet-encoding-sequential-lidar-points</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concealed Object Detection for Passive Millimeter-Wave Security Imaging Based on Task-Aligned Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concealed-object-detection-for-passive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Passive millimeter-wave (PMMW) is a significant potential technique for human security screening.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concealed-object-detection-for-passive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attribute-based Representations for Accurate and Interpretable Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-based-representations-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, we find that this simple representation is sufficient to achieve state-of-the-art performance in ShanghaiTech, the largest and most complex VAD dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-based-representations-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FakeOut: Leveraging Out-of-domain Self-supervision for Multi-modal Video Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakeout-leveraging-out-of-domain-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This poses a problem, especially in the era of social media, as synthetic videos of speaking humans can be used to spread misinformation in a convincing manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fakeout-leveraging-out-of-domain-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Image Restoration Using Denoising Diffusion Null-Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-restoration-using-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing Image Restoration (IR) models are task-specific, which can not be generalized to different degradation operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-restoration-using-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-Shot Models with Label Distribution Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-models-with-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new approach, CLIPPR (CLIP with Priors), which adapts zero-shot models for regression and classification on unlabelled datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-models-with-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Neural Voxels for Fast Multi-view Video Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-neural-voxels-for-fast-multi-view-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel method named MixVoxels to better represent the dynamic scenes with fast training speed and competitive rendering qualities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-neural-voxels-for-fast-multi-view-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EHRSQL: A Practical Text-to-SQL Benchmark for Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrsql-a-practical-text-to-sql-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new text-to-SQL dataset for electronic health records (EHRs), where the utterances are collected from 222 hospital staff—including physicians, nurses, insurance review and health records teams, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrsql-a-practical-text-to-sql-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Score Jacobian Chaining: Lifting Pretrained 2D Diffusion Models for 3D Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-jacobian-chaining-lifting-pretrained-2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose to apply chain rule on the learned gradients, and back-propagate the score of a diffusion model through the Jacobian of a differentiable renderer, which we instantiate to be a voxel radiance field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/score-jacobian-chaining-lifting-pretrained-2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semiconductor Defect Pattern Classification by Self-Proliferation-and-Attention Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semiconductor-defect-pattern-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel architecture that can perform defect classification in a more efficient way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semiconductor-defect-pattern-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Adaptive Optimization with Delayed Preconditioners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-adaptive-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Privacy noise may negate the benefits of using adaptive optimizers in differentially private model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-adaptive-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do you MEME? Generating Explanations for Visual Semantic Role Labelling in Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-you-meme-generating-explanations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce a novel task - EXCLAIM, generating explanations for visual semantic role labeling in memes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-you-meme-generating-explanations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early prediction of the risk of ICU mortality with Deep Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-prediction-of-the-risk-of-icu-mortality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we evaluate the ability of deep Federated Learning to predict the risk of Intensive Care Unit mortality at an early stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-prediction-of-the-risk-of-icu-mortality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Efficient Finetuning Using Cross-Task Nearest Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-finetuning-using-cross-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assume access to a small number (250--1000) of unlabeled target task instances, select their nearest neighbors from a pool of multitask data, and use the retrieved data to train target task-specific models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-finetuning-using-cross-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Combinatorial Structures via Markov Random Fields with Sampling through Lovász Local Lemma</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-combinatorial-structures-via-markov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of the highly intractable nature of the gradient estimation of the learning objective subject to combinatorial constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-combinatorial-structures-via-markov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Fast Unit Commitment Constraint Screening via Learning Cost Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-fast-unit-commitment-constraint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unit commitment (UC) are essential tools to transmission system operators for finding the most economical and feasible generation schedules and dispatch signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-fast-unit-commitment-constraint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Kernel Learning for Mortality Prediction in the Face of Temporal Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-kernel-learning-for-mortality-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This often leads to drop in the performance of neural models for prospective patients, especially in terms of their calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-kernel-learning-for-mortality-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CL4CTR: A Contrastive Learning Framework for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cl4ctr-a-contrastive-learning-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many Click-Through Rate (CTR) prediction works focused on designing advanced architectures to model complex feature interactions but neglected the importance of feature representation learning, e. g., adopting a plain embedding layer for each feature, which results in sub-optimal feature representations and thus inferior CTR prediction performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cl4ctr-a-contrastive-learning-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODPP: A Unified Algorithm Framework for Unsupervised Option Discovery based on Determinantal Point Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odpp-a-unified-algorithm-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning rich skills through temporal abstractions without supervision of external rewards is at the frontier of Reinforcement Learning research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odpp-a-unified-algorithm-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Compatibility between a Neural Network and a Partial Differential Equation for Physics-informed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-compatibility-between-a-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this pitfall, we prove that a linear PDE up to the $n$-th order can be strictly satisfied by an MLP with $C^n$ activation functions when the weights of its output layer lie on a certain hyperplane, as called the out-layer-hyperplane.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-compatibility-between-a-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRiT: A Generative Region-to-text Transformer for Object Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-a-generative-region-to-text-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, GRiT consists of a visual encoder to extract image features, a foreground object extractor to localize objects, and a text decoder to generate open-set object descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-a-generative-region-to-text-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generate Text-grounded Mask for Open-world Semantic Segmentation from Only Image-Text Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-text-grounded-mask-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing open-world segmentation methods have shown impressive advances by employing contrastive learning (CL) to learn diverse visual concepts and adapting the learned image-level understanding to the segmentation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-text-grounded-mask-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protein Language Models and Structure Prediction: Connection and Progression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protein-language-models-and-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The prediction of protein structures from sequences is an important task for function prediction, drug design, and related biological processes understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protein-language-models-and-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Slice Thigh CT Muscle Group Segmentation with Domain Adaptation and Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-slice-thigh-ct-muscle-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed pipeline is effective and robust in extracting muscle groups on 2D single slice CT thigh images. The container is available for public use at https://github. com/MASILab/DA_CT_muscle_seg]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-slice-thigh-ct-muscle-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Coarse to Fine: Hierarchical Pixel Integration for Lightweight Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-coarse-to-fine-hierarchical-pixel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the fine area, we use an Intra-Patch Self-Attention (IPSA) module to model long-range pixel dependencies in a local patch, and then a $3\times3$ convolution is applied to process the finest details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-coarse-to-fine-hierarchical-pixel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>General policy mapping: online continual reinforcement learning inspired on the insect brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-policy-mapping-online-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model leverages the offline training of a feature extraction and a common general policy layer to enable the convergence of RL algorithms in online settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/general-policy-mapping-online-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linking Sketch Patches by Learning Synonymous Proximity for Graphic Sketch Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-sketch-patches-by-learning-synonymous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cropped sketch patches are linked according to their global semantics or local geometric shapes, namely the synonymous proximity, by computing the cosine similarity between the captured patch embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linking-sketch-patches-by-learning-synonymous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Motion-Robust Remote Photoplethysmography through Arbitrary Resolution Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-motion-robust-remote</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote photoplethysmography (rPPG) enables non-contact heart rate (HR) estimation from facial videos which gives significant convenience compared with traditional contact-based measurements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-motion-robust-remote</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Properties of Quantum Systems with Conditional Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-properties-of-quantum-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alternatively, kernel methods can predict local observables by learning from measurements on different but related states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-properties-of-quantum-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
