<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 09:13:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation-Aware Mutual Learning for Semi-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-mutual-learning-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is based on a mutual learning strategy that incorporates two modules: the Cross-sample Mutual Attention Module (CMA) and the Omni-Correlation Consistency Module (OCC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-mutual-learning-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing Spatiotemporal Data with C-VAEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-spatiotemporal-data-with-c</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing region interpolation methods often fail to generate smooth and realistic representations of a region's evolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-spatiotemporal-data-with-c</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Batch Optimization of Contrastive Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-batch-optimization-of-contrastive-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning has gained significant attention as a method for self-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-batch-optimization-of-contrastive-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auxiliary-Tasks Learning for Physics-Informed Neural Network-Based Partial Differential Equations Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-learning-for-physics-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these issues, we proposed auxiliary-task learning-based physics-informed neural networks (ATL-PINNs), which provide four different auxiliary-task learning modes and investigate their performance compared with original PINNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-learning-for-physics-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Faster Gradient Descent via Long Steps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-faster-gradient-descent-via-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work establishes provably faster convergence rates for gradient descent via a computer-assisted analysis technique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-faster-gradient-descent-via-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-based estimation of whole-body kinematics from multi-view images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-estimation-of-whole-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is necessary to analyze the whole-body kinematics (including joint locations and joint angles) to assess risks of fatal and musculoskeletal injuries in occupational tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-estimation-of-whole-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeSeed: Frequency-band-aware and Self-guided Network for Sparse-view CT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseed-frequency-band-aware-and-self-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first propose a frequency-band-aware artifact modeling network (FreeNet), which learns artifact-related frequency-band attention in Fourier domain for better modeling the globally distributed streak artifact on the sparse-view CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseed-frequency-band-aware-and-self-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locally Adaptive Federated Learning via Stochastic Polyak Stepsizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-federated-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that FedSPS converges linearly in strongly convex and sublinearly in convex settings when the interpolation condition (overparametrization) is satisfied, and converges to a neighborhood of the solution in the general case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-federated-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhythm Modeling for Voice Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythm-modeling-for-voice-conversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice conversion aims to transform source speech into a different target voice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythm-modeling-for-voice-conversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Importance of Denoising when Learning to Compress Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-denoising-when-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image noise is ubiquitous in photography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-denoising-when-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiRP: Learning Robot Generalized Bimanual Coordination using Relative Parameterization Method on Human Demonstration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/birp-learning-robot-generalized-bimanual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the method using synthetic motions and human demonstration data and deploy it to a humanoid robot to perform a generalized bimanual coordination motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/birp-learning-robot-generalized-bimanual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Safe Self-Distillation of Internet-Scale Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-safe-self-distillation-of-internet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale image generation models, with impressive quality made possible by the vast amount of data available on the Internet, raise social concerns that these models may generate harmful or copyrighted content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-safe-self-distillation-of-internet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PID-Inspired Inductive Biases for Deep Reinforcement Learning in Partially Observable Control Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-inspired-inductive-biases-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When this is the case, the policy needs to leverage the history of observations to infer the current state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-inspired-inductive-biases-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The IMPTC Dataset: An Infrastructural Multi-Person Trajectory and Context Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-imptc-dataset-an-infrastructural-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to enable the entire stack of research capabilities, the dataset includes all data, starting from the sensor-, calibration- and detection data until trajectory and context data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-imptc-dataset-an-infrastructural-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeFormer: a Semi-Supervised Transformer-based Framework for Tree Counting from a Single High Resolution Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-a-semi-supervised-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic tree density estimation and counting using single aerial and satellite images is a challenging task in photogrammetry and remote sensing, yet has an important role in forest management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-a-semi-supervised-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rectifying Noisy Labels with Sequential Prior: Multi-Scale Temporal Feature Affinity Learning for Robust Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-noisy-labels-with-sequential-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, Temporal Feature Affinity Learning (TFAL) is devised to indicate possible noisy labels by evaluating the affinity between pixels in two adjacent frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-noisy-labels-with-sequential-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellGAN: Conditional Cervical Cell Synthesis for Augmenting Cytopathological Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellgan-conditional-cervical-cell-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CellGAN to synthesize cytopathological images of various cervical cell types for augmenting patch-level cell classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellgan-conditional-cervical-cell-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDNAS: Discretized Differentiable Neural Architecture Search for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddnas-discretized-differentiable-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Architecture Search (NAS) has shown promising capability in learning text representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddnas-discretized-differentiable-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLA-GCN: Global-local Adaptive Graph Convolutional Network for 3D Human</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gla-gcn-global-local-adaptive-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, we concentrate on improving the 3D human pose lifting via ground truth data for the future improvement of more quality estimated pose data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gla-gcn-global-local-adaptive-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning for Conversion Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-conversion-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tailor the contrastive learning task to the CVR prediction problem, we propose embedding masking (EM), rather than feature masking, to create two views of augmented samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-conversion-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Mitosis Detection: Towards Diverse Data and Feature Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-mitosis-detection-towards-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And the feature diversity is preserved by inter- and intra- class feature diversity-preserved module (InCDP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-mitosis-detection-towards-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashaar: Automatic Analysis and Generation of Arabic Poetry Using Deep Learning Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ashaar-automatic-analysis-and-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Poetry holds immense significance within the cultural and traditional fabric of any nation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ashaar-automatic-analysis-and-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sem-CS: Semantic CLIPStyler for Text-Based Image Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sem-cs-semantic-clipstyler-for-text-based-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the ground semantics of objects in the style transfer output is lost due to style spill-over on salient and background objects (content mismatch) or over-stylization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sem-cs-semantic-clipstyler-for-text-based-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluggable Neural Machine Translation Models via Memory-augmented Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-neural-machine-translation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although neural machine translation (NMT) models perform well in the general domain, it remains rather challenging to control their generation behavior to satisfy the requirement of different users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-neural-machine-translation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification of the Virial Black Hole Mass with Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-the-virial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to baseline approaches for prediction interval estimation, we show that the CQR method provides prediction intervals that adjust to the black hole mass and its related properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-the-virial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering recommender systems using automatically generated Knowledge Graphs and Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-recommender-systems-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized recommendations have a growing importance in direct marketing, which motivates research to enhance customer experiences by knowledge graph (KG) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-recommender-systems-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duncode Characters Shorter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duncode-characters-shorter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It discusses local encoders such as ASCII and GB-2312, which encode specific characters into shorter bytes, and universal encoders like UTF-8 and UTF-16, which can encode the complete Unicode set with greater space requirements and are gaining widespread acceptance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/duncode-characters-shorter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLUEX: A benchmark based on Brazilian Leading Universities Entrance eXams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bluex-a-benchmark-based-on-brazilian-leading</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One common trend in recent studies of language models (LMs) is the use of standardized tests for evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bluex-a-benchmark-based-on-brazilian-leading</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PKU-GoodsAD: A Supermarket Goods Dataset for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pku-goodsad-a-supermarket-goods-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It follows the unsupervised setting and only normal (defect-free) images are used for training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pku-goodsad-a-supermarket-goods-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformalization of Sparse Generalized Linear Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalization-of-sparse-generalized-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a sequence of observable variables $\{(x_1, y_1), \ldots, (x_n, y_n)\}$, the conformal prediction method estimates a confidence set for $y_{n+1}$ given $x_{n+1}$ that is valid for any finite sample size by merely assuming that the joint distribution of the data is permutation invariant.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformalization-of-sparse-generalized-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Algorithms for Federated Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-algorithms-for-federated-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then apply our methodology to evaluate 13 Federated DG methods, which include centralized DG methods adapted to the FL context, FL methods that handle client heterogeneity, and methods designed specifically for Federated DG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-algorithms-for-federated-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mao-Zedong At SemEval-2023 Task 4: Label Represention Multi-Head Attention Model With Contrastive Learning-Enhanced Nearest Neighbor Mechanism For Multi-Label Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mao-zedong-at-semeval-2023-task-4-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study of human values is essential in both practical and theoretical domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mao-zedong-at-semeval-2023-task-4-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Analysis of Triggers and Benign Features for Black-Box DNN Backdoor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-analysis-of-triggers-and-benign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Having the computed five metrics, five novelty detectors are trained from the validation dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-analysis-of-triggers-and-benign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Extraction on Wikipedia Tables using Convolutional and Memory Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-extraction-on-wikipedia-tables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relation extraction (RE) is the task of extracting relations between entities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-extraction-on-wikipedia-tables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Contrastive Graph Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-contrastive-graph-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, feature augmentation imposes the same scale noise augmentation on each node, which neglects the unique characteristics of nodes on the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-contrastive-graph-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Neural Diffusion Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-neural-diffusion-processes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we extend the framework of diffusion models to incorporate a series of geometric priors in infinite-dimension modelling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-neural-diffusion-processes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A stochastic optimization approach to minimize robust density power-based divergences for general parametric density models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Density power divergence (DPD) [Basu et al. (1998), Biometrika], designed to estimate the underlying distribution of the observations robustly, comprises an integral term of the power of the parametric density models to be estimated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stochastic-optimization-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epidemic Modeling with Generative Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epidemic-modeling-with-generative-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study offers a new paradigm of individual-level modeling to address the grand challenge of incorporating human behavior in epidemic models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epidemic-modeling-with-generative-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural-Symbolic Recommendation with Graph-Enhanced Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-symbolic-recommendation-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some researchers use user behavior for logic reasoning to achieve recommendation prediction from the perspective of cognitive reasoning, but this kind of reasoning is a local one and ignores implicit information on a global scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-symbolic-recommendation-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Study of the Extended Drug-target Interaction Network informed by Pain Related Voltage-Gated Sodium Channels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-study-of-the-extended-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pain is a significant global health issue, and the current treatment options for pain management have limitations in terms of effectiveness, side effects, and potential for addiction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-study-of-the-extended-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperspherical Embedding for Point Cloud Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspherical-embedding-for-point-cloud-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most real-world 3D measurements from depth sensors are incomplete, and to address this issue the point cloud completion task aims to predict the complete shapes of objects from partial observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperspherical-embedding-for-point-cloud-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Segmentation and Detection of Lesions in CT Scans Using Intensity Distribution Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-segmentation-and-detection-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method to incorporate the intensity information of a target lesion on CT scans in training segmentation and detection networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-segmentation-and-detection-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExFaceGAN: Exploring Identity Directions in GAN's Learned Latent Space for Synthetic Identity Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exfacegan-exploring-identity-directions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose in this work a framework, ExFaceGAN, to disentangle identity information in state-of-the-art pretrained GANs latent spaces, enabling the generation of multiple samples of any synthetic identity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exfacegan-exploring-identity-directions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised adversarial masking for 3D point cloud representation learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-masking-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce PointCAM, a novel adversarial method for learning a masking function for point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-masking-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Pretraining in Multimodality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-pretraining-in-multimodality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Emu, a Transformer-based multimodal foundation model, which can seamlessly generate images and texts in multimodal context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-pretraining-in-multimodality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modular Multimodal Architecture for Gaze Target Prediction: Application to Privacy-Sensitive Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-multimodal-architecture-for-gaze-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[to detect obstructions in the line of sight or apply attention priors that humans typically have when observing others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-multimodal-architecture-for-gaze-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFR: Depth from Rotation by Uncalibrated Image Rectification with Latitudinal Motion Assumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfr-depth-from-rotation-by-uncalibrated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the increasing prevalence of rotating-style capture (e. g., surveillance cameras), conventional stereo rectification techniques frequently fail due to the rotation-dominant motion and small baseline between views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfr-depth-from-rotation-by-uncalibrated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Anytime Optical Flow Estimation with Event Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-optical-flow-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose EVA-Flow, an EVent-based Anytime Flow estimation network to produce high-frame-rate event optical flow with only low-frame-rate optical flow ground truth for supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-optical-flow-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of RLHF in Large Language Models Part I: PPO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we explore the PPO-max, an advanced version of PPO algorithm, to efficiently improve the training stability of the policy model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact Twice Fusion Network for Edge Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-twice-fusion-network-for-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Compact Twice Fusion Network (CTFN) to fully integrate multi-scale features while maintaining the compactness of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-twice-fusion-network-for-edge</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
