<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 09:11:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Large Language Model for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-large-language-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there is a growing interest in developing next-generation recommender systems (RSs) based on pretrained large language models (LLMs), fully utilizing their encoded knowledge and reasoning ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-large-language-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheating Depth: Enhancing 3D Surface Anomaly Detection via Depth Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheating-depth-enhancing-3d-surface-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(ii) We tackle the lack of diverse industrial depth datasets by introducing a simulation process for learning informative depth features in the depth encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cheating-depth-enhancing-3d-surface-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COPAL-ID: Indonesian Language Reasoning with Local Culture and Nuances</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copal-id-indonesian-language-reasoning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present publicly available COPAL-ID, a novel Indonesian language common sense reasoning dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copal-id-indonesian-language-reasoning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Deepfakes Without Seeing Any</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-deepfakes-without-seeing-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We therefore introduce the concept of "fact checking", adapted from fake news detection, for detecting zero-day deepfake attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-deepfakes-without-seeing-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tailoring Mixup to Data using Kernel Warping functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-mixup-to-data-using-kernel-warping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation is an essential building block for learning efficient deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tailoring-mixup-to-data-using-kernel-warping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Language Models Be Tricked by Language Illusions? Easier with Syntax, Harder with Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-be-tricked-by-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We found that probabilities represented by LMs were more likely to align with human judgments of being "tricked" by the NPI illusion which examines a structural dependency, compared to the comparative and the depth-charge illusions which require sophisticated semantic understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-be-tricked-by-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Act As You Wish: Fine-Grained Control of Motion Diffusion Model with Hierarchical Semantic Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-as-you-wish-fine-grained-control-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these compact text representations may overemphasize the action names at the expense of other important properties and lack fine-grained details to guide the synthesis of subtly distinct motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/act-as-you-wish-fine-grained-control-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Common Ground: Annotating and Predicting Common Ground in Spoken Conversations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-common-ground-annotating-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An important part of cognitive state is the common ground, which is the content the speaker believes, and the speaker believes the audience believes, and so on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-common-ground-annotating-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better with Less: A Data-Active Perspective on Pre-Training Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-with-less-a-data-active-perspective-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed pre-training pipeline is called the data-active graph pre-training (APT) framework, and is composed of a graph selector and a pre-training model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-with-less-a-data-active-perspective-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Out-of-Distribution Robustness from Vision-Language Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-out-of-distribution-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a conceptually simple and lightweight framework for improving the robustness of vision models through the combination of knowledge distillation and data augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-out-of-distribution-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combating Bilateral Edge Noise for Robust Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-bilateral-edge-noise-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this dilemma, we propose an information-theory-guided principle, Robust Graph Information Bottleneck (RGIB), to extract reliable supervision signals and avoid representation collapse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-bilateral-edge-noise-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopicGPT: A Prompt-based Topic Modeling Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicgpt-a-prompt-based-topic-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic modeling is a well-established technique for exploring text corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topicgpt-a-prompt-based-topic-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Multimodal Information Bottleneck for Multimodality Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-information-bottleneck-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our information bottleneck module serves to filter out the task-irrelevant information and noises in the fused feature, and we further introduce a sufficiency loss to prevent dropping of task-relevant information, thus explicitly preserving the sufficiency of prediction information in the distilled feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-multimodal-information-bottleneck-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision-Language Interpreter for Robot Task Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-interpreter-for-robot-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim is to generate a problem description (PD), a machine-readable file used by the planners to find a plan.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-language-interpreter-for-robot-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video2Music: Suitable Music Generation from Videos using an Affective Multimodal Transformer model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video2music-suitable-music-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These distinct features are then employed as guiding input to our music generation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video2music-suitable-music-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Information-Guided Network using Contrastive Learning for Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-information-guided-network-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first incorporate the projected images from the point clouds and fuse the cross-modal features using the attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-information-guided-network-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concatenated Masked Autoencoders as Spatial-Temporal Learner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concatenated-masked-autoencoders-as-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning representations from videos requires understanding continuous motion and visual correspondences between frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concatenated-masked-autoencoders-as-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Human-AI Teams via Learned Natural Language Rules and Onboarding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-human-ai-teams-via-learned-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our novel region discovery algorithm finds local regions in the data as neighborhoods in an embedding space that corrects the human prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-human-ai-teams-via-learned-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPI++: Efficient Prediction-Powered Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppi-efficient-prediction-powered-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PPI++: a computationally lightweight methodology for estimation and inference based on a small labeled dataset and a typically much larger dataset of machine-learning predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ppi-efficient-prediction-powered-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating QM1B with PySCF$_{\text{IPU}}$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-qm1b-with-pyscf-text-ipu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similar benefits are yet to be unlocked for quantum chemistry, where the potential of deep learning is constrained by comparatively small datasets with 100k to 20M training examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-qm1b-with-pyscf-text-ipu</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance-Based Propagation for Efficient Knowledge Graph Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-propagation-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new class of methods have been proposed to tackle this problem by aggregating path information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-based-propagation-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilient Multiple Choice Learning: A learned scoring scheme with application to audio scene analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resilient-multiple-choice-learning-a-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple Choice Learning is a simple framework to tackle multimodal density estimation, using the Winner-Takes-All (WTA) loss for a set of hypotheses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resilient-multiple-choice-learning-a-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Measures of Individual Item Fairness for Recommender Systems: A Critical Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-measures-of-individual-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge, this is the first critical comparison of individual item fairness measures in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-measures-of-individual-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim2Real Bilevel Adaptation for Object Surface Classification using Vision-Based Tactile Sensors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim2real-bilevel-adaptation-for-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation is conducted on a dataset of tactile images obtained from a set of ten 3D printed YCB objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sim2real-bilevel-adaptation-for-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaboration and Transition: Distilling Item Transitions into Multi-Query Self-Attention for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaboration-and-transition-distilling-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we develop a transition-aware embedding distillation module that distills global item-to-item transition patterns into item embeddings, which enables the model to memorize and leverage transitional signals and serves as a calibrator for collaborative signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaboration-and-transition-distilling-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models for Reinforcement Learning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-reinforcement-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have emerged as a prominent class of generative models, surpassing previous methods regarding sample quality and training stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-for-reinforcement-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Chain of Thought Reasoning via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-chain-of-thought-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore an alternative reasoning approach: instead of explicitly producing the chain of thought reasoning steps, we use the language model's internal hidden states to perform implicit reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-chain-of-thought-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Imitation from Observation via Primal Wasserstein State Occupancy Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-imitation-from-observation-via-primal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose Primal Wasserstein DICE (PW-DICE), which minimizes the primal Wasserstein distance between the expert and learner state occupancies with a pessimistic regularizer and leverages a contrastively learned distance as the underlying metric for the Wasserstein distance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-imitation-from-observation-via-primal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinesewebtext: Large-scale high-quality Chinese web text extracted with effective evaluation model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinesewebtext-large-scale-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using our proposed approach, we release the largest and latest large-scale high-quality Chinese web text ChineseWebText, which consists of 1. 42 TB and each text is associated with a quality score, facilitating the LLM researchers to choose the data according to the desired quality thresholds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chinesewebtext-large-scale-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AiluRus: A Scalable ViT Framework for Dense Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ailurus-a-scalable-vit-framework-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, at the intermediate layer of the ViT, we utilize a spatial-aware density-based clustering algorithm to select representative tokens from the token sequence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ailurus-a-scalable-vit-framework-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight super resolution network for point cloud geometry compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-super-resolution-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an approach for compressing point cloud geometry by leveraging a lightweight super-resolution network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-super-resolution-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanitized Clustering against Confounding Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanitized-clustering-against-confounding-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therein, the interested clustering factor and the confounding factor are coarsely considered in the raw feature space, where the correlation between the data and the confounding factor is ideally assumed to be linear for convenient solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sanitized-clustering-against-confounding-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Operational Mathematical Derivations in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-operational-mathematical-derivations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce different multi-operational representation paradigms, modelling mathematical operations as explicit geometric transformations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-operational-mathematical-derivations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Transport-Guided Conditional Score-Based Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-guided-conditional-score</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional score-based diffusion model (SBDM) is for conditional generation of target data with paired data as condition, and has achieved great success in image translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-transport-guided-conditional-score</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DP-Mix: Mixup-based Data Augmentation for Differentially Private Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-mix-mixup-based-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation techniques, such as simple image transformations and combinations, are highly effective at improving the generalization of computer vision models, especially when training data is limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dp-mix-mixup-based-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Solution for Offline Imitation from Observations and Examples with Possibly Incomplete Trajectories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-solution-for-offline-imitation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline imitation from observations aims to solve MDPs where only task-specific expert states and task-agnostic non-expert state-action pairs are available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-solution-for-offline-imitation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Replicable Benchmarking of Neural Machine Translation (NMT) on Low-Resource Local Languages in Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/replicable-benchmarking-of-neural-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural machine translation (NMT) for low-resource local languages in Indonesia faces significant challenges, including the need for a representative benchmark and limited data availability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/replicable-benchmarking-of-neural-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SatBird: Bird Species Distribution Modeling with Remote Sensing and Citizen Science Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satbird-bird-species-distribution-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The wide availability of remote sensing data and the growing adoption of citizen science tools to collect species observations data at low cost offer an opportunity for improving biodiversity monitoring and enabling the modelling of complex ecosystems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/satbird-bird-species-distribution-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Preference Learning Heterogeneous Hypergraph Networks for Session-based Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-preference-learning-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, price preference and interest preference are interdependent and collectively determine user choice, necessitating that we jointly consider both price and interest preference for intent modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-preference-learning-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VCISR: Blind Single Image Super-Resolution with Video Compression Synthetic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcisr-blind-single-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we for the first time, present a video compression-based degradation model to synthesize low-resolution image data in the blind SISR task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vcisr-blind-single-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Unified Perspective For Fast Shapley Value Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-unified-perspective-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shapley values have emerged as a widely accepted and trustworthy tool, grounded in theoretical axioms, for addressing challenges posed by black-box models like deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-unified-perspective-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATHENA: Mathematical Reasoning with Thought Expansion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/athena-mathematical-reasoning-with-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solving math word problems depends on how to articulate the problems, the lens through which models view human linguistic expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/athena-mathematical-reasoning-with-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT-Powered Hierarchical Comparisons for Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-powered-hierarchical-comparisons-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The zero-shot open-vocabulary challenge in image classification is tackled by pretrained vision-language models like CLIP, which benefit from incorporating class-specific knowledge from large language models (LLMs) like ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-powered-hierarchical-comparisons-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Single-Channel Speaker-Turn Aware Conversational Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-single-channel-speaker-turn-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional speech-to-text translation (ST) systems are trained on single-speaker utterances, and they may not generalize to real-life scenarios where the audio contains conversations by multiple speakers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-single-channel-speaker-turn-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-latency Real-time Voice Conversion on CPU</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-real-time-voice-conversion-on-cpu</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To our knowledge LLVC achieves both the lowest resource usage as well as the lowest latency of any open-source voice conversion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-latency-real-time-voice-conversion-on-cpu</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Coordinate Shift: Whetted Automatic Differentiation for Physics-informed Operator Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-coordinate-shift-whetted-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic differentiation (AD) is a critical step in physics-informed machine learning, required for computing the high-order derivatives of network output w. r. t.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-coordinate-shift-whetted-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Embedded Diachronic Sense Change Model with a Case Study from Ancient Greek</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-embedded-diachronic-sense-change-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models represent the senses of a given target word such as "kosmos" (meaning decoration, order or world) as distributions over context words, and sense prevalence as a distribution over senses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-embedded-diachronic-sense-change-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Graph Clustering via Meta Weighting for Noisy Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-graph-clustering-via-meta-weighting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We add a learnable weight to each node pair, and MetaGC adaptively adjusts the weights of node pairs using meta-weighting so that the weights of meaningful node pairs increase and the weights of less-meaningful ones (e. g., noise edges) decrease.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-graph-clustering-via-meta-weighting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorting with Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sorting-with-predictions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the fundamental problem of sorting through the lens of learning-augmented algorithms, where algorithms can leverage possibly erroneous predictions to improve their efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sorting-with-predictions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Summarization with Normalizing Flows and Aggressive Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-summarization-with-normalizing-flows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents FlowSUM, a normalizing flows-based variational encoder-decoder framework for Transformer-based summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-summarization-with-normalizing-flows</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
