<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 09:15:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Communicate to Play: Pragmatic Reasoning for Efficient Cross-Cultural Communication in Codenames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communicate-to-play-pragmatic-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cultural differences in common ground may result in pragmatic failure and misunderstandings during communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communicate-to-play-pragmatic-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical-VQLA++: Adversarial Contrastive Learning for Calibrated Robust Visual Question-Localized Answering in Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqla-adversarial-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, surgical VQA can enhance the interpretation of surgical data, aiding in accurate diagnoses, effective education, and clinical interventions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqla-adversarial-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FUSE-ing Language Models: Zero-Shot Adapter Discovery for Prompt Optimization Across Tokenizers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuse-ing-language-models-zero-shot-adapter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The widespread use of large language models has resulted in a multitude of tokenizers and embedding spaces, making knowledge transfer in prompt discovery tasks difficult.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fuse-ing-language-models-zero-shot-adapter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECG-FM: An Open Electrocardiogram Foundation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecg-fm-an-open-electrocardiogram-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Affirming ECG-FM's effectiveness as a foundation model, we demonstrate how its command of contextual information results in strong performance, rich pretrained embeddings, and reliable interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecg-fm-an-open-electrocardiogram-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Artificial Cognition: Integrating Multiple AI Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-artificial-cognition-integrating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we present an innovative fusion of language models and query analysis techniques to unlock cognition in artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-artificial-cognition-integrating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bootstrap Latents of Nodes and Neighbors for Graph Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrap-latents-of-nodes-and-neighbors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose to expand the positive pair set with node-neighbor pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bootstrap-latents-of-nodes-and-neighbors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variational Bayesian Phylogenetic Inference with Semi-implicit Branch Length Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-phylogenetic-inference-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reconstructing the evolutionary history relating a collection of molecular sequences is the main subject of modern Bayesian phylogenetic inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variational-bayesian-phylogenetic-inference-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGrid: An Efficient-And-Rigorous Neural Multigrid Solver for Linear PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ugrid-an-efficient-and-rigorous-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical solvers of Partial Differential Equations (PDEs) are of fundamental significance to science and engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ugrid-an-efficient-and-rigorous-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weak-Annotation of HAR Datasets using Vision Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-annotation-of-har-datasets-using-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As wearable-based data annotation remains, to date, a tedious, time-consuming task requiring researchers to dedicate substantial time, benchmark datasets within the field of Human Activity Recognition in lack richness and size compared to datasets available within related fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weak-annotation-of-har-datasets-using-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepInteraction++: Multi-Modality Interaction for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepinteraction-multi-modality-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To demonstrate the effectiveness of the proposed strategy, we design DeepInteraction++, a multi-modal interaction framework characterized by a multi-modal representational interaction encoder and a multi-modal predictive interaction decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepinteraction-multi-modality-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cell Morphology-Guided Small Molecule Generation with GFlowNets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-morphology-guided-small-molecule</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider an alternative approach in which we leverage an unsupervised multimodal joint embedding to define a latent similarity as a reward for GFlowNets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cell-morphology-guided-small-molecule</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Lazy Visual Grounding for Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-defense-of-lazy-visual-grounding-for-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present lazy visual grounding, a two-stage approach of unsupervised object mask discovery followed by object grounding, for open-vocabulary semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-defense-of-lazy-visual-grounding-for-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CROCODILE: Causality aids RObustness via COntrastive DIsentangled LEarning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crocodile-causality-aids-robustness-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to domain shift, deep learning image classifiers perform poorly when applied to a domain different from the training one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crocodile-causality-aids-robustness-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProxyCLIP: Proxy Attention Improves CLIP for Open-Vocabulary Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxyclip-proxy-attention-improves-clip-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ProxyCLIP leverages the spatial feature correspondence from VFMs as a form of proxy attention to augment CLIP, thereby inheriting the VFMs' robust local consistency and maintaining CLIP's exceptional zero-shot transfer capacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxyclip-proxy-attention-improves-clip-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyper-YOLO: When Visual Object Detection Meets Hypergraph Computation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyper-yolo-when-visual-object-detection-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Hyper-YOLO, a new object detection method that integrates hypergraph computations to capture the complex high-order correlations among visual features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyper-yolo-when-visual-object-detection-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked adversarial neural network for cell type deconvolution in spatial transcriptomics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-adversarial-neural-network-for-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MACD employs adversarial learning to align real ST data with simulated ST data generated from scRNA-seq data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-adversarial-neural-network-for-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery of Linear Non-Gaussian Causal Models with Unobserved Confounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-of-linear-non-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this setting, the causal structure is identifiable, but, in general, it is not possible to identify the specific causal effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-of-linear-non-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the use of neurosymbolic AI for defending against cyber attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-neurosymbolic-ai-for-defending</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is generally accepted that all cyber attacks cannot be prevented, creating a need for the ability to detect and respond to cyber attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-neurosymbolic-ai-for-defending</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Jailbroken GenAI Model Can Cause Substantial Harm: GenAI-powered Applications are Vulnerable to PromptWares</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-jailbroken-genai-model-can-cause</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PromptWare exploits user inputs to jailbreak a GenAI model to force/perform malicious activity within the context of a GenAI-powered application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-jailbroken-genai-model-can-cause</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HistoKernel: Whole Slide Image Level Maximum Mean Discrepancy Kernels for Pan-Cancer Predictive Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histokernel-whole-slide-image-level-maximum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning in computational pathology (CPath) often aggregates patch-level predictions from multi-gigapixel Whole Slide Images (WSIs) to generate WSI-level prediction scores for crucial tasks such as survival prediction and drug effect prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/histokernel-whole-slide-image-level-maximum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniBench: Visual Reasoning Requires Rethinking Vision-Language Beyond Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unibench-visual-reasoning-requires-rethinking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate a systematic evaluation of VLM progress, we introduce UniBench: a unified implementation of 50+ VLM benchmarks spanning a comprehensive range of carefully categorized capabilities from object recognition to spatial awareness, counting, and much more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unibench-visual-reasoning-requires-rethinking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Order Matters in Hallucination: Reasoning Order as Benchmark and Reflexive Prompting for Large-Language-Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-matters-in-hallucination-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discovered that the order in which LLMs generate answers and reasoning impacts their consistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/order-matters-in-hallucination-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Metric for Multiple Anomaly Score Distributions with Discrete Severity Levels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-metric-for-multiple-anomaly-score</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the existing performance metrics, such as the area under the receiver operating characteristic curve (AUROC), do not effectively reflect the performance of models in classifying severity levels based on anomaly scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-metric-for-multiple-anomaly-score</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRAT: Bonus oRthogonAl Token for Architecture Agnostic Textual Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brat-bonus-orthogonal-token-for-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Textual Inversion remains a popular method for personalizing diffusion models, in order to teach models new subjects and styles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brat-bonus-orthogonal-token-for-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMRole: A Comprehensive Framework for Developing and Evaluating Multimodal Role-Playing Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrole-a-comprehensive-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce the concept of Multimodal Role-Playing Agents (MRPAs), and propose a comprehensive framework, MMRole, for their development and evaluation, which comprises a personalized multimodal dataset and a robust evaluation method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmrole-a-comprehensive-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiDAR-Event Stereo Fusion with Hallucinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-event-stereo-fusion-with-hallucinations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event stereo matching is an emerging technique to estimate depth from neuromorphic cameras; however, events are unlikely to trigger in the absence of motion or the presence of large, untextured regions, making the correspondence problem extremely challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lidar-event-stereo-fusion-with-hallucinations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Guided Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-guided-language-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For auto-regressive language models, existing guidance methods are prone to decoding errors that cascade during generation and degrade performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-guided-language-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Language Model Math Reasoning via Grounding in Educational Curricula</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-language-model-math-reasoning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work presents a novel angle for evaluating language models' (LMs) mathematical abilities, by investigating whether they can discern skills and concepts enabled by math content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-language-model-math-reasoning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMTeC: A Corpus of Eye Movements on Machine-Generated Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emtec-a-corpus-of-eye-movements-on-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the corpus includes the language models' internals that underlie the generation of the stimulus texts: the transition scores, the attention scores, and the hidden states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emtec-a-corpus-of-eye-movements-on-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Molecular Machine (Learned) Representations with Stereoelectronics-Infused Molecular Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-molecular-machine-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the explicit addition of stereoelectronic interactions significantly improves the performance of molecular machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-molecular-machine-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs Beat Humans in Debating? A Dynamic Multi-agent Framework for Competitive Debate</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-beat-humans-in-debating-a-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we introduce Agent for Debate (Agent4Debate), a dynamic, multi-agent framework based on LLMs designed to enhance their capabilities in competitive debate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-beat-humans-in-debating-a-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HydraFormer: One Encoder For All Subsampling Rates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hydraformer-one-encoder-for-all-subsampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In automatic speech recognition, subsampling is essential for tackling diverse scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hydraformer-one-encoder-for-all-subsampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantics or spelling? Probing contextual word embeddings with orthographic noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantics-or-spelling-probing-contextual-word</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pretrained language model (PLM) hidden states are frequently employed as contextual word embeddings (CWE): high-dimensional representations that encode semantic information given linguistic context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantics-or-spelling-probing-contextual-word</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ungrounded Alignment Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ungrounded-alignment-problem</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper examines a simplified version of the general problem, where an unsupervised learner is presented with a sequence of images for the characters in a text corpus, and this learner is later evaluated on its ability to recognize specific (possibly rare) sequential patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ungrounded-alignment-problem</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DC Algorithm for Estimation of Sparse Gaussian Graphical Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc-algorithm-for-estimation-of-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we formulate the sparse estimation problem for Gaussian graphical models using the $\ell_0$ norm and propose a method to solve this problem using the Difference of Convex functions Algorithm (DCA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dc-algorithm-for-estimation-of-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Accurate Pneumonia Detection Using a Novel Multi-Scale Transformer Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-accurate-pneumonia-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By employing our specialized transformer, we attain superior results with significantly fewer parameters compared to common transformer models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-accurate-pneumonia-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Forecast: A Multimodal Approach to Temporal Event Forecasting with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-forecast-a-multimodal-approach-to-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study an emerging and intriguing problem of multimodal temporal event forecasting with large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-forecast-a-multimodal-approach-to-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Power of Sparse Neural Networks for Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-power-of-sparse-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse Neural Networks (SNNs) have emerged as powerful tools for efficient feature selection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-power-of-sparse-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans-Tokenization and Cross-lingual Vocabulary Transfers: Language Adaptation of LLMs for Low-Resource NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trans-tokenization-and-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By lowering the data and time requirements for training high-quality models, our trans-tokenization strategy allows for the development of LLMs for a wider range of languages, especially those with limited resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trans-tokenization-and-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bias-Aware Low-Rank Adaptation: Mitigating Catastrophic Inheritance of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-aware-low-rank-adaptation-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have exhibited remarkable proficiency across a diverse array of natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bias-aware-low-rank-adaptation-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling Noisy Clients in Federated Learning with End-to-end Label Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-noisy-clients-in-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Intuitively, the performance degradation is dominated by clients with higher noise rates since their trained models contain more misinformation from data, thus it is necessary to devise an effective optimization scheme to mitigate the negative impacts of these noisy clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-noisy-clients-in-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of 3D Reconstruction Techniques for Deformable Tissues in Robotic Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-3d-reconstruction-techniques-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a crucial and intricate task in robotic minimally invasive surgery, reconstructing surgical scenes using stereo or monocular endoscopic video holds immense potential for clinical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-3d-reconstruction-techniques-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-View Meets Diffusion: Aerial Image Synthesis with Geometry and Text Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-meets-diffusion-aerial-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel Geometric Preserving Ground-to-Aerial (G2A) image synthesis (GPG2A) model that can generate realistic aerial images from ground images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-meets-diffusion-aerial-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Exposure Bias in Online Learning to Rank Recommendation: A Novel Reward Model for Cascading Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-exposure-bias-in-online-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study exposure bias in a class of well-known contextual bandit algorithms known as Linear Cascading Bandits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-exposure-bias-in-online-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference with the Upper Confidence Bound Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-with-the-upper-confidence-bound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that in such a case the arms are stable when $\frac{\log K}{\log T} \rightarrow 0$, and the number of near-optimal arms are large.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-with-the-upper-confidence-bound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Img-Diff: Contrastive Data Synthesis for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/img-diff-contrastive-data-synthesis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, we investigate alternative methods for generating image difference data through "object removal" and conduct a thorough evaluation to confirm the dataset's diversity, quality, and robustness, presenting several insights on the synthesis of such a contrastive dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/img-diff-contrastive-data-synthesis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Reasoning Biases in Large Language Models Through Syllogism: Insights from the NeuBAROCO Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-reasoning-biases-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also present experimental results and in-depth analysis using a new Chain-of-Thought prompting method, which asks LLMs to translate syllogisms into abstract logical expressions and then explain their reasoning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-reasoning-biases-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Fine-Grained Grounded Citations for Attributed Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fine-grained-grounded-citations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impressive performance on information-seeking tasks, large language models (LLMs) still struggle with hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-fine-grained-grounded-citations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mbrs: A Library for Minimum Bayes Risk Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbrs-a-library-for-minimum-bayes-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We published our mbrs as an MIT-licensed open-source project, and the code is available on GitHub.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbrs-a-library-for-minimum-bayes-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listwise Reward Estimation for Offline Preference-based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/listwise-reward-estimation-for-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Listwise Reward Estimation (LiRE), a novel approach for offline PbRL that leverages second-order preference information by constructing a Ranked List of Trajectories (RLT), which can be efficiently built by using the same ternary feedback type as traditional methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/listwise-reward-estimation-for-offline</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
