<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:12:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Semantic Tokenization for Deep CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-semantic-tokenization-for-deep-ctr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The content-encoding paradigm, which integrates user and item encoders directly into CTR models, prioritizes space over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-semantic-tokenization-for-deep-ctr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Causal Inspired Early-Branching Structure for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-inspired-early-branching-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By d-separation, we observe that the causal feature can be further characterized by being independent of the domain conditioned on the object, and we propose the following two strategies as complements for the basic framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-inspired-early-branching-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOLMES: HOLonym-MEronym based Semantic inspection for Convolutional Image Classifiers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holmes-holonym-meronym-based-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) are nowadays the model of choice in Computer Vision, thanks to their ability to automatize the feature extraction process in visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/holmes-holonym-meronym-based-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Prompting for Rehearsal-Free Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-prompting-for-rehearsal-free</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, all existing classifiers are exposed to prompt training, resulting in classifier consistency learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-prompting-for-rehearsal-free</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAIFIT: Human-Centered AI for Fashion Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/haifit-human-centered-ai-for-fashion-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method excels in preserving the distinctive style and intricate details essential for fashion design applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/haifit-human-centered-ai-for-fashion-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Loss Functions for Fact Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-loss-functions-for-fact</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore loss functions for fact verification in the FEVER shared task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-loss-functions-for-fact</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLQxform-UI: A Natural Language Interface for Querying DBLP Interactively</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlqxform-ui-a-natural-language-interface-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the DBLP computer science bibliography has been prominently used for searching scholarly information, such as publications, scholars, and venues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nlqxform-ui-a-natural-language-interface-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow-Your-Click: Open-domain Regional Image Animation via Short Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-your-click-open-domain-regional-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in image-to-video generation, better controllability and local animation are less explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/follow-your-click-open-domain-regional-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Inference of Removal-Based Node Influence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-of-removal-based-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new method of evaluating node influence, which measures the prediction change of a trained GNN model caused by removing a node.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-inference-of-removal-based-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iCONTRA: Toward Thematic Collection Design Via Interactive Concept Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icontra-toward-thematic-collection-design-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a user-friendly interface, iCONTRA enables both experienced designers and novices to effortlessly explore creative design concepts and efficiently generate thematic collections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/icontra-toward-thematic-collection-design-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiscale Low-Frequency Memory Network for Improved Feature Extraction in Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-low-frequency-memory-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Responding to these complexities, we introduce a novel framework, the Multiscale Low-Frequency Memory (MLFM) Network, with the goal to harness the full potential of CNNs while keeping their complexity unchanged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiscale-low-frequency-memory-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIM4D: Masked Modeling with Multi-View Video for Autonomous Driving Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mim4d-masked-modeling-with-multi-view-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning robust and scalable visual representations from massive multi-view video data remains a challenge in computer vision and autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mim4d-masked-modeling-with-multi-view-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Weak to Strong Sound Event Labels using Adaptive Change-Point Detection and Active Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-weak-to-strong-sound-event-labels-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose an audio recording segmentation method based on an adaptive change point detection (A-CPD) for machine guided weak label annotation of audio recording segments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-weak-to-strong-sound-event-labels-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaddingFlow: Improving Normalizing Flows with Padding-Dimensional Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paddingflow-improving-normalizing-flows-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, Flow-based models suffer two issues, which are manifold and discrete data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paddingflow-improving-normalizing-flows-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Binary and Multiclass SVMs Trained on a Quantum Annealer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-binary-and-multiclass-svms-trained-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the last years, with the advent of working quantum annealers, hybrid SVM models characterised by quantum training and classical execution have been introduced.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-binary-and-multiclass-svms-trained-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAM: Dynamic Adapter Merging for Continual Video QA Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-dynamic-adapter-merging-for-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our DAM model outperforms prior state-of-the-art continual learning approaches by 9. 1% while exhibiting 1. 9% less forgetting on 6 VidQA datasets spanning various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-dynamic-adapter-merging-for-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Score Generation for Multi-trait Essay Scoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-score-generation-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, encoder-only pre-trained models such as BERT have been successfully applied in automated essay scoring (AES) to predict a single overall score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-score-generation-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Power of Meta-tuning for Few-shot Generalization Through Sparse Interpolated Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-power-of-meta-tuning-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional wisdom suggests parameter-efficient fine-tuning of foundation models as the state-of-the-art method for transfer learning in vision, replacing the rich literature of alternatives such as meta-learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-the-power-of-meta-tuning-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Learning for Joint Image Denoising and Motion Artifact Correction of 3D Brain MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-learning-for-joint-image-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a Joint image Denoising and motion Artifact Correction (JDAC) framework via iterative learning to handle noisy MRIs with motion artifacts, consisting of an adaptive denoising model and an anti-artifact model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-learning-for-joint-image-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoleculeQA: A Dataset to Evaluate Factual Accuracy in Molecular Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moleculeqa-a-dataset-to-evaluate-factual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models are playing an increasingly significant role in molecular research, yet existing models often generate erroneous information, posing challenges to accurate molecular comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moleculeqa-a-dataset-to-evaluate-factual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tackling the Singularities at the Endpoints of Time Intervals in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-the-singularities-at-the-endpoints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most diffusion models assume that the reverse process adheres to a Gaussian distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tackling-the-singularities-at-the-endpoints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ambient Diffusion Posterior Sampling: Solving Inverse Problems with Diffusion Models trained on Corrupted Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambient-diffusion-posterior-sampling-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We open-source our code and the trained Ambient Diffusion MRI models: https://github. com/utcsilab/ambient-diffusion-mri .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ambient-diffusion-posterior-sampling-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViT-CoMer: Vision Transformer with Convolutional Multi-scale Feature Interaction for Dense Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vit-comer-vision-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the stateof-the-art, ViT-CoMer has the following advantages: (1) We inject spatial pyramid multi-receptive field convolutional features into the ViT architecture, which effectively alleviates the problems of limited local information interaction and single-feature representation in ViT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vit-comer-vision-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAFS: Landmark-based Facial Self-supervised Learning for Face Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lafs-landmark-based-facial-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enables our method - namely LAndmark-based Facial Self-supervised learning LAFS), to learn key representation that is more critical for face recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lafs-landmark-based-facial-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Large Language Models Identify Authorship?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-identify-authorship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) How can LLMs provide explainability in authorship analysis, particularly through the role of linguistic features?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-large-language-models-identify-authorship</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scattered Mixture-of-Experts Implementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scattered-mixture-of-experts-implementation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present ScatterMoE, an implementation of Sparse Mixture-of-Experts (SMoE) on GPUs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scattered-mixture-of-experts-implementation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Decade's Battle on Dataset Bias: Are We There Yet?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-decade-s-battle-on-dataset-bias-are-we</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We revisit the "dataset classification" experiment suggested by Torralba and Efros a decade ago, in the new era with large-scale, diverse, and hopefully less biased datasets as well as more capable neural network architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-decade-s-battle-on-dataset-bias-are-we</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Generative Story Transformer with Character Guidance and Caption Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-generative-story-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Story Visualization (SV) is a challenging generative vision task, that requires both visual quality and consistency between different frames in generated image sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-generative-story-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILCiteR: Evidence-grounded Interpretable Local Citation Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ilciter-evidence-grounded-interpretable-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We contribute a novel dataset for the evidence-grounded local citation recommendation task and demonstrate the efficacy of our proposed conditional neural rank-ensembling approach for re-ranking evidence spans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ilciter-evidence-grounded-interpretable-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Cloud Compression via Constrained Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-cloud-compression-via-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel point cloud compression method COT-PCC by formulating the task as a constrained optimal transport (COT) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-cloud-compression-via-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mean-Field Microcanonical Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-field-microcanonical-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Microcanonical gradient descent is a sampling procedure for energy-based models allowing for efficient sampling of distributions in high dimension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-field-microcanonical-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SM4Depth: Seamless Monocular Metric Depth Estimation across Multiple Cameras and Scenes by One Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sm4depth-seamless-monocular-metric-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Third, to reduce the reliance on massive training data, we propose a ``divide and conquer" solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sm4depth-seamless-monocular-metric-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models are Contrastive Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompting methods play a crucial role in enhancing the capabilities of pre-trained large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Optimized Orthogonal Basis Piecewise Polynomial Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-optimized-orthogonal-basis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that, using this regularization approach, Chebyshev basis performs better than power basis for all relevant optimizers in the combined approximation and continuity optimization setting and demonstrate usability of the presented approach within the electronic cam domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-optimized-orthogonal-basis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language models scale reliably with over-training and on downstream tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-scale-reliably-with-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We fit scaling laws that extrapolate in both the number of model parameters and the ratio of training tokens to parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-scale-reliably-with-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CleanAgent: Automating Data Standardization with LLM-based Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleanagent-automating-data-standardization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data standardization is a crucial part in data science life cycle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cleanagent-automating-data-standardization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Describe for Predicting Zero-shot Drug-Drug Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-describe-for-predicting-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adverse drug-drug interactions~(DDIs) can compromise the effectiveness of concurrent drug administration, posing a significant challenge in healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-describe-for-predicting-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Assisted Light: Leveraging Large Language Model Capabilities for Human-Mimetic Traffic Signal Control in Complex Urban Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-assisted-light-leveraging-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, a hybrid framework that augments LLMs with a suite of perception and decision-making tools is proposed, facilitating the interrogation of both the static and dynamic traffic information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-assisted-light-leveraging-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOTOPIA-$π$: Interactive Learning of Socially Intelligent Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sotopia-p-interactive-learning-of-socially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this gap, we propose an interactive learning method, SOTOPIA-$\pi$, improving the social intelligence of language agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sotopia-p-interactive-learning-of-socially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigate Target-level Insensitivity of Infrared Small Target Detection via Posterior Distribution Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigate-target-level-insensitivity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared Small Target Detection (IRSTD) aims to segment small targets from infrared clutter background.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigate-target-level-insensitivity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMART: Submodular Data Mixture Strategy for Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-submodular-data-mixture-strategy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instruction Tuning involves finetuning a language model on a collection of instruction-formatted datasets in order to enhance the generalizability of the model to unseen tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-submodular-data-mixture-strategy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoOcc: Digging into Monocular Semantic Occupancy Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monoocc-digging-into-monocular-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods rely on a complex cascaded framework with relatively limited information to restore 3D scenes, including a dependency on supervision solely on the whole network's output, single-frame input, and the utilization of a small backbone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monoocc-digging-into-monocular-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>METER: a mobile vision transformer architecture for monocular depth estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meter-a-mobile-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State of the art MDE models typically rely on vision transformers (ViT) architectures that are highly deep and complex, making them unsuitable for fast inference on devices with hardware constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meter-a-mobile-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COSTREAM: Learned Cost Models for Operator Placement in Edge-Cloud Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costream-learned-cost-models-for-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present COSTREAM, a novel learned cost model for Distributed Stream Processing Systems that provides accurate predictions of the execution costs of a streaming query in an edge-cloud environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/costream-learned-cost-models-for-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechColab Leaderboard: An Open-Source Platform for Automatic Speech Recognition Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechcolab-leaderboard-an-open-source</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we introduce the SpeechColab Leaderboard, a general-purpose, open-source platform designed for ASR evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechcolab-leaderboard-an-open-source</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoIN: A Benchmark of Continual Instruction tuNing for Multimodel Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coin-a-benchmark-of-continual-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce MoELoRA to MLLMs which is effective to retain the previous instruction alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coin-a-benchmark-of-continual-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Source-Free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-source-free-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this unified SFDA problem, we propose a novel approach called Latent Causal Factors Discovery (LCFD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-source-free-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensembling Prioritized Hybrid Policies for Multi-agent Pathfinding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-prioritized-hybrid-policies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first propose a selective communication block to gather richer information for better agent coordination within multi-agent environments and train the model with a Q-learning-based algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensembling-prioritized-hybrid-policies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorship Style Transfer with Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/authorship-style-transfer-with-policy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Authorship style transfer aims to rewrite a given text into a specified target while preserving the original meaning in the source.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/authorship-style-transfer-with-policy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked AutoDecoder is Effective Multi-Task Vision Generalist</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autodecoder-is-effective-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the success of general-purpose models in NLP, recent studies attempt to unify different vision tasks in the same sequence format and employ autoregressive Transformers for sequence prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autodecoder-is-effective-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
