<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 21:07:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging LDA Feature Extraction to Augment Human Activity Recognition Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-lda-feature-extraction-to-augment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research introduces a hybrid feature extraction approach that combines Linear Discriminant Analysis (LDA) and Multilayer Perceptron (MLP) methods to address the challenges of reducing feature vector dimensionality and accurately classifying smartphone-based human activities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-lda-feature-extraction-to-augment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVEAL-IT: REinforcement learning with Visibility of Evolving Agent poLicy for InTerpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reveal-it-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the agent's learning process in complicated environments or tasks is more challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reveal-it-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>aeon: a Python toolkit for learning from time series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeon-a-python-toolkit-for-learning-from-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[aeon is a unified Python 3 library for all machine learning tasks involving time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aeon-a-python-toolkit-for-learning-from-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MacroHFT: Memory Augmented Context-aware Reinforcement Learning On High Frequency Trading</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macrohft-memory-augmented-context-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these problems, we propose a novel Memory Augmented Context-aware Reinforcement learning method On HFT, \emph{a. k. a.}]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macrohft-memory-augmented-context-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CityBench: Evaluating the Capabilities of Large Language Model as World Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citybench-evaluating-the-capabilities-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on CitySim, we design 7 tasks in 2 categories of perception-understanding and decision-making group to evaluate the capability of LLMs as city-scale world model for urban domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citybench-evaluating-the-capabilities-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference-Time Decontamination: Reusing Leaked Benchmarks for Large Language Model Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-time-decontamination-reusing-leaked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On MMLU, using Inference-time Decontamination can lead to a decrease in the results of Phi3 and Mistral by 6. 7% and 3. 6% respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-time-decontamination-reusing-leaked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Fusion Based on Mutual-Cross-Attention Mechanism for EEG Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-fusion-based-on-mutual-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An objective and accurate emotion diagnostic reference is vital to psychologists, especially when dealing with patients who are difficult to communicate with for pathological reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-fusion-based-on-mutual-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxonomy-Guided Zero-Shot Recommendations with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-guided-zero-shot-recommendations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the emergence of large language models (LLMs) and their ability to perform a variety of tasks, their application in recommender systems (RecSys) has shown promise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-guided-zero-shot-recommendations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimulSeamless: FBK at IWSLT 2024 Simultaneous Speech Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulseamless-fbk-at-iwslt-2024-simultaneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the FBK's participation in the Simultaneous Translation Evaluation Campaign at IWSLT 2024.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulseamless-fbk-at-iwslt-2024-simultaneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReaLHF: Optimized RLHF Training for Large Language Models through Parameter Reallocation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realhf-optimized-rlhf-training-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this formulation, ReaLHF employs a tailored search algorithm with a lightweight cost estimator to discover an efficient execution plan.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realhf-optimized-rlhf-training-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Investigation of Prompt Variations for Zero-shot LLM-based Rankers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-prompt-variations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide a systematic understanding of the impact of specific components and wordings used in prompts on the effectiveness of rankers based on zero-shot Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-prompt-variations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PostMark: A Robust Blackbox Watermark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/postmark-a-robust-blackbox-watermark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The most effective techniques to detect LLM-generated text rely on inserting a detectable signature -- or watermark -- during the model's decoding process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/postmark-a-robust-blackbox-watermark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Bank Check Security: Introducing a Novel Dataset and Transformer-Based Approach for Detection and Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-bank-check-security-introducing-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce a novel dataset specifically designed for signature verification on bank checks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhanced-bank-check-security-introducing-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeciMamba: Exploring the Length Extrapolation Potential of Mamba</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decimamba-exploring-the-length-extrapolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Long-range sequence processing poses a significant challenge for Transformers due to their quadratic complexity in input length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decimamba-exploring-the-length-extrapolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Guided Regularization for Fine-tuning Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-guided-regularization-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The pretraining-fine-tuning paradigm has been the de facto strategy for transfer learning in modern language modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-guided-regularization-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/live-video-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we formally introduce the novel problem of LVC and propose new evaluation metrics tailored for the online scenario, demonstrating their superiority over traditional metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/live-video-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeYOLO, New Scalable and Efficient CNN Architecture for Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leyolo-new-scalable-and-efficient-cnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on design choices of neural network architectures for efficient object detection computation based on FLOP and propose several optimizations to enhance the efficiency of YOLO-based models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leyolo-new-scalable-and-efficient-cnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soft-QMIX: Integrating Maximum Entropy For Monotonic Value Function Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-qmix-integrating-maximum-entropy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an enhancement to QMIX by incorporating an additional local Q-value learning method within the maximum entropy RL framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soft-qmix-integrating-maximum-entropy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Elusive Pursuit of Replicating PATE-GAN: Benchmarking, Auditing, Debugging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-elusive-pursuit-of-replicating-pate-gan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze and benchmark six open-source PATE-GAN implementations, including three by (a subset of) the original authors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-elusive-pursuit-of-replicating-pate-gan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Sizing Field Prediction for Adaptive Mesh Generation From Expert Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-sizing-field-prediction-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To balance computational speed and accuracy meshes with adaptive resolution are used, allocating more resources to critical parts of the geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-sizing-field-prediction-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSAD: Self-supervised Auxiliary Detection Framework for Panoramic X-ray based Dental Disease Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssad-self-supervised-auxiliary-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enhance the encoder's ability to capture fine-grained features, we incorporate the image encoder of SAM to construct a texture consistency (TC) loss, which extracts image embedding from the input and output of reconstruction branch, and then enforces both embedding into the same feature space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssad-self-supervised-auxiliary-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Event-oriented Long Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-event-oriented-long-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging an effective instruction synthesis method and an adaptive model architecture, VIM surpasses both state-of-the-art open-source models and GPT-4V on the Event-Bench.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-event-oriented-long-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epicardium Prompt-guided Real-time Cardiac Ultrasound Frame-to-volume Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epicardium-prompt-guided-real-time-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A comprehensive guidance view for cardiac interventional surgery can be provided by the real-time fusion of the intraoperative 2D images and preoperative 3D volume based on the ultrasound frame-to-volume registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epicardium-prompt-guided-real-time-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL on Incorrect Synthetic Data Scales the Efficiency of LLM Math Reasoning by Eight-Fold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-on-incorrect-synthetic-data-scales-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this per-step scheme, we are able to attain consistent gains over only positive data, attaining performance similar to amplifying the amount of synthetic data by $\mathbf{8 \times}$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl-on-incorrect-synthetic-data-scales-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMBench-Video: A Long-Form Multi-Shot Benchmark for Holistic Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmbench-video-a-long-form-multi-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of large vision-language models (LVLMs) has spurred research into their applications in multi-modal contexts, particularly in video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmbench-video-a-long-form-multi-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoCAP: Towards Automatic Cross-lingual Alignment Planning for Zero-shot Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocap-towards-automatic-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cross-lingual chain-of-thought can effectively complete reasoning tasks across languages, which gains increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocap-towards-automatic-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmarking Study of Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks on Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmarking-study-of-kolmogorov-arnold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks (KANs) have very recently been introduced into the world of machine learning, quickly capturing the attention of the entire community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmarking-study-of-kolmogorov-arnold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Discover Knowledge: A Weakly-Supervised Partial Domain Adaptation Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-discover-knowledge-a-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, the key issues of WS-PDA are: 1) how to sufficiently discover the knowledge from the noisy labeled source domain and the unlabeled target domain, and 2) how to successfully adapt the knowledge across domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-discover-knowledge-a-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Tree Structure Should Sentence Be Generated</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-tree-structure-should-sentence-be</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper includes an illustration of the theoretical basis and validity of the approach, as well as a comparison of its fundamentals with the diffusion model in graphic generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-tree-structure-should-sentence-be</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Graph Convolution and Contrastive Learning in Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-graph-convolution-and-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By examining the learning dynamics and equilibrium of the contrastive loss, we offer a fresh lens to understand contrastive learning via graph theory, emphasizing its capability to capture high-order connectivity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-graph-convolution-and-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timo: Towards Better Temporal Reasoning for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timo-towards-better-temporal-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a crucial question: Can we build a universal framework to handle a variety of temporal reasoning tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/timo-towards-better-temporal-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask the Unknown: Assessing Different Strategies to Handle Weak Annotations in the MICCAI2023 Mediastinal Lymph Node Quantification Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-the-unknown-assessing-different</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the challenge submission, multiple methods for training on these weakly supervised data were explored, including noisy label training, loss masking of unlabeled data, and an approach that integrated the TotalSegmentator toolbox as a form of pseudo labeling in order to reduce the number of unknown voxels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-the-unknown-assessing-different</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Music Recommendation with a Heterogeneity-aware Deep Bayesian Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-music-recommendation-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ablation experiments and case studies further validate the effectiveness of our HDBN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personalized-music-recommendation-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An agent-based model of behaviour change calibrated to reversal learning data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-agent-based-model-of-behaviour-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model has only two parameters, and we use approximate Bayesian computation to demonstrate that they are fully identifiable from empirical reversal learning time series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-agent-based-model-of-behaviour-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation of Non-Small Cell Lung Carcinomas: Introducing DRU-Net and Multi-Lens Distortion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-of-non-small-cell-lung</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering the increased workload in pathology laboratories today, automated tools such as artificial intelligence models can help pathologists with their tasks and ease the workload.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-of-non-small-cell-lung</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Pre-Training Dynamics of In-Context Learning: Task Recognition vs. Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-pre-training-dynamics-of-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of in-context learning (ICL) is potentially attributed to two major abilities: task recognition (TR) for recognizing the task from demonstrations and utilizing pre-trained priors, and task learning (TL) for learning from demonstrations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-pre-training-dynamics-of-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seg-LSTM: Performance of xLSTM for Semantic Segmentation of Remotely Sensed Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-lstm-performance-of-xlstm-for-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in autoregressive networks with linear complexity have driven significant research progress, demonstrating exceptional performance in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-lstm-performance-of-xlstm-for-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the in-situ Trunk Identification and Length Measurement of Sea Cucumbers via Bézier Curve Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-in-situ-trunk-identification-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, by utilizing the depth information of pixels located along the trunk curve captured by a binocular camera, we propose accurately estimating the in-situ length of sea cucumbers through space curve integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-in-situ-trunk-identification-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoTPP Benchmark: Are We Good at the Long Horizon Events Forecasting?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hotpp-benchmark-are-we-good-at-the-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In sequential event prediction, which finds applications in finance, retail, social networks, and healthcare, a crucial task is forecasting multiple future events within a specified time horizon.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hotpp-benchmark-are-we-good-at-the-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instruction Pre-Training: Language Models are Supervised Multitask Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-pre-training-language-models-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised multitask pre-training has been the critical method behind the recent success of language models (LMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instruction-pre-training-language-models-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafeSora: Towards Safety Alignment of Text2Video Generation via a Human Preference Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safesora-towards-safety-alignment-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the risk of harmful outputs from large vision models (LVMs), we introduce the SafeSora dataset to promote research on aligning text-to-video generation with human values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safesora-towards-safety-alignment-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VLBiasBench: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Evaluating Bias in Large Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlbiasbench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of Large Vision-Language Models (LVLMs) marks significant strides towards achieving general artificial intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vlbiasbench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence of a log scaling law for political persuasion with large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidence-of-a-log-scaling-law-for-political</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models can now generate political messages as persuasive as those written by humans, raising concerns about how far this persuasiveness may continue to increase with model size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evidence-of-a-log-scaling-law-for-political</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LARP: Language Audio Relational Pre-training for Cold-Start Playlist Continuation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larp-language-audio-relational-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As online music consumption increasingly shifts towards playlist-based listening, the task of playlist continuation, in which an algorithm suggests songs to extend a playlist in a personalized and musically cohesive manner, has become vital to the success of music streaming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larp-language-audio-relational-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Definition generation for lexical semantic change detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/definition-generation-for-lexical-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use contextualized word definitions generated by large language models as semantic representations in the task of diachronic lexical semantic change detection (LSCD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/definition-generation-for-lexical-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistency Models Made Easy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-models-made-easy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consistency models (CMs) are an emerging class of generative models that offer faster sampling than traditional diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistency-models-made-easy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CollaFuse: Collaborative Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collafuse-collaborative-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to these challenges, we introduce a novel approach for distributed collaborative diffusion models inspired by split learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collafuse-collaborative-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Modularity Maximization for Graph Clustering: A Contrastive Learning Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-modularity-maximization-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Another promising line of research involves the adoption of modularity maximization, a popular and effective measure for community detection, as the guiding principle for clustering tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-modularity-maximization-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi Supervised Heterogeneous Domain Adaptation via Disentanglement and Pseudo-Labelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-heterogeneous-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such a setting is denoted as Semi-Supervised Heterogeneous Domain Adaptation (SSHDA) and it exhibits an even more severe distribution shift due to modality heterogeneity across domains. To cope with the challenging SSHDA setting, here we introduce SHeDD (Semi-supervised Heterogeneous Domain Adaptation via Disentanglement) an end-to-end neural framework tailored to learning a target domain classifier by leveraging both labelled and unlabelled data from heterogeneous data sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-heterogeneous-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning Like a Doctor: Improving Medical Dialogue Systems via Diagnostic Reasoning Process Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-like-a-doctor-improving-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel framework, Emulation, designed to generate an appropriate response that relies on abductive and deductive diagnostic reasoning analyses and aligns with clinician preferences through thought process modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-like-a-doctor-improving-medical</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
