<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 21:08:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TLP: A Deep Learning-based Cost Model for Tensor Program Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tlp-a-deep-learning-based-cost-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of extracting features from the tensor program itself, TLP extracts features from the schedule primitives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tlp-a-deep-learning-based-cost-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Set Covering to Generate Databases for Holistic Steganalysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-set-covering-to-generate-databases-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within an operational framework, covers used by a steganographer are likely to come from different sensors and different processing pipelines than the ones used by researchers for training their steganalysis models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-set-covering-to-generate-databases-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving Frame Net: SE(3)-Equivariant Network for Volumes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-frame-net-se-3-equivariant-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equivariance of neural networks to transformations helps to improve their performance and reduce generalization error in computer vision tasks, as they apply to datasets presenting symmetries (e. g. scalings, rotations, translations).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moving-frame-net-se-3-equivariant-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Model Bugs with Natural Language Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixing-model-bugs-with-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current approaches for fixing systematic problems in NLP models (e. g. regex patches, finetuning on more data) are either brittle, or labor-intensive and liable to shortcuts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fixing-model-bugs-with-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complex Hyperbolic Knowledge Graph Embeddings with Fast Fourier Transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-hyperbolic-knowledge-graph-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the performance of the hyperbolic KG embedding models for non-transitive relations is still unpromising, while the complex hyperbolic embeddings do not deal with multi-relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complex-hyperbolic-knowledge-graph-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debiasing Graph Transfer Learning via Item Semantic Clustering for Cross-Domain Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-graph-transfer-learning-via-item</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this data sparsity problem, cross-domain recommender systems (CDRSs) exploit the data from an auxiliary source domain to facilitate the recommendation on the sparse target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debiasing-graph-transfer-learning-via-item</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technical Report on Web-based Visual Corpus Construction for Visual Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-on-web-based-visual-corpus</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a dataset generator engine named Web-based Visual Corpus Builder (Webvicob).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/technical-report-on-web-based-visual-corpus</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfroLM: A Self-Active Learning-based Multilingual Pretrained Language Model for 23 African Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrolm-a-self-active-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present AfroLM, a multilingual language model pretrained from scratch on 23 African languages (the largest effort to date) using our novel self-active learning framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/afrolm-a-self-active-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black-Box Attack against GAN-Generated Image Detector with Contrastive Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-attack-against-gan-generated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is significant to assess the vulnerability of such forensic detectors against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/black-box-attack-against-gan-generated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatiotemporal forecasting of track geometry irregularities with exogenous factors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-forecasting-of-track-geometry</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a method to forecast one type of track geometry irregularity, vertical alignment, by incorporating spatial and exogenous factor calculations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatiotemporal-forecasting-of-track-geometry</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ERNIE-SAT: Speech and Text Joint Pretraining for Cross-Lingual Multi-Speaker Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-sat-speech-and-text-joint-pretraining-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we extend the pretraining method for cross-lingual multi-speaker speech synthesis tasks, including cross-lingual multi-speaker voice cloning and cross-lingual multi-speaker speech editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ernie-sat-speech-and-text-joint-pretraining-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accented Text-to-Speech Synthesis with a Conditional Variational Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accented-text-to-speech-synthesis-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accent plays a significant role in speech communication, influencing understanding capabilities and also conveying a person's identity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accented-text-to-speech-synthesis-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max-Min Off-Policy Actor-Critic Method Focusing on Worst-Case Robustness to Model Misspecification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/max-min-off-policy-actor-critic-method</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we focus on scenarios involving a simulation environment with uncertainty parameters and the set of their possible values, called the uncertainty parameter set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/max-min-off-policy-actor-critic-method</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Completion with Heterogeneously Filtered Spectral Hints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-completion-with-heterogeneously</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also prove the effectiveness of our design via ablation studies, from which one may notice that the aforementioned challenges, i. e. pattern unawareness, blurry textures, and structure distortion, can be noticeably resolved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-completion-with-heterogeneously</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Classification by Logical Reasoning on Natural Language Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-classification-by-logical-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans can classify an unseen category by reasoning on its language explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-classification-by-logical-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRIPP-VQA: Counterfactual Reasoning about Implicit Physical Properties via Video Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cripp-vqa-counterfactual-reasoning-about</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Videos often capture objects, their visible properties, their motion, and the interactions between different objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cripp-vqa-counterfactual-reasoning-about</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLOPT: Bandit Optimization Framework for Mutation-Based Fuzzing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slopt-bandit-optimization-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fuzzing can be optimized when targeting specific programs, and given that, some studies have employed online optimization methods to do it automatically, i. e., tuning fuzzers for any given program in a program-agnostic manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slopt-bandit-optimization-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Word Embedding Model Is Perfect: Evaluating the Representation Accuracy for Social Bias in the Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-word-embedding-model-is-perfect-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To cover the whole spectrum of political bias in the US, we collect 500k articles and review psychology literature with respect to expected social bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/no-word-embedding-model-is-perfect-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum-based Asymmetric Multi-task Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-asymmetric-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the negative influence of customizing the one-off training order in curriculum-based AMTL, CAMRL switches its training mode between parallel single-task RL and asymmetric multi-task RL (MTRL), according to an indicator regarding the training time, the overall performance, and the performance gap among tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-asymmetric-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Horseshoe Estimation via Expectation-Maximisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-horseshoe-estimation-via-expectation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A particular strength of our approach is that the M-step depends only on the form of the prior and it is independent of the form of the likelihood.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-horseshoe-estimation-via-expectation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pyGSL: A Graph Structure Learning Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygsl-a-graph-structure-learning-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implementations of differentiable graph structure learning models are written in PyTorch, allowing us to leverage the rich software ecosystem that exists e. g., around logging, hyperparameter search, and GPU-communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pygsl-a-graph-structure-learning-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPCSpell: A Transformer-based Detector-Purificator-Corrector Framework for Spelling Error Correction of Bangla and Resource Scarce Indic Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpcspell-a-transformer-based-detector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Earlier efforts on spelling error correction in Bangla and resource-scarce Indic languages focused on rule-based, statistical, and machine learning-based methods which we found rather inefficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpcspell-a-transformer-based-detector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Semantic Textual Similarity via Topic-informed Discrete Latent Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-semantic-textual-similarity-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, discrete latent variable models have received a surge of interest in both Natural Language Processing (NLP) and Computer Vision (CV), attributed to their comparable performance to the continuous counterparts in representation learning, while being more interpretable in their predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-semantic-textual-similarity-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Denoising Diffusions to Denoising Markov Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-denoising-diffusions-to-denoising-markov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising diffusions are state-of-the-art generative models which exhibit remarkable empirical performance and come with theoretical guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-denoising-diffusions-to-denoising-markov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlphaPose: Whole-Body Regional Multi-Person Pose Estimation and Tracking in Real-Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphapose-whole-body-regional-multi-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate whole-body multi-person pose estimation and tracking is an important yet challenging topic in computer vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alphapose-whole-body-regional-multi-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SC-DepthV3: Robust Self-supervised Monocular Depth Estimation for Dynamic Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-depthv3-robust-self-supervised-monocular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised monocular depth estimation has shown impressive results in static scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sc-depthv3-robust-self-supervised-monocular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Multi-order Gated Aggregation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-order-gated-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the recent success of Vision Transformers (ViTs), explorations toward transformer-style architectures have triggered the resurgence of modern ConvNets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-multi-order-gated-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Harmonic Loss: Towards Task-consistent and Time-friendly 3D Object Detection on Edge for Intelligent Transportation System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-harmonic-loss-towards-task-consistent-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Edge computing-based 3D perception has received attention in intelligent transportation systems (ITS) because real-time monitoring of traffic candidates potentially strengthens Vehicle-to-Everything (V2X) orchestration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-harmonic-loss-towards-task-consistent-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning enhanced Author-Style Headline Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-enhanced-author-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Seq2Seq model called CLH3G (Contrastive Learning enhanced Historical Headlines based Headline Generation) which can use the historical headlines of the articles that the author wrote in the past to improve the headline generation of current articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-enhanced-author-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeSOTIF: a Challenging Visual Dataset for Perception SOTIF Problems in Long-tail Traffic Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pesotif-a-challenging-visual-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perception algorithms in autonomous driving systems confront great challenges in long-tail traffic scenarios, where the problems of Safety of the Intended Functionality (SOTIF) could be triggered by the algorithm performance insufficiencies and dynamic operational environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pesotif-a-challenging-visual-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suffix Retrieval-Augmented Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suffix-retrieval-augmented-language-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SUREALM employs an embedding retriever to search for training sentences in a data store that share similar word history during sequence generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suffix-retrieval-augmented-language-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Lottery Tickets for Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-lottery-tickets-for-pre-trained-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works on Lottery Ticket Hypothesis have shown that pre-trained language models (PLMs) contain smaller matching subnetworks(winning tickets) which are capable of reaching accuracy comparable to the original models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-lottery-tickets-for-pre-trained-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WeakIdent: Weak formulation for Identifying Differential Equations using Narrow-fit and Trimming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakident-weak-formulation-for-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a general and robust framework to recover differential equations using a weak formulation, for both ordinary and partial differential equations (ODEs and PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakident-weak-formulation-for-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UATTA-ENS: Uncertainty Aware Test Time Augmented Ensemble for PIRC Diabetic Retinopathy Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uatta-ens-uncertainty-aware-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Ensemble Convolutional Neural Networks has become a methodology of choice for analyzing medical images with a diagnostic performance comparable to a physician, including the diagnosis of Diabetic Retinopathy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uatta-ens-uncertainty-aware-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning Language Models as Training Data Generators for Augmentation-Enhanced Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-language-models-as-training-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study few-shot learning with PLMs from a different perspective: We first tune an autoregressive PLM on the few-shot samples and then use it as a generator to synthesize a large amount of novel training samples which augment the original training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tuning-language-models-as-training-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calibration Meets Explanation: A Simple and Effective Approach for Model Confidence Estimates</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-meets-explanation-a-simple-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments on six datasets with two popular pre-trained language models in the in-domain and out-of-domain settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/calibration-meets-explanation-a-simple-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Style Transfer: Modular Low-Rank Adaptation for Deep Motion Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-style-transfer-modular-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce two components that exploit our prior knowledge of motion style shifts: (i) a low-rank motion style adapter that projects and adjusts the style features at a low-dimensional bottleneck; and (ii) a modular adapter strategy that disentangles the features of scene context and motion history to facilitate a fine-grained choice of adaptation layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-style-transfer-modular-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks for Community Detection on Sparse Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-community-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spectral methods provide consistent estimators for community detection in dense graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-for-community-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hear The Flow: Optical Flow-Based Self-Supervised Visual Sound Source Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hear-the-flow-optical-flow-based-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing work in this area focuses on creating attention maps to capture the correlation between the two modalities to localize the source of the sound.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hear-the-flow-optical-flow-based-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Dual-Fused Modality-Aware Representations for RGBD Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dual-fused-modality-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second aims at integrating the RGB-specific and depth-specific information to enhance the fused features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dual-fused-modality-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Data for Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-for-feature-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature selection is an important and active field of research in machine learning and data science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-data-for-feature-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characterizing the Efficiency of Graph Neural Network Frameworks with a Magnifying Glass</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-efficiency-of-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, unlike the traditional GNNs that are trained based on the entire graph in a full-batch manner, recent GNNs have been developed with different graph sampling techniques for mini-batch training of GNNs on large graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characterizing-the-efficiency-of-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Annotate Part Segmentation with Gradient Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-annotate-part-segmentation-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of state-of-the-art deep neural networks heavily relies on the presence of large-scale labelled datasets, which are extremely expensive and time-consuming to annotate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-annotate-part-segmentation-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Deep Face Restoration: Denoise, Super-Resolution, Deblur, Artifact Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-deep-face-restoration-denoise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we discuss the challenges of face restoration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-deep-face-restoration-denoise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Textual Manifold-based Defense Against Natural Language Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-manifold-based-defense-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, this is the first NLP defense that leverages the manifold structure against adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textual-manifold-based-defense-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Infer from Unlabeled Data: A Semi-supervised Learning Approach for Robust Natural Language Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-infer-from-unlabeled-data-a-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, despite its substantial success on single sentence classification tasks where the challenge in making use of unlabeled data is to assign "good enough" pseudo-labels, for NLI tasks, the nature of unlabeled data is more complex: one of the sentences in the pair (usually the hypothesis) along with the class label are missing from the data and require human annotations, which makes SSL for NLI more challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-infer-from-unlabeled-data-a-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Person, One Model--Learning Compound Router for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-person-one-model-learning-compound-router</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core idea of CANet is to route the input user behaviors with a light-weighted router module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-person-one-model-learning-compound-router</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Definitions and Evaluations for Saliency Methods: Staying Intrinsic, Complete and Sound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-definitions-and-evaluations-for-saliency-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Saliency methods compute heat maps that highlight portions of an input that were most {\em important} for the label assigned to it by a deep net.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-definitions-and-evaluations-for-saliency-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEKG: A Built Environment Knowledge Graph</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bekg-a-built-environment-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, more than 80, 000 paper abstracts in the built environment field were obtained to build a knowledge graph, a knowledge base storing entities and their connective relations in a graph-structured data model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bekg-a-built-environment-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Neural Computers with Memory Demon</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-neural-computers-with-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Differentiable Neural Computer (DNC) is a neural network with an external memory which allows for iterative content modification via read, write and delete operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-neural-computers-with-memory</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
