<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 09:12:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Generalization of Segmentation Foundation Model under Distribution Shift via Weakly Supervised Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-generalization-of-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of large language models has inspired the computer vision community to explore image segmentation foundation model that is able to zero/few-shot generalize through prompt engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-generalization-of-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skeleton-in-Context: Unified Skeleton Sequence Modeling with In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-in-context-unified-skeleton-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under this setting, the model can perceive tasks from prompts and accomplish them without any extra task-specific head predictions or model fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skeleton-in-context-unified-skeleton-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can language agents be alternatives to PPO? A Preliminary Empirical Study On OpenAI Gym</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-agents-be-alternatives-to-ppo-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The formidable capacity for zero- or few-shot decision-making in language agents encourages us to pose a compelling question: Can language agents be alternatives to PPO agents in traditional sequential decision-making tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-agents-be-alternatives-to-ppo-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Quality Facial Geometry and Appearance Capture at Home</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-quality-facial-geometry-and-appearance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facial geometry and appearance capture have demonstrated tremendous success in 3D scanning real humans in studios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-quality-facial-geometry-and-appearance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Planning Problems Can A Relational Neural Network Solve?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-planning-problems-can-a-relational-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Goal-conditioned policies are generally understood to be "feed-forward" circuits, in the form of neural networks that map from the current state and the goal specification to the next action to take.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-planning-problems-can-a-relational-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Object Saliency Ranking: A Novel Whole-flow Processing Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-object-saliency-ranking-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To conquer, this paper proposes a new paradigm for saliency ranking, which aims to completely focus on ranking salient objects by their "importance order".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-object-saliency-ranking-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-4 Enhanced Multimodal Grounding for Autonomous Driving: Leveraging Cross-Modal Attention with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4-enhanced-multimodal-grounding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of autonomous vehicles (AVs), accurately discerning commander intent and executing linguistic commands within a visual context presents a significant challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-4-enhanced-multimodal-grounding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBCopilot: Scaling Natural Language Querying to Massive Databases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbcopilot-scaling-natural-language-querying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-SQL simplifies database interactions by enabling non-experts to convert their natural language (NL) questions into Structured Query Language (SQL) queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbcopilot-scaling-natural-language-querying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physical Symbolic Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physical-symbolic-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a framework for constraining the automatic sequential generation of equations to obey the rules of dimensional analysis by construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physical-symbolic-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAFE: Towards Compact, Adaptive, and Fast Embedding for Large-scale Recommendation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cafe-towards-compact-adaptive-and-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Guided by our design philosophy, we further propose a multi-level hash embedding framework to optimize the embedding tables of non-hot features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cafe-towards-compact-adaptive-and-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reason2Drive: Towards Interpretable and Chain-based Reasoning for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reason2drive-towards-interpretable-and-chain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision-language models (VLMs) have garnered increasing interest in autonomous driving areas, due to their advanced capabilities in complex reasoning tasks essential for highly autonomous vehicle behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reason2drive-towards-interpretable-and-chain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizable Neural Physics Solvers by Baldwinian Evolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-neural-physics-solvers-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Physics-informed neural networks (PINNs) are at the forefront of scientific machine learning, making possible the creation of machine intelligence that is cognizant of physical laws and able to accurately simulate them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizable-neural-physics-solvers-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting legal case retrieval by query content selection with large language models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-legal-case-retrieval-by-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Legal case retrieval, which aims to retrieve relevant cases to a given query case, benefits judgment justice and attracts increasing attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-legal-case-retrieval-by-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain Invariant Representation Learning and Sleep Dynamics Modeling for Automatic Sleep Staging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-invariant-representation-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, previous studies face some critical problems in sleep studies; the heterogeneity of subjects' physiological signals, the inability to extract meaningful information from unlabeled sleep signal data to improve predictive performances, the difficulty in modeling correlations between sleep stages, and the lack of an effective mechanism to quantify predictive uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-invariant-representation-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multicoated and Folded Graph Neural Networks with Strong Lottery Tickets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multicoated-and-folded-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Strong Lottery Ticket Hypothesis (SLTH) demonstrates the existence of high-performing subnetworks within a randomly initialized model, discoverable through pruning a convolutional neural network (CNN) without any weight training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multicoated-and-folded-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JAMMIN-GPT: Text-based Improvisation using LLMs in Ableton Live</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jammin-gpt-text-based-improvisation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a system that allows users of Ableton Live to create MIDI-clips by naming them with musical descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jammin-gpt-text-based-improvisation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texture-Semantic Collaboration Network for ORSI Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texture-semantic-collaboration-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the TSCM, we first enhance the position of potential salient regions using semantic features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texture-semantic-collaboration-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speculative Exploration on the Concept of Artificial Agents Conducting Autonomous Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speculative-exploration-on-the-concept-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper engages in a speculative exploration of the concept of an artificial agent capable of conducting research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speculative-exploration-on-the-concept-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compressed Context Memory For Online Language Model Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressed-context-memory-for-online-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through evaluations on conversation, personalization, and multi-task learning, we demonstrate that our approach achieves the performance level of a full context model with $5\times$ smaller context memory space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compressed-context-memory-for-online-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Bias Mitigation through Bias Experts in Natural Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-bias-mitigation-through-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To mitigate the detrimental effect of the bias on the networks, previous works have proposed debiasing methods that down-weight the biased examples identified by an auxiliary model, which is trained with explicit bias labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-bias-mitigation-through-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMR Parsing is Far from Solved: GrAPES, the Granular AMR Parsing Evaluation Suite</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amr-parsing-is-far-from-solved-grapes-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Granular AMR Parsing Evaluation Suite (GrAPES), a challenge set for Abstract Meaning Representation (AMR) parsing with accompanying evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amr-parsing-is-far-from-solved-grapes-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PneumoLLM: Harnessing the Power of Large Language Model for Pneumoconiosis Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pneumollm-harnessing-the-power-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, this approach often requires optimization of extensive learnable parameters in the text branch and the dialogue head, potentially diminishing the LLMs' efficacy, especially with limited training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pneumollm-harnessing-the-power-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneLLM: One Framework to Align All Modalities with Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onellm-one-framework-to-align-all-modalities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In detail, we first train an image projection module to connect a vision encoder with LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onellm-one-framework-to-align-all-modalities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lazy-k: Decoding for Constrained Token Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lazy-k-decoding-for-constrained-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the possibility of improving probabilistic models in structured prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lazy-k-decoding-for-constrained-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-shot Object Learning with Mutual Exclusivity Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-shot-object-learning-with-mutual-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Low-shot Object Learning with Mutual Exclusivity Bias (LSME), the first computational framing of mutual exclusivity bias, a phenomenon commonly observed in infants during word learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-shot-object-learning-with-mutual-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-sourced Data Ecosystem in Autonomous Driving: the Present and Future</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-sourced-data-ecosystem-in-autonomous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the continuous maturation and application of autonomous driving technology, a systematic examination of open-source autonomous driving datasets becomes instrumental in fostering the robust evolution of the industry ecosystem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-sourced-data-ecosystem-in-autonomous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEP CATFormer: Spatial-Temporal Effective Body-Part Cross Attention Transformer for Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-catformer-spatial-temporal-effective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We think the key to skeleton-based action recognition is a skeleton hanging in frames, so we focus on how the Graph Convolutional Convolution networks learn different topologies and effectively aggregate joint features in the global temporal and local temporal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-catformer-spatial-temporal-effective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Vectorized HD Map Construction using Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-vectorized-hd-map-construction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we propose GeMap ($\textbf{Ge}$ometry $\textbf{Map}$), which end-to-end learns Euclidean shapes and relations of map instances beyond basic perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-vectorized-hd-map-construction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Action Scene Graphs for Long-Form Understanding of Egocentric Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-scene-graphs-for-long-form</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Egocentric Action Scene Graphs (EASGs), a new representation for long-form understanding of egocentric videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/action-scene-graphs-for-long-form</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFineBench: Towards Text-based Person Retrieval with Ultra-fine Granularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufinebench-towards-text-based-person</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly, we construct a new \textbf{dataset} named UFine6926.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufinebench-towards-text-based-person</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning From Scenarios for Stochastic Repairable Scheduling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-scenarios-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We are interested in a stochastic scheduling problem, in which processing times are uncertain, which brings uncertain values in the constraints, and thus repair of an initial schedule may be needed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-scenarios-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-conditioned Image Generation via Generating Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-conditioned-image-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During generation, RCG samples from such representation distribution using a representation diffusion model (RDM), and employs a pixel generator to craft image pixels conditioned on the sampled representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-conditioned-image-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Neural Network Training Under Class Imbalance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-neural-network-training-under-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world datasets are often highly class-imbalanced, which can adversely impact the performance of deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplifying-neural-network-training-under-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MKA: A Scalable Medical Knowledge Assisted Mechanism for Generative Models on Medical Conversation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mka-a-scalable-medical-knowledge-assisted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation of our method is carried out on two typical medical datasets, MedDG and MedDialog-CN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mka-a-scalable-medical-knowledge-assisted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniswap Daily Transaction Indices by Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniswap-daily-transaction-indices-by-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeFi is transforming financial services by removing intermediaries and producing a wealth of open-source data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniswap-daily-transaction-indices-by-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Vision Therapy: Multimodal Large Language Models Can Enhance Visual Robustness via Denoising In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-vision-therapy-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, by estimating a transition matrix that captures the probability of one class being confused with another, an instruction containing a correct exemplar and an erroneous one from the most probable noisy class can be constructed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-vision-therapy-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexModel: A Framework for Interpretability of Distributed Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexmodel-a-framework-for-interpretability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the growth of large language models, now incorporating billions of parameters, the hardware prerequisites for their training and deployment have seen a corresponding increase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexmodel-a-framework-for-interpretability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Agents: Empowering Agents with Imagination for Creative Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-agents-empowering-agents-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We benchmark creative tasks with the challenging open-world game Minecraft, where the agents are asked to create diverse buildings given free-form language instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-agents-empowering-agents-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Market-Based Framework for Increasing Responsive Loads In Distribution Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-market-based-framework-for-increasing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The utilization of these loads in the competitive environment of the power market has led to a decrease in costs and an increase in the flexibility of the distribution system and, consequently, the power system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-market-based-framework-for-increasing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diversified in-domain synthesis with efficient fine-tuning for few-shot classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversified-in-domain-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot image classification aims to learn an image classifier using only a small set of labeled examples per class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diversified-in-domain-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaRA: Aligning Large Language Models with Sequential Recommenders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llara-aligning-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To harness the complementary strengths of traditional recommenders (which encode user behavioral knowledge) and LLMs (which possess world knowledge about items), we propose LLaRA -- a Large Language and Recommendation Assistant framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llara-aligning-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Ego Status All You Need for Open-Loop End-to-End Autonomous Driving?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-ego-status-all-you-need-for-open-loop-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We initially observed that the nuScenes dataset, characterized by relatively simple driving scenarios, leads to an under-utilization of perception information in end-to-end models incorporating ego status, such as the ego vehicle's velocity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-ego-status-all-you-need-for-open-loop-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-Assisted Remote Sensing Imagery Semantic Segmentation with Object and Boundary Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-assisted-remote-sensing-imagery-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, the boundary loss capitalizes on the distinctive features of SGB by directing the model's attention to the boundary information of the object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-assisted-remote-sensing-imagery-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Vision Transformers More Data Hungry Than Newborn Visual Systems?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-transformers-more-data-hungry-than-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, ViTs were not more data hungry than newborn visual systems: both learned view invariant object representations in impoverished visual environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-vision-transformers-more-data-hungry-than-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchLMM: Benchmarking Cross-style Visual Capability of Large Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchlmm-benchmarking-cross-style-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) such as GPT-4V and LLaVA have shown remarkable capabilities in visual reasoning with common image styles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchlmm-benchmarking-cross-style-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion-SS3D: Diffusion Model for Semi-supervised 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-ss3d-diffusion-model-for-semi-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised object detection is crucial for 3D scene understanding, efficiently addressing the limitation of acquiring large-scale 3D bounding box annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-ss3d-diffusion-model-for-semi-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E4SRec: An Elegant Effective Efficient Extensible Solution of Large Language Models for Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e4srec-an-elegant-effective-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, practical ID-based recommendation strategies, reliant on a huge number of unique identities (IDs) to represent users and items, have gained prominence in real-world recommender systems due to their effectiveness and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e4srec-an-elegant-effective-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Initialization of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-initialization-of-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze the variance of forward and backward propagation across GNN layers and show that the variance instability of GNN initializations comes from the combined effect of the activation function, hidden dimension, graph structure and message passing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-initialization-of-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEMTO: Memory-guided Transformer for Multivariate Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memto-memory-guided-transformer-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is designed to incorporate a novel memory module that can learn the degree to which each memory item should be updated in response to the input data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memto-memory-guided-transformer-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Measuring Representational Similarity of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-measuring-representational-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the similarity of the numerous released large language models (LLMs) has many uses, e. g., simplifying model selection, detecting illegal model reuse, and advancing our understanding of what makes LLMs perform well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-measuring-representational-similarity</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
