<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 09:11:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unite-Divide-Unite: Joint Boosting Trunk and Structure for High-accuracy Dichotomous Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unite-divide-unite-joint-boosting-trunk-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, a dual-size input feeds into the shared backbone to produce more holistic and detailed features while keeping the model lightweight.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unite-divide-unite-joint-boosting-trunk-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Networks-based Hybrid Framework For Predicting Particle Crushing Strength</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-based-hybrid-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we firstly generate a dataset with 45, 000 numerical simulations and 900 particle types to facilitate the research progress of machine learning for particle crushing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-networks-based-hybrid-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Semantic Subspace Traverser: Empowering 3D Generative Model with Shape Editing Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-semantic-subspace-traverser-empowering-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method utilizes implicit functions as the 3D shape representation and combines a novel latent-space GAN with a linear subspace model to discover semantic dimensions in the local latent space of 3D shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-semantic-subspace-traverser-empowering-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AViT: Adapting Vision Transformers for Small Skin Lesion Segmentation Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avit-adapting-vision-transformers-for-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we employ a shallow CNN as a prompt generator to create a prompt embedding from the input image, which grasps fine-grained information and CNN's inductive biases to guide the segmentation task on small datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/avit-adapting-vision-transformers-for-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WavJourney: Compositional Audio Creation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavjourney-compositional-audio-creation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present WavJourney, a system that leverages LLMs to connect various audio models for audio content generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavjourney-compositional-audio-creation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Position Bias Model for Short-Video Recommendation Feeds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-position-bias-model-for-short</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Empirical insights from a large-scale social media platform show how our probabilistic position bias model more accurately captures empirical exposure than existing models, and paves the way for unbiased evaluation and learning-to-rank.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-position-bias-model-for-short</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning sources of variability from high-dimensional observational studies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-sources-of-variability-from-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Causal inference studies whether the presence of a variable influences an observed outcome.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-sources-of-variability-from-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrammarGPT: Exploring Open-Source LLMs for Native Chinese Grammatical Error Correction with Supervised Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammargpt-exploring-open-source-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although model parameters are 20x larger than the SOTA baseline, the required amount of data for instruction tuning is 1200x smaller, illustrating the potential of open-source LLMs on native CGEC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grammargpt-exploring-open-source-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Representation-Enhanced Sampling for Bayesian Active Learning in Musculoskeletal Segmentation of Lower Extremities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-representation-enhanced-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on BAL, this study introduces a hybrid representation-enhanced sampling strategy that integrates density and diversity criteria to save manual annotation costs by efficiently selecting the most informative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-representation-enhanced-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Moral Beliefs Encoded in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-moral-beliefs-encoded-in-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(2) We apply this method to study what moral beliefs are encoded in different LLMs, especially in ambiguous cases where the right choice is not obvious.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-moral-beliefs-encoded-in-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Anything in High Quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-anything-in-high-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the quality of tracking masks, a pretrained MR model is employed to refine the tracking results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-anything-in-high-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Double Descent in Vision Transformers: real or phantom threat?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-double-descent-in-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision transformers (ViT) have been of broad interest in recent theoretical and empirical works.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-double-descent-in-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIDE: A Vision-Driven Multi-View, Multi-Modal, Multi-Tasking Dataset for Assistive Driving Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aide-a-vision-driven-multi-view-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Driver distraction has become a significant cause of severe traffic accidents over the past decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aide-a-vision-driven-multi-view-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consensus-Adaptive RANSAC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consensus-adaptive-ransac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed attention mechanism and one-step transformer provide an adaptive behavior that enhances the performance of RANSAC, making it a more effective tool for robust estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consensus-adaptive-ransac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi3WOZ: A Multilingual, Multi-Domain, Multi-Parallel Dataset for Training and Evaluating Culturally Adapted Task-Oriented Dialog Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi3woz-a-multilingual-multi-domain-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating high-quality annotated data for task-oriented dialog (ToD) is known to be notoriously difficult, and the challenges are amplified when the goal is to create equitable, culturally adapted, and large-scale ToD datasets for multiple languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi3woz-a-multilingual-multi-domain-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Does Diffusion Influence Pretrained Language Models on Out-of-Distribution Data?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-diffusion-influence-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It shows that finetuning PLMs with diffusion degrades the reconstruction ability on OOD data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-does-diffusion-influence-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-aware Robust Optimization for Out-of-distribution Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-robust-optimization-for-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) generalization is a challenging machine learning problem yet highly desirable in many high-stake applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-robust-optimization-for-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Learning of Discrete-Continuous Computation Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-learning-of-discrete-continuous-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze the behavior of more complex stochastic computations graphs with multiple sequential discrete components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-learning-of-discrete-continuous-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisguisOR: Holistic Face Anonymization for the Operating Room</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disguisor-holistic-face-anonymization-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Methods: RGB and depth images from multiple cameras are fused into a 3D point cloud representation of the scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disguisor-holistic-face-anonymization-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artifact Restoration in Histology Images with Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-restoration-in-histology-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Histological whole slide images (WSIs) can be usually compromised by artifacts, such as tissue folding and bubbles, which will increase the examination difficulty for both pathologists and Computer-Aided Diagnosis (CAD) systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artifact-restoration-in-histology-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creative Birds: Self-Supervised Single-View 3D Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-birds-self-supervised-single-view-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our focus lies primarily on birds, a popular subject in 3D reconstruction, for which no existing single-view 3D transfer methods have been developed. The method we propose seeks to generate a 3D mesh shape and texture of a bird from two single-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creative-birds-self-supervised-single-view-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>trajdata: A Unified Interface to Multiple Human Trajectory Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajdata-a-unified-interface-to-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The field of trajectory forecasting has grown significantly in recent years, partially owing to the release of numerous large-scale, real-world human trajectory datasets for autonomous vehicles (AVs) and pedestrian motion tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trajdata-a-unified-interface-to-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabR: Unlocking the Power of Retrieval-Augmented Tabular Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabr-unlocking-the-power-of-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we highlight several details of the attention mechanism that turn out to have a massive impact on the performance on tabular data problems, but that were not explored in prior work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabr-unlocking-the-power-of-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOBench: Benchmarking Efficient Object Detectors on Embedded Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolobench-benchmarking-efficient-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present YOLOBench, a benchmark comprised of 550+ YOLO-based object detection models on 4 different datasets and 4 different embedded hardware platforms (x86 CPU, ARM CPU, Nvidia GPU, NPU).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolobench-benchmarking-efficient-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Constraint Enforcement Deep Reinforcement Learning Framework for Optimal Energy Storage Systems Dispatch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-constraint-enforcement-deep-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The optimal dispatch of energy storage systems (ESSs) presents formidable challenges due to the uncertainty introduced by fluctuations in dynamic prices, demand consumption, and renewable-based energy generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-constraint-enforcement-deep-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitting Auditory Filterbanks with Multiresolution Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-auditory-filterbanks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Waveform-based deep learning faces a dilemma between nonparametric and parametric approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitting-auditory-filterbanks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuIP: 2-Bit Quantization of Large Language Models With Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quip-2-bit-quantization-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work studies post-training parameter quantization in large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quip-2-bit-quantization-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Unifying Anatomy Segmentation: Automated Generation of a Full-body CT Dataset via Knowledge Aggregation and Anatomical Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-anatomy-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We examine its plausibility and usefulness using three complementary checks: Human expert evaluation which approved the dataset, a Deep Learning usefulness benchmark on the BTCV dataset in which we achieve 85% dice score without using its training dataset, and medical validity checks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unifying-anatomy-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strivec: Sparse Tri-Vector Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strivec-sparse-tri-vector-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to TensoRF which uses a global tensor and focuses on their vector-matrix decomposition, we propose to utilize a cloud of local tensors and apply the classic CANDECOMP/PARAFAC (CP) decomposition to factorize each tensor into triple vectors that express local feature distributions along spatial axes and compactly encode a local neural field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strivec-sparse-tri-vector-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuickQual: Lightweight, convenient retinal image quality scoring with off-the-shelf pretrained models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quickqual-lightweight-convenient-retinal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this task, we present a second model, QuickQual MEga Minified Estimator (QuickQual-MEME), that consists of only 10 parameters on top of an off-the-shelf Densenet121 and can distinguish between gradable and ungradable images with an accuracy of 89. 18% (AUC: 0. 9537).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quickqual-lightweight-convenient-retinal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotHawk: An Approach for Bots Detection in Open Source Software Projects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bothawk-an-approach-for-bots-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Identifying bot accounts and behavior is a challenging task in the OSS project.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bothawk-an-approach-for-bots-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Learning Dynamics of Attention Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-dynamics-of-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attention models are typically learned by optimizing one of three standard loss functions that are variously called -- soft attention, hard attention, and latent variable marginal likelihood (LVML) attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-learning-dynamics-of-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Importance Measurement based on Decision Tree Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-importance-measurement-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Random forest is effective for prediction tasks but the randomness of tree generation hinders interpretability in feature importance analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-importance-measurement-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinterpreting survival analysis in the universal approximator age</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinterpreting-survival-analysis-in-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to provide the tools needed to fully harness the potential of survival analysis in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinterpreting-survival-analysis-in-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Calibration in Dense Classification with Adaptive Label Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-calibration-in-dense-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve model calibration, we propose Adaptive Stochastic Label Perturbation (ASLP) which learns a unique label perturbation level for each training image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-calibration-in-dense-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectrum-guided Multi-granularity Referring Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrum-guided-multi-granularity-referring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the drift problem, we propose a Spectrum-guided Multi-granularity (SgMg) approach, which performs direct segmentation on the encoded features and employs visual details to further optimize the masks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectrum-guided-multi-granularity-referring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fashion Matrix: Editing Photos by Just Talking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fashion-matrix-editing-photos-by-just-talking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The utilization of Large Language Models (LLMs) for the construction of AI systems has garnered significant attention across diverse fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fashion-matrix-editing-photos-by-just-talking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RoSAS: Deep Semi-Supervised Anomaly Detection with Contamination-Resilient Continuous Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosas-deep-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[anomaly contamination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rosas-deep-semi-supervised-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scoring Cycling Environments Perceived Safety using Pairwise Image Comparisons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoring-cycling-environments-perceived-safety</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, this approach facilitates the continuous assessment of changing cycling environments, allows for a short-term evaluation of measures, and is efficiently deployed in different locations or contexts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scoring-cycling-environments-perceived-safety</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Mainstream Bias in Recommendation via Cost-sensitive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-mainstream-bias-in-recommendation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mainstream bias, where some users receive poor recommendations because their preferences are uncommon or simply because they are less active, is an important aspect to consider regarding fairness in recommender systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-mainstream-bias-in-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Segmentation Keras : Implementation of Segnet, FCN, UNet, PSPNet and other models in Keras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-segmentation-keras-implementation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic segmentation plays a vital role in computer vision tasks, enabling precise pixel-level understanding of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-segmentation-keras-implementation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FacTool: Factuality Detection in Generative AI -- A Tool Augmented Framework for Multi-Task and Multi-Domain Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factool-factuality-detection-in-generative-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the above challenges in mind, in this paper, we propose FacTool, a task and domain agnostic framework for detecting factual errors of texts generated by large language models (e. g., ChatGPT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factool-factuality-detection-in-generative-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combating the Curse of Multilinguality in Cross-Lingual WSD by Aligning Sparse Contextualized Word Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-the-curse-of-multilinguality-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we advocate for using large pre-trained monolingual language models in cross lingual zero-shot word sense disambiguation (WSD) coupled with a contextualized mapping mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combating-the-curse-of-multilinguality-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundational Models Defining a New Era in Vision: A Survey and Outlook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundational-models-defining-a-new-era-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision systems to see and reason about the compositional nature of visual scenes are fundamental to understanding our world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundational-models-defining-a-new-era-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlaneRecTR: Unified Query learning for 3D Plane Recovery from a Single View</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planerectr-unified-query-learning-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D plane recovery from a single image can usually be divided into several subtasks of plane detection, segmentation, parameter estimation and possibly depth estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planerectr-unified-query-learning-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CosSIF: Cosine similarity-based image filtering to overcome low inter-class variation in synthetic medical image datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cossif-cosine-similarity-based-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FBGT involves the removal of real images that exhibit similarities to images of other classes before utilizing them as the training dataset for a GAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cossif-cosine-similarity-based-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient-Based Spectral Embeddings of Random Dot Product Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-spectral-embeddings-of-random</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RDPGs crucially postulate that edge formation probabilities are given by the dot product of the corresponding latent positions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-based-spectral-embeddings-of-random</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Design Analog Circuits to Meet Threshold Specifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-design-analog-circuits-to-meet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a method for generating from simulation data a dataset on which a system can be trained via supervised learning to design circuits to meet threshold specifications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-design-analog-circuits-to-meet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E^2VPT: An Effective and Efficient Approach for Visual Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-2vpt-an-effective-and-efficient-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a set of learnable key-value prompts and visual prompts into self-attention and input layers, respectively, to improve the effectiveness of model fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/e-2vpt-an-effective-and-efficient-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empower Your Model with Longer and Better Context Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empower-your-model-with-longer-and-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, with the emergence of numerous Large Language Models (LLMs), the implementation of AI has entered a new era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empower-your-model-with-longer-and-better</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
