<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 09:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Visual Analytics Framework for Evaluating Evolutionary Processes in Multi-objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-visual-analytics-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary multi-objective optimization (EMO) algorithms have been demonstrated to be effective in solving multi-criteria decision-making problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-visual-analytics-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double-chain Constraints for 3D Human Pose Estimation in Images and Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-chain-constraints-for-3d-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, our model achieves state-of-the-art performance on all action categories in the Human3. 6M dataset using detected 2D poses from CPN, and our code is available at: https://github. com/KHB1698/DC-GCT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/double-chain-constraints-for-3d-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-domain Recommendation with Embedding Disentangling and Domain Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-domain-recommendation-with-embedding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new MDR method named EDDA with two key components, i. e., embedding disentangling recommender and domain alignment, to tackle the two challenges respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-domain-recommendation-with-embedding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is there progress in activity progress prediction?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-there-progress-in-activity-progress</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conclude that the progress prediction task is ill-posed on the currently used real-world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-there-progress-in-activity-progress</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Asymmetric Loss for Multi-Label Long-Tailed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-asymmetric-loss-for-multi-label-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although a model can be highly fine-tuned due to a large number of hyper-parameters, it is difficult to optimize all hyper-parameters at the same time, and there might be a risk of overfitting a model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-asymmetric-loss-for-multi-label-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deformable Mixer Transformer with Gating for Multi-Task Learning of Dense Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-mixer-transformer-with-gating-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel MTL model by combining both merits of deformable CNN and query-based Transformer with shared gating for multi-task learning of dense prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deformable-mixer-transformer-with-gating-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Progressive Spatio-temporal Perception for Audio-Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-spatio-temporal-perception-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such naturally multi-modal videos are composed of rich and complex dynamic audio-visual components, where most of which could be unrelated to the given questions, or even play as interference in answering the content of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progressive-spatio-temporal-perception-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-Driven 3D Face Animation with Composite and Regional Facial Movements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-driven-3d-face-animation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper emphasizes the importance of considering both the composite and regional natures of facial movements in speech-driven 3D face animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-driven-3d-face-animation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surface Masked AutoEncoder: Self-Supervision for Cortical Imaging Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-masked-autoencoder-self-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By reconstructing surface data from a masked version of the input, the proposed method effectively models cortical structure to learn strong representations that translate to improved performance in downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-masked-autoencoder-self-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RLSAC: Reinforcement Learning enhanced Sample Consensus for End-to-End Robust Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlsac-reinforcement-learning-enhanced-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, RLSAC can avoid differentiating to learn the features and the feedback of downstream tasks for end-to-end robust estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rlsac-reinforcement-learning-enhanced-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Low-light Light Field Images with A Deep Compensation Unfolding Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-low-light-light-field-images-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel and interpretable end-to-end learning framework, called the deep compensation unfolding network (DCUNet), for restoring light field (LF) images captured under low-light conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-low-light-light-field-images-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapTRv2: An End-to-End Framework for Online Vectorized HD Map Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptrv2-an-end-to-end-framework-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a unified permutation-equivalent modeling approach, \ie, modeling map element as a point set with a group of equivalent permutations, which accurately describes the shape of map element and stabilizes the learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/maptrv2-an-end-to-end-framework-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow Datasets, New challenging datasets for Causal Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-datasets-new-challenging-datasets-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most causal representation learning (CRL) methods are fully supervised, which is impractical due to costly labeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shadow-datasets-new-challenging-datasets-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Fusion Transformer Network with Weighted Vector-Wise Keypoints Voting for Robust 6D Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fusion-transformer-network-with-weighted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One critical challenge in 6D object pose estimation from a single RGBD image is efficient integration of two different modalities, i. e., color and depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-fusion-transformer-network-with-weighted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Taxonomy Learning and Historical Patterns Modelling for Patent Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-taxonomy-learning-and-historical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we combine the contextual information of patent texts that contains the semantics of IPC codes, and assignees' sequential preferences to make predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-taxonomy-learning-and-historical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINER: Enhancing State-of-the-art Classifiers with Feature Attribution to Facilitate Security Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finer-enhancing-state-of-the-art-classifiers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although feature attribution (FA) methods can be used to explain deep learning, the underlying classifier is still blind to what behavior is suspicious, and the generated explanation cannot adapt to downstream tasks, incurring poor explanation fidelity and intelligibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finer-enhancing-state-of-the-art-classifiers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Preliminary Study of the Intrinsic Relationship between Complexity and Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-of-the-intrinsic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By adjusting the number of added nodes, we can control the difficulty level in the modified instruction data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-of-the-intrinsic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlankAssembly: Robust 3D Reconstruction from Three Orthographic Views with Learnt Shape Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plankassembly-robust-3d-reconstruction-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we develop a new method to automatically convert 2D line drawings from three orthographic views into 3D CAD models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plankassembly-robust-3d-reconstruction-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSLRec: A Self-Supervised Learning Library for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sslrec-a-self-supervised-learning-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our SSLRec platform covers a comprehensive set of state-of-the-art SSL-enhanced recommendation models across different scenarios, enabling researchers to evaluate these cutting-edge models and drive further innovation in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sslrec-a-self-supervised-learning-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring XAI for the Arts: Explaining Latent Space in Generative Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-xai-for-the-arts-explaining-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We increase the explainability of the model by: i) using latent space regularisation to force some specific dimensions of the latent space to map to meaningful musical attributes, ii) providing a user interface feedback loop to allow people to adjust dimensions of the latent space and observe the results of these changes in real-time, iii) providing a visualisation of the musical attributes in the latent space to help people understand and predict the effect of changes to latent space dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-xai-for-the-arts-explaining-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Assessment of Multi-view fusion learning for Crop Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-assessment-of-multi-view-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we present a comparison of multi-view fusion methods for three different datasets and show that, depending on the test region, different methods obtain the best performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-assessment-of-multi-view-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Semantics: Learning a Behavior Augmented Relevance Model with Self-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-semantics-learning-a-behavior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing inspiration from this, we devise a novel Behavior Augmented Relevance Learning model for Alipay Search (BARL-ASe) that leverages neighbor queries of target item and neighbor items of target query to complement target query-item semantic matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-semantics-learning-a-behavior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Monocular Depth Estimation by Direction-aware Cumulative Convolution Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-monocular-depth-estimation-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we propose a new Direction-aware Cumulative Convolution Network (DaCCN), which improves the depth feature representation in two aspects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-monocular-depth-estimation-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interaction-aware Joint Attention Estimation Using People Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-aware-joint-attention-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a specialized MLP head with positional embedding to the Transformer so that it predicts pixelwise confidence of joint attention for generating the confidence heatmap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interaction-aware-joint-attention-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Cross-modality Reasoning for Weakly Supervised Video Moment Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-cross-modality-reasoning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, by suppressing the unimodal effect of masked query, we can rectify the reconstructions of video proposals to perform reasonable contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-cross-modality-reasoning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Performance Analysis of Transformer Based Models (BERT, ALBERT and RoBERTa) in Fake News Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-analysis-of-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, some studies suggest the performance can be improved with the use of improved BERT models known as ALBERT and RoBERTa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/performance-analysis-of-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decorrelating neurons using persistence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decorrelating-neurons-using-persistence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel way to improve the generalisation capacity of deep learning models by reducing high correlations between neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decorrelating-neurons-using-persistence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformer-based Target-Speaker Automatic Speech Recognition for Single-Channel Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformer-based-target-speaker-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose CONF-TSASR, a non-autoregressive end-to-end time-frequency domain architecture for single-channel target-speaker automatic speech recognition (TS-ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformer-based-target-speaker-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Gated Multi-Layer Perceptron for Land Use and Land Cover Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-gated-multi-layer-perceptron-for-land</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results illustrated the superiority of the developed SGU-MLP classification algorithm over several CNN and CNN-ViT-based models, including HybridSN, ResNet, iFormer, EfficientFormer and CoAtNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-gated-multi-layer-perceptron-for-land</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Multi-Shot Diffusion-Weighted MRI with Zero-Shot Self-Supervised Learning Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-multi-shot-diffusion-weighted-mri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce a novel msEPI reconstruction approach called zero-MIRID (zero-shot self-supervised learning of Multi-shot Image Reconstruction for Improved Diffusion MRI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-multi-shot-diffusion-weighted-mri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kairos: : Practical Intrusion Detection and Investigation using Whole-system Provenance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kairos-practical-intrusion-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sifting through their design documents, we identify four common dimensions that drive the development of provenance-based intrusion detection systems (PIDSes): scope (can PIDSes detect modern attacks that infiltrate across application boundaries?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kairos-practical-intrusion-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When and How Does Known Class Help Discover Unknown Ones? Provable Understanding Through Spectral Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-how-does-known-class-help-discover</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper bridges the gap by providing an analytical framework to formalize and investigate when and how known classes can help discover novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-and-how-does-known-class-help-discover</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Learning From Distributed Data With Differentially Private Synthetic Twin Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-learning-from-distributed-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consider a setting where multiple parties holding sensitive data aim to collaboratively learn population level statistics, but pooling the sensitive data sets is not possible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-learning-from-distributed-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Class Deep SVDD: Anomaly Detection Approach in Astronomy with Distinct Inlier Categories</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-deep-svdd-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate the efficacy of MCDSVDD in detecting anomalous sources while leveraging the presence of different inlier categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-class-deep-svdd-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intrinsic Motivation via Surprise Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-motivation-via-surprise-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new computing model for intrinsic rewards in reinforcement learning that addresses the limitations of existing surprise-driven explorations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intrinsic-motivation-via-surprise-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource Constrained Model Compression via Minimax Optimization for Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-constrained-model-compression-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an improved end-to-end Minimax optimization method for this sparse learning problem to better balance the model performance and the computation efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-constrained-model-compression-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards true discovery of the differential equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-true-discovery-of-the-differential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Differential equation discovery, a machine learning subfield, is used to develop interpretable models, particularly in nature-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-true-discovery-of-the-differential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SelectNAdapt: Support Set Selection for Few-Shot Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectnadapt-support-set-selection-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Few-shot domain adaptation mitigates this issue by adapting deep neural networks pre-trained on the source domain to the target domain using a randomly selected and annotated support set from the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selectnadapt-support-set-selection-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Intents Graph Modeling for User-centric Group Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-intents-graph-modeling-for-user-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, user-centric group discovery task, i. e., recommending groups to users can help both users' online experiences and platforms' long-term developments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-intents-graph-modeling-for-user-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directed differential equation discovery using modified mutation and cross-over operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-differential-equation-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The discovery of equations with knowledge of the process origin is a tempting prospect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-differential-equation-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUnAA: Sparse Unmixing using Archetypal Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sunaa-sparse-unmixing-using-archetypal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike most conventional sparse unmixing methods, here the minimization problem is non-convex.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sunaa-sparse-unmixing-using-archetypal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bipartite Graph is All We Need for Enhancing Emotional Reasoning with Commonsense Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bipartite-graph-is-all-we-need-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most previous knowledge infusion methods perform empirical knowledge filtering and design highly customized architectures for knowledge interaction with the utterances, which can discard useful knowledge aspects and limit their generalizability to different knowledge sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bipartite-graph-is-all-we-need-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiVa: An Iterative Framework to Harvest More Diverse and Valid Labels from User Comments for Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-an-iterative-framework-to-harvest-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the observation that such missing information may already be presented in user comments, we propose to study the automated music labeling in an essential but under-explored setting, where the model is required to harvest more diverse and valid labels from the users' comments given limited gold labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diva-an-iterative-framework-to-harvest-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Early Detection of Virus Yellows: Developing a Hybrid Convolutional Neural Network for Automatic Aphid Counting in Sugar Beet Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-early-detection-of-virus-yellows</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aphids are efficient vectors to transmit virus yellows in sugar beet fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-early-detection-of-virus-yellows</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptPaint: Steering Text-to-Image Generation Through Paint Medium-like Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptpaint-steering-text-to-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Just as we iteratively tune colors through layered placements of paint on a physical canvas, PromptPaint similarly allows users to apply different prompts to different canvas areas and times of the generative process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptpaint-steering-text-to-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sound propagation in realistic interactive 3D scenes with parameterized sources using deep neural operators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sound-propagation-in-realistic-interactive-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the challenge of sound propagation simulations in $3$D virtual rooms with moving sources, which have applications in virtual/augmented reality, game audio, and spatial computing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sound-propagation-in-realistic-interactive-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parallel Knowledge Enhancement based Framework for Multi-behavior Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-knowledge-enhancement-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the fusion step, advanced neural networks are used to model the hierarchical correlations between user behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parallel-knowledge-enhancement-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMeBench: A Flexible Framework for Accelerating LLMs Benchmarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmebench-a-flexible-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Initially developed to evaluate Arabic NLP tasks using OpenAI's GPT and BLOOM models; it can be seamlessly customized for any NLP task and model, regardless of language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llmebench-a-flexible-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector quantization loss analysis in VQGANs: a single-GPU ablation study for image-to-image synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantization-loss-analysis-in-vqgans-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study performs an ablation analysis of Vector Quantized Generative Adversarial Networks (VQGANs), concentrating on image-to-image synthesis utilizing a single NVIDIA A100 GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-quantization-loss-analysis-in-vqgans-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-view Semantic Alignment for Livestreaming Product Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-semantic-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, a cRoss-vIew semantiC alignmEnt (RICE) model is proposed to learn discriminative instance features from the image and video views of the products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-semantic-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
