<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 09:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Early Rumor Detection Using Neural Hawkes Process with a New Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-rumor-detection-using-neural-hawkes-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Little attention has been paid on \underline{EA}rly \underline{R}umor \underline{D}etection (EARD), and EARD performance was evaluated inappropriately on a few datasets where the actual early-stage information is largely missing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-rumor-detection-using-neural-hawkes-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classification of Edge-dependent Labels of Nodes in Hypergraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-edge-dependent-labels-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, many real-world systems modeled as hypergraphs contain edge-dependent node labels, i. e., node labels that vary depending on hyperedges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/classification-of-edge-dependent-labels-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Editing for Text Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-editing-for-text-summarization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Summarizing lengthy documents is a common and essential task in our daily lives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-editing-for-text-summarization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructZero: Efficient Instruction Optimization for Black-Box Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructzero-efficient-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models~(LLMs) are instruction followers, but it can be challenging to find the best instruction for different situations, especially for black-box LLMs on which backpropagation is forbidden.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructzero-efficient-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Monte Carlo Steering of Large Language Models using Probabilistic Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-monte-carlo-steering-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even after fine-tuning and reinforcement learning, large language models (LLMs) can be difficult, if not impossible, to control reliably with prompts alone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-monte-carlo-steering-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Style Analysis and Visualization With Explainable AI -- Case Studies on Brand Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-style-analysis-and-visualization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the first case study, BIGNet not only classifies phone brands but also captures brand-related features across multiple scales, such as the location of the lens, the height-width ratio, and the screen-frame gap, as confirmed by AI evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-style-analysis-and-visualization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Implicit Neural Representations for Global-Scale Species Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-implicit-neural-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating the geographical range of a species from sparse observations is a challenging and important geospatial prediction problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-implicit-neural-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACE: 5D Temporal Regression of Avatars with Dynamic Cameras in 3D Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trace-5d-temporal-regression-of-avatars-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the estimation of 3D human pose and shape (HPS) is rapidly progressing, current methods still cannot reliably estimate moving humans in global coordinates, which is critical for many applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trace-5d-temporal-regression-of-avatars-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-range UAV Thermal Geo-localization with Satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-uav-thermal-geo-localization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a novel thermal geo-localization framework using satellite imagery, which includes multiple domain adaptation methods to address the limited availability of paired thermal and satellite images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-range-uav-thermal-geo-localization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human Spine Motion Capture using Perforated Kinesiology Tape</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-spine-motion-capture-using-perforated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A maximal focus is on the accurate detection of markers and fast usage of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-spine-motion-capture-using-perforated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyclic Learning: Bridging Image-level Labels and Nuclei Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclic-learning-bridging-image-level-labels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on three datasets demonstrate the good generality of our method, which outperforms other image-level weakly supervised methods for nuclei instance segmentation, and achieves comparable performance to fully-supervised methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cyclic-learning-bridging-image-level-labels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Diffusion Models with Local-Global Context Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-diffusion-models-with-local-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct a local-global context guidance strategy to capture the multi-perceptual embedding of the past fragment to boost the consistency of future prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-diffusion-models-with-local-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflated 3D Convolution-Transformer for Weakly-supervised Carotid Stenosis Grading with Ultrasound Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inflated-3d-convolution-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, to avoid the requirement of laborious and unreliable annotation, we propose a novel and effective video classification network for weakly-supervised CSG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inflated-3d-convolution-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReContrast: Domain-Specific Anomaly Detection via Contrastive Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recontrast-domain-specific-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most advanced unsupervised anomaly detection (UAD) methods rely on modeling feature representations of frozen encoder networks pre-trained on large-scale datasets, e. g. ImageNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recontrast-domain-specific-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scene as Occupancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-as-occupancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human driver can easily describe the complex traffic scene by visual system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scene-as-occupancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do-GOOD: Towards Distribution Shift Evaluation for Pre-Trained Visual Document Understanding Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-good-towards-distribution-shift-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results from the experiments demonstrate that there is a significant performance gap between the in-distribution (ID) and OOD settings for document images, and that fine-grained analysis of distribution shifts can reveal the brittle nature of existing pre-trained VDU models and OOD generalization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-good-towards-distribution-shift-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Grammar-based Sequence-to-Sequence Modeling with Decomposition and Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-grammar-based-sequence-to-sequence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural QCFG is a grammar-based sequence-tosequence (seq2seq) model with strong inductive biases on hierarchical structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-grammar-based-sequence-to-sequence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Substitute Spans towards Improving Compositional Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-substitute-spans-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rising prevalence of neural sequence models, recent empirical evidences suggest their deficiency in compositional generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-substitute-spans-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DecompX: Explaining Transformers Decisions by Propagating Token Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decompx-explaining-transformers-decisions-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An emerging solution for explaining Transformer-based models is to use vector-based analysis on how the representations are formed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decompx-explaining-transformers-decisions-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-LLaMA: An Instruction-tuned Audio-Visual Language Model for Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-llama-an-instruction-tuned-audio-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Video-LLaMA, a multi-modal framework that empowers Large Language Models (LLMs) with the capability of understanding both visual and auditory content in the video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-llama-an-instruction-tuned-audio-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RepoBench: Benchmarking Repository-Level Code Auto-Completion Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repobench-benchmarking-repository-level-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have greatly advanced code auto-completion systems, with a potential for substantial productivity enhancements for developers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repobench-benchmarking-repository-level-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Conversational Recommendation Systems via Counterfactual Data Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-conversational-recommendation-4</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To develop our approach, we characterize user preference and organize the conversation flow by the entities involved in the dialogue, and design a multi-stage recommendation dialogue simulator based on a conversation flow language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-conversational-recommendation-4</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Deep Learning Approach Utilizing Covariance Matrix Analysis for the ISBI Edited MRS Reconstruction Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-utilizing-covariance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a method to accelerate the acquisition of high-quality edited magnetic resonance spectroscopy (MRS) scans using machine learning models taking the sample covariance matrix as input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-deep-learning-approach-utilizing-covariance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Middle-Trained Language Models for Neural Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-middle-trained-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare both dense and sparse approaches under various finetuning protocols and middle training on different collections (MS MARCO, Wikipedia or Tripclick).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-middle-trained-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Relate to Previous Turns in Conversational Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-relate-to-previous-turns-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An effective way to improve retrieval effectiveness is to expand the current query with historical queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-relate-to-previous-turns-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LibAUC: A Deep Learning Library for X-Risk Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libauc-a-deep-learning-library-for-x-risk</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the award-winning deep learning (DL) library called LibAUC for implementing state-of-the-art algorithms towards optimizing a family of risk functions named X-risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libauc-a-deep-learning-library-for-x-risk</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Probabilistic Symmetrization for Architecture Agnostic Equivariance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-probabilistic-symmetrization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrary to equivariant architectures, we use an arbitrary base model (such as an MLP or a transformer) and symmetrize it to be equivariant to the given group by employing a small equivariant network that parameterizes the probabilistic distribution underlying the symmetrization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-probabilistic-symmetrization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhance Diffusion to Improve Robust Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-diffusion-to-improve-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We approximate the dynamic of PGD-AT by a continuous-time Stochastic Differential Equation (SDE), and show that the diffusion term of this SDE determines the robust generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhance-diffusion-to-improve-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Two-Faced Truth: Disentangling Morphed Identities for Face Morphing Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-two-faced-truth-disentangling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over time they have become simpler to perform and more realistic, as such, the usage of deep learning systems to detect these attacks has grown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-the-two-faced-truth-disentangling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Makes Entities Similar? A Similarity Flooding Perspective for Multi-sourced Knowledge Graph Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-entities-similar-a-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a similarity flooding perspective to explain existing translation-based and aggregation-based EA models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-makes-entities-similar-a-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCTS: A Multi-Reference Chinese Text Simplification Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcts-a-multi-reference-chinese-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope to build a basic understanding of Chinese text simplification through the foundational work and provide references for future research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcts-a-multi-reference-chinese-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Anytime Classification in Early-Exit Architectures by Enforcing Conditional Monotonicity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-classification-in-early-exit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern predictive models are often deployed to environments in which computational budgets are dynamic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-classification-in-early-exit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming Weak Visual-Textual Alignment for Video Moment Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-weak-visual-textual-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our model learns to predict the target moment from the joint probability of the given query and the complement of negative queries for each candidate frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overcoming-weak-visual-textual-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evading Black-box Classifiers Without Breaking Eggs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-black-box-classifiers-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then design new attacks that reduce the number of bad queries by $1. 5$-$7. 3\times$, but often at a significant increase in total (non-bad) queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-black-box-classifiers-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Language Representation with Constructional Information for Natural Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-language-representation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adopt usage-based construction grammar as the basis of our work, which is highly compatible with statistical models such as PLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-language-representation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIDECOR: A Unified Deception Corpus for Cross-Corpus Deception Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidecor-a-unified-deception-corpus-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Verbal deception has been studied in psychology, forensics, and computational linguistics for a variety of reasons, like understanding behaviour patterns, identifying false testimonies, and detecting deception in online communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidecor-a-unified-deception-corpus-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-SAGE: Scale Meta-Learning Scheduled Adaptation with Guided Exploration for Mitigating Scale Shift on Combinatorial Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-sage-scale-meta-learning-scheduled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, SML transforms the context embedding for subsequent adaptation of SAGE based on scale information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-sage-scale-meta-learning-scheduled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Role of the Bottleneck in Slot-Based Models Through Covariance Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-role-of-the-bottleneck-in-slot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this project we attempt to make slot-based models with an image reconstruction objective competitive with those that use a feature reconstruction objective on real world datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-role-of-the-bottleneck-in-slot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Explanatory Multiverse Through Counterfactual Path Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-explanatory-multiverse-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual explanations are the de facto standard when tasked with interpreting decisions of (opaque) predictive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-explanatory-multiverse-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Relationship between Alignment and Cross-lingual Transfer in Multilingual Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-relationship-between-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Namely, we find that realignment works better on tasks for which alignment is correlated with cross-lingual transfer when generalizing to a distant language and with smaller models, as well as when using a bilingual dictionary rather than FastAlign to extract realignment pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-relationship-between-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Driven Robot Program Synthesis from Human VR Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-robot-program-synthesis-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aging societies, labor shortages and increasing wage costs call for assistance robots capable of autonomously performing a wide array of real-world tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-driven-robot-program-synthesis-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Pre-training and Local Re-training: Transferable Representation Learning on Multi-source Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-pre-training-and-local-re-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We pre-train a large teacher KG embedding model over linked multi-source KGs and distill knowledge to train a student model for a task-specific KG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-pre-training-and-local-re-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Path-Specific Counterfactual Fairness for Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-specific-counterfactual-fairness-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[But since sensitive features may also affect user interests in a fair manner (e. g., race on culture-based preferences), indiscriminately eliminating all the influences of sensitive features inevitably degenerate the recommendations quality and necessary diversities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/path-specific-counterfactual-fairness-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMET: Learning Cardinality Constrained Mixture of Experts with Trees and Local Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comet-learning-cardinality-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with this challenge, we propose a novel, permutation-based local search method that can complement first-order methods in training any sparse gate, e. g., Hash routing, Top-k, DSelect-k, and COMET.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comet-learning-cardinality-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformal Prediction with Missing Values</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-with-missing-values</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This motivates our novel generalized conformalized quantile regression framework, missing data augmentation, which yields prediction intervals that are valid conditionally to the patterns of missing values, despite their exponential number.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformal-prediction-with-missing-values</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is ChatGPT a Good Teacher Coach? Measuring Zero-Shot Performance For Scoring and Providing Actionable Insights on Classroom Instruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-teacher-coach-measuring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In doing so, we propose three teacher coaching tasks for generative AI: (A) scoring transcript segments based on classroom observation instruments, (B) identifying highlights and missed opportunities for good instructional strategies, and (C) providing actionable suggestions for eliciting more student reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-chatgpt-a-good-teacher-coach-measuring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decentralized SGD and Average-direction SAM are Asymptotically Equivalent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-sgd-and-average-direction-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decentralized stochastic gradient descent (D-SGD) allows collaborative learning on massive devices simultaneously without the control of a central server.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decentralized-sgd-and-average-direction-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing naive classifier for positive unlabeled data based on logistic regression approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-naive-classifier-for-positive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that for analysis of Positive Unlabeled (PU) data under Selected Completely At Random (SCAR) assumption it is fruitful to view the problem as fitting of misspecified model to the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-naive-classifier-for-positive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Study of Probabilistic Calibration in Neural Network Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-study-of-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also analyze the performance of recalibration, conformal, and regularization methods to enhance probabilistic calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-study-of-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-DAG: Multi-task DAG Learning for Multi-modal Data -- with Application for Traffic Congestion Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-dag-multi-task-dag-learning-for-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This encourages the multi-task design: with each DAG as a task, the MM-DAG tries to learn the multiple DAGs jointly so that their consensus and consistency are maximized.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-dag-multi-task-dag-learning-for-multi</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
