<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 09:27:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>From Roots to Rewards: Dynamic Tree Reasoning with RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-roots-to-rewards-dynamic-tree-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modern language models address complex questions through chain-of-thought (CoT) reasoning (Wei et al., 2023) and retrieval augmentation (Lewis et al., 2021), yet struggle with error propagation and knowledge integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-roots-to-rewards-dynamic-tree-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Language Model a Hierarchical Classifier and Generator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-language-model-a-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language heads of the last layer are copied to different selected intermediate layers, and fine-tuned with different task inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-language-model-a-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergence of Functionally Differentiated Structures via Mutual Information Optimization in Recurrent Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-functionally-differentiated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analysis of network performance, correlation patterns, and weight matrices reveals that mutual information minimization yields high task performance alongside clear functional modularity and moderate structural modularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emergence-of-functionally-differentiated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhysX: Physical-Grounded 3D Asset Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physx-physical-grounded-3d-asset-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D modeling is moving from virtual to physical.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physx-physical-grounded-3d-asset-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing Visual Augmented Q&amp;A System using Scalable Vision Embedding Retrieval &amp; Late Interaction Re-ranker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-visual-augmented-q-a-system-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose multi-step custom implementation utilizing widely adopted hybrid search (metadata & embedding) and state of the art late interaction re-ranker to retrieve best matching pages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/developing-visual-augmented-q-a-system-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Describe Anything Model for Visual Question Answering on Text-rich Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describe-anything-model-for-visual-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress has been made in region-aware vision-language modeling, particularly with the emergence of the Describe Anything Model (DAM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/describe-anything-model-for-visual-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructFLIP: Exploring Unified Vision-Language Model for Face Anti-spoofing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructflip-exploring-unified-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate the effectiveness of InstructFLIP by outperforming SOTA models in accuracy and substantially reducing training redundancy across diverse domains in FAS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructflip-exploring-unified-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Fuzzy Approach to Project Success: Measuring What Matters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fuzzy-approach-to-project-success-measuring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel approach to project success evaluation by integrating fuzzy logic into an existing construct.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-fuzzy-approach-to-project-success-measuring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for Large-Scale, Pixel-Wise Crop Mapping and Transfer Learning Workflows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-practices-for-large-scale-pixel-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents the first comprehensive review of large-scale, pixel-wise crop mapping workflows, encompassing both conventional supervised methods and emerging transfer learning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-practices-for-large-scale-pixel-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVFL-Net: A Lightweight Distilled Video Focal Modulation Network for Spatio-Temporal Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvfl-net-a-lightweight-distilled-video-focal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We employ forward Kullback-Leibler (KL) divergence alongside spatio-temporal focal modulation to effectively transfer both local and global context from the Video-FocalNet Base (teacher) to the proposed VFL-Net (student).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvfl-net-a-lightweight-distilled-video-focal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assay2Mol: large language model-based drug design using BioAssay context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assay2mol-large-language-model-based-drug</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific databases aggregate vast amounts of quantitative data alongside descriptive text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assay2mol-large-language-model-based-drug</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCR: Quantifying Data Contamination in LLMs Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcr-quantifying-data-contamination-in-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of large language models (LLMs) has heightened concerns about benchmark data contamination (BDC), where models inadvertently memorize evaluation data, inflating performance metrics and undermining genuine generalization assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcr-quantifying-data-contamination-in-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGT-I: Scaling Spatiotemporal GNNs with Memory-Efficient Distributed Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgt-i-scaling-spatiotemporal-gnns-with-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal graph neural networks (ST-GNNs) are powerful tools for modeling spatial and temporal data dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgt-i-scaling-spatiotemporal-gnns-with-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Task-Specific Reasoning: A Unified Conditional Generative Framework for Abstract Visual Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-task-specific-reasoning-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we illustrate that, under the proposed framework, training one conditional generative model can solve various AVR tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-task-specific-reasoning-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precision Spatio-Temporal Feature Fusion for Robust Remote Sensing Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-spatio-temporal-feature-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Remote sensing change detection is vital for monitoring environmental and urban transformations but faces challenges like manual feature extraction and sensitivity to noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-spatio-temporal-feature-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SystolicAttention: Fusing FlashAttention within a Single Systolic Array</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systolicattention-fusing-flashattention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The frequent data swaps between the systolic array and external vector units result in low systolic array utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/systolicattention-fusing-flashattention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Wizards at CheckThat! 2025: Enhancing Transformer-Based Embeddings with Sentiment for Subjectivity Detection in News Articles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-wizards-at-checkthat-2025-enhancing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents AI Wizards' participation in the CLEF 2025 CheckThat!]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-wizards-at-checkthat-2025-enhancing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Tune Like an Expert: Interpretable and Scene-Aware Navigation via MLLM Reasoning and CVAE-Based Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-tune-like-an-expert-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Service robots are increasingly deployed in diverse and dynamic environments, where both physical layouts and social contexts change over time and across locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-tune-like-an-expert-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step-wise Policy for Rare-tool Knowledge (SPaRK): Offline RL that Drives Diverse Tool Use in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-wise-policy-for-rare-tool-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Step-wise Policy for Rare-tool Knowledge (SPaRK), a novel reinforcement learning framework that teaches large language models to explore diverse tool usage patterns beyond conventional high-temperature sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-wise-policy-for-rare-tool-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Data Imbalance in Transformer-Based Multi-Label Emotion Detection with Weighted Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-data-imbalance-in-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the application of a simple weighted loss function to Transformer-based models for multi-label emotion detection in SemEval-2025 Shared Task 11.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-data-imbalance-in-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WildFX: A DAW-Powered Pipeline for In-the-Wild Audio FX Graph Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildfx-a-daw-powered-pipeline-for-in-the-wild</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite rapid progress in end-to-end AI music generation, AI-driven modeling of professional Digital Signal Processing (DSP) workflows remains challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wildfx-a-daw-powered-pipeline-for-in-the-wild</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoTranhAbyssCoreMicro and PoliticalCore: A Unified Framework for Simulating Complex Economic and Political Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votranhabysscoremicro-and-politicalcore-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The VoTranhAbyssCoreMicro framework, integrated with the PoliticalCore mod- ule, provides a robust platform for simulating complex economic and political dy- namics with a validated accuracy of 90% across multiple tested economies and polit- ical scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/votranhabysscoremicro-and-politicalcore-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning or Memorization? Unreliable Results of Reinforcement Learning Due to Data Contamination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-or-memorization-unreliable-results</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reasoning capabilities of large language models (LLMs) have been a longstanding focus of research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-or-memorization-unreliable-results</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Visual Semantic Constrained AI-Generated Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-visual-semantic-constrained-ai-generated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach integrates key capabilities from multiple models and tackles the aforementioned challenges by introducing two core modules: the Text-assisted Semantic Alignment Module (TSAM), which leverages Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) to bridge the semantic gap by generating an image description and comparing it against the original prompt for a refined consistency check, and the Frequency-domain Fine-Grained Degradation Perception Module (FFDPM), which draws inspiration from Human Visual System (HVS) properties by employing frequency domain analysis combined with perceptual sensitivity weighting to better quantify subtle visual distortions and enhance the capture of fine-grained visual quality details in images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-visual-semantic-constrained-ai-generated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Gradual Semantics for Assumption-Based Argumentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-gradual-semantics-for-assumption-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we fill this gap and propose a family of novel gradual semantics for equipping assumptions, which are the core components in ABA frameworks, with dialectical strengths.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-gradual-semantics-for-assumption-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LifelongPR: Lifelong knowledge fusion for point cloud place recognition based on replay and prompt learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelongpr-lifelong-knowledge-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud place recognition (PCPR) plays a crucial role in photogrammetry and robotics applications such as autonomous driving, intelligent transportation, and augmented reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifelongpr-lifelong-knowledge-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Robustness and Generalization Against Word Substitution Attacks in NLP via the Growth Bound Matrix Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-robustness-and-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite advancements in Natural Language Processing (NLP), models remain vulnerable to adversarial attacks, such as synonym substitutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-robustness-and-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REST: Stress Testing Large Reasoning Models by Asking Multiple Problems at Once</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rest-stress-testing-large-reasoning-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent Large Reasoning Models (LRMs) have achieved remarkable progress on task-specific benchmarks, yet their evaluation methods remain constrained by isolated problem-solving paradigms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rest-stress-testing-large-reasoning-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZClassifier: Temperature Tuning and Manifold Approximation via KL Divergence on Logit Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zclassifier-temperature-tuning-and-manifold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel classification framework, ZClassifier, that replaces conventional deterministic logits with diagonal Gaussian-distributed logits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zclassifier-temperature-tuning-and-manifold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Enhanced Pediatric Pneumonia Detection: A CNN-Based Approach Using Data Augmentation and Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-enhanced-pediatric-pneumonia-detection-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a machine learning-based Pediatric Chest Pneumonia Classification System to assist healthcare professionals in diagnosing pneumonia from chest X-ray images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-enhanced-pediatric-pneumonia-detection-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanoDiff-SR: Synthesizing Dental Panoramic Radiographs using Diffusion and Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panodiff-sr-synthesizing-dental-panoramic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inception scores were 2. 55, 2. 30, 2. 90 and 2. 98 for real HR, synthetic HR, real LR and synthetic LR images, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panodiff-sr-synthesizing-dental-panoramic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Reinforcement Learning with Gradient Eligibility Traces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-with-gradient-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving fast and stable off-policy learning in deep reinforcement learning (RL) is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-with-gradient-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fairness Is Not Enough: Auditing Competence and Intersectional Bias in AI-powered Resume Screening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-is-not-enough-auditing-competence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing use of generative AI for resume screening is predicated on the assumption that it offers an unbiased alternative to biased human decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairness-is-not-enough-auditing-competence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Design of Multi-Agent LLM Dialogues for Research Ideation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-design-of-multi-agent-llm-dialogues</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show that enlarging the agent cohort, deepening the interaction depth, and broadening agent persona heterogeneity each enrich the diversity of generated ideas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-design-of-multi-agent-llm-dialogues</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Two-Stage Recipe for Mathematical LLMs: Maximizing Accuracy with SFT and Efficiency with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-two-stage-recipe-for-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enhancing the mathematical reasoning of Large Language Models (LLMs) is a pivotal challenge in advancing AI capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-two-stage-recipe-for-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conformation-Aware Structure Prediction of Antigen-Recognizing Immune Proteins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformation-aware-structure-prediction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Ibex, a pan-immunoglobulin structure prediction model that achieves state-of-the-art accuracy in modeling the variable domains of antibodies, nanobodies, and T-cell receptors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conformation-aware-structure-prediction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Object Counting and Position Estimation via Extension of the CLIP-EBC Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-object-counting-and-position-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the applicability of the CLIP-EBC framework, originally designed for crowd counting, to car object counting using the CARPK dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/car-object-counting-and-position-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Scale Network Dynamics and Systemic Risk: A Model Context Protocol Approach to Financial Markets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-network-dynamics-and-systemic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel framework for analyzing systemic risk in financial markets through multi-scale network dynamics using Model Context Protocol (MCP) for agent communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-network-dynamics-and-systemic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards High-Resolution 3D Anomaly Detection: A Scalable Dataset and Real-Time Framework for Subtle Industrial Defects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-resolution-3d-anomaly-detection-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In industrial point cloud analysis, detecting subtle anomalies demands high-resolution spatial data, yet prevailing benchmarks emphasize low-resolution inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-high-resolution-3d-anomaly-detection-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNN-CNN: An Efficient Hybrid Model of Convolutional and Graph Neural Networks for Text Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-cnn-an-efficient-hybrid-model-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time, cost, and energy efficiency are critical considerations in Deep-Learning (DL), particularly when processing long texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnn-cnn-an-efficient-hybrid-model-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAMO: A Lightweight Sharpness-Aware Approach for Multi-Task Optimization with Joint Global-Local Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samo-a-lightweight-sharpness-aware-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sharpness-aware minimization (SAM) minimizes task loss while simultaneously reducing the sharpness of the loss landscape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samo-a-lightweight-sharpness-aware-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCOOTER: A Human Evaluation Framework for Unrestricted Adversarial Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scooter-a-human-evaluation-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This issue necessitates a unified framework that supports and streamlines such an assessment for evaluating and comparing unrestricted attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scooter-a-human-evaluation-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Query-based Transformer for Continual Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-query-based-transformer-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these, we conduct an in-depth investigation of the built-in objectness and find that highly aggregated image features provide a shortcut for queries to generate masks through simple feature alignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-query-based-transformer-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PacGDC: Label-Efficient Generalizable Depth Completion with Projection Ambiguity and Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pacgdc-label-efficient-generalizable-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents PacGDC, a label-efficient technique that enhances data diversity with minimal annotation effort for generalizable depth completion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pacgdc-label-efficient-generalizable-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OST-Bench: Evaluating the Capabilities of MLLMs in Online Spatio-temporal Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ost-bench-evaluating-the-capabilities-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in multimodal large language models (MLLMs) have shown remarkable capabilities in integrating vision and language for complex reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ost-bench-evaluating-the-capabilities-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiM2SAM: Enhancing SAM2 with Hierarchical Motion Estimation and Memory Optimization towards Long-term Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/him2sam-enhancing-sam2-with-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents enhancements to the SAM2 framework for video object tracking task, addressing challenges such as occlusions, background clutter, and target reappearance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/him2sam-enhancing-sam2-with-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HNOSeg-XS: Extremely Small Hartley Neural Operator for Efficient and Resolution-Robust 3D Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnoseg-xs-extremely-small-hartley-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For transformers, although long-range correlations can be captured by multi-head attention, its quadratic complexity with respect to input size is computationally demanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnoseg-xs-extremely-small-hartley-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Interpretable Time Series Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-time-series-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the distillation of time series reasoning capabilities into small, instruction-tuned language models as a step toward building interpretable time series foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-interpretable-time-series-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Planning &amp; Control System with Language Agents for Autonomous Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-planning-control-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a multi-agent system for automation of scientific research tasks, cmbagent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-planning-control-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bilateral Collaboration with Large Vision-Language Models for Open Vocabulary Human-Object Interaction Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-collaboration-with-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework includes an Attention Bias Guidance (ABG) component, which guides the VLM to produce fine-grained instance-level interaction features according to the attention bias provided by the HOI detector.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bilateral-collaboration-with-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
