<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 09:12:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LimSim: A Long-term Interactive Multi-scenario Traffic Simulator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limsim-a-long-term-interactive-multi-scenario</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the growing popularity of digital twin and autonomous driving in transportation, the demand for simulation systems capable of generating high-fidelity and reliable scenarios is increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/limsim-a-long-term-interactive-multi-scenario</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Functional Structured Data Generators Rooted in Out-of-Equilibrium Physics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-functional-structured-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address the challenge of using energy-based models to produce high-quality, label-specific data in complex structured datasets, such as population genetics, RNA or protein sequences data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-functional-structured-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rectifying Noisy Labels with Sequential Prior: Multi-Scale Temporal Feature Affinity Learning for Robust Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-noisy-labels-with-sequential-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, Temporal Feature Affinity Learning (TFAL) is devised to indicate possible noisy labels by evaluating the affinity between pixels in two adjacent frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rectifying-noisy-labels-with-sequential-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Safe Self-Distillation of Internet-Scale Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-safe-self-distillation-of-internet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale image generation models, with impressive quality made possible by the vast amount of data available on the Internet, raise social concerns that these models may generate harmful or copyrighted content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-safe-self-distillation-of-internet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Importance of Denoising when Learning to Compress Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-denoising-when-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image noise is ubiquitous in photography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-importance-of-denoising-when-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSE: a drone swarm search environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsse-a-drone-swarm-search-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Drone Swarm Search project is an environment, based on PettingZoo, that is to be used in conjunction with multi-agent (or single-agent) reinforcement learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dsse-a-drone-swarm-search-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PID-Inspired Inductive Biases for Deep Reinforcement Learning in Partially Observable Control Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-inspired-inductive-biases-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When this is the case, the policy needs to leverage the history of observations to infer the current state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pid-inspired-inductive-biases-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Learning for Conversion Rate Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-conversion-rate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tailor the contrastive learning task to the CVR prediction problem, we propose embedding masking (EM), rather than feature masking, to create two views of augmented samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-learning-for-conversion-rate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TreeFormer: a Semi-Supervised Transformer-based Framework for Tree Counting from a Single High Resolution Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-a-semi-supervised-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic tree density estimation and counting using single aerial and satellite images is a challenging task in photogrammetry and remote sensing, yet has an important role in forest management.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/treeformer-a-semi-supervised-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The IMPTC Dataset: An Infrastructural Multi-Person Trajectory and Context Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-imptc-dataset-an-infrastructural-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to enable the entire stack of research capabilities, the dataset includes all data, starting from the sensor-, calibration- and detection data until trajectory and context data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-imptc-dataset-an-infrastructural-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CellGAN: Conditional Cervical Cell Synthesis for Augmenting Cytopathological Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellgan-conditional-cervical-cell-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose CellGAN to synthesize cytopathological images of various cervical cell types for augmenting patch-level cell classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cellgan-conditional-cervical-cell-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Mitosis Detection: Towards Diverse Data and Feature Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-mitosis-detection-towards-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[And the feature diversity is preserved by inter- and intra- class feature diversity-preserved module (InCDP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-mitosis-detection-towards-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auxiliary-Tasks Learning for Physics-Informed Neural Network-Based Partial Differential Equations Solving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-learning-for-physics-informed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these issues, we proposed auxiliary-task learning-based physics-informed neural networks (ATL-PINNs), which provide four different auxiliary-task learning modes and investigate their performance compared with original PINNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auxiliary-tasks-learning-for-physics-informed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sem-CS: Semantic CLIPStyler for Text-Based Image Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sem-cs-semantic-clipstyler-for-text-based-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the ground semantics of objects in the style transfer output is lost due to style spill-over on salient and background objects (content mismatch) or over-stylization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sem-cs-semantic-clipstyler-for-text-based-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FreeSeed: Frequency-band-aware and Self-guided Network for Sparse-view CT Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseed-frequency-band-aware-and-self-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we first propose a frequency-band-aware artifact modeling network (FreeNet), which learns artifact-related frequency-band attention in Fourier domain for better modeling the globally distributed streak artifact on the sparse-view CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/freeseed-frequency-band-aware-and-self-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locally Adaptive Federated Learning via Stochastic Polyak Stepsizes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-federated-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that FedSPS converges linearly in strongly convex and sublinearly in convex settings when the interpolation condition (overparametrization) is satisfied, and converges to a neighborhood of the solution in the general case.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-federated-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reconstructing Spatiotemporal Data with C-VAEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-spatiotemporal-data-with-c</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing region interpolation methods often fail to generate smooth and realistic representations of a region's evolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconstructing-spatiotemporal-data-with-c</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-based estimation of whole-body kinematics from multi-view images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-estimation-of-whole-body</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is necessary to analyze the whole-body kinematics (including joint locations and joint angles) to assess risks of fatal and musculoskeletal injuries in occupational tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-estimation-of-whole-body</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Batch Optimization of Contrastive Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-batch-optimization-of-contrastive-loss</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive learning has gained significant attention as a method for self-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-batch-optimization-of-contrastive-loss</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMBench: Is Your Multi-modal Model an All-around Player?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmbench-is-your-multi-modal-model-an-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to these challenges, we propose MMBench, a novel multi-modality benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmbench-is-your-multi-modal-model-an-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rhythm Modeling for Voice Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythm-modeling-for-voice-conversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice conversion aims to transform source speech into a different target voice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rhythm-modeling-for-voice-conversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correlation-Aware Mutual Learning for Semi-supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-mutual-learning-for-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is based on a mutual learning strategy that incorporates two modules: the Cross-sample Mutual Attention Module (CMA) and the Omni-Correlation Consistency Module (OCC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/correlation-aware-mutual-learning-for-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiRP: Learning Robot Generalized Bimanual Coordination using Relative Parameterization Method on Human Demonstration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/birp-learning-robot-generalized-bimanual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the method using synthetic motions and human demonstration data and deploy it to a humanoid robot to perform a generalized bimanual coordination motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/birp-learning-robot-generalized-bimanual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Faster Gradient Descent via Long Steps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-faster-gradient-descent-via-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work establishes provably faster convergence rates for gradient descent via a computer-assisted analysis technique.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-faster-gradient-descent-via-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDNAS: Discretized Differentiable Neural Architecture Search for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddnas-discretized-differentiable-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Architecture Search (NAS) has shown promising capability in learning text representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddnas-discretized-differentiable-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoK: Comparing Different Membership Inference Attacks with a Comprehensive Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-comparing-different-membership-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have identified three principles for the proposed "comparing different MI attacks" methodology, and we have designed and implemented the MIBench benchmark with 84 evaluation scenarios for each dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-comparing-different-membership-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLA-GCN: Global-local Adaptive Graph Convolutional Network for 3D Human</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gla-gcn-global-local-adaptive-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, we concentrate on improving the 3D human pose lifting via ground truth data for the future improvement of more quality estimated pose data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gla-gcn-global-local-adaptive-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ashaar: Automatic Analysis and Generation of Arabic Poetry Using Deep Learning Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ashaar-automatic-analysis-and-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Poetry holds immense significance within the cultural and traditional fabric of any nation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ashaar-automatic-analysis-and-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pluggable Neural Machine Translation Models via Memory-augmented Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-neural-machine-translation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although neural machine translation (NMT) models perform well in the general domain, it remains rather challenging to control their generation behavior to satisfy the requirement of different users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pluggable-neural-machine-translation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>balance -- a Python package for balancing biased data samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-a-python-package-for-balancing-biased</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The balance workflow includes three steps: understanding the initial bias in the data relative to a target we would like to infer, adjusting the data to correct for the bias by producing weights for each unit in the sample based on propensity scores, and evaluating the final biases and the variance inflation after applying the fitted weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balance-a-python-package-for-balancing-biased</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compact Twice Fusion Network for Edge Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-twice-fusion-network-for-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a Compact Twice Fusion Network (CTFN) to fully integrate multi-scale features while maintaining the compactness of the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compact-twice-fusion-network-for-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExFaceGAN: Exploring Identity Directions in GAN's Learned Latent Space for Synthetic Identity Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exfacegan-exploring-identity-directions-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose in this work a framework, ExFaceGAN, to disentangle identity information in state-of-the-art pretrained GANs latent spaces, enabling the generation of multiple samples of any synthetic identity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exfacegan-exploring-identity-directions-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised adversarial masking for 3D point cloud representation learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-masking-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce PointCAM, a novel adversarial method for learning a masking function for point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-adversarial-masking-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modular Multimodal Architecture for Gaze Target Prediction: Application to Privacy-Sensitive Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-multimodal-architecture-for-gaze-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[to detect obstructions in the line of sight or apply attention priors that humans typically have when observing others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-multimodal-architecture-for-gaze-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFR: Depth from Rotation by Uncalibrated Image Rectification with Latitudinal Motion Assumption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfr-depth-from-rotation-by-uncalibrated-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the increasing prevalence of rotating-style capture (e. g., surveillance cameras), conventional stereo rectification techniques frequently fail due to the rotation-dominant motion and small baseline between views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfr-depth-from-rotation-by-uncalibrated-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural-Symbolic Recommendation with Graph-Enhanced Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-symbolic-recommendation-with-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some researchers use user behavior for logic reasoning to achieve recommendation prediction from the perspective of cognitive reasoning, but this kind of reasoning is a local one and ignores implicit information on a global scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-symbolic-recommendation-with-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting small molecules solubilities on endpoint devices using deep ensemble neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-small-molecules-solubilities-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, ease of use remains a concern for any computational technique, resulting in the sustained popularity of group-based contribution methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-small-molecules-solubilities-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Cross-lingual Behavioral Testing of NLP Models with Typological Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-cross-lingual-behavioral-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A challenge towards developing NLP systems for the world's languages is understanding how they generalize to typological differences relevant for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-cross-lingual-behavioral-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relational Extraction on Wikipedia Tables using Convolutional and Memory Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-extraction-on-wikipedia-tables</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relation extraction (RE) is the task of extracting relations between entities in text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relational-extraction-on-wikipedia-tables</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Feedback Efficiency of Interactive Reinforcement Learning by Adaptive Learning from Scores</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-feedback-efficiency-of-interactive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a new method that uses scores provided by humans, instead of pairwise preferences, to improve the feedback efficiency of interactive reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-feedback-efficiency-of-interactive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnuraSet: A dataset for benchmarking Neotropical anuran calls identification in passive acoustic monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anuraset-a-dataset-for-benchmarking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we highlight the challenges of the dataset to encourage machine learning researchers to solve the problem of anuran call identification towards conservation policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anuraset-a-dataset-for-benchmarking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Anytime Optical Flow Estimation with Event Cameras</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-optical-flow-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose EVA-Flow, an EVent-based Anytime Flow estimation network to produce high-frame-rate event optical flow with only low-frame-rate optical flow ground truth for supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-anytime-optical-flow-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks on DNNs using Adversarial Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-on-dnns-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, we utilize the framework to propose two novel attacks: (1) Adversarial Membership Inference Attack (AMIA) efficiently utilizes the membership and the non-membership information of the subjects while adversarially minimizing a novel loss function, achieving 6% TPR on both Fashion-MNIST and MNIST datasets; and (2) Enhanced AMIA (E-AMIA) combines EMIA and AMIA to achieve 8% and 4% TPRs on Fashion-MNIST and MNIST datasets respectively, at 1% FPR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-on-dnns-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Uncertainty: The Role of Short-Term Trajectory Prediction in Autonomous Vehicle Safety</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-uncertainty-the-role-of-short-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we have developed a synthetic dataset for short-term trajectory prediction tasks using the CARLA simulator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-uncertainty-the-role-of-short-term</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secrets of RLHF in Large Language Models Part I: PPO</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we explore the PPO-max, an advanced version of PPO algorithm, to efficiently improve the training stability of the policy model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/secrets-of-rlhf-in-large-language-models-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering recommender systems using automatically generated Knowledge Graphs and Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-recommender-systems-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized recommendations have a growing importance in direct marketing, which motivates research to enhance customer experiences by knowledge graph (KG) applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-recommender-systems-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Active Subspaces and Discovering Important Features with Gaussian Radial Basis Functions Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-active-subspaces-and-discovering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Providing a model that achieves a strong predictive performance and at the same time is interpretable by humans is one of the most difficult challenges in machine learning research due to the conflicting nature of these two objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-active-subspaces-and-discovering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mao-Zedong At SemEval-2023 Task 4: Label Represention Multi-Head Attention Model With Contrastive Learning-Enhanced Nearest Neighbor Mechanism For Multi-Label Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mao-zedong-at-semeval-2023-task-4-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The study of human values is essential in both practical and theoretical domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mao-zedong-at-semeval-2023-task-4-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgoAdapt: A multi-stream evaluation study of adaptation to real-world egocentric user video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egoadapt-a-multi-stream-evaluation-study-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an evaluation framework that directly exploits the user's data stream with new metrics to measure the adaptation gain over the population model, online generalization, and hindsight performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egoadapt-a-multi-stream-evaluation-study-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification of the Virial Black Hole Mass with Conformal Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-the-virial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to baseline approaches for prediction interval estimation, we show that the CQR method provides prediction intervals that adjust to the black hole mass and its related properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-of-the-virial</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
