<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 09:13:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Dynamic Filtering Network for Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-dynamic-filtering-network-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate these issues, we propose to employ dynamic convolution to improve the learning of high-frequency and multi-scale features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-dynamic-filtering-network-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One for All, All for One: Learning and Transferring User Embeddings for Cross-Domain Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-all-all-for-one-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CAT-ART boosts the recommendation performance in any target domain through the combined use of the learned global user representation and knowledge transferred from other domains, in addition to the original user embedding in the target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-for-all-all-for-one-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ModelDiff: A Framework for Comparing Learning Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeldiff-a-framework-for-comparing-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of (learning) algorithm comparison, where the goal is to find differences between models trained with two different learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeldiff-a-framework-for-comparing-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Transferability of Visual Features in Generalized Zero-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-transferability-of-visual-features-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalized Zero-Shot Learning (GZSL) aims to train a classifier that can generalize to unseen classes, using a set of attributes as auxiliary information, and the visual features extracted from a pre-trained convolutional neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-transferability-of-visual-features-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SinDiffusion: Learning a Diffusion Model from a Single Natural Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sindiffusion-learning-a-diffusion-model-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SinDiffusion, leveraging denoising diffusion models to capture internal distribution of patches from a single natural image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sindiffusion-learning-a-diffusion-model-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video compression dataset and benchmark of learning-based video-quality metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-compression-dataset-and-benchmark-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video-quality measurement is a critical task in video processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-compression-dataset-and-benchmark-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can denoising diffusion probabilistic models generate realistic astrophysical fields?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we investigate the ability of these models to generate fields in two astrophysical contexts: dark matter mass density fields from cosmological simulations and images of interstellar dust.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-denoising-diffusion-probabilistic-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Ensemble Protection: Training Checkpoints Are Good Data Protectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-ensemble-protection-training-checkpoints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we uncover them by modeling checkpoints' gradients, forming the proposed self-ensemble protection (SEP), which is very effective because (1) learning on examples ignored during normal training tends to yield DNNs ignoring normal examples; (2) checkpoints' cross-model gradients are close to orthogonal, meaning that they are as diverse as DNNs with different architectures in conventional ensemble.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-ensemble-protection-training-checkpoints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task Learning for Camera Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-camera-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As far as we are aware, our approach is the first one that uses an approach to multi-task learning that includes mathematical formulas in a framework for learning to estimate camera parameters to predict both the extrinsic and intrinsic parameters jointly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-learning-for-camera-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X$^2$-VLM: All-In-One Pre-trained Model For Vision-Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-2-vlm-all-in-one-pre-trained-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we show that the modular design of X$^2$-VLM results in high transferability for X$^2$-VLM to be utilized in any language or domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-2-vlm-all-in-one-pre-trained-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIM: Iterative Self-Improved Model for Weakly Supervised Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isim-iterative-self-improved-model-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, to obtain more coherent CAMs with segmentation labels, we propose a framework that employs an iterative approach in a modified encoder-decoder-based segmentation model, which simultaneously supports classification and segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/isim-iterative-self-improved-model-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teach-DETR: Better Training DETR with Teachers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teach-detr-better-training-detr-with-teachers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel training scheme, namely Teach-DETR, to learn better DETR-based detectors from versatile teacher detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teach-detr-better-training-detr-with-teachers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cross-Residual Learning for Image Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-residual-learning-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ResNets and its variants play an important role in various fields of image recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-residual-learning-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$S^2$-Flow: Joint Semantic and Style Editing of Facial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-flow-joint-semantic-and-style-editing-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, methods that use semantic masks to edit images have difficulty preserving the identity and are unable to perform controlled style edits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-2-flow-joint-semantic-and-style-editing-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepJoin: Learning a Joint Occupancy, Signed Distance, and Normal Field Function for Shape Repair</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepjoin-learning-a-joint-occupancy-signed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We generate a high-resolution restoration shape by inferring a corresponding complete shape and a break surface from an input fractured shape.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepjoin-learning-a-joint-occupancy-signed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person Image Synthesis via Denoising Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/person-image-synthesis-via-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show how denoising diffusion models can be applied for high-fidelity person image synthesis with strong sample diversity and enhanced mode coverage of the learnt data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/person-image-synthesis-via-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ontology-aware Learning and Evaluation for Audio Tagging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-aware-learning-and-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed metric, ontology-aware mean average precision (OmAP) addresses the weaknesses of mAP by utilizing the AudioSet ontology information during the evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ontology-aware-learning-and-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping City-Wide Perceptions of Neighbourhood Quality using Street View Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-city-wide-perceptions-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Researchers demonstrated the efficacy of crowd-sourcing perception ratings of image pairs across 56 cities and training a model to predict perceptions from street-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-city-wide-perceptions-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visually Grounded Commonsense Knowledge Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-grounded-commonsense-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present CLEVER, which formulates CKE as a distantly supervised multi-instance learning problem, where models learn to summarize commonsense relations from a bag of images about an entity pair without any human annotation on image instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visually-grounded-commonsense-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>imitation: Clean Imitation Learning Implementations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-clean-imitation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[imitation provides open-source implementations of imitation and reward learning algorithms in PyTorch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-clean-imitation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Converge to the Truth: Factual Error Correction via Iterative Constrained Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converge-to-the-truth-factual-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a possibly false claim sentence, how can we automatically correct it with minimal editing?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converge-to-the-truth-factual-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy-guided domain adaptation for 3D in-bed human pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-guided-domain-adaptation-for-3d-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a remedy, we present a novel domain adaptation method, adapting a model from a labeled source to a shifted unlabeled target domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-guided-domain-adaptation-for-3d-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BESS: Balanced Entity Sampling and Sharing for Large-Scale Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bess-balanced-entity-sampling-and-sharing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the award-winning submission to the WikiKG90Mv2 track of OGB-LSC@NeurIPS 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bess-balanced-entity-sampling-and-sharing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-Flow: A U-shaped Normalizing Flow for Anomaly Detection with Unsupervised Threshold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-flow-a-u-shaped-normalizing-flow-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we propose a non-contrastive method for anomaly detection and segmentation in images, that benefits both from a modern machine learning approach and a more classic statistical detection theory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/u-flow-a-u-shaped-normalizing-flow-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Graph-Based Method for Soccer Action Spotting Using Unsupervised Player Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-based-method-for-soccer-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Action spotting in soccer videos is the task of identifying the specific time when a certain key action of the game occurs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-graph-based-method-for-soccer-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep-Learning-Based Computer Vision Approach For The Segmentation Of Ball Deliveries And Tracking In Cricket</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-computer-vision-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our research tries to solve one of these problems by segmenting ball deliveries in a cricket broadcast using deep learning models, MobileNet and YOLO, thus enabling researchers to use our work as a dataset for their research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-computer-vision-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pred&amp;Guide: Labeled Target Class Prediction for Guiding Semi-Supervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pred-guide-labeled-target-class-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we propose a novel framework, Pred&Guide, which leverages the inconsistency between the predicted and the actual class labels of the few labeled target examples to effectively guide the domain adaptation in a semi-supervised setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pred-guide-labeled-target-class-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-level play in the game of Diplomacy by combining language models with strategic reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-level-play-in-the-game-of-diplomacy-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite much progress in training AI systems to imitate human language, building agents that use language to communicate intentionally with humans in interactive environments remains a major challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-level-play-in-the-game-of-diplomacy-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation, Classification, and Quality Assessment of UW-OCTA Images for the Diagnosis of Diabetic Retinopathy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-classification-and-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diabetic Retinopathy (DR) is a severe complication of diabetes that can cause blindness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-classification-and-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneous Multiple Object Detection and Pose Estimation using 3D Model Infusion with Monocular Vision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-multiple-object-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the labeling method, we provide the KITTI-6DoF dataset with $\sim7. 5$K annotated frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneous-multiple-object-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Efficacy of Pre-trained Checkpoints in Text-to-Music Generation Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-efficacy-of-pre-trained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benefiting from large-scale datasets and pre-trained models, the field of generative models has recently gained significant momentum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-efficacy-of-pre-trained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Directed Acyclic Graph Factorization Machines for CTR Prediction via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-graph-factorization-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some recent knowledge distillation based methods transfer knowledge from complex teacher models to shallow student models for accelerating the online model inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/directed-acyclic-graph-factorization-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orientation recognition and correction of Cardiac MRI with deep neural network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-recognition-and-correction-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, the problem of orientation correction in cardiac MRI images is investigated and a framework for orientation recognition via deep neural networks is proposed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-recognition-and-correction-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PS-Transformer: Learning Sparse Photometric Stereo Network using Self-Attention Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-transformer-learning-sparse-photometric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While they are effective with the dense capture, simple first-order operations often fail to capture the high-order interactions among observations under small number of different lights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ps-transformer-learning-sparse-photometric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Generalization Improvement Guided by Random Weight Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-generalization-improvement-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fully uncover the great potential of deep neural networks (DNNs), various learning algorithms have been developed to improve the model's generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-generalization-improvement-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel transfer learning schemes based on Siamese networks and synthetic data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-transfer-learning-schemes-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We make the data sets available at https://pub. uni-bielefeld. de/record/2960030.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-transfer-learning-schemes-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are All Combinations Equal? Combining Textual and Visual Features with Multiple Space Learning for Text-Based Video Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-all-combinations-equal-combining-textual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we tackle the cross-modal video retrieval problem and, more specifically, we focus on text-to-video retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-all-combinations-equal-combining-textual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last-Mile Embodied Visual Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/last-mile-embodied-visual-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Realistic long-horizon tasks like image-goal navigation involve exploratory and exploitative phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/last-mile-embodied-visual-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Contrastive Learning for Robust Reasoning in VQA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-contrastive-learning-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For each positive pair, we regard the images from different graphs as negative samples and deduct the version of multi-positive contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-contrastive-learning-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exhaustive Symbolic Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exhaustive-symbolic-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues we introduce a new method for SR -- Exhaustive Symbolic Regression (ESR) -- which systematically and efficiently considers all possible equations and is therefore guaranteed to find not only the true optimum but also a complete function ranking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exhaustive-symbolic-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Place Recognition under Occlusion and Changing Appearance via Disentangled Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/place-recognition-under-occlusion-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Place recognition is a critical and challenging task for mobile robots, aiming to retrieve an image captured at the same place as a query image from a database.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/place-recognition-under-occlusion-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blind Knowledge Distillation for Robust Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-knowledge-distillation-for-robust-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Blind Knowledge Distillation - a novel teacher-student approach for learning with noisy labels by masking the ground truth related teacher output to filter out potentially corrupted knowledge and to estimate the tipping point from generalizing to overfitting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blind-knowledge-distillation-for-robust-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding and Improving Visual Prompting: A Label-Mapping Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-visual-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As highlighted below, we show that when reprogramming an ImageNet-pretrained ResNet-18 to 13 target tasks, our method outperforms baselines by a substantial margin, e. g., 7. 9% and 6. 7% accuracy improvements in transfer learning to the target Flowers102 and CIFAR100 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-and-improving-visual-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering Fine Details for Neural Implicit Surface Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-fine-details-for-neural-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works on implicit neural representations have made significant strides.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-fine-details-for-neural-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-specific and Model-adaptive Supervision for Semi-supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-specific-and-model-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relying on the model's performance, iMAS employs a class-weighted symmetric intersection-over-union to evaluate quantitative hardness of each unlabeled instance and supervises the training on unlabeled data in a model-adaptive manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-specific-and-model-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Graph Structures for Congestion and ETA Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-graph-structures-for-congestion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traffic4cast is an annual competition to predict spatio temporal traffic based on real world data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-graph-structures-for-congestion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Parametric Classification Baseline for Generalized Category Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-parametric-classification-baseline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works in GCD argue that a non-parametric classifier formed using semi-supervised $k$-means can outperform strong baselines which use parametric classifiers as it can alleviate the over-fitting to seen categories in the labelled set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-parametric-classification-baseline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural network based generation of 1-dimensional stochastic fields with turbulent velocity statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-based-generation-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We define and study a fully-convolutional neural network stochastic model, NN-Turb, which generates 1-dimensional fields with turbulent velocity statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-network-based-generation-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAILD: Towards Leveraging Relation Features for Inductive Link Prediction In Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raild-towards-leveraging-relation-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, a novel Relation Aware Inductive Link preDiction (RAILD) is proposed for KG completion which learns representations for both unseen entities and unseen relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/raild-towards-leveraging-relation-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Value-based CTDE Methods in Symmetric Two-team Markov Game: from Cooperation to Team Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-based-ctde-methods-in-symmetric-two</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we identify the best learning scenario to train a team of agents to compete against multiple possible strategies of opposing teams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/value-based-ctde-methods-in-symmetric-two</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
