<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:10:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Attention on Multiword Expressions: A Multilingual Study of BERT-based Models with Regard to Idiomaticity and Microsyntax</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-on-multiword-expressions-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to understand whether fine-tuning BERT-based models on specific tasks influences their attention to MWEs, and how this attention differs between semantic and syntactic tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-on-multiword-expressions-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Skin: Enhancing Dermatology Vision-Language Model with an Image-Text Dataset Derived from Textbooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-skin-enhancing-dermatology-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Comprehensive benchmark evaluations of SkinVL on VQA, supervised fine-tuning (SFT) and zero-shot classification tasks across 8 datasets, reveal its exceptional performance for skin diseases in comparison to both general and medical VLM models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-skin-enhancing-dermatology-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summarisation of German Judgments in conjunction with a Class-based Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarisation-of-german-judgments-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The automated summarisation of long legal documents can be a great aid for legal experts in their daily work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/summarisation-of-german-judgments-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiGIT: Multi-Dilated Gated Encoder and Central-Adjacent Region Integrated Decoder for Temporal Action Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digit-multi-dilated-gated-encoder-and-central</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed encoder reduces the redundant information caused by multi-level features while maintaining the ability to capture fine-grained and long-range temporal information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/digit-multi-dilated-gated-encoder-and-central</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Pixels to Perception: Interpretable Predictions via Instance-wise Grouped Feature Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-pixels-to-perception-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the decision-making process of machine learning models provides valuable insights into the task, the data, and the reasons behind a model's failures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-pixels-to-perception-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFEN: Dual Feature Equalization Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfen-dual-feature-equalization-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these methods have shown effective performance, none of them take into account the fact that pixels at the boundary and regions with a low number of class pixels capture more contextual feature information from other classes, leading to misclassification of pixels by unequal contextual feature information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dfen-dual-feature-equalization-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-Consistent Siamese-Diffusion for Medical Image Synthesis and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-consistent-siamese-diffusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning has revolutionized medical image segmentation, yet its full potential remains constrained by the paucity of annotated datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-consistent-siamese-diffusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniVLA: Learning to Act Anywhere with Task-centric Latent Actions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/univla-learning-to-act-anywhere-with-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learned from internet-scale videos, the generalist policy can be deployed to various robots through efficient latent action decoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/univla-learning-to-act-anywhere-with-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGTrack: Cascade Gating Network with Hierarchical Feature Aggregation for UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgtrack-cascade-gating-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in visual object tracking have markedly improved the capabilities of unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV) tracking, which is a critical component in real-world robotics applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cgtrack-cascade-gating-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Short-circuiting Shortcuts: Mechanistic Investigation of Shortcuts in Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-circuiting-shortcuts-mechanistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reliance on spurious correlations (shortcuts) has been shown to underlie many of the successes of language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/short-circuiting-shortcuts-mechanistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Infrastructure Surveying: A Framework for Geometric Measurements and Compliance Assessment Using Point Cloud Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-infrastructure-surveying-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a proof of concept, we apply this framework to automatically evaluate the compliance of curb ramps with the Americans with Disabilities Act (ADA), demonstrating the utility of point cloud data in survey automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-infrastructure-surveying-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-level Fuzzy Learning with Patch Guidance for Image Ordinal Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-fuzzy-learning-with-patch-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Dual-level Fuzzy Learning with Patch Guidance framework, named DFPG that learns precise feature-based grading boundaries from ambiguous ordinal labels, with patch-level supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-level-fuzzy-learning-with-patch-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeoQA: Evidence-based Question Answering with Generated News Events</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neoqa-evidence-based-question-answering-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce NeoQA (News Events for Out-of-training Question Answering), a benchmark designed to address this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neoqa-evidence-based-question-answering-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Music Audio Representations With Limited Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-music-audio-representations-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large deep-learning models for music, including those focused on learning general-purpose music audio representations, are often assumed to require substantial training data to achieve high performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-music-audio-representations-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realistic Adversarial Attacks for Robustness Evaluation of Trajectory Prediction Models via Future State Perturbation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-adversarial-attacks-for-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These results underscore the need for more comprehensive adversarial testing to better evaluate and improve the reliability of trajectory prediction models for autonomous vehicles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realistic-adversarial-attacks-for-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining the Source of Defects from a Mechanical Perspective for 3D Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-the-source-of-defects-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we go beyond identifying anomalies only in structural terms and think about better anomaly detection motivated by anomaly causes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/examining-the-source-of-defects-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Get Lost In Multi-Turn Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-get-lost-in-multi-turn-conversation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are conversational interfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-get-lost-in-multi-turn-conversation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Diffusion Maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-diffusion-maps</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimensionality reduction methods make it possible to combat the so-called curse of dimensionality, visualize high-dimensional data and, in general, improve the efficiency of storing and processing large data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-diffusion-maps</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Stragglers in Large Model Training Using What-if Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-stragglers-in-large-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language model (LLM) training is one of the most demanding distributed computations today, often requiring thousands of GPUs with frequent synchronization across machines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-stragglers-in-large-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Set Label Shift with Test Time Out-of-Distribution Reference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-set-label-shift-with-test-time-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With reasonable assumptions on the ID/OOD classifier, the estimators are assembled into a sequence of three stages: 1) an estimate of the source label distribution of the OOD class, 2) an EM algorithm for Maximum Likelihood estimates (MLE) of the target label distribution, and 3) an estimate of the target label distribution of OOD class under relaxed assumptions on the OOD classifier.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-set-label-shift-with-test-time-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards order of magnitude X-ray dose reduction in breast cancer imaging using phase contrast and deep denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-order-of-magnitude-x-ray-dose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The image quality has been assessed both in terms of objective metrics, such as spatial resolution and contrast-to-noise ratio, as well as in an observer study by experienced medical imaging specialists and radiologists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-order-of-magnitude-x-ray-dose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scDrugMap: Benchmarking Large Foundation Models for Drug Response Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scdrugmap-benchmarking-large-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the pooled-data scenario, scFoundation achieved the best performance, with mean F1 scores of 0. 971 (layer freezing) and 0. 947 (fine-tuning), outperforming the lowest-performing model by over 50%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scdrugmap-benchmarking-large-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Large Language Models with Faster Code Preprocessing for Vulnerability Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-language-models-with-faster</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results show a 97. 3\% reduction in processing time with SCoPE2, along with an improved F1-score for the LLM, solely due to the refined preprocessing approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-language-models-with-faster</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cardioformer: Advancing AI in ECG Analysis with Multi-Granularity Patching and ResNet</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardioformer-advancing-ai-in-ecg-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Electrocardiogram (ECG) classification is crucial for automated cardiac disease diagnosis, yet existing methods often struggle to capture local morphological details and long-range temporal dependencies simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cardioformer-advancing-ai-in-ecg-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EquiHGNN: Scalable Rotationally Equivariant Hypergraph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equihgnn-scalable-rotationally-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Molecular interactions often involve high-order relationships that cannot be fully captured by traditional graph-based models limited to pairwise connections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equihgnn-scalable-rotationally-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KG-HTC: Integrating Knowledge Graphs into LLMs for Effective Zero-shot Hierarchical Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-htc-integrating-knowledge-graphs-into-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Knowledge Graphs for zero-shot Hierarchical Text Classification (KG-HTC), which aims to address these challenges of HTC in applications by integrating knowledge graphs with Large Language Models (LLMs) to provide structured semantic context during classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kg-htc-integrating-knowledge-graphs-into-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Thought Machines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-thought-machines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CTM has two core innovations: (1) neuron-level temporal processing, where each neuron uses unique weight parameters to process a history of incoming signals; and (2) neural synchronization employed as a latent representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continuous-thought-machines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Transfer Attacks: Towards Super Transferable Adversarial Attacks on CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-transfer-attacks-towards-super-transferable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Contrastive Language-Image Pre-training (CLIP) models are increasingly adopted for diverse downstream tasks and integrated into large vision-language models (VLMs), their susceptibility to adversarial perturbations has emerged as a critical concern.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-transfer-attacks-towards-super-transferable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Preliminary Study for GPT-4o on Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-for-gpt-4o-on-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenAI's GPT-4o model, integrating multi-modal inputs and outputs within an autoregressive architecture, has demonstrated unprecedented performance in image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-preliminary-study-for-gpt-4o-on-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Imaging Biomarkers for Robust Unsupervised Segmentation of Histopathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-imaging-biomarkers-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The biomarkers extracted through this approach demonstrate enhanced robustness and generalizability against rotation compared to models using standard convolution kernels, holding promise for enhancing the accuracy, consistency, and robustness of ML models in digital pathology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-imaging-biomarkers-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CityNavAgent: Aerial Vision-and-Language Navigation with Hierarchical Semantic Planning and Global Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citynavagent-aerial-vision-and-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose \textbf{CityNavAgent}, a large language model (LLM)-empowered agent that significantly reduces the navigation complexity for urban aerial VLN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/citynavagent-aerial-vision-and-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Starts: Accelerating Convergence through Uncommon Region Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-starts-accelerating-convergence-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Initialization profoundly affects evolutionary algorithm (EA) efficacy by dictating search trajectories and convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smart-starts-accelerating-convergence-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Front-door Adjustment for Heterogeneous Treatment Assignment Effect Estimation Under Non-adherence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-front-door-adjustment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimates of heterogeneous treatment assignment effects can inform treatment decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-front-door-adjustment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTDC: A multimodal machine learning training, evaluation, and inference platform for biomedical foundation models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytdc-a-multimodal-machine-learning-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing biomedical benchmarks do not provide end-to-end infrastructure for training, evaluation, and inference of models that integrate multimodal biological data and a broad range of machine learning tasks in therapeutics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytdc-a-multimodal-machine-learning-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Common Interface for Automatic Differentiation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-common-interface-for-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For scientific machine learning tasks with a lot of custom code, picking the right Automatic Differentiation (AD) system matters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-common-interface-for-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Term Individual Causal Effect Estimation via Identifiable Latent Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-individual-causal-effect-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating long-term causal effects by combining long-term observational and short-term experimental data is a crucial but challenging problem in many real-world scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-individual-causal-effect-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Blind Speech Separation with a Diffusion Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-blind-speech-separation-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We only need a simple single-speaker speech diffusion model as a prior along with the mixtures recorded at the microphones; no microphone array information is necessary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-blind-speech-separation-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Satellite Object Localization with Dilated Convolutions and Attention-aided Spatial Pooling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-satellite-object-localization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object localization in satellite imagery is particularly challenging due to the high variability of objects, low spatial resolution, and interference from noise and dominant features such as clouds and city lights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-satellite-object-localization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V-EfficientNets: Vector-Valued Efficiently Scaled Convolutional Neural Network Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-efficientnets-vector-valued-efficiently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EfficientNet models are convolutional neural networks optimized for parameter allocation by jointly balancing network width, depth, and resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v-efficientnets-vector-valued-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt to Polyp: Clinically-Aware Medical Image Synthesis with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-to-polyp-clinically-aware-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The generation of realistic medical images from text descriptions has significant potential to address data scarcity challenges in healthcare AI while preserving patient privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-to-polyp-clinically-aware-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiteLMGuard: Seamless and Lightweight On-Device Prompt Filtering for Safeguarding Small Language Models against Quantization-induced Risks and Vulnerabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litelmguard-seamless-and-lightweight-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our LLMG formalizes prompt filtering as a deep learning (DL)-based prompt answerability classification task, leveraging semantic understanding to determine whether a query should be answered by any SLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/litelmguard-seamless-and-lightweight-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain-of-Thought Tokens are Computer Program Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-thought-tokens-are-computer-program</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chain-of-thoughts (CoT) requires large language models (LLMs) to generate intermediate steps before reaching the final answer, and has been proven effective to help LLMs solve complex reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-thought-tokens-are-computer-program</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StabStitch++: Unsupervised Online Video Stitching with Spatiotemporal Bidirectional Warps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabstitch-unsupervised-online-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose StabStitch++, a novel video stitching framework to realize spatial stitching and temporal stabilization with unsupervised learning simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stabstitch-unsupervised-online-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threshold Modulation for Online Test-Time Adaptation of Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threshold-modulation-for-online-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method offers a practical solution for online test-time adaptation of SNNs, providing inspiration for the design of future neuromorphic chips.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/threshold-modulation-for-online-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiTransProQA: an LLM-based Literary Translation evaluation metric with Professional Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transproqa-an-llm-based-literary-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the long run, this bias could result in a permanent decline in translation quality and cultural authenticity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transproqa-an-llm-based-literary-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmented Deep Contexts for Spatially Embedded Video Coding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-deep-contexts-for-spatially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To relieve the limitations, we propose a Spatially Embedded Video Codec (SEVC), in which the low-resolution video is compressed for spatial references.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmented-deep-contexts-for-spatially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UncertainSAM: Fast and Efficient Uncertainty Quantification of the Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainsam-fast-and-efficient-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The introduction of the Segment Anything Model (SAM) has paved the way for numerous semantic segmentation applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainsam-fast-and-efficient-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Physically Stable and Buildable LEGO Designs from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-physically-stable-and-buildable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that LegoGPT produces stable, diverse, and aesthetically pleasing LEGO designs that align closely with the input text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-physically-stable-and-buildable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow-GRPO: Training Flow Matching Models via Online RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-grpo-training-flow-matching-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Flow-GRPO, the first method integrating online reinforcement learning (RL) into flow matching models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-grpo-training-flow-matching-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAPSO: A Unified Optimization View for Learning-Augmented Power System Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapso-a-unified-optimization-view-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adopting a native optimization perspective, LAPSO is centered on the operation stage and aims to break the boundary between temporally siloed power system tasks, such as forecast, operation and control, while unifying the objectives of machine learning and model-based optimizations at both training and inference stages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lapso-a-unified-optimization-view-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
