<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 21:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the Output Structure of Sparse Matrix Multiplication with Sampled Compression Ratio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-output-structure-of-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a reference design of the existing sampling-based method with optimized computing overheads to demonstrate the better accuracy of the proposed method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-the-output-structure-of-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Recognition by Request</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-by-request</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel protocol of annotation and evaluation for visual recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-recognition-by-request</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Syntactic Modelling Structures in Biomedical Ontologies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-syntactic-modelling-structures-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the large-scale uptake of semantic technologies in the biomedical domain, little is known about common modelling practices in published ontologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-syntactic-modelling-structures-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EEG2Mel: Reconstructing Sound from Brain Responses to Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg2mel-reconstructing-sound-from-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information retrieval from brain responses to auditory and visual stimuli has shown success through classification of song names and image classes presented to participants while recording EEG signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eeg2mel-reconstructing-sound-from-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Data Augmentation Technique for Out-of-Distribution Sample Detection using Compounded Corruptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-data-augmentation-technique-for-out</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major advantages of CnC is that it does not require any hold-out data apart from the training set.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-data-augmentation-technique-for-out</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Aligned Matching for Enhanced DETR Convergence and Multi-Scale Feature Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aligned-matching-for-enhanced-detr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently proposed DEtection TRansformer (DETR) has established a fully end-to-end paradigm for object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-aligned-matching-for-enhanced-detr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Training of Language Models to Fill in the Middle</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-of-language-models-to-fill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we run a series of ablations on key hyperparameters, such as the data transformation frequency, the structure of the transformation, and the method of selecting the infill span.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-training-of-language-models-to-fill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety-Enhanced Autonomous Driving Using Interpretable Sensor Fusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-enhanced-autonomous-driving-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale deployment of autonomous vehicles has been continually delayed due to safety concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-enhanced-autonomous-driving-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Acoustic Mosquito Detection in Noisy Conditions Using Trainable Kernels and Augmentations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-acoustic-mosquito</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate a unique recipe to enhance the effectiveness of audio machine learning approaches by fusing pre-processing techniques into a deep learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-acoustic-mosquito</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utterance-by-utterance overlap-aware neural diarization with Graph-PIT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utterance-by-utterance-overlap-aware-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we argue that such an approach involving the segmentation has several issues; for example, it inevitably faces a dilemma that larger segment sizes increase both the context available for enhancing the performance and the number of speakers for the local EEND module to handle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utterance-by-utterance-overlap-aware-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HorNet: Efficient High-Order Spatial Interactions with Recursive Gated Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the key ingredients behind the vision Transformers, namely input-adaptive, long-range and high-order spatial interactions, can also be efficiently implemented with a convolution-based framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dive into Machine Learning Algorithms for Influenza Virus Host Prediction with Hemagglutinin Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-machine-learning-algorithms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Influenza viruses mutate rapidly and can pose a threat to public health, especially to those in vulnerable groups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dive-into-machine-learning-algorithms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining Cross-Person Cues for Body-Part Interactiveness Learning in HOI Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-cross-person-cues-for-body-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though significant progress has been made, interactiveness learning remains a challenging problem in HOI detection: existing methods usually generate redundant negative H-O pair proposals and fail to effectively extract interactive pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-cross-person-cues-for-body-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humans disagree with the IoU for measuring object detector localization error</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humans-disagree-with-the-iou-for-measuring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our work is the first to evaluate IoU with humans and makes it clear that relying on IoU scores alone to evaluate localization errors might not be sufficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humans-disagree-with-the-iou-for-measuring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequence to sequence pretraining for a less-resourced Slovenian language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-to-sequence-pretraining-for-a-less</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pretrained language models have recently conquered the area of natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequence-to-sequence-pretraining-for-a-less</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonteBoxFinder: Detecting and Filtering Primitives to Fit a Noisy Point Cloud</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monteboxfinder-detecting-and-filtering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MonteBoxFinder, a method that, given a noisy input point cloud, fits cuboids to the input scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monteboxfinder-detecting-and-filtering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewriting Geometric Rules of a GAN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewriting-geometric-rules-of-a-gan</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method allows a user to create a model that synthesizes endless objects with defined geometric changes, enabling the creation of a new generative model without the burden of curating a large-scale dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rewriting-geometric-rules-of-a-gan</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A general framework for multi-step ahead adaptive conformal heteroscedastic time series forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-multi-step-ahead</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The exponential growth of machine learning (ML) has prompted a great deal of interest in quantifying the uncertainty of each prediction for a user-defined level of confidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-general-framework-for-multi-step-ahead</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Limited Annotations: A Survey on Deep Semi-Supervised Learning for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-limited-annotations-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Medical image segmentation is a fundamental and critical step in many image-guided clinical approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-limited-annotations-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Performance of Robust Control through Event-Triggered Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-performance-of-robust-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in practice, many systems also exhibit uncertainty in the form of changes over time, e. g., due to weight shifts or wear and tear, leading to decreased performance or instability of the learning-based controller.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-performance-of-robust-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Step Deductive Reasoning Over Natural Language: An Empirical Study on Out-of-Distribution Generalisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-step-deductive-reasoning-over-natural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our model, reasoning is performed using an iterative memory neural network based on RNN with a gate attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-step-deductive-reasoning-over-natural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelixFold-Single: MSA-free Protein Structure Prediction by Using Protein Language Model as an Alternative</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-single-msa-free-protein-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed method, HelixFold-Single, first pre-trains a large-scale protein language model (PLM) with thousands of millions of primary sequences utilizing the self-supervised learning paradigm, which will be used as an alternative to MSAs and templates for learning the co-evolution information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/helixfold-single-msa-free-protein-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Sample Average Approximation with Covariate Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study optimization for data-driven decision-making when we have observations of the uncertain parameters within the optimization model together with concurrent observations of covariates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-driven-sample-average-approximation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransNorm: Transformer Provides a Strong Spatial Normalization Mechanism for a Deep Segmentation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the past few years, convolutional neural networks (CNNs), particularly U-Net, have been the prevailing technique in the medical image processing era.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transnorm-transformer-provides-a-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardly Perceptible Trojan Attack against Neural Networks with Bit Flips</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The security of deep neural networks (DNNs) has attracted increasing attention due to their widespread use in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hardly-perceptible-trojan-attack-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Break and Make: Interactive Structural Understanding Using LEGO Bricks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/break-and-make-interactive-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We pair this simulator with a new dataset of fan-made LEGO creations that have been uploaded to the internet in order to provide complex scenes containing over a thousand unique brick shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/break-and-make-interactive-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoTransition: Learning to Recommend Video Transition Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First we learn the embedding of video transitions through a video transition classification task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autotransition-learning-to-recommend-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe and Robust Experience Sharing for Deterministic Policy Gradient Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning in high dimensional continuous tasks is challenging, mainly when the experience replay memory is very limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-and-robust-experience-sharing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mid-level Representation Enhancement and Graph Embedded Uncertainty Suppressing for Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, GUS is introduced to suppress the feature ambiguity in the representation space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mid-level-representation-enhancement-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marker and source-marker reprogramming of Most Permissive Boolean networks and ensembles with BoNesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate how the software BoNesis can be employed to exhaustively identify combinations of perturbations which enforce properties on their fixed points and attractors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marker-and-source-marker-reprogramming-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALBench: A Framework for Evaluating Active Learning in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate the research in this field, this paper contributes an active learning benchmark framework named as ALBench for evaluating active learning in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/albench-a-framework-for-evaluating-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evolutionary Multiparty Distance Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the field of evolutionary multiobjective optimization, the decision maker (DM) concerns conflicting objectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evolutionary-multiparty-distance-minimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Leaf Clinical Trials Corpus: a new resource for query generation from clinical trial eligibility criteria</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-leaf-clinical-trials-corpus-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to identify potential participants at scale, these criteria must first be translated into queries on clinical databases, which can be labor-intensive and error-prone.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-leaf-clinical-trials-corpus-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Attention of Disentangled Modalities for 3D Human Mesh Recovery with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-of-disentangled-modalities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformer encoder architectures have recently achieved state-of-the-art results on monocular 3D human mesh reconstruction, but they require a substantial number of parameters and expensive computations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-of-disentangled-modalities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Video Deblurring Guided by Motion Magnitude</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video deblurring is a highly under-constrained problem due to the spatially and temporally varying blur.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-video-deblurring-guided-by-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shift-tolerant Perceptual Similarity Metric</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-tolerant-perceptual-similarity-metric-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the effect of small misalignment, specifically a small shift between the input and reference image, on existing metrics, and accordingly develops a shift-tolerant similarity metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shift-tolerant-perceptual-similarity-metric-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAUDI: A Neural Architect for Immersive 3D Scene Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaudi-a-neural-architect-for-immersive-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GAUDI, a generative model capable of capturing the distribution of complex and realistic 3D scenes that can be rendered immersively from a moving camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaudi-a-neural-architect-for-immersive-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A model for COVID-19 and bacterial pneumonia coinfection with community- and hospital-acquired infections</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-model-for-covid-19-and-bacterial-pneumonia</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new mathematical model to study the coinfection dynamics of COVID-19 and bacterial pneumonia.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-model-for-covid-19-and-bacterial-pneumonia</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SiRi: A Simple Selective Retraining Mechanism for Transformer-based Visual Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, SiRi conveys a significant principle to the research of visual grounding, i. e., a better initialized vision-language encoder would help the model converge to a better local minimum, advancing the performance accordingly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/siri-a-simple-selective-retraining-mechanism</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the Neuroevolution of Low-level Artificial General Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate a method to evolve a biologically-inspired artificial neural network that learns from environment reactions named Neuroevolution of Artificial General Intelligence (NAGI), a framework for low-level AGI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-neuroevolution-of-low-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factorial User Modeling with Hierarchical Graph Neural Network for Enhanced Sequential Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most sequential recommendation (SR) systems employing graph neural networks (GNNs) only model a user's interaction sequence as a flat graph without hierarchy, overlooking diverse factors in the user's preference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factorial-user-modeling-with-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camouflaged Object Detection via Context-aware Cross-level Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a novel Context-aware Cross-level Fusion Network (C2F-Net), which fuses context-aware cross-level features for accurately identifying camouflaged objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camouflaged-object-detection-via-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Pix2Vox++ for 3D Cardiac Reconstruction from 2D echo views</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate geometric quantification of the human heart is a key step in the diagnosis of numerous cardiac diseases, and in the management of cardiac patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-pix2vox-for-3d-cardiac</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstracting Sketches through Simple Primitives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Toward equipping machines with such capabilities, we propose the Primitive-based Sketch Abstraction task where the goal is to represent sketches using a fixed set of drawing primitives under the influence of a budget.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abstracting-sketches-through-simple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast expansion into harmonics on the disk: a steerable basis with fast radial convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a fast and numerically accurate method for expanding digitized $L \times L$ images representing functions on $[-1, 1]^2$ supported on the disk $\{x \in \mathbb{R}^2 : |x|<1\}$ in the harmonics (Dirichlet Laplacian eigenfunctions) on the disk.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-expansion-into-harmonics-on-the-disk-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning with Combinatorial Optimization Layers: a Probabilistic Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-combinatorial-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combinatorial optimization (CO) layers in machine learning (ML) pipelines are a powerful tool to tackle data-driven decision tasks, but they come with two main challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-with-combinatorial-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Vizier: Distributed Infrastructure and API for Reliable and Flexible Blackbox Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vizier is the de-facto blackbox and hyperparameter optimization service across Google, having optimized some of Google's largest products and research efforts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-source-vizier-distributed-infrastructure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealTime QA: What's the Answer Right Now?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realtime-qa-what-s-the-answer-right-now</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce RealTime QA, a dynamic question answering (QA) platform that announces questions and evaluates systems on a regular basis (weekly in this version).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realtime-qa-what-s-the-answer-right-now</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Classification in Memristor-based Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-classification-in-memristor-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We take two approaches to obtain trained spiking neural networks with memristor models: 1) by converting a pre-trained artificial neural network (ANN) to a memristor-based SNN, or 2) by training a memristor-based SNN directly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-classification-in-memristor-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generator Knows What Discriminator Should Learn in Unconditional GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here we explore the efficacy of dense supervision in unconditional generation and find generator feature maps can be an alternative of cost-expensive semantic label maps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generator-knows-what-discriminator-should</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
