<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 21:08:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MiCEval: Unveiling Multimodal Chain of Thought's Quality via Image Description and Reasoning Steps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miceval-unveiling-multimodal-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose Multimodal Chain-of-Thought Evaluation (MiCEval), a framework designed to assess the correctness of reasoning chains by evaluating the quality of both the description and each reasoning step.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miceval-unveiling-multimodal-chain-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised contrastive learning performs non-linear system identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-contrastive-learning-performs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) approaches have brought tremendous success across many tasks and domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-contrastive-learning-performs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal DLT-based Solutions for the Perspective-n-Point</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-dlt-based-solutions-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a modified normalized direct linear transform (DLT) algorithm for solving the perspective-n-point (PnP) problem with much better behavior than the conventional DLT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-dlt-based-solutions-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaAlign: Align Large Language Models with Diverse Preferences during Inference Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaalign-align-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) acquire extensive knowledge and remarkable abilities from extensive text corpora, making them powerful tools for various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaalign-align-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoMAL: Collaborative Multi-Agent Large Language Models for Mixed-Autonomy Traffic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comal-collaborative-multi-agent-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It utilizes a Perception Module to observe surrounding agents and a Memory Module to store strategies for each agent.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comal-collaborative-multi-agent-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xPerT: Extended Persistence Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpert-extended-persistence-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, due to its nature as a set, incorporating it as a feature into a machine learning framework is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpert-extended-persistence-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Transcription: Exploring Noise Injection Strategies for Training Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-transcription-exploring-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Automatic Piano Transcription (APT) have significantly improved system performance, but the impact of noisy environments on the system performance remains largely unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-transcription-exploring-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Source Spatial Knowledge Understanding for Immersive Visual Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-spatial-knowledge-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the issues, we propose a novel multi-source spatial knowledge understanding scheme for immersive VTTS, termed MS$^2$KU-VTTS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-spatial-knowledge-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViConsFormer: Constituting Meaningful Phrases of Scene Texts using Transformer-based Method in Vietnamese Text-based Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viconsformer-constituting-meaningful-phrases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main challenge of text-based VQA is exploiting the meaning and information from scene texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/viconsformer-constituting-meaningful-phrases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distance between Relevant Information Pieces Causes Bias in Long-Context LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-between-relevant-information-pieces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These experiments reveal that while most current models are robust against the "lost in the middle" issue, there exist significant biases related to the spacing of relevant information pieces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distance-between-relevant-information-pieces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Annotator Reliability Assessment and Sample Weighting for Knowledge-Based Misinformation Detection on Social Media</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-annotator-reliability-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The EffiARA annotation framework is introduced, aiming to utilise inter- and intra-annotator agreement to understand the reliability of each annotator and influence the training of large language models for classification based on annotator reliability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-annotator-reliability-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decomposing The Dark Matter of Sparse Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposing-the-dark-matter-of-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse autoencoders (SAEs) are a promising technique for decomposing language model activations into interpretable linear features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decomposing-the-dark-matter-of-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SNAC: Multi-Scale Neural Audio Codec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snac-multi-scale-neural-audio-codec</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural audio codecs have recently gained popularity because they can represent audio signals with high fidelity at very low bitrates, making it feasible to use language modeling approaches for audio generation and understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/snac-multi-scale-neural-audio-codec</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting time-varying flux and balance in metabolic systems using structured neural-ODE processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-time-varying-flux-and-balance-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a novel data-driven framework as an alternative to dynamic flux balance analysis, bypassing the demand for deep domain knowledge and manual efforts to formulate the optimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-time-varying-flux-and-balance-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedMSE: Federated learning for IoT network intrusion detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmse-federated-learning-for-iot-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enhances the performance of intrusion detection by effectively representing normal network data and accurately identifying anomalies in the decentralized strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmse-federated-learning-for-iot-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Models to Balance Resisting and Accepting Persuasion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-models-to-balance-resisting-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PBT consistently improves resistance to misinformation and resilience to being challenged while also resulting in the best overall performance on holistic data containing both positive and negative persuasion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-models-to-balance-resisting-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating the Causal Effects of T Cell Receptors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-causal-effects-of-t-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce a method to infer the causal effects of T cell receptor (TCR) sequences on patient outcomes using observational TCR repertoire sequencing data and clinical outcomes data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-the-causal-effects-of-t-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiGR: Harnessing Binary Latent Codes for Image Generation and Improved Visual Representation Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigr-harnessing-binary-latent-codes-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce BiGR, a novel conditional image generation model using compact binary latent codes for generative training, focusing on enhancing both generation and representation capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bigr-harnessing-binary-latent-codes-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tell me what I need to know: Exploring LLM-based (Personalized) Abstractive Multi-Source Meeting Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tell-me-what-i-need-to-know-exploring-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous attempts to address these issues by considering related supplementary resources (e. g., presentation slides) alongside transcripts are hindered by models' limited context sizes and handling the additional complexities of the multi-source tasks, such as identifying relevant information in additional files and seamlessly aligning it with the meeting content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tell-me-what-i-need-to-know-exploring-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Osteoporosis screening: Leveraging EfficientNet with complete and cropped facial panoramic radiography imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osteoporosis-screening-leveraging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EfficientNet B5, B6, and B7 models were trained to identify osteoporosis in both full PR images and cropped sections focusing on the mandibular cortical region.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/osteoporosis-screening-leveraging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Effective Planning Strategies for Dynamic Opinion Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-planning-strategies-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we investigate the under-explored intervention planning aimed at disseminating accurate information within dynamic opinion networks by leveraging learning strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-planning-strategies-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Deep Reinforcement Learning for Navigation in Denied Sensor Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-deep-reinforcement-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We anticipate this benchmark of different DRL methods and the usage of adversarial training to be a starting point for the development of more elaborate navigation strategies that are capable of dealing with uncertain and denied sensor readings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-deep-reinforcement-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>syren-new: Precise formulae for the linear and nonlinear matter power spectra with massive neutrinos and dynamical dark energy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syren-new-precise-formulae-for-the-linear-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to construct accurate and interpretable symbolic approximations to the linear and nonlinear matter power spectra as a function of cosmological parameters in extended $\Lambda$CDM models which contain massive neutrinos and non-constant equations of state for dark energy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syren-new-precise-formulae-for-the-linear-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REEF: Representation Encoding Fingerprints for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reef-representation-encoding-fingerprints-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, model owners and third parties need to identify whether a suspect model is a subsequent development of the victim model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reef-representation-encoding-fingerprints-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable Aperture Bokeh Rendering via Customized Focal Plane Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-aperture-bokeh-rendering-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[benchmark dataset and our constructed dataset VABD have demonstrated that the customized focal plane together aperture prompt can bootstrap model to simulate realistic bokeh effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variable-aperture-bokeh-rendering-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Large Language Models' Situated Faithfulness to External Contexts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-language-models-situated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SCR enables models to self-access the confidence of external information relative to their own internal knowledge to produce the most accurate answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-large-language-models-situated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST-MoE-BERT: A Spatial-Temporal Mixture-of-Experts Framework for Long-Term Cross-City Mobility Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-moe-bert-a-spatial-temporal-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to existing methods, our approach frames the prediction task as a spatial-temporal classification problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/st-moe-bert-a-spatial-temporal-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convergence of Manifold Filter-Combine Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-of-manifold-filter-combine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to better understand manifold neural networks (MNNs), we introduce Manifold Filter-Combine Networks (MFCNs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convergence-of-manifold-filter-combine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Faithful Natural Language Explanations: A Study Using Activation Patching in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-faithful-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are capable of generating persuasive Natural Language Explanations (NLEs) to justify their answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-faithful-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ANT: Adaptive Noise Schedule for Time Series Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-adaptive-noise-schedule-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Adaptive Noise schedule for Time series diffusion models (ANT), which automatically predetermines proper noise schedules for given TS datasets based on their statistics representing non-stationarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ant-adaptive-noise-schedule-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Systematic Study of Cross-Layer KV Sharing for Efficient LLM Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-study-of-cross-layer-kv-sharing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, sharing key-value (KV) cache across layers has been found effective in efficient inference of large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-systematic-study-of-cross-layer-kv-sharing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Almost-Linear RNNs Yield Highly Interpretable Symbolic Codes in Dynamical Systems Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/almost-linear-rnns-yield-highly-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PWL models are popular in engineering and a frequent choice in mathematics for analyzing the topological properties of DS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/almost-linear-rnns-yield-highly-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MomentumSMoE: Integrating Momentum into Sparse Mixture of Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/momentumsmoe-integrating-momentum-into-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse Mixture of Experts (SMoE) has become the key to unlocking unparalleled scalability in deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/momentumsmoe-integrating-momentum-into-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Real-Time Recalibration for Infrared Multi-Camera Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-real-time-recalibration-for-infrared</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike traditional calibration techniques that lack adaptability and struggle with on-the-fly recalibrations, we propose a neural network-based method capable of dynamic real-time calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-real-time-recalibration-for-infrared</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: Selective Reduction of CT Data for Self-Supervised Pre-Training of Deep Learning Models with Contrastive Learning Improves Downstream Classification Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-selective-reduction-of-ct-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effect of these different reduction strategies on contrastive learning is evaluated on two pre-training datasets and several downstream classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-selective-reduction-of-ct-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-Guided Residual U-Net with SE Connection and ASPP for Watershed-Based Cell Segmentation in Microscopy Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-residual-u-net-with-se</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these issues, we propose a novel framework called RA-SE-ASPP-Net, which incorporates Residual Blocks, Attention Mechanism, Squeeze-and-Excitation connection, and Atrous Spatial Pyramid Pooling to achieve precise and robust cell segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-guided-residual-u-net-with-se</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-NeuroDAVIS: A Neural Network model for generalized embedding, data visualization and sample generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-neurodavis-a-neural-network-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by this aspect, in this study, a novel generative model, called G-NeuroDAVIS, has been developed, which is capable of visualizing high-dimensional data through a generalized embedding, and thereby generating new samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/g-neurodavis-a-neural-network-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Evaluation of Clustered Federated Learning Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-evaluation-of-clustered-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore the performance of two state-of-theart CFL algorithms with respect to a proposed taxonomy of data heterogeneities in federated learning (FL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-evaluation-of-clustered-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Questions Generation: Motivation and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critical-questions-generation-motivation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The development of Large Language Models (LLMs) has brought impressive performances on mitigation strategies against misinformation, such as counterargument generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/critical-questions-generation-motivation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SurgeryV2: Bridging the Gap Between Model Merging and Multi-Task Learning with Deep Representation Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgeryv2-bridging-the-gap-between-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in this paper, we examine the merged model's representation distribution and uncover a critical issue of "representation bias".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgeryv2-bridging-the-gap-between-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlearning Backdoor Attacks for LLMs with Weak-to-Strong Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-backdoor-attacks-for-llms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, this teacher model guides the large-scale poisoned student model in unlearning the backdoor, leveraging PEFT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlearning-backdoor-attacks-for-llms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnomalyNCD: Towards Novel Anomaly Class Discovery in Industrial Scenarios</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyncd-towards-novel-anomaly-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with the current methods, AnomalyNCD combined with zero-shot anomaly detection method achieves a 10. 8% $F_1$ gain, 8. 8% NMI gain, and 9. 5% ARI gain on MVTec AD, 12. 8% $F_1$ gain, 5. 7% NMI gain, and 10. 8% ARI gain on MTD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomalyncd-towards-novel-anomaly-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape Transformation Driven by Active Contour for Class-Imbalanced Semi-Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-transformation-driven-by-active-contour</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The significant size differences among various organs in the human body lead to imbalanced class distribution, which is a major challenge in the real-world application of these SSL approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-transformation-driven-by-active-contour</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Croc: Pretraining Large Multimodal Models with Cross-Modal Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/croc-pretraining-large-multimodal-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then, we conceptualize visual tokens as analogous to a "foreign language" for the LLMs and propose a mixed attention mechanism with bidirectional visual attention and unidirectional textual attention to comprehensively enhance the understanding of visual tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/croc-pretraining-large-multimodal-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Generalizing Visual Brain Decoding to Unseen Subjects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-generalizing-visual-brain-decoding-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This dataset allows us to investigate the brain decoding performance with the increase of participants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-generalizing-visual-brain-decoding-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montessori-Instruct: Generate Influential Training Data Tailored for Student Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/montessori-instruct-generate-influential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Montessori-Instruct, a novel data synthesis framework that tailors the data synthesis ability of the teacher language model toward the student language model's learning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/montessori-instruct-generate-influential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiCo: Hierarchical Controllable Diffusion Model for Layout-to-image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hico-hierarchical-controllable-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of layout-to-image generation involves synthesizing images based on the captions of objects and their spatial positions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hico-hierarchical-controllable-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Kernel Thinning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-kernel-thinning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we generalize the KT algorithm to speed up supervised learning problems involving kernel methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-kernel-thinning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Kuramoto Oscillatory Neurons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-kuramoto-oscillatory-neurons</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has long been known in both neuroscience and AI that ``binding'' between neurons leads to a form of competitive learning where representations are compressed in order to represent more abstract concepts in deeper layers of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-kuramoto-oscillatory-neurons</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evolved Universal Transformer Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior methods propose to offset the escalating costs of modern foundation models by dropping specific parts of their contexts with hand-designed rules, while attempting to preserve their original performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
