<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:07:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CATANet: Efficient Content-Aware Token Aggregation for Lightweight Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catanet-efficient-content-aware-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SR typically leverages the redundancy of images for reconstruction, and this redundancy appears not only in local regions but also in long-range regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catanet-efficient-content-aware-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REF-VLM: Triplet-Based Referring Paradigm for Unified Visual Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-vlm-triplet-based-referring-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address complex visual decoding scenarios, we introduce the Triplet-Based Referring Paradigm (TRP), which explicitly decouples three critical dimensions in visual decoding tasks through a triplet structure: concepts, decoding types, and targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ref-vlm-triplet-based-referring-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOE: Real-Time Seeing Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yoloe-real-time-seeing-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection and segmentation are widely employed in computer vision applications, yet conventional models like YOLO series, while efficient and accurate, are limited by predefined categories, hindering adaptability in open scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yoloe-real-time-seeing-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Reusing to Forecasting: Accelerating Diffusion Models with TaylorSeers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-reusing-to-forecasting-accelerating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve this problem, feature caching has been proposed to accelerate diffusion models by caching the features in the previous timesteps and then reusing them in the following timesteps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-reusing-to-forecasting-accelerating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Anything: Any to Motion Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-anything-any-to-motion-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional motion generation has been extensively studied in computer vision, yet two critical challenges remain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-anything-any-to-motion-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepNuParc: A Novel Deep Clustering Framework for Fine-scale Parcellation of Brain Nuclei Using Diffusion MRI Tractography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepnuparc-a-novel-deep-clustering-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion MRI tractography is an advanced imaging technique that can estimate the brain's white matter structural connectivity to potentially reveal the topography of the nuclei of interest for studying its subdivisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepnuparc-a-novel-deep-clustering-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implicit Reasoning in Transformers is Reasoning through Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-reasoning-in-transformers-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-time compute is emerging as a new paradigm for enhancing language models' complex multi-step reasoning capabilities, as demonstrated by the success of OpenAI's o1 and o3, as well as DeepSeek's R1.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implicit-reasoning-in-transformers-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seg-Zero: Reasoning-Chain Guided Segmentation via Cognitive Reinforcement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-zero-reasoning-chain-guided-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods for reasoning segmentation rely on supervised fine-tuning with categorical labels and simple descriptions, limiting its out-of-domain generalization and lacking explicit reasoning processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-zero-reasoning-chain-guided-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemHiTok: A Unified Image Tokenizer via Semantic-Guided Hierarchical Codebook for Multimodal Understanding and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semhitok-a-unified-image-tokenizer-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SemHiTok, a unified image Tokenizer via Semantic-Guided Hierarchical codebook that provides consistent discrete feature representations for multimodal understanding and generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semhitok-a-unified-image-tokenizer-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emulating Self-attention with Convolution for Efficient Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emulating-self-attention-with-convolution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By utilizing the ConvAttn module, we significantly reduce the reliance on self-attention and its involved memory-bound operations while maintaining the representational capability of transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emulating-self-attention-with-convolution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Routing for Large ML Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-for-large-ml-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large language models (LLMs), and other large machine learning models, involves repeated communication of large volumes of data across a data center network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/routing-for-large-ml-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoPainter: Any-length Video Inpainting and Editing with Plug-and-Play Context Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopainter-any-length-video-inpainting-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video inpainting, which aims to restore corrupted video content, has experienced substantial progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopainter-any-length-video-inpainting-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColFigPhotoAttnNet: Reliable Finger Photo Presentation Attack Detection Leveraging Window-Attention on Color Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colfigphotoattnnet-reliable-finger-photo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finger photo Presentation Attack Detection (PAD) can significantly strengthen smartphone device security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colfigphotoattnnet-reliable-finger-photo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptPex: Automatic Test Generation for Language Model Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptpex-automatic-test-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These tests are instrumental in identifying regressions when a prompt is changed and also serve as a tool to understand how prompts are interpreted by different models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptpex-automatic-test-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnyAnomaly: Zero-Shot Customizable Video Anomaly Detection with LVLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anyanomaly-zero-shot-customizable-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, this study proposes customizable video anomaly detection (C-VAD) technique and the AnyAnomaly model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anyanomaly-zero-shot-customizable-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhiloBERTA: A Transformer-Based Cross-Lingual Analysis of Greek and Latin Lexicons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/philoberta-a-transformer-based-cross-lingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PhiloBERTA, a cross-lingual transformer model that measures semantic relationships between ancient Greek and Latin lexicons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/philoberta-a-transformer-based-cross-lingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balcony: A Lightweight Approach to Dynamic Inference of Generative Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balcony-a-lightweight-approach-to-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By freezing the pretrained LLM and inserting additional transformer layers at selected exit points, Balcony maintains the full model's performance while enabling real-time adaptation to different computational budgets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/balcony-a-lightweight-approach-to-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Question-Aware Gaussian Experts for Audio-Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-aware-gaussian-experts-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing methods mainly use question information implicitly, limiting focus on question-specific details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/question-aware-gaussian-experts-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEVDriver: Leveraging BEV Maps in LLMs for Robust Closed-Loop Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevdriver-leveraging-bev-maps-in-llms-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous driving has the potential to set the stage for more efficient future mobility, requiring the research domain to establish trust through safe, reliable and transparent driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bevdriver-leveraging-bev-maps-in-llms-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttackSeqBench: Benchmarking Large Language Models' Understanding of Sequential Patterns in Cyber Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attackseqbench-benchmarking-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The overarching goal of this work is to provide a benchmark that advances LLM-driven CTI report understanding and fosters its application in real-world cybersecurity operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attackseqbench-benchmarking-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CHOP: Mobile Operating Assistant with Constrained High-frequency Optimized Subtask Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chop-mobile-operating-assistant-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The subtask level, linking high-level goals with low-level executable actions, is crucial for task completion but faces two challenges: ineffective subtasks that lower-level agent cannot execute and inefficient subtasks that fail to contribute to the completion of the higher-level task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chop-mobile-operating-assistant-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preserving Cultural Identity with Context-Aware Translation Through Multi-Agent AI Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-cultural-identity-with-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This research underscores the potential of multi-agent AI in fostering equitable, sustainable, and culturally sensitive NLP technologies, aligning with the AI Governance, Cultural NLP, and Sustainable NLP pillars of Language Models for Underserved Communities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/preserving-cultural-identity-with-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiRe-JAX: A JAX based Dimensionality Reduction Algorithm for Large-scale Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dire-jax-a-jax-based-dimensionality-reduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DiRe - JAX is a new dimensionality reduction toolkit designed to address some of the challenges faced by traditional methods like UMAP and tSNE such as loss of global structure and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dire-jax-a-jax-based-dimensionality-reduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualising Policy-Reward Interplay to Inform Zeroth-Order Preference Optimisation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualising-policy-reward-interplay-to-inform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While it falls short of some state-of-the-art methods, our work is the first to apply Zeroth-Order methods to Preference Optimisation in LLMs, going beyond classification tasks and paving the way for a largely unexplored research direction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visualising-policy-reward-interplay-to-inform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring specialization and sensitivity of convolutional neural networks in the context of simultaneous image augmentations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-specialization-and-sensitivity-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing parallels with the way biological networks are studied, we adapt the treatment--control paradigm to explainable artificial intelligence research and enrich it through multi-parametric input alterations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-specialization-and-sensitivity-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAIR: A Novel Large Language Model-Guided Selection Strategy for Evolutionary Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pair-a-novel-large-language-model-guided</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary Algorithms (EAs) employ random or simplistic selection methods, limiting their exploration of solution spaces and convergence to optimal solutions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pair-a-novel-large-language-model-guided</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEN3C: 3D-Informed World-Consistent Video Generation with Precise Camera Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gen3c-3d-informed-world-consistent-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate more precise camera control than prior work, as well as state-of-the-art results in sparse-view novel view synthesis, even in challenging settings such as driving scenes and monocular dynamic video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gen3c-3d-informed-world-consistent-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-Based Performance Evaluation of 3D Object Detection Methods with Deep Learning for a LiDAR Point Cloud Dataset in a SOTIF-related Use Case</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-performance-evaluation-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safety of the Intended Functionality (SOTIF) addresses sensor performance limitations and deep learning-based object detection insufficiencies to ensure the intended functionality of Automated Driving Systems (ADS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-performance-evaluation-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe LLM-Controlled Robots with Formal Guarantees via Reachability Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-llm-controlled-robots-with-formal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deployment of Large Language Models (LLMs) in robotic systems presents unique safety challenges, particularly in unpredictable environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-llm-controlled-robots-with-formal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attentive Reasoning Queries: A Systematic Method for Optimizing Instruction-Following in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-reasoning-queries-a-systematic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Attentive Reasoning Queries (ARQs), a novel structured reasoning approach that significantly improves instruction-following in Large Language Models through domain-specialized reasoning blueprints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-reasoning-queries-a-systematic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State-offset Tuning: State-based Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning for State Space Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-offset-tuning-state-based-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At every timestep, our method directly affects the state at the current step, leading to more effective adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-offset-tuning-state-based-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNNMerge: Merging of GNN Models Without Accessing Training Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnnmerge-merging-of-gnn-models-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging has gained prominence in machine learning as a method to integrate multiple trained models into a single model without accessing the original training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gnnmerge-merging-of-gnn-models-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leap: Inductive Link Prediction via Learnable TopologyAugmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leap-inductive-link-prediction-via-learnable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Link prediction is a crucial task in many downstream applications of graph machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leap-inductive-link-prediction-via-learnable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving LLM Safety Alignment with Dual-Objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-llm-safety-alignment-with-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing training-time safety alignment techniques for large language models (LLMs) remain vulnerable to jailbreak attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-llm-safety-alignment-with-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnPuzzle: A Unified Framework for Pathology Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpuzzle-a-unified-framework-for-pathology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pathology image analysis plays a pivotal role in medical diagnosis, with deep learning techniques significantly advancing diagnostic accuracy and research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpuzzle-a-unified-framework-for-pathology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Synthetic-to-Real Gaps: Frequency-Aware Perturbation and Selection for Single-shot Multi-Parametric Mapping Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-synthetic-to-real-gaps-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-centric artificial intelligence (AI) has remarkably advanced medical imaging, with emerging methods using synthetic data to address data scarcity while introducing synthetic-to-real gaps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-synthetic-to-real-gaps-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4D Radar Ground Truth Augmentation with LiDAR-to-4D Radar Data Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-radar-ground-truth-augmentation-with-lidar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, directly applying GT-Aug to 4D Radar tensor data overlooks important measurements outside the GT bboxes-such as sidelobes-leading to synthetic distributions that deviate from real-world 4D Radar data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/4d-radar-ground-truth-augmentation-with-lidar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA-LoT: Multi-Agent Lean-based Long Chain-of-Thought Reasoning enhances Formal Theorem Proving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-lot-multi-agent-lean-based-long-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To solve these issues, we propose MA-LoT: Multi-Agent Lean-based Long Chain-of-Thought framework, (to the best of our knowledge), the first multi-agent framework for Lean4 theorem proving that balance high-level NL reasoning and FL verification in Long CoT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-lot-multi-agent-lean-based-long-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intermediate Domain-guided Adaptation for Unsupervised Chorioallantoic Membrane Vessel Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intermediate-domain-guided-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, research on CAM vessel segmentation algorithms remains limited, and the lack of public datasets contributes to poor prediction performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/intermediate-domain-guided-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CURVALID: Geometrically-guided Adversarial Prompt Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvalid-geometrically-guided-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial prompts capable of jailbreaking large language models (LLMs) and inducing undesirable behaviours pose a significant obstacle to their safe deployment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvalid-geometrically-guided-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Enabled Conversational Journaling for Advancing Parkinson's Disease Symptom Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-enabled-conversational-journaling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Journaling plays a crucial role in managing chronic conditions by allowing patients to document symptoms and medication intake, providing essential data for long-term care.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ai-enabled-conversational-journaling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEAL: Safety Enhanced Trajectory Planning and Control Framework for Quadrotor Flight in Complex Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-safety-enhanced-trajectory-planning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of dynamic obstacles would further worsen the situation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seal-safety-enhanced-trajectory-planning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biased Heritage: How Datasets Shape Models in Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biased-heritage-how-datasets-shape-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the rapid development of artificial intelligence (AI) systems has raised concerns about our ability to ensure their fairness, that is, how to avoid discrimination based on protected characteristics such as gender, race, or age.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biased-heritage-how-datasets-shape-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DongbaMIE: A Multimodal Information Extraction Dataset for Evaluating Semantic Understanding of Dongba Pictograms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dongbamie-a-multimodal-information-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose DongbaMIE, the first multimodal dataset for semantic understanding and extraction of Dongba pictographs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dongbamie-a-multimodal-information-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-DoF Egomotion Estimation for Event Cameras Using Geometric Solvers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-dof-egomotion-estimation-for-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the possibility of recovering full-DoF egomotion parameters for both angular and linear velocities without requiring extra sensor measurements or motion priors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-dof-egomotion-estimation-for-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Quality Virtual Single-Viewpoint Surgical Video: Geometric Autocalibration of Multiple Cameras in Surgical Lights</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-quality-virtual-single-viewpoint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This algorithm results in a stabilized video with less occlusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-quality-virtual-single-viewpoint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoSDH: Communication-Efficient Collaborative Perception via Supply-Demand Awareness and Intermediate-Late Hybridization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosdh-communication-efficient-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-agent collaborative perception enhances perceptual capabilities by utilizing information from multiple agents and is considered a fundamental solution to the problem of weak single-vehicle perception in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosdh-communication-efficient-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Effective and Sparse Adversarial Attack on Spiking Neural Networks via Breaking Invisible Surrogate Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-and-sparse-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce an innovative potential-dependent surrogate gradient (PDSG) method to establish a robust connection between the SG and the model, thereby enhancing the adaptability of adversarial attacks across various models with invisible SGs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-effective-and-sparse-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP is Strong Enough to Fight Back: Test-time Counterattacks towards Zero-shot Adversarial Robustness of CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-is-strong-enough-to-fight-back-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our paradigm is simple and training-free, providing the first method to defend CLIP from adversarial attacks at test time, which is orthogonal to existing methods aiming to boost zero-shot adversarial robustness of CLIP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-is-strong-enough-to-fight-back-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing for the Shortest Path in Denoising Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-for-the-shortest-path-in-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research, we propose a novel denoising diffusion model based on shortest-path modeling that optimizes residual propagation to enhance both denoising efficiency and quality. Drawing on Denoising Diffusion Implicit Models (DDIM) and insights from graph theory, our model, termed the Shortest Path Diffusion Model (ShortDF), treats the denoising process as a shortest-path problem aimed at minimizing reconstruction error.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-for-the-shortest-path-in-denoising</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
