<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 21:06:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Boundary Discretization and Reliable Classification Network for Temporal Action Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-discretization-and-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the boundary discretization module (BDM) elegantly merges anchor-based and anchor-free approaches in the form of boundary discretization, avoiding the handcrafted anchors design required by traditional mixed methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boundary-discretization-and-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MemSum-DQA: Adapting An Efficient Long Document Extractive Summarizer for Document Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memsum-dqa-adapting-an-efficient-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce MemSum-DQA, an efficient system for document question answering (DQA) that leverages MemSum, a long document extractive summarizer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memsum-dqa-adapting-an-efficient-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Knowledge Graph Transformer Framework for Multi-Modal Entity Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-knowledge-graph-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a novel MMEA transformer, called MoAlign, that hierarchically introduces neighbor features, multi-modal attributes, and entity types to enhance the alignment task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-knowledge-graph-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfoCL: Alleviating Catastrophic Forgetting in Continual Text Classification from An Information Theoretic Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infocl-alleviating-catastrophic-forgetting-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual learning (CL) aims to constantly learn new knowledge over time while avoiding catastrophic forgetting on old tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infocl-alleviating-catastrophic-forgetting-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Pose-Guided Image Synthesis with Progressive Conditional Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-pose-guided-image-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in the first stage, we design a simple prior conditional diffusion model that predicts the global features of the target image by mining the global alignment relationship between pose coordinates and image appearance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-pose-guided-image-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Adaptation of Large Vision Transformer via Adapter Re-Composing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-adaptation-of-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Consequently, effectively adapting large pre-trained models to downstream tasks in an efficient manner has become a prominent research area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-adaptation-of-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SUBP: Soft Uniform Block Pruning for 1xN Sparse CNNs Multithreading Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subp-soft-uniform-block-pruning-for-1xn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome them, this paper proposes a novel \emph{\textbf{S}oft \textbf{U}niform \textbf{B}lock \textbf{P}runing} (SUBP) approach to train a uniform 1$\times$N sparse structured network from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subp-soft-uniform-block-pruning-for-1xn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing AI Algorithms for Optimizing Elliptic Curve Cryptography Parameters in Third-Party E-Commerce Integrations: A Pre-Quantum Era Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-ai-algorithms-for-optimizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a comparative analysis between the Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Particle Swarm Optimization (PSO), two vital artificial intelligence algorithms, focusing on optimizing Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC) parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-ai-algorithms-for-optimizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What If the TV Was Off? Examining Counterfactual Reasoning Abilities of Multi-modal Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-if-the-tv-was-off-examining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on benchmarking the counterfactual reasoning ability of multi-modal large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-if-the-tv-was-off-examining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Mask2Former: Panoptic Segmentation of Crops, Weeds and Leaves</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-mask2former-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We achieve a PQ{\dag} of 75. 99.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-mask2former-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REVO-LION: Evaluating and Refining Vision-Language Instruction Tuning Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revo-lion-evaluating-and-refining-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of evaluating the models directly, in this paper we try to evaluate the Vision-Language Instruction-Tuning (VLIT) datasets themselves and further seek the way of building a dataset for developing an all-powerful VLIT model, which we believe could also be of utility for establishing a grounded protocol for benchmarking VLIT models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revo-lion-evaluating-and-refining-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Be Careful What You Smooth For: Label Smoothing Can Be a Privacy Shield but Also a Catalyst for Model Inversion Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-careful-what-you-smooth-for-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Label smoothing -- using softened labels instead of hard ones -- is a widely adopted regularization method for deep learning, showing diverse benefits such as enhanced generalization and calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/be-careful-what-you-smooth-for-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S4Sleep: Elucidating the design space of deep-learning-based sleep stage classification models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s4sleep-elucidating-the-design-space-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scoring sleep stages in polysomnography recordings is a time-consuming task plagued by significant inter-rater variability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s4sleep-elucidating-the-design-space-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Embeddings Reveal (Almost) As Much As Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-embeddings-reveal-almost-as-much-as-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How much private information do text embeddings reveal about the original text?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-embeddings-reveal-almost-as-much-as-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Administrative Data Inventories to Create a Reliable Transnational Reference Database for Crop Type Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-administrative-data-inventories-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With leaps in machine learning techniques and their applicationon Earth observation challenges has unlocked unprecedented performance across the domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-administrative-data-inventories-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepLSH: Deep Locality-Sensitive Hash Learning for Fast and Efficient Near-Duplicate Crash Report Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplsh-deep-locality-sensitive-hash-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is indeed not trivial to derive hash functions that satisfy the so-called locality-sensitive property for the most advanced crash bucketing metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplsh-deep-locality-sensitive-hash-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep reinforcement learning uncovers processes for separating azeotropic mixtures without prior knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-uncovers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning agents, trained without prior knowledge, have shown to outperform humans in various complex planning problems in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-reinforcement-learning-uncovers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rationale-Enhanced Language Models are Better Continual Relation Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rationale-enhanced-language-models-are-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Continual relation extraction (CRE) aims to solve the problem of catastrophic forgetting when learning a sequence of newly emerging relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rationale-enhanced-language-models-are-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging Diffusion-Based Image Variations for Robust Training on Poisoned Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-diffusion-based-image-variations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a novel approach that enables model training on potentially poisoned datasets by utilizing the power of recent diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leveraging-diffusion-based-image-variations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Model Selection and Decoding for Keyphrase Generation with Pre-trained Sequence-to-Sequence Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-model-selection-and-decoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From our insights, we propose DeSel, a likelihood-based decode-select algorithm that improves greedy search by an average of 4. 7% semantic F1 across five datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-model-selection-and-decoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Contrastive Learning Method for Clickbait Detection on RoCliCo: A Romanian Clickbait Corpus of News Articles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-contrastive-learning-method-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the importance of the task, to the best of our knowledge, there is no publicly available clickbait corpus for the Romanian language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-contrastive-learning-method-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-CoT: Generalizable Chain-of-Thought Prompting in Mixed-task Scenarios with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-cot-generalizable-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have unveiled remarkable reasoning capabilities by exploiting chain-of-thought (CoT) prompting, which generates intermediate reasoning chains to serve as the rationale for deriving the answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-cot-generalizable-chain-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisit Input Perturbation Problems for LLMs: A Unified Robustness Evaluation Framework for Noisy Slot Filling Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-input-perturbation-problems-for-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a unified robustness evaluation framework based on the slot-filling task to systematically evaluate the dialogue understanding capability of LLMs in diverse input perturbation scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisit-input-perturbation-problems-for-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoinSeg: Contrast Inter- and Intra- Class Representations for Incremental Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coinseg-contrast-inter-and-intra-class-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most state-of-the-art methods use the freeze strategy for stability, which compromises the model's plasticity. In contrast, releasing parameter training for plasticity could lead to the best performance for all categories, but this requires discriminative feature representation. Therefore, we prioritize the model's plasticity and propose the Contrast inter- and intra-class representations for Incremental Segmentation (CoinSeg), which pursues discriminative representations for flexible parameter tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coinseg-contrast-inter-and-intra-class-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BridgeHand2Vec Bridge Hand Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridgehand2vec-bridge-hand-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contract bridge is a game characterized by incomplete information, posing an exciting challenge for artificial intelligence methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridgehand2vec-bridge-hand-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variance Reduced Online Gradient Descent for Kernelized Pairwise Learning with Limited Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduced-online-gradient-descent-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we establish a clear connection between the variance of online gradients and the regret, and construct online gradients using the most recent stratified samples with a limited buffer of size of $s$ representing all past data, which have a complexity of $O(sT)$ and employs $O(\sqrt{T}\log{T})$ random Fourier features for kernel approximation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduced-online-gradient-descent-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral 7B</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mistral-7b</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Mistral 7B v0. 1, a 7-billion-parameter language model engineered for superior performance and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mistral-7b</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Propaganda Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-propaganda</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate the models' performance by assessing metrics such as $F1$ score, $Precision$, and $Recall$, comparing the results with the current state-of-the-art approach using RoBERTa.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-propaganda</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3DS-SLAM: A 3D Object Detection based Semantic SLAM towards Dynamic Indoor Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ds-slam-a-3d-object-detection-based-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We designed a 3D part-aware hybrid transformer for point cloud-based object detection to identify dynamic objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3ds-slam-a-3d-object-detection-based-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lo-Hi: Practical ML Drug Discovery Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lo-hi-practical-ml-drug-discovery-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyzed modern benchmarks and showed that they are unrealistic and overoptimistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lo-hi-practical-ml-drug-discovery-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retromorphic Testing: A New Approach to the Test Oracle Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retromorphic-testing-a-new-approach-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the mathematical concept of inverse function, we present Retromorphic Testing, a novel black-box testing methodology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retromorphic-testing-a-new-approach-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Transformer's Capabilities in Commonsense Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-transformer-s-capabilities-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim to bridge the gap by introducing current ML-based methods to improve general purpose pre-trained language models in the task of commonsense reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-transformer-s-capabilities-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni3D: Exploring Unified 3D Representation at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3d-exploring-unified-3d-representation-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scaling up representations for images or text has been extensively investigated in the past few years and has led to revolutions in learning vision and language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3d-exploring-unified-3d-representation-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Robustness in Graph Neural Networks: A Hamiltonian Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustness-in-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) are vulnerable to adversarial perturbations, including those that affect both node features and graph topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustness-in-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P5: Plug-and-Play Persona Prompting for Personalized Response Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p5-plug-and-play-persona-prompting-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our system can function as a standard open-domain chatbot if persona information is not available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p5-plug-and-play-persona-prompting-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdRec: 3D Crowd Reconstruction from Single Color Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdrec-3d-crowd-reconstruction-from-single</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To promote a more reasonable spatial distribution, we further propose a crowd constraint to refine the single-person network parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crowdrec-3d-crowd-reconstruction-from-single</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filter Pruning For CNN With Enhanced Linear Representation Redundancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-pruning-for-cnn-with-enhanced-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new structured pruning method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filter-pruning-for-cnn-with-enhanced-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We are what we repeatedly do: Inducing and deploying habitual schemas in persona-based responses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-are-what-we-repeatedly-do-inducing-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We capture such habitual knowledge using an explicit schema representation, and propose an approach to dialogue generation that retrieves relevant schemas to condition a large language model to generate persona-based responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-are-what-we-repeatedly-do-inducing-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TopoMLP: An Simple yet Strong Pipeline for Driving Topology Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topomlp-an-simple-yet-strong-pipeline-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we propose TopoMLP, a simple yet high-performance pipeline for driving topology reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topomlp-an-simple-yet-strong-pipeline-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geographic Location Encoding with Spherical Harmonics and Sinusoidal Representation Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geographic-location-encoding-with-spherical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a novel location encoder for globally distributed geographic data that combines spherical harmonic basis functions, natively defined on spherical surfaces, with sinusoidal representation networks (SirenNets) that can be interpreted as learned Double Fourier Sphere embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geographic-location-encoding-with-spherical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whispering LLaMA: A Cross-Modal Generative Error Correction Framework for Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whispering-llama-a-cross-modal-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new cross-modal fusion technique designed for generative error correction in automatic speech recognition (ASR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whispering-llama-a-cross-modal-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FABind: Fast and Accurate Protein-Ligand Binding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fabind-fast-and-accurate-protein-ligand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose $\mathbf{FABind}$, an end-to-end model that combines pocket prediction and docking to achieve accurate and fast protein-ligand binding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fabind-fast-and-accurate-protein-ligand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Impact of a Supervised Classification Filter on Flow-based Hybrid Network Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-impact-of-a-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We perform our experiments by employing a hybrid anomaly detection approach in network flow data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-impact-of-a-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporally Aligning Long Audio Interviews with Questions: A Case Study in Multimodal Data Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-aligning-long-audio-interviews</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of audio-to-text alignment has seen significant amount of research using complete supervision during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-aligning-long-audio-interviews</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lemur: Harmonizing Natural Language and Code for Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemur-harmonizing-natural-language-and-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Lemur and Lemur-Chat, openly accessible language models optimized for both natural language and coding capabilities to serve as the backbone of versatile language agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lemur-harmonizing-natural-language-and-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking PointNet: Spiking Neural Networks for Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-pointnet-spiking-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discover that the two huge obstacles limiting the application of SNNs in point clouds are: the intrinsic optimization obstacle of SNNs that impedes the training of a big spiking model with large time steps, and the expensive memory and computation cost of PointNet that makes training a big spiking point model unrealistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-pointnet-spiking-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRACE: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Continual Learning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trace-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce TRACE, a novel benchmark designed to evaluate continual learning in LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trace-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>V2X-AHD:Vehicle-to-Everything Cooperation Perception via Asymmetric Heterogenous Distillation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-ahd-vehicle-to-everything-cooperation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The V2X-AHD can effectively improve the accuracy of 3D object detection and reduce the number of network parameters, according to this study, which serves as a benchmark for cooperative perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/v2x-ahd-vehicle-to-everything-cooperation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DockGame: Cooperative Games for Multimeric Rigid Protein Docking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dockgame-cooperative-games-for-multimeric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most traditional and deep learning methods for docking have focused mainly on binary docking, following either a search-based, regression-based, or generative modeling paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dockgame-cooperative-games-for-multimeric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Scalable Meta Learning Practical</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-scalable-meta-learning-practical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its flexibility to learn diverse inductive biases in machine learning programs, meta learning (i. e., learning to learn) has long been recognized to suffer from poor scalability due to its tremendous compute/memory costs, training instability, and a lack of efficient distributed training support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-scalable-meta-learning-practical</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
