<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 09:14:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic bSDD: Improving the GraphQL, JSON and RDF Representations of buildingSmart Data Dictionary</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-bsdd-improving-the-graphql-json-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The buildingSmart Data Dictionary (bSDD) is an important shared resource in the Architecture, Engineering, Construction, and Operations (AECO) domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-bsdd-improving-the-graphql-json-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Binary domain generalization for sparsifying binary neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binary-domain-generalization-for-sparsifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Binary neural networks (BNNs) are an attractive solution for developing and deploying deep neural network (DNN)-based applications in resource constrained devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binary-domain-generalization-for-sparsifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Paradigm for Generative Adversarial Networks based on Randomized Decision Rules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-paradigm-for-generative-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the new formulation, the discriminator converges to a fixed point while the generator converges to a distribution at the Nash equilibrium.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-paradigm-for-generative-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Online Processing with Deep Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-online-processing-with-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The capabilities and adoption of deep neural networks (DNNs) grow at an exhilarating pace: Vision models accurately classify human actions in videos and identify cancerous tissue in medical scans as precisely than human experts; large language models answer wide-ranging questions, generate code, and write prose, becoming the topic of everyday dinner-table conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-online-processing-with-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing the Efficacy of Fine-Tuning and Meta-Learning for Few-Shot Policy Imitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-the-efficacy-of-fine-tuning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its simplicity this baseline is competitive with meta-learning methods on a variety of conditions and is able to imitate target policies trained on unseen variations of the original environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparing-the-efficacy-of-fine-tuning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Descriptive Image Captioning via Semipermeable Maximum Likelihood Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-descriptive-image-captioning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For instance, when the model predicts a word expressing richer semantics than the label, it will be penalized and optimized to prefer more concise expressions, referred to as conciseness optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-descriptive-image-captioning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Convergence Rate of Gaussianization with Random Rotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-convergence-rate-of-gaussianization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussianization is a simple generative model that can be trained without backpropagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-convergence-rate-of-gaussianization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FPGA Implementation of Convolutional Neural Network for Real-Time Handwriting Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fpga-implementation-of-convolutional-neural-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning (ML) has recently been a skyrocketing field in Computer Science.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fpga-implementation-of-convolutional-neural-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-Constraint Recurrent Flow for 6D Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-constraint-recurrent-flow-for-6d-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a shape-constraint recurrent matching framework for 6D object pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-constraint-recurrent-flow-for-6d-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Own Data! Self-Supervised Evaluation for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-your-own-data-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rise of Large Language Models (LLMs) and their ubiquitous deployment in diverse domains, measuring language model behavior on realistic data is imperative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bring-your-own-data-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Robustness Certification for Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustness-certification-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the problem of certifying the robustness of Bayesian neural networks (BNNs) to adversarial input perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-robustness-certification-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Large Language Model (MLLM) recently has been a new rising research hotspot, which uses powerful Large Language Models (LLMs) as a brain to perform multimodal tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProRes: Exploring Degradation-aware Visual Prompt for Universal Image Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prores-exploring-degradation-aware-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then leverage degradation-aware visual prompts to establish a controllable and universal model for image restoration, called ProRes, which is applicable to an extensive range of image restoration tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prores-exploring-degradation-aware-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling MLPs: A Tale of Inductive Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-mlps-a-tale-of-inductive-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the performance of MLPs drastically improves with scale (93% on CIFAR10, 79% on CIFAR100, 69% on TinyImageNet), highlighting that lack of inductive bias can indeed be compensated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-mlps-a-tale-of-inductive-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation and Tracking of Vegetable Plants by Exploiting Vegetable Shape Feature for Precision Spray of Agricultural Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-and-tracking-of-vegetable-plants</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Regarding the robust tracking of vegetable plants, to solve the challenging problem of associating vegetables with similar color and texture in consecutive images, in this paper, a novel method of Multiple Object Tracking and Segmentation (MOTS) is proposed for instance segmentation and tracking of multiple vegetable plants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segmentation-and-tracking-of-vegetable-plants</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MME: A Comprehensive Evaluation Benchmark for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mme-a-comprehensive-evaluation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Large Language Model (MLLM) relies on the powerful LLM to perform multimodal tasks, showing amazing emergent abilities in recent studies, such as writing poems based on an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mme-a-comprehensive-evaluation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightGlue: Local Feature Matching at Light Speed</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightglue-local-feature-matching-at-light</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LightGlue, a deep neural network that learns to match local features across images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightglue-local-feature-matching-at-light</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Penalty Gradient Normalization for Generative Adversarial Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penalty-gradient-normalization-for-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel normalization method called penalty gradient normalization (PGN) to tackle the training instability of Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) caused by the sharp gradient space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/penalty-gradient-normalization-for-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MI-Motion Dataset and Benchmark for 3D Multi-Person Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mi-motion-dataset-and-benchmark-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We believe that the proposed MI-Motion benchmark dataset and baseline will facilitate future research in this area, ultimately leading to better understanding and modeling of multi-person interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mi-motion-dataset-and-benchmark-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding quantum machine learning also requires rethinking generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-quantum-machine-learning-also</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, through systematic randomization experiments, we show that traditional approaches to understanding generalization fail to explain the behavior of such quantum models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-quantum-machine-learning-also</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutually Guided Few-shot Learning for Relational Triple Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutually-guided-few-shot-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our method consists of an entity-guided relation proto-decoder to classify the relations firstly and a relation-guided entity proto-decoder to extract entities based on the classified relations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutually-guided-few-shot-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WBCAtt: A White Blood Cell Dataset Annotated with Detailed Morphological Attributes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wbcatt-a-white-blood-cell-dataset-annotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then annotated ten thousand WBC images with these attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wbcatt-a-white-blood-cell-dataset-annotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Torsion Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torsion-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This demonstrates that analytic torsion is a highly efficient topological invariant in the characterization of graph structures and can significantly boost the performance of GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/torsion-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Log-Cumulant Based Estimation of Roughness Information in SAR imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-log-cumulant-based-estimation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic Aperture Radar (SAR) image understanding is crucial in remote sensing applications, but it is hindered by its intrinsic noise contamination, called speckle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-log-cumulant-based-estimation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Image Cleaning using Budget-Aware Black-Box Approximation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-image-cleaning-using-budget-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose two sample selection algorithms to train an OCR preprocessor with less than 10% of the original system's OCR engine queries, resulting in more than 60% reduction of the total training time without significant loss of accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-image-cleaning-using-budget-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ladder Fine-tuning approach for SAM integrating complementary network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladder-fine-tuning-approach-for-sam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently, ongoing research focuses on exploring the effective utilization of these generalized models for specific domains, such as medical imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ladder-fine-tuning-approach-for-sam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-Resolution of BVOC Emission Maps Via Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-of-bvoc-emission-maps-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our work, we aim at super-resolving low resolution emission maps derived from satellite observations by leveraging the information of emission maps obtained through numerical simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-resolution-of-bvoc-emission-maps-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftGPT: Learn Goal-oriented Soft Object Manipulation Skills by Generative Pre-trained Heterogeneous Graph Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softgpt-learn-goal-oriented-soft-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Soft object manipulation tasks in domestic scenes pose a significant challenge for existing robotic skill learning techniques due to their complex dynamics and variable shape characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softgpt-learn-goal-oriented-soft-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Semantic Segmentation: Strong Adversarial Attacks and Fast Training of Robust Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semantic-segmentation-strong</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While a large amount of work has focused on designing adversarial attacks against image classifiers, only a few methods exist to attack semantic segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semantic-segmentation-strong</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xSIM++: An Improved Proxy to Bitext Mining Performance for Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsim-an-improved-proxy-to-bitext-mining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In comparison to xSIM, we show that xSIM++ is better correlated with the downstream BLEU scores of translation systems trained on mined bitexts, providing a reliable proxy of bitext mining performance without needing to run expensive bitext mining pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xsim-an-improved-proxy-to-bitext-mining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of Robust and Multilingual Automatic Evaluation Metrics for Open-Domain Dialogue Systems at DSTC 11 Track 4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-robust-and-multilingual-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent and fast development of neural networks have revolutionized the research on dialogue systems and subsequently have triggered various challenges regarding their automatic evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-robust-and-multilingual-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Global Narratives: A Multilingual Twitter Dataset of News Media on the Russo-Ukrainian Conflict</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-global-narratives-a-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ongoing Russo-Ukrainian conflict has been a subject of intense media coverage worldwide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unveiling-global-narratives-a-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the use of the Gram matrix for multivariate functional principal components analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-the-gram-matrix-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dimension reduction is crucial in functional data analysis (FDA).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-of-the-gram-matrix-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HypeRS: Building a Hypergraph-driven ensemble Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypers-building-a-hypergraph-driven-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel ensemble recommender system that combines predictions made by different models into a unified hypergraph ranking framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypers-building-a-hypergraph-driven-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fitted Value Iteration Methods for Bicausal Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitted-value-iteration-methods-for-bicausal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a fitted value iteration (FVI) method to compute bicausal optimal transport (OT) where couplings have an adapted structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fitted-value-iteration-methods-for-bicausal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Discrimination in Insurance with Wasserstein Barycenters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-discrimination-in-insurance-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given that such discrimination can often be attributed to historical data biases, an elimination or at least mitigation is desirable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-discrimination-in-insurance-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AugDMC: Data Augmentation Guided Deep Multiple Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augdmc-data-augmentation-guided-deep-multiple</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thereafter, multiple clusterings based on different aspects of the data can be obtained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augdmc-data-augmentation-guided-deep-multiple</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Affine Correspondences between Multi-Camera Systems for Relative Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affine-correspondences-between-multi-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel method to compute the relative pose of multi-camera systems using two affine correspondences (ACs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/affine-correspondences-between-multi-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly accurate and efficient deep learning paradigm for full-atom protein loop modeling with KarmaLoop</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-accurate-and-efficient-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein loop modeling is the most challenging yet highly non-trivial task in protein structure prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/highly-accurate-and-efficient-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squeeze, Recover and Relabel: Dataset Condensation at ImageNet Scale From A New Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-recover-and-relabel-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new dataset condensation framework termed Squeeze, Recover and Relabel (SRe$^2$L) that decouples the bilevel optimization of model and synthetic data during training, to handle varying scales of datasets, model architectures and image resolutions for effective dataset condensation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/squeeze-recover-and-relabel-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identifying and Extracting Rare Disease Phenotypes with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-and-extracting-rare-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite this, ChatGPT achieved similar or higher accuracy for certain entities (i. e., rare diseases and signs) in the one-shot setting (F1 of 0. 776 and 0. 725).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identifying-and-extracting-rare-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Word Models to World Models: Translating from Natural Language to the Probabilistic Language of Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-word-models-to-world-models-translating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our architecture integrates two computational tools that have not previously come together: we model thinking with probabilistic programs, an expressive representation for commonsense reasoning; and we model meaning construction with large language models (LLMs), which support broad-coverage translation from natural language utterances to code expressions in a probabilistic programming language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-word-models-to-world-models-translating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Solution of Portfolio Optimization Problems via Dimension Reduction and Sparsification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-solution-of-portfolio-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The size reduction is based on predictions from machine learning techniques and the solution to a linear programming problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-solution-of-portfolio-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Scale-Up ExpansionIoU and Deep Features Association for Multi-Object Tracking in Sports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-scale-up-expansioniou-and-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to this reason, we proposed a novel online and robust multi-object tracking approach, named Iterative Scale-Up ExpansionIoU and Deep Features for multi-object tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-scale-up-expansioniou-and-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Knowledge Switching for Pancreas Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-knowledge-switching-for-pancreas</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pancreas segmentation is challenging due to the small proportion and highly changeable anatomical structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-knowledge-switching-for-pancreas</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating SNN Training with Stochastic Parallelizable Spiking Neurons</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-snn-training-with-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the Stochastic Parallelizable Spiking Neuron (SPSN) to overcome the sequential training limitation of LIF neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-snn-training-with-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class-Incremental Learning based on Label Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-learning-based-on-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the great success of pre-trained language models, it is still a challenge to use these models for continual learning, especially for the class-incremental learning (CIL) setting due to catastrophic forgetting (CF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-learning-based-on-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evading Forensic Classifiers with Attribute-Conditioned Adversarial Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-forensic-classifiers-with-attribute-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While these forensic models can detect whether a face image is synthetic or real with high accuracy, they are also vulnerable to adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evading-forensic-classifiers-with-attribute-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pruning for Better Domain Generalizability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pruning-for-better-domain-generalizability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On DomainBed benchmark and state-of-the-art MIRO, we can further boost its performance by 1 point only by introducing 10% sparsity into the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pruning-for-better-domain-generalizability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1st Place Solution to MultiEarth 2023 Challenge on Multimodal SAR-to-EO Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-to-multiearth-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Multimodal Learning for Earth and Environment Workshop (MultiEarth 2023) aims to harness the substantial amount of remote sensing data gathered over extensive periods for the monitoring and analysis of Earth's ecosystems'health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1st-place-solution-to-multiearth-2023</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
