<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 21:08:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Opening the Black Box of 3D Reconstruction Error Analysis with VECTOR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-of-3d-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We report on how this tool was used to debug and improve terrain reconstruction for the Mars 2020 mission.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opening-the-black-box-of-3d-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Non-Native Language Context Limitation: Native Language Prompting Facilitates Knowledge Elicitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-non-native-language-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multilingual large language models (MLLMs) struggle to answer questions posed in non-dominant languages, even though they have already acquired the relevant knowledge from their dominant language corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-non-native-language-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgformer: Surgical Transformer with Hierarchical Temporal Attention for Surgical Phase Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgformer-surgical-transformer-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we propose a novel Hierarchical Temporal Attention (HTA) to capture both global and local information within varied temporal resolutions from a target frame-centric perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgformer-surgical-transformer-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Multimodal Large Language Models with Quantization-Aware Scale Learning for Efficient Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method is grounded in two key innovations: (1) The learning of group-wise scale factors for quantized LLM weights to mitigate the quantization error arising from activation outliers and achieve more effective vision-language instruction tuning; (2) The implementation of a multimodal warmup that progressively integrates linguistic and multimodal training samples, thereby preventing overfitting of the quantized model to multimodal data while ensuring stable adaptation of multimodal large language models to downstream vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodexGraph: Bridging Large Language Models and Code Repositories via Code Graph Databases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codexgraph-bridging-large-language-models-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Similarity-based retrieval often has low recall in complex tasks, while manual tools and APIs are typically task-specific and require expert knowledge, reducing their generalizability across diverse code tasks and real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codexgraph-bridging-large-language-models-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM2-PATH: A better segment anything model for semantic segmentation in digital pathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2-path-a-better-segment-anything-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The semantic segmentation task in pathology plays an indispensable role in assisting physicians in determining the condition of tissue lesions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam2-path-a-better-segment-anything-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FacialPulse: An Efficient RNN-based Depression Detection via Temporal Facial Landmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facialpulse-an-efficient-rnn-based-depression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depression is a prevalent mental health disorder that significantly impacts individuals' lives and well-being.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facialpulse-an-efficient-rnn-based-depression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Reproducible Analysis of Sequential Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-analysis-of-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging sequential data, SRSs can identify temporal patterns in user behaviour, significantly improving recommendation accuracy and relevance. Ensuring the reproducibility of these models is paramount for advancing research and facilitating comparisons between them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reproducible-analysis-of-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pick of the Bunch: Detecting Infrared Small Targets Beyond Hit-Miss Trade-Offs via Selective Rank-Aware Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-of-the-bunch-detecting-infrared-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Infrared small target detection faces the inherent challenge of precisely localizing dim targets amidst complex background clutter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pick-of-the-bunch-detecting-infrared-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-MASSIVE: A Multilingual Speech Dataset for SLU and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-massive-a-multilingual-speech-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Speech-MASSIVE, a multilingual Spoken Language Understanding (SLU) dataset comprising the speech counterpart for a portion of the MASSIVE textual corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-massive-a-multilingual-speech-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Generation Scheme for Thermal Modality with Edge-Guided Adversarial Conditional Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-generation-scheme-for-thermal-modality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework aims to produce meticulously aligned pseudo thermal images at the pixel level, leveraging edge information extracted from visible images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-generation-scheme-for-thermal-modality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayes-optimal learning of an extensive-width neural network from quadratically many samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayes-optimal-learning-of-an-extensive-width</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of learning a target function corresponding to a single hidden layer neural network, with a quadratic activation function after the first layer, and random weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayes-optimal-learning-of-an-extensive-width</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NACL: A General and Effective KV Cache Eviction Framework for LLMs at Inference Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nacl-a-general-and-effective-kv-cache</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have ignited an innovative surge of AI applications, marking a new era of exciting possibilities equipped with extended context windows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nacl-a-general-and-effective-kv-cache</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUI Element Detection Using SOTA YOLO Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gui-element-detection-using-sota-yolo-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detection of Graphical User Interface (GUI) elements is a crucial task for automatic code generation from images and sketches, GUI testing, and GUI search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gui-element-detection-using-sota-yolo-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5-Pints Technical Report: Pretraining in Days, Not Months -- Your Language Model Thrives on Quality Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1-5-pints-technical-report-pretraining-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a compute-efficient approach to pre-training a Language Model-the "1. 5-Pints"-in only 9 days, while outperforming state-of-the-art models as an instruction-following assistant. Based on MT-Bench (a benchmark that emulates human judgments), 1. 5-Pints outperforms Apple's OpenELM and Microsoft's Phi. This is achieved by a carefully curated pre-training dataset of 57 billion tokens, using a mix of automated workflows and manual human review.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/1-5-pints-technical-report-pretraining-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeeManc at the PLABA Track of TAC-2023: Investigating LLMs and Controllable Attributes for Improving Biomedical Text Readability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beemanc-at-the-plaba-track-of-tac-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the official human evaluation, our model BART-w-CTs ranks 2nd on Sentence-Simplicity (score 92. 84), 3rd on Term-Simplicity (score 82. 33) among all 7 evaluated systems; It also produced a high score 91. 57 on Fluency in comparison to the highest score 93. 53.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beemanc-at-the-plaba-track-of-tac-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time is Not Enough: Time-Frequency based Explanation for Time-Series Black-Box Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-is-not-enough-time-frequency-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct extensive experiments in the generated synthetic dataset and various UCR Time-Series datasets to first compare the explanation performance of FIA and other existing perturbation-based XAI methods in both time-domain and time-frequency domain, and then show the superiority of our FIA in the time-frequency domain with the SpectralX framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-is-not-enough-time-frequency-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Contrastive Learning via Batch Instance Discrimination and Feature Clustering for Small Sample SAR ATR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-contrastive-learning-via-batch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Technically, instance labels are assigned to the unlabeled data in per batch and random augmentation and training are performed few times on these augmented data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-contrastive-learning-via-batch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAS-ViT: Convolutional Additive Self-attention Vision Transformers for Efficient Mobile Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cas-vit-convolutional-additive-self-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce CAS-ViT: Convolutional Additive Self-attention Vision Transformers, to achieve a balance between efficiency and performance in mobile applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cas-vit-convolutional-additive-self-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D2Styler: Advancing Arbitrary Style Transfer with Discrete Diffusion Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2styler-advancing-arbitrary-style-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This makes it easy to move features from the style image to the content image without bias.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/d2styler-advancing-arbitrary-style-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relevance meets Diversity: A User-Centric Framework for Knowledge Exploration through Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relevance-meets-diversity-a-user-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use diversity as a surrogate of the amount of knowledge obtained by the user while interacting with the system, and we seek to maximize diversity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relevance-meets-diversity-a-user-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Long-Context Language Models Better Multi-Hop Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03246</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in long-context modeling have enhanced language models (LMs) for complex tasks across multiple NLP applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03246</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StructEval: Deepen and Broaden Large Language Model Assessment via Structured Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03281</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation is the baton for the development of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03281</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BodySLAM: A Generalized Monocular Visual SLAM Framework for Surgical Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bodyslam-a-generalized-monocular-visual-slam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Endoscopic surgery relies on two-dimensional views, posing challenges for surgeons in depth perception and instrument manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bodyslam-a-generalized-monocular-visual-slam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topic Modeling with Fine-tuning LLMs and Bag of Sentences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03099</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset is then used to fine-tune an encoder LLM, which can be leveraged by any topic modeling approach using embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03099</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of Segment Anything Model 2: The Role of SAM2 in the Underwater Environment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02924</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report aims to explore the potential of SAM2 in marine science by evaluating it on the underwater instance segmentation benchmark datasets UIIS and USIS10K.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02924</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extend Model Merging from Fine-Tuned to Pre-Trained Large Language Models via Weight Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extend-model-merging-from-fine-tuned-to-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the experiments, we merge Qwen1. 5-Chat (an FT LLM with instruction-following skills) with Sailor (a PT LLM with multilingual abilities) across 7B and 14B model scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extend-model-merging-from-fine-tuned-to-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MedTrinity-25M: A Large-scale Multimodal Dataset with Multigranular Annotations for Medicine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02900</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then build a comprehensive knowledge base and prompt multimodal large language models to perform retrieval-augmented generation with the identified ROIs as guidance, resulting in multigranular texual descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02900</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenOmni: A Collaborative Open Source Tool for Building Future-Ready Multimodal Conversational Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openomni-a-collaborative-open-source-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal conversational agents are highly desirable because they offer natural and human-like interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openomni-a-collaborative-open-source-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COMMENTATOR: A Code-mixed Multilingual Text Annotation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03125</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the NLP community increasingly addresses challenges associated with multilingualism, robust annotation tools are essential to handle multilingual datasets efficiently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03125</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated Convolution with Learnable Spacings makes visual models more aligned with humans: a Grad-CAM study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03164</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we observed that Grad-CAM generated random heatmaps for two models in our study: CAFormer and ConvFormer models, leading to low interpretability scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03164</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Line-based 6-DoF Object Pose Estimation and Tracking With an Event Camera</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03225</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a line-based robust pose estimation and tracking method for planar or non-planar objects using an event camera.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03225</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comb, Prune, Distill: Towards Unified Pruning for Vision Model Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03046</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate the generalizability of our framework, encompassing both convolutional neural network (CNN) and transformer models, as well as image classification and segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03046</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lighthouse: A User-Friendly Library for Reproducible Video Moment Retrieval and Highlight Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02901</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lighthouse addresses these issues by implementing a unified reproducible codebase that includes six models, three features, and five datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02901</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Combining Diverse Information for Coordinated Action: Stochastic Bandit Algorithms for Heterogeneous Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-diverse-information-for-coordinated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stochastic multi-agent multi-armed bandits typically assume that the rewards from each arm follow a fixed distribution, regardless of which agent pulls the arm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combining-diverse-information-for-coordinated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effect of Kernel Size on CNN-Vision-Transformer-Based Gaze Prediction Using Electroencephalography Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-kernel-size-on-cnn-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an algorithm of gaze prediction from Electroencephalography (EEG) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effect-of-kernel-size-on-cnn-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ULLME: A Unified Framework for Large Language Model Embeddings with Generation-Augmented Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ullme-a-unified-framework-for-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is due to their causal attention mechanism and the misalignment between their pre-training objectives and the text ranking tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ullme-a-unified-framework-for-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamLCM: Towards High-Quality Text-to-3D Generation via Latent Consistency Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02993</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the SDS method always generates 3D objects with poor quality due to the over-smooth issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02993</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SuperSimpleNet: Unifying Unsupervised and Supervised Learning for Fast and Reliable Surface Defect Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03143</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim of surface defect detection is to identify and localise abnormal regions on the surfaces of captured objects, a task that's increasingly demanded across various industries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-03143</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EC-Guide: A Comprehensive E-Commerce Guide for Instruction Tuning and Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02970</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have attracted considerable attention in various fields for their cost-effective solutions to diverse challenges, especially with advancements in instruction tuning and quantization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02970</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation Style Discovery: Application to Skin Lesion Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02787</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Variability in medical image segmentation, arising from annotator preferences, expertise, and their choice of tools, has been well documented.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02787</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hardware Aware Ensemble Selection for Balancing Predictive Accuracy and Cost</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02280</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our evaluation using 83 classification datasets shows that our approach sustains competitive accuracy and can significantly improve ensembles' operational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02280</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Conditional Multi-Modal Prompts for Zero-shot HOI Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02484</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach enhances the generalization of large foundation models, such as CLIP, when fine-tuned for HOI detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02484</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DaCapo: a modular deep learning framework for scalable 3D image segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02834</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DaCapo is a specialized deep learning library tailored to expedite the training and application of existing machine learning approaches on large, near-isotropic image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02834</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesion Elevation Prediction from Skin Images Improves Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02792</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While deep learning-based computer-aided diagnosis for skin lesion image analysis is approaching dermatologists' performance levels, there are several works showing that incorporating additional features such as shape priors, texture, color constancy, and illumination further improves the lesion diagnosis performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02792</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FPT+: A Parameter and Memory Efficient Transfer Learning Method for High-resolution Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02426</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Fine-grained Prompt Tuning plus (FPT+), a PETL method designed for high-resolution medical image classification, which significantly reduces memory consumption compared to other PETL methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02426</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProCreate, Don't Reproduce! Propulsive Energy Diffusion for Creative Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02226</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose ProCreate, a simple and easy-to-implement method to improve sample diversity and creativity of diffusion-based image generative models and to prevent training data reproduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02226</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-Cost Self-Ensembles Based on Multi-Branch Transformation and Grouped Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02307</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new low-cost ensemble learning, which can simultaneously achieve high efficiency and classification performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02307</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRFormer: Multi-Scale Transformer Utilizing Diverse Receptive Fields for Long Time-Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02279</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed model, named DRFormer, is evaluated on various real-world datasets, and experimental results demonstrate its superiority compared to existing methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02279</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimensionality Reduction and Nearest Neighbors for Improving Out-of-Distribution Detection in Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02761</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work applied the Mahalanobis distance (MD) post hoc to the bottleneck features of four Swin UNETR and nnU-net models that segmented the liver on T1-weighted magnetic resonance imaging and computed tomography.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2408-02761</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
