<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 21:05:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed neural networks for highly compressible flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-highly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This thesis shows that physics-informed neural networks struggle with highly compressible problems for two independent reasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-neural-networks-for-highly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChemBERTa-2: Fine-Tuning for Molecule’s HIV Replication Inhibition Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemberta-2-fine-tuning-for-molecules-hiv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two versions of Large Language ChemBERTa-2 models, pre-trained with two different methods, were fine-tuned in this work for HIV replication inhibition prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemberta-2-fine-tuning-for-molecules-hiv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DePT: Decoupled Prompt Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dept-decoupled-prompt-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, through an in-depth analysis of the learned features of the base and new tasks, we observe that the BNT stems from a channel bias issue, i. e., the vast majority of feature channels are occupied by base-specific knowledge, resulting in the collapse of taskshared knowledge important to new tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dept-decoupled-prompt-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Diffusion with Task-awareness for Procedure Planning in Instructional Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-diffusion-with-task-awareness-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The introduced mask acts akin to a task-oriented attention filter, enabling the diffusion/denoising process to concentrate on a subset of action types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-diffusion-with-task-awareness-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnCodecMAE: Leveraging neural codecs for universal audio representation learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encodecmae-leveraging-neural-codecs-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of universal audio representation learning is to obtain foundational models that can be used for a variety of downstream tasks involving speech, music or environmental sounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encodecmae-leveraging-neural-codecs-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Adversarial Attacks via Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-adversarial-attacks-via-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then there are two variants of this framework: 1) the Semantic Transformation (ST) approach fine-tunes the latent space of the generated image and/or the diffusion model itself; 2) the Latent Masking (LM) approach masks the latent space with another target image and local backpropagation-based interpretation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-adversarial-attacks-via-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIGT: Hierarchical Interaction Graph-Transformer for Whole Slide Image Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higt-hierarchical-interaction-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that the information from different resolutions is complementary and can benefit each other during the learning process, we further design a novel Bidirectional Interaction block to establish communication between different levels within the WSI pyramids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/higt-hierarchical-interaction-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EP2P-Loc: End-to-End 3D Point to 2D Pixel Localization for Large-Scale Visual Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ep2p-loc-end-to-end-3d-point-to-2d-pixel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual localization is the task of estimating a 6-DoF camera pose of a query image within a provided 3D reference map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ep2p-loc-end-to-end-3d-point-to-2d-pixel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Spatial and Temporal Learning for Efficient Image-to-Video Transfer Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-spatial-and-temporal-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When pre-training on the large-scale Kinetics-710, we achieve 89. 7% on Kinetics-400 with a frozen ViT-L model, which verifies the scalability of DiST.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-spatial-and-temporal-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust and Unconstrained Full Range of Rotation Head Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-and-unconstrained-full-range</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Together with new accumulated training data that provides full head pose rotation data and a geodesic loss approach for stable learning, we design an advanced model that is able to predict an extended range of head orientations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-and-unconstrained-full-range</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMEAD: MS MARCO Entity Annotations and Disambiguations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmead-ms-marco-entity-annotations-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MMEAD, or MS MARCO Entity Annotations and Disambiguations, is a resource for entity links for the MS MARCO datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmead-ms-marco-entity-annotations-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure-Preserving Transformers for Sequences of SPD Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, Transformer-based auto-attention mechanisms have been successfully applied to the analysis of a variety of context-reliant data types, from texts to images and beyond, including data from non-Euclidean geometries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-preserving-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIB-200: A Simple, Inclusive, and Big Evaluation Dataset for Topic Classification in 200+ Languages and Dialects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sib-200-a-simple-inclusive-and-big-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the progress we have recorded in the last few years in multilingual natural language processing, evaluation is typically limited to a small set of languages with available datasets which excludes a large number of low-resource languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sib-200-a-simple-inclusive-and-big-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Warm-Start Fixed-Point Optimization Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-warm-start-fixed-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a machine-learning framework to warm-start fixed-point optimization algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-warm-start-fixed-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Prompt Learning with Distilled Connective Knowledge for Implicit Discourse Relation Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-prompt-learning-with-distilled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit discourse relation recognition (IDRR) aims at recognizing the discourse relation between two text segments without an explicit connective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-prompt-learning-with-distilled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nucleus-aware Self-supervised Pretraining Using Unpaired Image-to-image Translation for Histopathology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nucleus-aware-self-supervised-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised pretraining attempts to enhance model performance by obtaining effective features from unlabeled data, and has demonstrated its effectiveness in the field of histopathology images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nucleus-aware-self-supervised-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NineRec: A Benchmark Dataset Suite for Evaluating Transferable Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ninerec-a-benchmark-dataset-suite-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning a recommender system model from an item's raw modality features (such as image, text, audio, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ninerec-a-benchmark-dataset-suite-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emo-StarGAN: A Semi-Supervised Any-to-Many Non-Parallel Emotion-Preserving Voice Conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emo-stargan-a-semi-supervised-any-to-many-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Speech anonymisation prevents misuse of spoken data by removing any personal identifier while preserving at least linguistic content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emo-stargan-a-semi-supervised-any-to-many-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PromptASR for contextualized ASR with controllable style</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptasr-for-contextualized-asr-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An additional style prompt can be given to the text encoder and guide the ASR system to output different styles of transcriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/promptasr-for-contextualized-asr-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client-side Gradient Inversion Against Federated Learning from Poisoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-side-gradient-inversion-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the first time, we show the feasibility of a client-side adversary with limited knowledge being able to recover the training samples from the aggregated global model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/client-side-gradient-inversion-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some notes concerning a generalized KMM-type optimization method for density ratio estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-notes-concerning-a-generalized-kmm-type</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the present paper we introduce new optimization algorithms for the task of density ratio estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/some-notes-concerning-a-generalized-kmm-type</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Audio Captioning Models without Audio</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-audio-captioning-models-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, the text encoder is replaced with the pretrained CLAP audio encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-audio-captioning-models-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A DenseNet-based method for decoding auditory spatial attention with EEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-densenet-based-method-for-decoding-auditory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ASAD methods are inspired by the brain lateralization of cortical neural responses during the processing of auditory spatial attention, and show promising performance for the task of auditory attention decoding (AAD) with neural recordings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-densenet-based-method-for-decoding-auditory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C-Pack: Packaged Resources To Advance General Chinese Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-pack-packaged-resources-to-advance-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along with our resources on general Chinese embedding, we release our data and models for English text embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-pack-packaged-resources-to-advance-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinical Text Summarization: Adapting Large Language Models Can Outperform Human Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinical-text-summarization-adapting-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sifting through vast textual data and summarizing key information imposes a substantial burden on how clinicians allocate their time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clinical-text-summarization-adapting-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Human-Scene Interaction via Prompted Chain-of-Contacts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-human-scene-interaction-via-prompted</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on the definition, UniHSI constitutes a Large Language Model (LLM) Planner to translate language prompts into task plans in the form of CoC, and a Unified Controller that turns CoC into uniform task execution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-human-scene-interaction-via-prompted</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Dross Into Gold Loss: is BERT4Rec really better than SASRec?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-dross-into-gold-loss-is-bert4rec</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we show that SASRec could be effectively trained with negative sampling and still outperform BERT4Rec, but the number of negative examples should be much larger than one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-dross-into-gold-loss-is-bert4rec</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Conversation is Worth A Thousand Recommendations: A Survey of Holistic Conversational Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-conversation-is-worth-a-thousand</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, not all CRS approaches use human conversations as their source of interaction data; the majority of prior CRS work simulates interactions by exchanging entity-level information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-conversation-is-worth-a-thousand</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents: An Open-source Framework for Autonomous Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-an-open-source-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances on large language models (LLMs) enable researchers and developers to build autonomous language agents that can automatically solve various tasks and interact with environments, humans, and other agents using natural language interfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-an-open-source-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CATfOOD: Counterfactual Augmented Training for Improving Out-of-Domain Performance and Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catfood-counterfactual-augmented-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable capabilities at scale, particularly at generating text conditioned on a prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/catfood-counterfactual-augmented-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExpertQA: Expert-Curated Questions and Attributed Answers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertqa-expert-curated-questions-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As language models are adapted by a more sophisticated and diverse set of users, the importance of guaranteeing that they provide factually correct information supported by verifiable sources is critical across fields of study & professions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expertqa-expert-curated-questions-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CiwaGAN: Articulatory information exchange</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ciwagan-articulatory-information-exchange</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces CiwaGAN, a model of human spoken language acquisition that combines unsupervised articulatory modeling with an unsupervised model of information exchange through the auditory modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ciwagan-articulatory-information-exchange</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Quasi-Static 3D Models of Markerless Deformable Linear Objects for Bimanual Robotic Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quasi-static-3d-models-of-markerless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper analyzes several learning-based 3D models of the DLO and proposes a new one based on the Transformer architecture that achieves superior accuracy, even on the DLOs of different lengths, thanks to the proposed scaling method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-quasi-static-3d-models-of-markerless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRE: Vision-Language Prompt Learning with Reparameterization Encoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-vision-language-prompt-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Prompt Learning with Reparameterization Encoder (PRE) - a simple and efficient method that enhances the generalization ability of the learnable prompt to unseen classes while maintaining the capacity to learn Base classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-vision-language-prompt-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety-Tuned LLaMAs: Lessons From Improving the Safety of Large Language Models that Follow Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-tuned-llamas-lessons-from-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training large language models to follow instructions makes them perform better on a wide range of tasks, generally becoming more helpful.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-tuned-llamas-lessons-from-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grid-Aware On-Route Fast-Charging Infrastructure Planning for Battery Electric Bus with Equity Considerations: A Case Study in South King County</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grid-aware-on-route-fast-charging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The transition from traditional bus fleets to zero-emission ones necessitates the development of effective planning models for battery electric bus (BEB) charging infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grid-aware-on-route-fast-charging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Universal Speech Discrete Tokens: A Case Study for ASR and TTS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-universal-speech-discrete-tokens-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) proficiency in speech-related tasks has driven research into utilizing discrete tokens for speech tasks like recognition and translation, which offer lower storage requirements and great potential to employ natural language processing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-universal-speech-discrete-tokens-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dimensional Speech Quality Assessment in Crowdsourcing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-speech-quality-assessment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The commonly used standard ITU-T Rec.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-speech-quality-assessment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Tube-Certified Control Using Robust Contraction Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-tube-certified-control-using-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, for nonlinear systems subject to bounded disturbances, we present a framework for jointly learning a robust nonlinear controller and a contraction metric using a novel disturbance rejection objective that certifies a universal $\mathcal L_\infty$ gain bound using NNs for user-specified variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-tube-certified-control-using-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rise and Potential of Large Language Model Based Agents: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-rise-and-potential-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a long time, humanity has pursued artificial intelligence (AI) equivalent to or surpassing the human level, with AI agents considered a promising vehicle for this pursuit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-rise-and-potential-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMICL: Empowering Vision-language Model with Multi-Modal In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmicl-empowering-vision-language-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the current VLMs primarily emphasize utilizing multi-modal data with a single image some, rather than multi-modal prompts with interleaved multiple images and text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmicl-empowering-vision-language-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDTR-Net: A Real-Time High-Definition Teeth Restoration Network for Arbitrary Talking Face Generation Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdtr-net-a-real-time-high-definition-teeth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose a Fine-Grained Feature Fusion (FGFF) module to effectively capture fine texture feature information around teeth and surrounding regions, and use these features to fine-grain the feature map to enhance the clarity of teeth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdtr-net-a-real-time-high-definition-teeth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Survival Time of Ball Bearings in the Presence of Censoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-survival-time-of-ball-bearings-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach to predict the time to failure in ball bearings using survival analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-survival-time-of-ball-bearings-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamics of cell-type transition mediated by epigenetic modifications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-of-cell-type-transition-mediated-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through model simulations, we demonstrate that random inheritance of epigenetic states during cell divisions can spontaneously induce cell differentiation, dedifferentiation, and transdifferentiation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamics-of-cell-type-transition-mediated-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive KalmanNet: Data-Driven Kalman Filter with Fast Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-kalmannet-data-driven-kalman-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Combining the classical Kalman filter (KF) with a deep neural network (DNN) enables tracking in partially known state space (SS) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-kalmannet-data-driven-kalman-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated segmentation of rheumatoid arthritis immunohistochemistry stained synovial tissue</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-segmentation-of-rheumatoid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model obtains a DICE score of 0. 865 and successfully segments different types of IHC staining, as well as dealing with variance in colours, intensity and common WSIs artefacts from the different clinical centres.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-segmentation-of-rheumatoid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the TopMost: A Topic Modeling System Toolkit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-topmost-a-topic-modeling-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topic models have been proposed for decades with various applications and recently refreshed by the neural variational inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-the-topmost-a-topic-modeling-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sight Beyond Text: Multi-Modal Training Enhances LLMs in Truthfulness and Ethics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sight-beyond-text-multi-modal-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) are trained based on large language models (LLM), with an enhanced capability to comprehend multi-modal inputs and generate textual responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sight-beyond-text-multi-modal-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPI-Flow: Learning Realistic Optical Flow with Multiplane Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-flow-learning-realistic-optical-flow-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accuracy of learning-based optical flow estimation models heavily relies on the realism of the training datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mpi-flow-learning-realistic-optical-flow-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONVERSER: Few-Shot Conversational Dense Retrieval with Synthetic Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converser-few-shot-conversational-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational search provides a natural interface for information retrieval (IR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/converser-few-shot-conversational-dense</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
