<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 21:06:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-augmented conformer for improved end-to-end long-form ASR</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-augmented-conformer-for-improved-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformers have recently been proposed as a promising modelling approach for automatic speech recognition (ASR), outperforming recurrent neural network-based approaches and transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-augmented-conformer-for-improved-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JCoLA: Japanese Corpus of Linguistic Acceptability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jcola-japanese-corpus-of-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce JCoLA (Japanese Corpus of Linguistic Acceptability), which consists of 10, 020 sentences annotated with binary acceptability judgments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jcola-japanese-corpus-of-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Action-Induced Invariant Representation for Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-action-induced-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose a Sequential Action--induced invariant Representation (SAR) method, in which the encoder is optimized by an auxiliary learner to only preserve the components that follow the control signals of sequential actions, so the agent can be induced to learn the robust representation against distractions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-action-induced-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic similarity prediction is better than other semantic similarity measures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-similarity-prediction-is-better-than</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semantic similarity between natural language texts is typically measured either by looking at the overlap between subsequences (e. g., BLEU) or by using embeddings (e. g., BERTScore, S-BERT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-similarity-prediction-is-better-than</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMPLIFY:Attention-based Mixup for Performance Improvement and Label Smoothing in Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplify-attention-based-mixup-for-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method uses the Attention mechanism of Transformer itself to reduce the influence of noises and aberrant values in the original samples on the prediction results, without increasing additional trainable parameters, and the computational cost is very low, thereby avoiding the problem of high resource consumption in common Mixup methods such as Sentence Mixup .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amplify-attention-based-mixup-for-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MosaicFusion: Diffusion Models as Data Augmenters for Large Vocabulary Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mosaicfusion-diffusion-models-as-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present MosaicFusion, a simple yet effective diffusion-based data augmentation approach for large vocabulary instance segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mosaicfusion-diffusion-models-as-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BayesDLL: Bayesian Deep Learning Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesdll-bayesian-deep-learning-library</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release a new Bayesian neural network library for PyTorch for large-scale deep networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesdll-bayesian-deep-learning-library</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate and Fast Compressed Video Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-fast-compressed-video-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Addressing this, we study video captioning from a different perspective in compressed domain, which brings multi-fold advantages over the existing pipeline: 1) Compared to raw images from the decoded video, the compressed video, consisting of I-frames, motion vectors and residuals, is highly distinguishable, which allows us to leverage the entire video for learning without manual sampling through a specialized model design; 2) The captioning model is more efficient in inference as smaller and less redundant information is processed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-and-fast-compressed-video-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BGF-YOLO: Enhanced YOLOv8 with Multiscale Attentional Feature Fusion for Brain Tumor Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bgf-yolo-enhanced-yolov8-with-multiscale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[You Only Look Once (YOLO)-based object detectors have shown remarkable accuracy for automated brain tumor detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bgf-yolo-enhanced-yolov8-with-multiscale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invariant Learning via Probability of Sufficient and Necessary Causes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-learning-via-probability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To capture the information of sufficient and necessary causes, we employ a classical concept, the probability of sufficiency and necessary causes (PNS), which indicates the probability of whether one is the necessary and sufficient cause.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/invariant-learning-via-probability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LMC: Large Model Collaboration with Cross-assessment for Training-Free Open-Set Object Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmc-large-model-collaboration-with-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-set object recognition aims to identify if an object is from a class that has been encountered during training or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lmc-large-model-collaboration-with-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A matter of attitude: Focusing on positive and active gradients to boost saliency maps</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-matter-of-attitude-focusing-on-positive-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Saliency maps have become one of the most widely used interpretability techniques for convolutional neural networks (CNN) due to their simplicity and the quality of the insights they provide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-matter-of-attitude-focusing-on-positive-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Boost: Leveraging Synthetic Data for Enhanced Vision-Language Segmentation in Echocardiography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-boost-leveraging-synthetic-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the lack of readily available data in echocardiography hampers the training of VLSMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-boost-leveraging-synthetic-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAi's GPT4 as coding assistant</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openai-s-gpt4-as-coding-assistant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lately, Large Language Models have been widely used in code generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openai-s-gpt4-as-coding-assistant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Study on Learning Social Robot Navigation with Multimodal Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-on-learning-social-robot-navigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous mobile robots need to perceive the environments with their onboard sensors (e. g., LiDARs and RGB cameras) and then make appropriate navigation decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-study-on-learning-social-robot-navigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect Every Thing with Few Examples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-every-thing-with-few-examples</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For COCO, DE-ViT outperforms the open-vocabulary SoTA by 6. 9 AP50 and achieves 50 AP50 in novel classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-every-thing-with-few-examples</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Background Activation Suppression for Weakly Supervised Object Localization and Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/background-activation-suppression-for-weakly-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, our method also achieves state-of-the-art weakly supervised semantic segmentation performance on the PASCAL VOC 2012 and MS COCO 2014 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/background-activation-suppression-for-weakly-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incremental Constrained Clustering by Minimal Weighted Modification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-constrained-clustering-by-minimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering is a well-known task in Data Mining that aims at grouping data instances according to their similarity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-constrained-clustering-by-minimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRRF: 3D Reconstruction and View Synthesis for Transparent and Specular Objects with Neural Refractive-Reflective Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerrf-3d-reconstruction-and-view-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce the refractive-reflective field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerrf-3d-reconstruction-and-view-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Translation and Alignment for Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-translation-and-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid advances in high-throughput sequencing technologies, the focus of survival analysis has shifted from examining clinical indicators to incorporating genomic profiles with pathological images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-translation-and-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Cloud Network: An Order of Magnitude Improvement in Linear Layer Parameter Count</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-cloud-network-an-order-of-magnitude</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AlexNet-PCN16, our PCN equivalent to AlexNet, achieves comparable efficacy (test accuracy) to the original architecture with a 99. 5% reduction of parameters in its linear layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-cloud-network-an-order-of-magnitude</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneNet: Enhancing Time Series Forecasting Models under Concept Drift by Online Ensembling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onenet-enhancing-time-series-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online updating of time series forecasting models aims to address the concept drifting problem by efficiently updating forecasting models based on streaming data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onenet-enhancing-time-series-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReConcile: Round-Table Conference Improves Reasoning via Consensus among Diverse LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconcile-round-table-conference-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also experiment with GPT-4 itself as one of the agents in ReConcile and demonstrate that its initial performance also improves by absolute 10. 0% through discussion and feedback from other agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reconcile-round-table-conference-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Deep Gradient Leakage via Inversion Influence Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-deep-gradient-leakage-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Gradient Leakage (DGL) is a highly effective attack that recovers private training images from gradient vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-deep-gradient-leakage-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Robust is Google's Bard to Adversarial Image Attacks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-google-s-bard-to-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By attacking white-box surrogate vision encoders or MLLMs, the generated adversarial examples can mislead Bard to output wrong image descriptions with a 22% success rate based solely on the transferability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-robust-is-google-s-bard-to-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic stiffness identification and response estimation of Timoshenko beams via physics-informed Gaussian processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-stiffness-identification-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach has potential applications in the field of structural health monitoring (SHM) for both mechanical and structural systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-stiffness-identification-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Transformers for Wireless Communications: A Case Study in Beam Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-transformers-for-wireless</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wireless communications at high-frequency bands with large antenna arrays face challenges in beam management, which can potentially be improved by multimodality sensing information from cameras, LiDAR, radar, and GPS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-transformers-for-wireless</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemEval-2022 Task 7: Identifying Plausible Clarifications of Implicit and Underspecified Phrases in Instructional Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semeval-2022-task-7-identifying-plausible-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe SemEval-2022 Task 7, a shared task on rating the plausibility of clarifications in instructional texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semeval-2022-task-7-identifying-plausible-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Reversal Curse: LLMs trained on "A is B" fail to learn "B is A"</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reversal-curse-llms-trained-on-a-is-b</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This shows a failure of logical deduction that we hypothesize is caused by the Reversal Curse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-reversal-curse-llms-trained-on-a-is-b</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uplift vs. predictive modeling: a theoretical analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uplift-vs-predictive-modeling-a-theoretical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the growing popularity of machine-learning techniques in decision-making, the added value of causal-oriented strategies with respect to pure machine-learning approaches has rarely been quantified in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uplift-vs-predictive-modeling-a-theoretical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PanoVOS: Bridging Non-panoramic and Panoramic Views with Transformer for Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panovos-bridging-non-panoramic-and-panoramic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our dataset poses new challenges in panoramic VOS and we hope that our PanoVOS can advance the development of panoramic segmentation/tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panovos-bridging-non-panoramic-and-panoramic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Event Prediction using Case-Based Reasoning over Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-prediction-using-case-based-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generalize our methods beyond the domain of event prediction, we frame our task as a 2-hop LP task, where the first hop is a causal relation connecting a cause event to a new effect event and the second hop is a property about the new event which we wish to predict.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/event-prediction-using-case-based-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-OCTA: A Fine-Tuning Strategy for Applying Foundation Model to OCTA Image Segmentation Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-octa-a-fine-tuning-strategy-for-applying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the analysis of optical coherence tomography angiography (OCTA) images, the operation of segmenting specific targets is necessary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-octa-a-fine-tuning-strategy-for-applying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Activation Compression of Graph Neural Networks using Block-wise Quantization with Improved Variance Minimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activation-compression-of-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we present a correction to the assumptions on the distribution of intermediate activation maps in EXACT (assumed to be uniform) and show improved variance estimations of the quantization and dequantization steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activation-compression-of-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boolformer: Symbolic Regression of Logic Functions with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boolformer-symbolic-regression-of-logic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce Boolformer, the first Transformer architecture trained to perform end-to-end symbolic regression of Boolean functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boolformer-symbolic-regression-of-logic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>t-EER: Parameter-Free Tandem Evaluation of Countermeasures and Biometric Comparators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eer-parameter-free-tandem-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed approach is a strong candidate metric for the tandem evaluation of PAD systems and biometric comparators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-eer-parameter-free-tandem-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smooth ECE: Principled Reliability Diagrams via Kernel Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-ece-principled-reliability-diagrams</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that a simple modification fixes both constructions: first smooth the observations using an RBF kernel, then compute the Expected Calibration Error (ECE) of this smoothed function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smooth-ece-principled-reliability-diagrams</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongDocFACTScore: Evaluating the Factuality of Long Document Abstractive Summarisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longdocfactscore-evaluating-the-factuality-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework outperforms existing state-of-the-art metrics in its ability to correlate with human measures of factuality when used to evaluate long document summarisation data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longdocfactscore-evaluating-the-factuality-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling up COMETKIWI: Unbabel-IST 2023 Submission for the Quality Estimation Shared Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-cometkiwi-unbabel-ist-2023</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our team participated on all tasks: sentence- and word-level quality prediction (task 1) and fine-grained error span detection (task 2).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-up-cometkiwi-unbabel-ist-2023</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ContextRef: Evaluating Referenceless Metrics For Image Description Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextref-evaluating-referenceless-metrics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[None of the methods is successful with ContextRef, but we show that careful fine-tuning yields substantial improvements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextref-evaluating-referenceless-metrics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AceGPT, Localizing Large Language Models in Arabic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acegpt-localizing-large-language-models-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the imperative need and methodology for developing a localized Large Language Model (LLM) tailored for Arabic, a language with unique cultural characteristics that are not adequately addressed by current mainstream models like ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acegpt-localizing-large-language-models-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised Automated Audio Captioning via text only training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-automated-audio-captioning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach leverages the similarity between audio and text embeddings in CLAP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-automated-audio-captioning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FluentEditor: Text-based Speech Editing by Considering Acoustic and Prosody Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluenteditor-text-based-speech-editing-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-based speech editing (TSE) techniques are designed to enable users to edit the output audio by modifying the input text transcript instead of the audio itself.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluenteditor-text-based-speech-editing-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Hierarchical Structures for Improved Time Series Classification Using Stochastic Splitting Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-hierarchical-structures-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces a novel hierarchical divisive clustering approach with stochastic splitting functions (SSFs) to enhance classification performance in multi-class datasets through hierarchical classification (HC).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-hierarchical-structures-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation of digital MemComputing using standard electronic components</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-of-digital-memcomputing-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Digital MemComputing machines (DMMs), which employ nonlinear dynamical systems with memory (time non-locality), have proven to be a robust and scalable unconventional computing approach for solving a wide variety of combinatorial optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-of-digital-memcomputing-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cambridge Law Corpus: A Corpus for Legal AI Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-cambridge-law-corpus-a-corpus-for-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Cambridge Law Corpus (CLC), a corpus for legal AI research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-cambridge-law-corpus-a-corpus-for-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaMath: Bootstrap Your Own Mathematical Questions for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamath-bootstrap-your-own-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our MetaMath-7B model achieves 66. 4% on GSM8K and 19. 4% on MATH, exceeding the state-of-the-art models of the same size by 11. 5% and 8. 7%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metamath-bootstrap-your-own-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralLabeling: A versatile toolset for labeling vision datasets using Neural Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurallabeling-a-versatile-toolset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present NeuralLabeling, a labeling approach and toolset for annotating a scene using either bounding boxes or meshes and generating segmentation masks, affordance maps, 2D bounding boxes, 3D bounding boxes, 6DOF object poses, depth maps and object meshes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neurallabeling-a-versatile-toolset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FGFusion: Fine-Grained Lidar-Camera Fusion for 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgfusion-fine-grained-lidar-camera-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Fine-Grained Lidar-Camera Fusion (FGFusion) that make full use of multi-scale features of image and point cloud and fuse them in a fine-grained way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fgfusion-fine-grained-lidar-camera-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevating Skeleton-Based Action Recognition with Efficient Multi-Modality Self-Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elevating-skeleton-based-action-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These works overlooked the differences in performance among modalities, which led to the propagation of erroneous knowledge between modalities while only three fundamental modalities, i. e., joints, bones, and motions are used, hence no additional modalities are explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elevating-skeleton-based-action-recognition</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
