<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:07:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>IUST at ClimateActivism 2024: Towards Optimal Stance Detection: A Systematic Study of Architectural Choices and Data Cleaning Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iust-at-climateactivism-2024-towards-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work presents a systematic search of various model architecture configurations and data cleaning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iust-at-climateactivism-2024-towards-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Framework for Model Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-model-editing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With EMMET, we present a closed form solution for the equality-constrained version of the preservation-memorization objective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unified-framework-for-model-editing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Historical Image Retrieval with Compositional Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-historical-image-retrieval-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In analyzing vast amounts of digitally stored historical image data, existing content-based retrieval methods often overlook significant non-semantic information, limiting their effectiveness for flexible exploration across varied themes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-historical-image-retrieval-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detoxifying Large Language Models via Knowledge Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxifying-large-language-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates using knowledge editing techniques to detoxify Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detoxifying-large-language-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Segmentation Ability to Multi-modal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-segmentation-ability-to-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models (MLLMs) can understand image-language prompts and demonstrate impressive reasoning ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empowering-segmentation-ability-to-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reactor Optimization Benchmark by Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactor-optimization-benchmark-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neutronic calculations for reactors are a daunting task when using Monte Carlo (MC) methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reactor-optimization-benchmark-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pensieve: Retrospect-then-Compare Mitigates Visual Hallucination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pensieve-retrospect-then-compare-mitigates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) demonstrate remarkable success across various vision-language tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pensieve-retrospect-then-compare-mitigates</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering Latent Confounders from High-dimensional Proxy Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-latent-confounders-from-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting latent confounders from proxy variables is an essential problem in causal effect estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-latent-confounders-from-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Concept Trustworthiness in Concept Bottleneck Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-concept-trustworthiness-in-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concept Bottleneck Models (CBMs), which break down the reasoning process into the input-to-concept mapping and the concept-to-label prediction, have garnered significant attention due to their remarkable interpretability achieved by the interpretable concept bottleneck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-concept-trustworthiness-in-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Rex2: Towards Generic Object Detection via Text-Visual Prompt Synergy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-rex2-towards-generic-object-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing the complementary strengths and weaknesses of both text and visual prompts, we introduce T-Rex2 that synergizes both prompts within a single model through contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-rex2-towards-generic-object-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight Attention-based Deep Network via Multi-Scale Feature Fusion for Multi-View Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-attention-based-deep-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, the PWFS block employs a feature selection mechanism that discards less meaningful features prior to the fusion process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-attention-based-deep-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact Assessment of Missing Data in Model Predictions for Earth Observation Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-assessment-of-missing-data-in-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we assess the impact of missing temporal and static EO sources in trained models across four datasets with classification and regression tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-assessment-of-missing-data-in-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Models with Ensembled Structure-Based Anomaly Scoring for Unsupervised Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-ensembled-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that this ensembling strategy can enhance the performance of DMs and mitigate the sensitivity to different kernel sizes across varying pathologies, highlighting its promise for brain MRI anomaly detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-models-with-ensembled-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVSplat: Efficient 3D Gaussian Splatting from Sparse Multi-View Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose MVSplat, an efficient feed-forward 3D Gaussian Splatting model learned from sparse multi-view images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvsplat-efficient-3d-gaussian-splatting-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoftPatch: Unsupervised Anomaly Detection with Noisy Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-unsupervised-anomaly-detection-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Noise discriminators are utilized to generate outlier scores for patch-level noise elimination before coreset construction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/softpatch-unsupervised-anomaly-detection-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Trajectory Data Management and Mining: A Survey and Beyond</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-trajectory-data-management</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a comprehensive review of the development and recent advances in deep learning for trajectory computing (DL4Traj).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-trajectory-data-management</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Genetic Programming for Explainable Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-programming-for-explainable-manifold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experimental analysis demonstrates that GP-EMaL is able to match the performance of the existing approach in most cases, while using simpler, smaller, and more interpretable tree structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/genetic-programming-for-explainable-manifold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Image Classification Accuracy through Complementary Intra-Class and Inter-Class Mixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-classification-accuracy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, our integrated solution seamlessly combines our intra-class mixup method with an existing mixup approach such as MixUp or Manifold MixUp.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-image-classification-accuracy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reinforcement learning guided hybrid evolutionary algorithm for the latency location routing problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-guided-hybrid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The latency location routing problem integrates the facility location problem and the multi-depot cumulative capacitated vehicle routing problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-reinforcement-learning-guided-hybrid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less but Better: Enabling Generalized Zero-shot Learning Towards Unseen Domains by Intrinsic Learning from Redundant LLM Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-but-better-enabling-generalized-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from existing GZSL methods which alleviate DSP by generating features of unseen classes with semantics, CDGZSL needs to construct a common feature space across domains and acquire the corresponding intrinsic semantics shared among domains to transfer from seen to unseen domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-but-better-enabling-generalized-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiFactDiff: A Large, Realistic, and Temporally Adaptable Dataset for Atomic Factual Knowledge Update in Causal Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikifactdiff-a-large-realistic-and-temporally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study this task, we present WikiFactDiff, a dataset that describes the evolution of factual knowledge between two dates as a collection of simple facts divided into three categories: new, obsolete, and static.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikifactdiff-a-large-realistic-and-temporally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Enhanced Recommendation with User-Centric Subgraph Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-recommendation-with-user</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recommendation systems, as widely implemented nowadays on various platforms, recommend relevant items to users based on their preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-recommendation-with-user</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can ChatGPT Detect DeepFakes? A Study of Using Multimodal Large Language Models for Media Forensics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-chatgpt-detect-deepfakes-a-study-of-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DeepFakes, which refer to AI-generated media content, have become an increasing concern due to their use as a means for disinformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-chatgpt-detect-deepfakes-a-study-of-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DomainLab: A modular Python package for domain generalization in deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domainlab-a-modular-python-package-for-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DomainLab is a modular Python package for training user specified neural networks with composable regularization loss terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domainlab-a-modular-python-package-for-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HAC: Hash-grid Assisted Context for 3D Gaussian Splatting Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-hash-grid-assisted-context-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian Splatting (3DGS) has emerged as a promising framework for novel view synthesis, boasting rapid rendering speed with high fidelity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hac-hash-grid-assisted-context-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CombiNeRF: A Combination of Regularization Techniques for Few-Shot Neural Radiance Field View Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinerf-a-combination-of-regularization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When dealing with few-shot settings, i. e. with a small set of input views, the training could overfit those views, leading to artifacts and geometric and chromatic inconsistencies in the resulting rendering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/combinerf-a-combination-of-regularization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSALM: Pixelwise SegmentAtion with Large Multi-Modal Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psalm-pixelwise-segmentation-with-large-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PSALM is a powerful extension of the Large Multi-modal Model (LMM) to address the segmentation task challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psalm-pixelwise-segmentation-with-large-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary Attention Maps with Token Optimization for Semantic Segmentation in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-attention-maps-with-token</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach limits the generation of segmentation masks derived from word tokens not contained in the text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-attention-maps-with-token</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View-decoupled Transformer for Person Re-identification under Aerial-ground Camera Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-decoupled-transformer-for-person-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on two datasets show that VDT is a feasible and effective solution for AGPReID, surpassing the previous method on mAP/Rank1 by up to 5. 0%/2. 7% on CARGO and 3. 7%/5. 2% on AG-ReID, keeping the same magnitude of computational complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/view-decoupled-transformer-for-person-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>emoDARTS: Joint Optimisation of CNN &amp; Sequential Neural Network Architectures for Superior Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emodarts-joint-optimisation-of-cnn-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents emoDARTS, a DARTS-optimised joint CNN and Sequential Neural Network (SeqNN: LSTM, RNN) architecture that enhances SER performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emodarts-joint-optimisation-of-cnn-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-learning invariant foliations in forced systems for reduced order modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-invariant-foliations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We identify reduced order models (ROM) of forced systems from data using invariant foliations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-invariant-foliations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMIDR: Teaching Large Language Model to Interpret Multimodal Misinformation via Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmidr-teaching-large-language-model-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic detection of multimodal misinformation has gained a widespread attention recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmidr-teaching-large-language-model-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Repository for Long Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-repository-for-long-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a Language Repository (LangRepo) for LLMs, that maintains concise and structured information as an interpretable (i. e., all-textual) representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-repository-for-long-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for Cross-dataset Isolated Sign Language Recognition in Under-Resourced Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-cross-dataset-isolated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sign language recognition (SLR) has recently achieved a breakthrough in performance thanks to deep neural networks trained on large annotated sign datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-cross-dataset-isolated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLC++: Source-Free Universal Domain Adaptation through Global-Local Clustering and Contrastive Affinity Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glc-source-free-universal-domain-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GLC++ enhances the novel category clustering accuracy of GLC by 4. 3% in open-set scenarios on Office-Home.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glc-source-free-universal-domain-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAmBLA: A Framework for Evaluating the Reliability of LLMs as Assistants in the Biomedical Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rambla-a-framework-for-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) increasingly support applications in a wide range of domains, some with potential high societal impact such as biomedicine, yet their reliability in realistic use cases is under-researched.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rambla-a-framework-for-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Enhanced Data-free Approach for Federated Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-enhanced-data-free-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this field, Data-Free Knowledge Transfer (DFKT) plays a crucial role in addressing catastrophic forgetting and data privacy problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-enhanced-data-free-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HETAL: Efficient Privacy-preserving Transfer Learning with Homomorphic Encryption</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hetal-efficient-privacy-preserving-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although numerous previous studies proposed to use homomorphic encryption to resolve the data privacy issue in transfer learning in the machine learning as a service setting, most of them only focused on encrypted inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hetal-efficient-privacy-preserving-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChainLM: Empowering Large Language Models with Improved Chain-of-Thought Prompting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chainlm-empowering-large-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In response to this challenge, we present an empirical investigation of CoT prompting and introduce CoTGenius, a novel framework designed for the automatic generation of superior CoT prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chainlm-empowering-large-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loop Improvement: An Efficient Approach for Extracting Shared Features from Heterogeneous Data without Central Server</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loop-improvement-an-efficient-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LI integrates a loop topology with layer-wise and end-to-end training, compatible with various neural network models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loop-improvement-an-efficient-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Unlabeled Data: A Paradigm for Cross-View Geo-Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-unlabeled-data-a-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper investigates the effective utilization of unlabeled data for large-area cross-view geo-localization (CVGL), encompassing both unsupervised and semi-supervised settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-unlabeled-data-a-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperGALE: ASD Classification via Hypergraph Gated Attention with Learnable Hyperedges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergale-asd-classification-via-hypergraph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) is a neurodevelopmental condition characterized by varied social cognitive challenges and repetitive behavioral patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hypergale-asd-classification-via-hypergraph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Text-to-Vision Self Supervised Alignment for Improved Histopathology Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-text-to-vision-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised representation learning has been highly promising for histopathology image analysis with numerous approaches leveraging their patient-slide-patch hierarchy to learn better representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-text-to-vision-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRM: Large Gaussian Reconstruction Model for Efficient 3D Reconstruction and Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grm-large-gaussian-reconstruction-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GRM, a large-scale reconstructor capable of recovering a 3D asset from sparse-view images in around 0. 1s.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grm-large-gaussian-reconstruction-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LlamaFactory: Unified Efficient Fine-Tuning of 100+ Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamafactory-unified-efficient-fine-tuning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient fine-tuning is vital for adapting large language models (LLMs) to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llamafactory-unified-efficient-fine-tuning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Sampling-based Framework for Hypothesis Testing on Large Attributed Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sampling-based-framework-for-hypothesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments on real datasets demonstrate the ability of our framework to leverage common graph sampling methods for hypothesis testing, and the superiority of hypothesis-aware sampling in terms of accuracy and time efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-sampling-based-framework-for-hypothesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Point Learning and Refining for Category-Agnostic Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-point-learning-and-refining-for-category</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods only rely on the features extracted at support keypoints to predict or refine the keypoints on query image, but a few support feature vectors are local and inadequate for CAPE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-point-learning-and-refining-for-category</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DESIRE-ME: Domain-Enhanced Supervised Information REtrieval using Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desire-me-domain-enhanced-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-domain question answering requires retrieval systems able to cope with the diverse and varied nature of questions, providing accurate answers across a broad spectrum of query types and topics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desire-me-domain-enhanced-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grounding Spatial Relations in Text-Only Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-spatial-relations-in-text-only</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper shows that text-only Language Models (LM) can learn to ground spatial relations like "left of" or "below" if they are provided with explicit location information of objects and they are properly trained to leverage those locations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grounding-spatial-relations-in-text-only</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PuzzleVQA: Diagnosing Multimodal Reasoning Challenges of Language Models with Abstract Visual Patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzlevqa-diagnosing-multimodal-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As recognizing patterns and abstracting concepts are key to general intelligence, we introduce PuzzleVQA, a collection of puzzles based on abstract patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/puzzlevqa-diagnosing-multimodal-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
