<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 09:10:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-Temporal Graph Mixformer for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-graph-mixformer-for-traffic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we train an estimator model that express the contribution of a node over the desired prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-temporal-graph-mixformer-for-traffic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimCKP: Simple Contrastive Learning of Keyphrase Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simckp-simple-contrastive-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keyphrase generation (KG) aims to generate a set of summarizing words or phrases given a source document, while keyphrase extraction (KE) aims to identify them from the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simckp-simple-contrastive-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DualAug: Exploiting Additional Heavy Augmentation with OOD Data Rejection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualaug-exploiting-additional-heavy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing data augmentation methods tend to find a compromise in augmenting the data, \textit{i. e.}, increasing the amplitude of augmentation carefully to avoid degrading some data too much and doing harm to the model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualaug-exploiting-additional-heavy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Fast Minimum-Norm Attacks with Hyperparameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fast-minimum-norm-attacks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluating the adversarial robustness of machine learning models using gradient-based attacks is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-fast-minimum-norm-attacks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Our Privacy With Backdoors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-our-privacy-with-backdoors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach provides not only a new "dual-use" perspective on backdoor attacks, but also presents a promising avenue to enhance the privacy of individuals within models trained on uncurated web-scraped data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-our-privacy-with-backdoors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Tailed Classification Based on Coarse-Grained Leading Forest and Multi-Center Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-classification-based-on-coarse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this method, we designed an unsupervised learning method, i. e., CLF, to better characterize the distribution of attributes within a class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-tailed-classification-based-on-coarse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of Object-Centric Embeddings for Cell Instance Segmentation in Microscopy Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-object-centric-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we show theoretically that, under assumptions commonly found in microscopy images, OCEs can be learnt through a self-supervised task that predicts the spatial offset between image patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-object-centric-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoVP: An Automated Visual Prompting Framework and Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autovp-an-automated-visual-prompting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we propose AutoVP, an end-to-end expandable framework for automating VP design choices, along with 12 downstream image-classification tasks that can serve as a holistic VP-performance benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autovp-an-automated-visual-prompting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniPAD: A Universal Pre-training Paradigm for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipad-a-universal-pre-training-paradigm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of autonomous driving, the significance of effective feature learning is widely acknowledged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipad-a-universal-pre-training-paradigm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of time and note duration tokenizations on deep learning symbolic music modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-time-and-note-duration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Symbolic music is widely used in various deep learning tasks, including generation, transcription, synthesis, and Music Information Retrieval (MIR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-time-and-note-duration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Scientific Synthesis, Inference and Explanation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a method for using general-purpose large language models to make inferences from scientific datasets of the form usually associated with special-purpose machine learning algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Combinatorial Optimization with Heavy Decoder: Toward Large Scale Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-combinatorial-optimization-with-heavy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural combinatorial optimization (NCO) is a promising learning-based approach for solving challenging combinatorial optimization problems without specialized algorithm design by experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-combinatorial-optimization-with-heavy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To token or not to token: A Comparative Study of Text Representations for Cross-Lingual Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-token-or-not-to-token-a-comparative-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To understand the downstream implications of text representation choices, we perform a comparative analysis on language models having diverse text representation modalities including 2 segmentation-based models (\texttt{BERT}, \texttt{mBERT}), 1 image-based model (\texttt{PIXEL}), and 1 character-level model (\texttt{CANINE}).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-token-or-not-to-token-a-comparative-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLP-AMDC: An MLP Architecture for Adaptive-Mask-based Dual-Camera snapshot hyperspectral imaging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlp-amdc-an-mlp-architecture-for-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to improve the inference speed of the reconstruction network, this paper proposes An MLP Architecture for Adaptive-Mask-based Dual-Camera (MLP-AMDC) to replace the transformer structure of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlp-amdc-an-mlp-architecture-for-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Memes to Words for Multimodal Hateful Meme Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-memes-to-words-for-multimodal-hateful</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal image-text memes are prevalent on the internet, serving as a unique form of communication that combines visual and textual elements to convey humor, ideas, or emotions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-memes-to-words-for-multimodal-hateful</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 Detection Using Swin Transformer Approach from Computed Tomography Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-19-detection-using-swin-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accurate and efficient diagnosis of COVID-19 is of paramount importance, particularly in the context of large-scale medical imaging datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/covid-19-detection-using-swin-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling from Vision-Language Models for Improved OOD Generalization in Vision Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-from-vision-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The client aims to minimize inference cost by distilling the VLM to a student model using the limited available task-specific data, and further deploying this student model in the downstream application.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-from-vision-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniPose: Detecting Any Keypoints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipose-detecting-any-keypoints</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work proposes a unified framework called UniPose to detect keypoints of any articulated (e. g., human and animal), rigid, and soft objects via visual or textual prompts for fine-grained vision understanding and manipulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unipose-detecting-any-keypoints</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding the Vocabulary of BERT for Knowledge Base Construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-the-vocabulary-of-bert-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we present Vocabulary Expandable BERT for knowledge base construction, which expand the language model's vocabulary while preserving semantic embeddings for newly added words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/expanding-the-vocabulary-of-bert-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can We Edit Multimodal Large Language Models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-edit-multimodal-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we focus on editing Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-we-edit-multimodal-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-HRNet: Towards Lightweight Human Pose Estimation with Spatially Unidimensional Self-Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-hrnet-towards-lightweight-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this observation, we introduce a lightweight and powerful alternative, Spatially Unidimensional Self-Attention (SUSA), to the pointwise (1x1) convolution that is the main computational bottleneck in the depthwise separable 3c3 convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-hrnet-towards-lightweight-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalized Logit Adjustment: Calibrating Fine-tuned Models by Removing Label Bias in Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-logit-adjustment-calibrating-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we systematically examine the biases in foundation models and demonstrate the efficacy of our proposed Generalized Logit Adjustment (GLA) method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalized-logit-adjustment-calibrating-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn From Model Beyond Fine-Tuning: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-from-model-beyond-fine-tuning-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LFM focuses on the research, modification, and design of FM based on the model interface, so as to better understand the model structure and weights (in a black box environment), and to generalize the model to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learn-from-model-beyond-fine-tuning-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplicity Level Estimate (SLE): A Learned Reference-Less Metric for Sentence Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicity-level-estimate-sle-a-learned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic evaluation for sentence simplification remains a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplicity-level-estimate-sle-a-learned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PonderV2: Pave the Way for 3D Foundataion Model with A Universal Pre-training Paradigm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ponderv2-pave-the-way-for-3d-foundataion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a comprehensive 3D pre-training framework designed to facilitate the acquisition of efficient 3D representations, thereby establishing a pathway to 3D foundational models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ponderv2-pave-the-way-for-3d-foundataion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of multi-armed bandit strategies on deep recurrent reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-multi-armed-bandit-strategies-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We aim to show that adaptive stochastic methods for exploration better approximate the trade-off between exploration and exploitation as, in general, Softmax and Max-Boltzmann strategies are able to outperform epsilon-greedy techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-multi-armed-bandit-strategies-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we formulate the novel problem of counterfactual generation for time series forecasting, and propose an algorithm, called ForecastCF, that solves the problem by applying gradient-based perturbations to the original time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context Compression for Auto-regressive Transformers with Sentinel Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-compression-for-auto-regressive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quadratic complexity of the attention module makes it gradually become the bulk of compute in Transformer-based LLMs during generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-compression-for-auto-regressive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-Forward Relaying: A Novel Framework Towards 6G Cooperative Communications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-forward-relaying-a-novel-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This letter proposes a novel relaying framework, semantic-forward (SF), for cooperative communications towards the sixth-generation (6G) wireless networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-forward-relaying-a-novel-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HoneyBee: Progressive Instruction Finetuning of Large Language Models for Materials Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/honeybee-progressive-instruction-finetuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an instruction-based process for trustworthy data curation in materials science (MatSci-Instruct), which we then apply to finetune a LLaMa-based language model targeted for materials science (HoneyBee).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/honeybee-progressive-instruction-finetuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Unified Analysis of Kernel-based Methods Under Covariate Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-analysis-of-kernel-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two types of covariate shift problems are the focus of this paper and the sharp convergence rates are established for a general loss function to provide a unified theoretical analysis, which concurs with the optimal results in literature where the squared loss is used.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-analysis-of-kernel-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extensions of Heterogeneity in Integration and Prediction (HIP) with R Shiny Application</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extensions-of-heterogeneity-in-integration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple data views measured on the same set of participants is becoming more common and has the potential to deepen our understanding of many complex diseases by analyzing these different views simultaneously.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extensions-of-heterogeneity-in-integration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infinite Width Graph Neural Networks for Node Regression/ Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinite-width-graph-neural-networks-for-node</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work analyzes Graph Neural Networks, a generalization of Fully-Connected Deep Neural Nets on Graph structured data, when their width, that is the number of nodes in each fullyconnected layer is increasing to infinity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infinite-width-graph-neural-networks-for-node</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-Agnostic Covariate-Assisted Inference on Partially Identified Causal Effects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-covariate-assisted-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we propose an efficient computational framework, enabling implementation on many practical problems in causal inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-agnostic-covariate-assisted-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Models are Universal Embedders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-universal-embedders</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such cases span from English to other natural or programming languages, from retrieval to classification and beyond, it is desirable to build a unified embedding model rather than dedicated ones for each scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-models-are-universal-embedders</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XIMAGENET-12: An Explainable AI Benchmark Dataset for Model Robustness Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ximagenet-12-an-explainable-ai-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of standardized robustness metrics and the widespread reliance on numerous unrelated benchmark datasets for testing have created a gap between academically validated robust models and their often problematic practical adoption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ximagenet-12-an-explainable-ai-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not All Demonstration Examples are Equally Beneficial: Reweighting Demonstration Examples for In-Context Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-demonstration-examples-are-equally</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assess the quality of weights in the absence of additional validation data, we design a masked self-prediction (MSP) score that exhibits a strong correlation with the final ICL performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/not-all-demonstration-examples-are-equally</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Uncertainty-based Retrieval Framework for Ancient Chinese CWS and POS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-uncertainty-based-retrieval-framework-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic analysis for modern Chinese has greatly improved the accuracy of text mining in related fields, but the study of ancient Chinese is still relatively rare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-uncertainty-based-retrieval-framework-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MProto: Multi-Prototype Network with Denoised Optimal Transport for Distantly Supervised Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mproto-multi-prototype-network-with-denoised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Distantly supervised named entity recognition (DS-NER) aims to locate entity mentions and classify their types with only knowledge bases or gazetteers and unlabeled corpus.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mproto-multi-prototype-network-with-denoised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incorporating Domain Knowledge Graph into Multimodal Movie Genre Classification with Self-Supervised Attention and Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-domain-knowledge-graph-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Firstly we retrieve the relevant embedding from the knowledge graph by utilizing group relations in metadata and then integrate it with other modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incorporating-domain-knowledge-graph-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphextQA: A Benchmark for Evaluating Graph-Enhanced Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphextqa-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed dataset is designed to evaluate graph-language models' ability to understand graphs and make use of it for answer generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphextqa-a-benchmark-for-evaluating-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Question Generation in Bengali</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-question-generation-in-bengali</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our quantitative and qualitative results establish the first state of the art models for VQG task in Bengali and demonstrate that our models are capable of generating grammatically correct and relevant questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-question-generation-in-bengali</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZEST: Attention-based Zero-Shot Learning for Unseen IoT Device Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zest-attention-based-zero-shot-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research works have proposed machine learning models for classifying IoT devices connected to a network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zest-attention-based-zero-shot-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Core-sets for Fair and Diverse Data Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-sets-for-fair-and-diverse-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider two natural diversity measures: sum-of-pairwise distances and sum-of-nearest-neighbor distances, and show improved core-set construction algorithms with respect to these measures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/core-sets-for-fair-and-diverse-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Negative Pairs in Code Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-negative-pairs-in-code-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our proposed loss function, we apply three methods to estimate the weights of negative pairs and show that the vanilla InfoNCE loss is a special case of Soft-InfoNCE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-negative-pairs-in-code-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Data-Type Understanding does not emerge from Scaling Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-data-type-understanding-does-not</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This finding points to a blind spot in current frontier VLMs: they excel in recognizing semantic content but fail to acquire an understanding of visual \textit{data-types} through scaling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-data-type-understanding-does-not</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Diffusion via Information Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-diffusion-via-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For diffusion models, we show that a natural non-negative decomposition of mutual information emerges, allowing us to quantify informative relationships between words and pixels in an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-diffusion-via-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transport-Hub-Aware Spatial-Temporal Adaptive Graph Transformer for Traffic Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transport-hub-aware-spatial-temporal-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we design an extra spatial-temporal knowledge distillation module for incremental learning of traffic flow prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transport-hub-aware-spatial-temporal-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lag-Llama: Towards Foundation Models for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lag-llama-towards-foundation-models-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aiming to build foundation models for time-series forecasting and study their scaling behavior, we present here our work-in-progress on Lag-Llama, a general-purpose univariate probabilistic time-series forecasting model trained on a large collection of time-series data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lag-llama-towards-foundation-models-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaBox: A Benchmark Platform for Meta-Black-Box Optimization with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metabox-a-benchmark-platform-for-meta-black</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we introduce MetaBox, the first benchmark platform expressly tailored for developing and evaluating MetaBBO-RL methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metabox-a-benchmark-platform-for-meta-black</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
