<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 21:10:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>STAR: SQL Guided Pre-Training for Context-dependent Text-to-SQL Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-sql-guided-pre-training-for-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Concretely, we propose two novel pre-training objectives which respectively explore the context-dependent interactions of NL utterances and SQL queries within each text-to-SQL conversation: (i) schema state tracking (SST) objective that tracks and explores the schema states of context-dependent SQL queries in the form of schema-states by predicting and updating the value of each schema slot during interaction; (ii) utterance dependency tracking (UDT) objective that employs weighted contrastive learning to pull together two semantically similar NL utterances and push away the representations of semantically dissimilar NL utterances within each conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-sql-guided-pre-training-for-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing text representations to capture (dis)similarity between political parties</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-text-representations-to-capture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though fine-tuned neural language models have been pivotal in enabling "deep" automatic text analysis, optimizing text representations for specific applications remains a crucial bottleneck.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-text-representations-to-capture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Vision-and-Language Transformers Learn Grounded Predicate-Noun Dependencies?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-vision-and-language-transformers-learn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in vision-and-language modeling have seen the development of Transformer architectures that achieve remarkable performance on multimodal reasoning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-vision-and-language-transformers-learn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$m^4Adapter$: Multilingual Multi-Domain Adaptation for Machine Translation with a Meta-Adapter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-4adapter-multilingual-multi-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider a very challenging scenario: adapting the MNMT model both to a new domain and to a new language pair at the same time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-4adapter-multilingual-multi-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empathetic Dialogue Generation via Sensitive Emotion Recognition and Sensible Knowledge Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empathetic-dialogue-generation-via-sensitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a fine-grained encoding strategy which is more sensitive to the emotion dynamics (emotion flow) in the conversations to predict the emotion-intent characteristic of response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/empathetic-dialogue-generation-via-sensitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Bayesian optimization via maximizing probability of descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-bayesian-optimization-via-maximizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local optimization presents a promising approach to expensive, high-dimensional black-box optimization by sidestepping the need to globally explore the search space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-bayesian-optimization-via-maximizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spectral Probing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-probing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Linguistic information is encoded at varying timescales (subwords, phrases, etc.)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spectral-probing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amos: An Adam-style Optimizer with Adaptive Weight Decay towards Model-Oriented Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amos-an-adam-style-optimizer-with-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Amos, a stochastic gradient-based optimizer designed for training deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/amos-an-adam-style-optimizer-with-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust Dynamics through Variational Sparse Gating</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-dynamics-through-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning world models from their sensory inputs enables agents to plan for actions by imagining their future outcomes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-dynamics-through-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploration of the Usage of Color Terms by Color-blind Participants in Online Discussion Platforms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-the-usage-of-color-terms-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prominent questions about the role of sensory vs. linguistic input in the way we acquire and use language have been extensively studied in the psycholinguistic literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-the-usage-of-color-terms-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Enhanced Stereo Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-enhanced-stereo-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We construct our stereo depth estimation model, Context Enhanced Stereo Transformer (CSTR), by plugging CEP into the state-of-the-art stereo depth estimation method Stereo Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-enhanced-stereo-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CEFR-Based Sentence Difficulty Annotation and Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cefr-based-sentence-difficulty-annotation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Controllable text simplification is a crucial assistive technique for language learning and teaching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cefr-based-sentence-difficulty-annotation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Tuned Parameters are Task Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-tuned-parameters-are-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, we propose to exploit these efficiently tuned parameters as off-the-shelf task embeddings for the efficient selection of source datasets for intermediate-task transfer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-tuned-parameters-are-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multitask Brain Tumor Inpainting with Diffusion Models: A Methodological Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-brain-tumor-inpainting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although the majority of inpainting techniques for medical imaging data use generative adversarial networks (GANs), the performance of these algorithms is frequently suboptimal due to their limited output variety, a problem that is already well-known for GANs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multitask-brain-tumor-inpainting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triplet Losses-based Matrix Factorization for Robust Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-losses-based-matrix-factorization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much like other learning-based models, recommender systems can be affected by biases in the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triplet-losses-based-matrix-factorization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaCo: Parameter-Compositional Multi-Task Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paco-parameter-compositional-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the gaps between contents and difficulties of different tasks bring us challenges on both which tasks should share the parameters and what parameters should be shared, as well as the optimization challenges due to parameter sharing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paco-parameter-compositional-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structural Kernel Search via Bayesian Optimization and Symbolical Optimal Transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-kernel-search-via-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent advances in automated machine learning, model selection is still a complex and computationally intensive process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structural-kernel-search-via-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCSCSet: A Specialist-annotated Dataset for Medical-domain Chinese Spelling Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcscset-a-specialist-annotated-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we define the task of Medical-domain Chinese Spelling Correction and propose MCSCSet, a large scale specialist-annotated dataset that contains about 200k samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mcscset-a-specialist-annotated-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Range Imaging for Learning Scene Priors of 3D LiDAR Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-range-imaging-for-learning-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the fidelity and diversity of our model in comparison with the point-based and image-based state-of-the-art generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-range-imaging-for-learning-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning Fixed to Adaptive: Integrating Post-Evaluation into Simultaneous Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-fixed-to-adaptive-integrating-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the fixed policy, the adaptive policy achieves better latency-quality tradeoffs by adopting a flexible translation policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/turning-fixed-to-adaptive-integrating-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decoding a Neural Retriever's Latent Space for Query Suggestion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-a-neural-retriever-s-latent-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural retrieval models have superseded classic bag-of-words methods such as BM25 as the retrieval framework of choice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/decoding-a-neural-retriever-s-latent-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransLIST: A Transformer-Based Linguistically Informed Sanskrit Tokenizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translist-a-transformer-based-linguistically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing lexicon driven approaches for SWS make use of Sanskrit Heritage Reader, a lexicon-driven shallow parser, to generate the complete candidate solution space, over which various methods are applied to produce the most valid solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/translist-a-transformer-based-linguistically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing and Evaluating Faithfulness in Dialogue Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-and-evaluating-faithfulness-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The factual correctness of summaries has the highest priority before practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-and-evaluating-faithfulness-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLING: Sino Linguistic Evaluation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sling-sino-linguistic-evaluation-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To understand what kinds of linguistic knowledge are encoded by pretrained Chinese language models (LMs), we introduce the benchmark of Sino LINGuistics (SLING), which consists of 38K minimal sentence pairs in Mandarin Chinese grouped into 9 high-level linguistic phenomena.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sling-sino-linguistic-evaluation-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustifying Sentiment Classification by Maximally Exploiting Few Counterfactuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustifying-sentiment-classification-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate the effectiveness of our approach in sentiment classification, using IMDb data for training and other sets for OOD tests (i. e., Amazon, SemEval and Yelp).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustifying-sentiment-classification-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syntax-guided Localized Self-attention by Constituency Syntactic Distance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntax-guided-localized-self-attention-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works have revealed that Transformers are implicitly learning the syntactic information in its lower layers from data, albeit is highly dependent on the quality and scale of the training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntax-guided-localized-self-attention-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stochastic Adaptive Activation Function</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-adaptive-activation-function</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The simulation of human neurons and neurotransmission mechanisms has been realized in deep neural networks based on the theoretical implementations of activation functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stochastic-adaptive-activation-function</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Reasoning: Consistent Contrastive Learning for Math Word Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-reasoning-consistent-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Math word problem solver requires both precise relation reasoning about quantities in the text and reliable generation for the diverse equation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-reasoning-consistent-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling the Undistillable: Learning from a Nasty Teacher</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-the-undistillable-learning-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inadvertent stealing of private/sensitive information using Knowledge Distillation (KD) has been getting significant attention recently and has guided subsequent defense efforts considering its critical nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-the-undistillable-learning-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Face Pyramid Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-pyramid-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A novel Face Pyramid Vision Transformer (FPVT) is proposed to learn a discriminative multi-scale facial representations for face recognition and verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/face-pyramid-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Counterfactual Explainer for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-counterfactual-explainer-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One way to address this is counterfactual reasoning where the objective is to change the GNN prediction by minimal changes in the input graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-counterfactual-explainer-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Augmenting Multi-Turn Text-to-SQL Datasets with Self-Play</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-multi-turn-text-to-sql-datasets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first design a SQL-to-text model conditioned on a sampled goal query, which represents a user's intent, that then converses with a text-to-SQL semantic parser to generate new interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/augmenting-multi-turn-text-to-sql-datasets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twin Contrastive Learning for Online Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twin-contrastive-learning-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we find that when the data is projected into a feature space with a dimensionality of the target cluster number, the rows and columns of its feature matrix correspond to the instance and cluster representation, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twin-contrastive-learning-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Visual Counterfactual Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-visual-counterfactual-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two modifications to the diffusion process are key for our DVCEs: first, an adaptive parameterization, whose hyperparameters generalize across images and models, together with distance regularization and late start of the diffusion process, allow us to generate images with minimal semantic changes to the original ones but different classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-visual-counterfactual-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting vision transformers for image retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-vision-transformers-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(4) We enhance locality of interactions at the deeper layers of the encoder, which is the relative weakness of vision transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-vision-transformers-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-Preserved Neural Graph Similarity Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserved-neural-graph-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To develop effective and efficient graph similarity learning (GSL) models, a series of data-driven neural algorithms have been proposed in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserved-neural-graph-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Non-Asymptotic Moreau Envelope Theory for High-Dimensional Generalized Linear Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-non-asymptotic-moreau-envelope-theory-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove a new generalization bound that shows for any class of linear predictors in Gaussian space, the Rademacher complexity of the class and the training error under any continuous loss $\ell$ can control the test error under all Moreau envelopes of the loss $\ell$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-non-asymptotic-moreau-envelope-theory-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient identification of informative features in simulation-based inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-identification-of-informative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, many SBI methods employ a set of summary statistics or scientifically interpretable features to estimate a surrogate likelihood or posterior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-identification-of-informative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Networks for Zero-Shot Coordination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-networks-for-zero-shot</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Successful coordination in Dec-POMDPs requires agents to adopt robust strategies and interpretable styles of play for their partner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-networks-for-zero-shot</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Causal Framework to Quantify the Robustness of Mathematical Reasoning with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-framework-to-quantify-the-robustness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By grounding the behavioral analysis in a causal graph describing an intuitive reasoning process, we study the behavior of language models in terms of robustness and sensitivity to direct interventions in the input space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-causal-framework-to-quantify-the-robustness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Data Optimization for Problems in Computer Vision Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-data-optimization-for-problems-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we organize these data optimization works according to data problems addressed, and provide a systematic and comparative description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-data-optimization-for-problems-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRT-6D: Fast 6D Object Pose Estimation with Cascaded Refinement Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crt-6d-fast-6d-object-pose-estimation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning based 6D object pose estimation methods rely on computing large intermediate pose representations and/or iteratively refining an initial estimation with a slow render-compare pipeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crt-6d-fast-6d-object-pose-estimation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning for $K$-adaptability in Two-stage Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-k-adaptability-in-two</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the solution approaches to this class of problems is $K$-adaptability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-for-k-adaptability-in-two</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Dataset Shortcuts with Grammar Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-dataset-shortcuts-with-grammar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many NLP datasets have been found to contain shortcuts: simple decision rules that achieve surprisingly high accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finding-dataset-shortcuts-with-grammar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Feature Learning in the Presence of Spurious Correlations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-feature-learning-in-the-presence-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep classifiers are known to rely on spurious features $\unicode{x2013}$ patterns which are correlated with the target on the training data but not inherently relevant to the learning problem, such as the image backgrounds when classifying the foregrounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-feature-learning-in-the-presence-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HesScale: Scalable Computation of Hessian Diagonals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hesscale-scalable-computation-of-hessian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second-order optimization uses curvature information about the objective function, which can help in faster convergence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hesscale-scalable-computation-of-hessian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-batch Optimization for Dense Visual Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-batch-optimization-for-dense-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose a simple yet effective algorithm, named Adaptive Gradient Variance Modulator (AGVM), which can train dense visual predictors with very large batch size, enabling several benefits more appealing than prior arts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-batch-optimization-for-dense-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOWO-Plus: An Incremental Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yowo-plus-an-incremental-improvement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the AVA, our optimized YOWO achieves 20. 6\% frame mAP with 16 frames, also exceeding the official YOWO.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yowo-plus-an-incremental-improvement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConfMix: Unsupervised Domain Adaptation for Object Detection via Confidence-based Mixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confmix-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised Domain Adaptation (UDA) for object detection aims to adapt a model trained on a source domain to detect instances from a new target domain for which annotations are not available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/confmix-unsupervised-domain-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Learning Approaches for Long-Term Action Anticipation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-learning-approaches-for-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Action anticipation involves predicting future actions having observed the initial portion of a video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-learning-approaches-for-long-term</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
