<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 21:06:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Latent Variable Models for Few-Shot High-Dimensional Time-Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared the presented framework with a comprehensive set of baseline models trained 1) globally on the large meta-training set with diverse dynamics, and 2) individually on single dynamics, both with and without fine-tuning to k-shot support series used by the meta-models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-latent-variable-models-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAANet: Ghost Auto Anchor Network for Detecting Varying Size Drones in Dark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaanet-ghost-auto-anchor-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome those limitations and improve the detection accuracy at night, we propose an object detector called Ghost Auto Anchor Network (GAANet) for infrared (IR) images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaanet-ghost-auto-anchor-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Product Classification on Leaflet Advertisements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-product-classification-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show, that the combination of image and text as input improves the classification of visual difficult to distinguish products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-product-classification-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large Cross-Modal Video Retrieval Dataset with Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-cross-modal-video-retrieval-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing cross-modal language-to-video retrieval (VR) research focuses on single-modal input from video, i. e., visual representation, while the text is omnipresent in human environments and frequently critical to understand video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-cross-modal-video-retrieval-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Hyperparameters with Conformal Quantile Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-hyperparameters-with-conformal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many state-of-the-art hyperparameter optimization (HPO) algorithms rely on model-based optimizers that learn surrogate models of the target function to guide the search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimizing-hyperparameters-with-conformal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Semantic Similarity Measurement for Unsupervised Word Sense Disambiguation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-semantic-similarity-measurement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The issue of word sense ambiguity poses a significant challenge in natural language processing due to the scarcity of annotated data to feed machine learning models to face the challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-semantic-similarity-measurement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing Idleness in Financial Cloud via Multi-objective Evolutionary Reinforcement Learning based Load Balancer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-idleness-in-financial-cloud-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, various companies started to shift their data services from traditional data centers onto cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reducing-idleness-in-financial-cloud-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransESC: Smoothing Emotional Support Conversation via Turn-Level State Transition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transesc-smoothing-emotional-support</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we construct the state transition graph with a two-step way, named transit-then-interact, to grasp such three types of turn-level transition information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transesc-smoothing-emotional-support</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verify-and-Edit: A Knowledge-Enhanced Chain-of-Thought Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verify-and-edit-a-knowledge-enhanced-chain-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As large language models (LLMs) have become the norm in NLP, demonstrating good performance in generation and reasoning tasks, one of its most fatal disadvantages is the lack of factual correctness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verify-and-edit-a-knowledge-enhanced-chain-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Inference for Fairness Auditing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-fairness-auditing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our methods can be used to flag subpopulations affected by model underperformance, and certify subpopulations for which the model performs adequately.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-fairness-auditing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlowText: Synthesizing Realistic Scene Text Video with Optical Flow Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowtext-synthesizing-realistic-scene-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel video text synthesis technique called FlowText, which utilizes optical flow estimation to synthesize a large amount of text video data at a low cost for training robust video text spotters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flowtext-synthesizing-realistic-scene-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiPool: Modeling Long Documents Using Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hipool-modeling-long-documents-using-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Encoding long sequences in Natural Language Processing (NLP) is a challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hipool-modeling-long-documents-using-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Topological Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-topological-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze the sensitivity of persistence diagrams in terms of the bottleneck distance, and we show that the commonly used \v{C}ech complex has sensitivity that does not decrease as the sample size $n$ increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-topological-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-free Reinforcement Learning of Semantic Communication by Stochastic Policy Gradient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-reinforcement-learning-of-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the recent success of Machine Learning tools in wireless communications, the idea of semantic communication by Weaver from 1949 has gained attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-reinforcement-learning-of-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White-Box Multi-Objective Adversarial Attack on Dialogue Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/white-box-multi-objective-adversarial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such language models are, however, vulnerable to various adversarial samples as studied in traditional tasks such as text classification, which inspires our curiosity about their robustness in DG systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/white-box-multi-objective-adversarial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSPDet3D: Dynamic Spatial Pruning for 3D Small Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspdet3d-dynamic-spatial-pruning-for-3d-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With in-depth study, we find increasing the spatial resolution of the feature maps significantly boosts the performance of 3D small object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dspdet3d-dynamic-spatial-pruning-for-3d-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HD2Reg: Hierarchical Descriptors and Detectors for Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd2reg-hierarchical-descriptors-and-detectors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature Descriptors and Detectors are two main components of feature-based point cloud registration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hd2reg-hierarchical-descriptors-and-detectors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparsifying Bayesian neural networks with latent binary variables and normalizing flows</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsifying-bayesian-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we will consider two extensions to the LBBNN method: Firstly, by using the local reparametrization trick (LRT) to sample the hidden units directly, we get a more computationally efficient algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsifying-bayesian-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduction of Class Activation Uncertainty with Background Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduction-of-class-activation-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multitask learning is a popular approach to training high-performing neural networks with improved generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduction-of-class-activation-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scope Restriction for Scalable Real-Time Railway Rescheduling: An Exploratory Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scope-restriction-for-scalable-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we propose defining a core problem that restricts a rescheduling problem in response to a disturbance to only trains that need to be rescheduled, hence restricting the scope in both time and space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scope-restriction-for-scalable-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generic and Robust Root Cause Localization for Multi-Dimensional Data in Online Service Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-and-robust-root-cause-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such attribute combinations are substantial clues to the underlying root causes and thus are called root causes of multidimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-and-robust-root-cause-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Acquisition of Fine-grained Visual Concepts by Exploiting Semantics of Generic Characterizations in Discourse</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-acquisition-of-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interactive Task Learning (ITL) concerns learning about unforeseen domain concepts via natural interactions with human users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-acquisition-of-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT for Semi-Automated Data Science: Introducing CAAFE for Context-Aware Automated Feature Engineering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-for-semi-automated-data-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method produces both Python code for creating new features and explanations for the utility of the generated features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-for-semi-automated-data-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MindGames: Targeting Theory of Mind in Large Language Models with Dynamic Epistemic Modal Logic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindgames-targeting-theory-of-mind-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theory of Mind (ToM) is a critical component of intelligence, yet accurately measuring it continues to be a subject of debate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mindgames-targeting-theory-of-mind-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composite Motion Learning with Task Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-motion-learning-with-task-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to existing data-driven approaches using reinforcement learning that imitate full-body motions, we learn decoupled motions for specific body parts from multiple reference motions simultaneously and directly by leveraging the use of multiple discriminators in a GAN-like setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composite-motion-learning-with-task-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAMO-NLP at SemEval-2023 Task 2: A Unified Retrieval-augmented System for Multilingual Named Entity Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-nlp-at-semeval-2023-task-2-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, we discover that the limited context length causes the retrieval knowledge to be invisible to the model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-nlp-at-semeval-2023-task-2-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repairing Deep Neural Networks Based on Behavior Imitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repairing-deep-neural-networks-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For the fine-tuning repair process, BIRDNN analyzes the behavior differences of neurons on positive and negative samples to identify the most responsible neurons for the erroneous behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repairing-deep-neural-networks-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLI4CT: Multi-Evidence Natural Language Inference for Clinical Trial Reports</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nli4ct-multi-evidence-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel resource to advance research on NLI for reasoning on CTRs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nli4ct-multi-evidence-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuromodulation Gated Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromodulation-gated-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel architecture, the Neuromodulation Gated Transformer (NGT), which is a simple implementation of neuromodulation in transformers via a multiplicative effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromodulation-gated-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Graph Convolutional Subspace Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-graph-convolutional-subspace</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spectral-type subspace clustering algorithms have shown excellent performance in many subspace clustering applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-graph-convolutional-subspace</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Encoding For Healthcare Data Democratisation and Information Leakage Prevention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-encoding-for-healthcare-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental evaluation highlights that models trained on encoded time-series data effectively uphold the information bottleneck principle and hence, exhibit lesser information leakage from trained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-encoding-for-healthcare-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Decision Trees with Gradient Descent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-decision-trees-with-gradient-descent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decision Trees (DTs) are commonly used for many machine learning tasks due to their high degree of interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-decision-trees-with-gradient-descent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Segment Anything Model (SAM) Boost Medical Image Segmentation?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-segment-anything-model-sam-boost-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the flexibility of prompting, foundation models have become the dominant force in the domains of natural language processing and image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-segment-anything-model-sam-boost-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining bias-target Alignment from Voronoi Cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-bias-target-alignment-from-voronoi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite significant research efforts, deep neural networks are still vulnerable to biases: this raises concerns about their fairness and limits their generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mining-bias-target-alignment-from-voronoi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentence Embedding Leaks More Information than You Expect: Generative Embedding Inversion Attack to Recover the Whole Sentence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-embedding-leaks-more-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we further investigate the information leakage issue and propose a generative embedding inversion attack (GEIA) that aims to reconstruct input sequences based only on their sentence embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-embedding-leaks-more-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Graph Contrastive Learning for Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the paper, we delve into the misconception and propose Multi-GNN and Augmented Graph contrastive framework MAG, which unified the existing GCAD methods in the contrastive self-supervised perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-graph-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuttlefish: Low-Rank Model Training without All the Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cuttlefish leverages the observation that after a few epochs of full-rank training, the stable rank (i. e., an approximation of the true rank) of each layer stabilizes at a constant value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cuttlefish-low-rank-model-training-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Graph Learning and Model Fitting in Laplacian Regularized Stratified Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Laplacian regularized stratified models (LRSM) are models that utilize the explicit or implicit network structure of the sub-problems as defined by the categorical features called strata (e. g., age, region, time, forecast horizon, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-graph-learning-and-model-fitting-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PGB: A PubMed Graph Benchmark for Heterogeneous Network Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgb-a-pubmed-graph-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although graph mining research via heterogeneous graph neural networks has taken center stage, it remains unclear whether these approaches capture the heterogeneity of the PubMed database, a vast digital repository containing over 33 million articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pgb-a-pubmed-graph-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VendorLink: An NLP approach for Identifying &amp; Linking Vendor Migrants &amp; Potential Aliases on Darknet Markets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vendorlink-an-nlp-approach-for-identifying</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The anonymity on the Darknet allows vendors to stay undetected by using multiple vendor aliases or frequently migrating between markets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vendorlink-an-nlp-approach-for-identifying</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controllable Visual-Tactile Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-visual-tactile-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep generative models have various content creation applications such as graphic design, e-commerce, and virtual Try-on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controllable-visual-tactile-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZipIt! Merging Models from Different Tasks without Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While this works for models trained on the same task, we find that this fails to account for the differences in models trained on disjoint tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipit-merging-models-from-different-tasks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faithful Question Answering with Monte-Carlo Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose FAME (FAithful question answering with MontE-carlo planning) to answer questions based on faithful reasoning steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faithful-question-answering-with-monte-carlo</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panda LLM: Training Data and Evaluation for Open-Sourced Chinese Instruction-Following Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-llm-training-data-and-evaluation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This project focuses on enhancing open-source large language models through instruction-tuning and providing comprehensive evaluations of their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panda-llm-training-data-and-evaluation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Dialogue Topic Segmentation with Topic-aware Utterance Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dialogue Topic Segmentation (DTS) plays an essential role in a variety of dialogue modeling tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-dialogue-topic-segmentation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedCBO: Reaching Group Consensus in Clustered Federated Learning through Consensus-based Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is an important framework in modern machine learning that seeks to integrate the training of learning models from multiple users, each user having their own local data set, in a way that is sensitive to data privacy and to communication loss constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedcbo-reaching-group-consensus-in-clustered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled Contrastive Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-contrastive-collaborative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies show that graph neural networks (GNNs) are prevalent to model high-order relationships for collaborative filtering (CF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-contrastive-collaborative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understand Waiting Time in Transaction Fee Mechanism: An Interdisciplinary Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understand-waiting-time-in-transaction-fee</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study identified NFT drops as a unique source of market congestion -- holiday effects -- beyond trend and season effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understand-waiting-time-in-transaction-fee</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LatentAugment: Dynamically Optimized Latent Probabilities of Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although data augmentation is a powerful technique for improving the performance of image classification tasks, it is difficult to identify the best augmentation policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latentaugment-dynamically-optimized-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smaller3d: Smaller Models for 3D Semantic Segmentation Using Minkowski Engine and Knowledge Distillation Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smaller3d-smaller-models-for-3d-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are various optimization techniques in the realm of 3D, including point cloud-based approaches that use mesh, texture, and voxels which optimize how you store, and how do calculate in 3D.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smaller3d-smaller-models-for-3d-semantic</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
