<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 21:07:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Suicide Prevention from Bipolar Disorder with Temporal Symptom-Aware Multitask Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-suicide-prevention-from-bipolar</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Bipolar disorder (BD) is closely associated with an increased risk of suicide.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-suicide-prevention-from-bipolar</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IoT-Based Air Quality Monitoring System with Machine Learning for Accurate and Real-time Data Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iot-based-air-quality-monitoring-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the issue of air pollution awareness, Air Pollution Monitoring systems are used to measure the concentration of gases like CO2, smoke, alcohol, benzene, and NH3 present in the air.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iot-based-air-quality-monitoring-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuro-Symbolic Sudoku Solver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-sudoku-solver</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our study, we showcase an NLM which is capable of obtaining 100% accuracy for solving a Sudoku with empty cells ranging from 3 to 10.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuro-symbolic-sudoku-solver</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting multiple sclerosis lesion segmentation through attention mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-multiple-sclerosis-lesion-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic resonance imaging is a fundamental tool to reach a diagnosis of multiple sclerosis and monitoring its progression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-multiple-sclerosis-lesion-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using joint training speaker encoder with consistency loss to achieve cross-lingual voice conversion and expressive voice conversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-joint-training-speaker-encoder-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice conversion systems have made significant advancements in terms of naturalness and similarity in common voice conversion tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-joint-training-speaker-encoder-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHARCS: Shared Concept Space for Explainable Multimodal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharcs-shared-concept-space-for-explainable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal learning is an essential paradigm for addressing complex real-world problems, where individual data modalities are typically insufficient to accurately solve a given modelling task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharcs-shared-concept-space-for-explainable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WaveMixSR: A Resource-efficient Neural Network for Image Super-resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavemixsr-a-resource-efficient-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new neural network -- WaveMixSR -- for image super-resolution based on WaveMix architecture which uses a 2D-discrete wavelet transform for spatial token-mixing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavemixsr-a-resource-efficient-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WavePaint: Resource-efficient Token-mixer for Self-supervised Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavepaint-resource-efficient-token-mixer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current state-of-the-art models for image inpainting are computationally heavy as they are based on transformer or CNN backbones that are trained in adversarial or diffusion settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wavepaint-resource-efficient-token-mixer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursive Algorithmic Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-algorithmic-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning models that execute algorithms can enable us to address a key problem in deep learning: generalizing to out-of-distribution data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-algorithmic-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisCo: Disentangled Control for Referring Human Dance Generation in Real World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-disentangled-control-for-referring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative AI has made significant strides in computer vision, particularly in image/video synthesis conditioned on text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-disentangled-control-for-referring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Music Hierarchies with a Graph-Based Neural Decoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-music-hierarchies-with-a-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes a data-driven framework to parse musical sequences into dependency trees, which are hierarchical structures used in music cognition research and music analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-music-hierarchies-with-a-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Predictive Accuracy of Neural Temporal Point Process Models for Continuous-time Event Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-predictive-accuracy-of-neural-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we present a comprehensive large-scale experimental study that systematically evaluates the predictive accuracy of state-of-the-art neural TPP models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-predictive-accuracy-of-neural-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAUTILUS: boosting Bayesian importance nested sampling with deep learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nautilus-boosting-bayesian-importance-nested</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel approach to boost the efficiency of the importance nested sampling (INS) technique for Bayesian posterior and evidence estimation using deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nautilus-boosting-bayesian-importance-nested</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sampling weights of deep neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-weights-of-deep-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For Barron functions, we show that the $L^2$-approximation error of sampled shallow networks decreases with the square root of the number of neurons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sampling-weights-of-deep-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Time and Memory Efficiency of Genetic Algorithms by Storing Populations as Minimum Spanning Trees of Patches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-time-and-memory-efficiency-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many applications of evolutionary algorithms the computational cost of applying operators and storing populations is comparable to the cost of fitness evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-time-and-memory-efficiency-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralFuse: Learning to Improve the Accuracy of Access-Limited Neural Network Inference in Low-Voltage Regimes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralfuse-learning-to-improve-the-accuracy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we introduce NeuralFuse, a novel add-on module that addresses the accuracy-energy tradeoff in low-voltage regimes by learning input transformations to generate error-resistant data representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralfuse-learning-to-improve-the-accuracy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ducho: A Unified Framework for the Extraction of Multimodal Features in Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-a-unified-framework-for-the-extraction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the outlined aspects, we propose Ducho, a unified framework for the extraction of multimodal features in recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ducho-a-unified-framework-for-the-extraction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BinaryViT: Pushing Binary Vision Transformers Towards Convolutional Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binaryvit-pushing-binary-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increasing popularity and the increasing size of vision transformers (ViTs), there has been an increasing interest in making them more efficient and less computationally costly for deployment on edge devices with limited computing resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/binaryvit-pushing-binary-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PCDAL: A Perturbation Consistency-Driven Active Learning Approach for Medical Image Segmentation and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcdal-a-perturbation-consistency-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we propose an AL-based method that can be simultaneously applied to 2D medical image classification, segmentation, and 3D medical image segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pcdal-a-perturbation-consistency-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ManimML: Communicating Machine Learning Architectures with Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manimml-communicating-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A user can take a preexisting neural network architecture and easily write a specification for an animation in ManimML, which will then automatically compose animations for different components of the system into a final animation of the entire neural network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/manimml-communicating-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing the Performance of 1D-Convolution Neural Networks to Predict Concentration of Mixture Components from Raman Spectra</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-performance-of-1d-convolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finding the optimal algorithm for a specific bioreactor environment is challenging due to the lack of freely available Raman mixture datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-the-performance-of-1d-convolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Representation Power of SPLADE Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-representation-power-of-splade</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SPLADE (SParse Lexical AnD Expansion) model is a highly effective approach to learned sparse retrieval, where documents are represented by term impact scores derived from large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-representation-power-of-splade</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIS-FM: 3D Medical Image Segmentation using Foundation Models Pretrained on a Large-Scale Unannotated Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mis-fm-3d-medical-image-segmentation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed model was pretrained with 110k unannotated 3D CT volumes, and experiments with different downstream segmentation targets including head and neck organs, thoracic/abdominal organs showed that our pretrained model largely outperformed training from scratch and several state-of-the-art self-supervised training methods and segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mis-fm-3d-medical-image-segmentation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detect Any Deepfakes: Segment Anything Meets Face Forgery Detection and Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-any-deepfakes-segment-anything-meets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancements in computer vision have stimulated remarkable progress in face forgery techniques, capturing the dedicated attention of researchers committed to detecting forgeries and precisely localizing manipulated areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detect-any-deepfakes-segment-anything-meets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEDLAM: A Synthetic Dataset of Bodies Exhibiting Detailed Lifelike Animated Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bedlam-a-synthetic-dataset-of-bodies-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BEDLAM is useful for a variety of tasks and all images, ground truth bodies, 3D clothing, support code, and more are available for research purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bedlam-a-synthetic-dataset-of-bodies-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised 3D registration through optimization-guided cyclical self-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-3d-registration-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art deep learning-based registration methods employ three different learning strategies: supervised learning, which requires costly manual annotations, unsupervised learning, which heavily relies on hand-crafted similarity metrics designed by domain experts, or learning from synthetic data, which introduces a domain shift.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-3d-registration-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RL4CO: an Extensive Reinforcement Learning for Combinatorial Optimization Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4co-an-extensive-reinforcement-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope RL4CO will encourage the exploration of novel solutions to complex real-world tasks, allowing to compare with existing methods through a standardized interface that decouples the science from the software engineering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rl4co-an-extensive-reinforcement-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEMD-ABSA: A Multi-Element Multi-Domain Dataset for Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memd-absa-a-multi-element-multi-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect-based sentiment analysis is a long-standing research interest in the field of opinion mining, and in recent years, researchers have gradually shifted their focus from simple ABSA subtasks to end-to-end multi-element ABSA tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memd-absa-a-multi-element-multi-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkiROS2: A skill-based Robot Control Platform for ROS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skiros2-a-skill-based-robot-control-platform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The need for autonomous robot systems in both the service and the industrial domain is larger than ever.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skiros2-a-skill-based-robot-control-platform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Demographic Data Generation for Card Fraud Detection Using GANs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-demographic-data-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study can help improve the cognition of synthetic data and further explore the application of synthetic data generation in card fraud detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-demographic-data-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alternative Telescopic Displacement: An Efficient Multimodal Alignment Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alternative-telescopic-displacement-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature alignment is the primary means of fusing multimodal data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alternative-telescopic-displacement-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foundation Model for Endoscopy Video Analysis via Large-scale Self-supervised Pre-train</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-for-endoscopy-video-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models have exhibited remarkable success in various applications, such as disease diagnosis and text report generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundation-model-for-endoscopy-video-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singing Voice Synthesis Using Differentiable LPC and Glottal-Flow-Inspired Wavetables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singing-voice-synthesis-using-differentiable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces GlOttal-flow LPC Filter (GOLF), a novel method for singing voice synthesis (SVS) that exploits the physical characteristics of the human voice using differentiable digital signal processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singing-voice-synthesis-using-differentiable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate PET Reconstruction from Reduced Set of Measurements based on GMM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-pet-reconstruction-from-reduced-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A vast majority of PET imaging methods are based on reconstruction model that is defined by values on some pixel/voxel grid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-pet-reconstruction-from-reduced-set</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numerical Data Imputation for Multimodal Data Sets: A Probabilistic Nearest-Neighbor Kernel Density Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-data-imputation-for-multimodal-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare our method with previous data imputation methods using artificial and real-world data with different data missing scenarios and various data missing rates, and show that our method can cope with complex original data structure, yields lower data imputation errors, and provides probabilistic estimates with higher likelihood than current methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/numerical-data-imputation-for-multimodal-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparison of Single- and Multi- Objective Optimization Quality for Evolutionary Equation Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-single-and-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evolutionary differential equation discovery proved to be a tool to obtain equations with less a priori assumptions than conventional approaches, such as sparse symbolic regression over the complete possible terms library.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparison-of-single-and-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obeying the Order: Introducing Ordered Transfer Hyperparameter Optimisation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obeying-the-order-introducing-ordered</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ordered transfer hyperparameter optimisation (OTHPO), a version of transfer learning for hyperparameter optimisation (HPO) where the tasks follow a sequential order.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/obeying-the-order-introducing-ordered</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Sampling-based Meta-Learning for Molecular Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sampling-based-meta-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To effectively utilize many-to-many correlations of molecules and properties, we propose a Graph Sampling-based Meta-learning (GS-Meta) framework for few-shot molecular property prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-sampling-based-meta-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical Phase and Instrument Recognition: How to identify appropriate Dataset Splits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-phase-and-instrument-recognition-how</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Purpose: The development of machine learning models for surgical workflow and instrument recognition from temporal data represents a challenging task due to the complex nature of surgical workflows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-phase-and-instrument-recognition-how</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filtered-Guided Diffusion: Fast Filter Guidance for Black-Box Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filtered-guided-diffusion-fast-filter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that much of this low-level control can be achieved without additional training or any access to features of the diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filtered-guided-diffusion-fast-filter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimPLe: Similarity-Aware Propagation Learning for Weakly-Supervised Breast Cancer Segmentation in DCE-MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-similarity-aware-propagation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The network first utilizes the pseudo-masks generated using the extreme points to train itself, by minimizing a contrastive loss, which encourages the network to learn more representative features for cancerous voxels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-similarity-aware-propagation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokenization and the Noiseless Channel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenization-and-the-noiseless-channel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subword tokenization is a key part of many NLP pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenization-and-the-noiseless-channel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computationally Assisted Quality Control for Public Health Data Streams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computationally-assisted-quality-control-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing outlier detection frameworks perform poorly on this task because they do not account for the data volume or for the statistical properties of public health streams.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computationally-assisted-quality-control-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised MRI Reconstruction with Unrolled Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-mri-reconstruction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) produces excellent soft tissue contrast, albeit it is an inherently slow imaging modality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-mri-reconstruction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Drunkard's Odometry: Estimating Camera Motion in Deforming Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-drunkard-s-odometry-estimating-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating camera motion in deformable scenes poses a complex and open research challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-drunkard-s-odometry-estimating-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provable Advantage of Curriculum Learning on Parity Targets with Mixed Inputs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-advantage-of-curriculum-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results have shown that curriculum learning, i. e., presenting simpler examples before more complex ones, can improve the efficiency of learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provable-advantage-of-curriculum-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-source Semantic Graph-based Multimodal Sarcasm Explanation Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-semantic-graph-based-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Sarcasm Explanation (MuSE) is a new yet challenging task, which aims to generate a natural language sentence for a multimodal social post (an image as well as its caption) to explain why it contains sarcasm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-source-semantic-graph-based-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelangelo: Conditional 3D Shape Generation based on Shape-Image-Text Aligned Latent Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/michelangelo-conditional-3d-shape-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel alignment-before-generation approach to tackle the challenging task of generating general 3D shapes based on 2D images or texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/michelangelo-conditional-3d-shape-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond CO2 Emissions: The Overlooked Impact of Water Consumption of Information Retrieval Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-co2-emissions-the-overlooked-impact-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As in other fields of artificial intelligence, the information retrieval community has grown interested in investigating the power consumption associated with neural models, particularly models of search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-co2-emissions-the-overlooked-impact-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would I have gotten that reward? Long-term credit assignment by counterfactual contribution analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/would-i-have-gotten-that-reward-long-term</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that measuring contributions w. r. t.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/would-i-have-gotten-that-reward-long-term</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
