<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 09:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Contextual Emotion Recognition Using Transformer Based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to increase the precision of emotion identification in text, this research suggests a context-aware emotion recognition system employing transformer models, especially BERT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-emotion-recognition-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Distortion-free Watermarks for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-distortion-free-watermarks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We generate watermarked text by mapping a sequence of random numbers -- which we compute using a randomized watermark key -- to a sample from the language model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-distortion-free-watermarks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Offline Reinforcement Learning on Real-Robot Hardware</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-offline-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To coordinate the efforts of the research community toward tackling this problem, we propose a benchmark including: i) a large collection of data for offline learning from a dexterous manipulation platform on two tasks, obtained with capable RL agents trained in simulation; ii) the option to execute learned policies on a real-world robotic system and a simulation for efficient debugging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-offline-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shrink-Perturb Improves Architecture Mixing during Population Based Training for Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrink-perturb-improves-architecture-mixing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we show that simultaneously training and mixing neural networks is a promising way to conduct Neural Architecture Search (NAS).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shrink-perturb-improves-architecture-mixing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskExpert: Dynamically Assembling Multi-Task Representations with Memorial Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskexpert-dynamically-assembling-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, to establish long-range modeling of the task-specific representations from different layers of TaskExpert, we design a multi-task feature memory that updates at each layer and acts as an additional feature expert for dynamic task-specific feature decoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskexpert-dynamically-assembling-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLIC++: Linear Complexity Multi-Reference Entropy Modeling for Learned Image Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlic-linear-complexity-multi-reference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, multi-reference entropy model has been proposed, which captures channel-wise, local spatial, and global spatial correlations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlic-linear-complexity-multi-reference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defocus Blur Synthesis and Deblurring via Interpolation and Extrapolation in Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defocus-blur-synthesis-and-deblurring-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train autoencoders with implicit and explicit regularization techniques to enforce linearity relations among the representations of different blur levels in the latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defocus-blur-synthesis-and-deblurring-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Solution to Co-occurrence Bias: Attributes Disentanglement via Mutual Information Minimization for Pedestrian Attribute Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-co-occurrence-bias-attributes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent studies on pedestrian attribute recognition progress with either explicit or implicit modeling of the co-occurrence among attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-solution-to-co-occurrence-bias-attributes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCID-GAN: Conditional Generative Models to Locate Unfairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucid-gan-conditional-generative-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most group fairness notions detect unethical biases by computing statistical parity metrics on a model's output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucid-gan-conditional-generative-models-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recovering high-quality FODs from a reduced number of diffusion-weighted images using a model-driven deep learning architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-high-quality-fods-from-a-reduced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a spherical deconvolution network, a model-driven deep learning FOD reconstruction architecture, that ensures intermediate and output FODs produced by the network are consistent with the input DWI signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recovering-high-quality-fods-from-a-reduced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODTlearn: A Package for Learning Optimal Decision Trees for Prediction and Prescription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odtlearn-a-package-for-learning-optimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ODTLearn is an open-source Python package that provides methods for learning optimal decision trees for high-stakes predictive and prescriptive tasks based on the mixed-integer optimization (MIO) framework proposed in Aghaei et al. (2019) and several of its extensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odtlearn-a-package-for-learning-optimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Framework to Automatically Determine the Quality of Open Data Catalogs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framework-to-automatically-determine-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data catalogs play a crucial role in modern data-driven organizations by facilitating the discovery, understanding, and utilization of diverse data assets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/framework-to-automatically-determine-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Instance Learning Framework with Masked Hard Instance Mining for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-framework-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The whole slide image (WSI) classification is often formulated as a multiple instance learning (MIL) problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiple-instance-learning-framework-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Lexical Simplification via Paraphrase Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-lexical-simplification-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After feeding the input sentence into the encoder of paraphrase modeling, we generate the substitutes based on a novel decoding strategy that concentrates solely on the lexical variations of the complex word.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-lexical-simplification-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is this model reliable for everyone? Testing for strong calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-model-reliable-for-everyone-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a well-calibrated risk prediction model, the average predicted probability is close to the true event rate for any given subgroup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-this-model-reliable-for-everyone-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'What are you referring to?' Evaluating the Ability of Multi-Modal Dialogue Models to Process Clarificational Exchanges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-you-referring-to-evaluating-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Referential ambiguities arise in dialogue when a referring expression does not uniquely identify the intended referent for the addressee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-are-you-referring-to-evaluating-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Recipe for Federated Learning Under Statistical Heterogeneity Experimental Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-recipe-for-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many of the works use inconsistent experimental settings and there are no comprehensive studies on the effect of FL-specific experimental variables on the results and practical insights for a more comparable and consistent FL experimental setup.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-recipe-for-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improvable Gap Balancing for Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvable-gap-balancing-for-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, following the loss balancing framework, we propose two novel improvable gap balancing (IGB) algorithms for MTL: one takes a simple heuristic, and the other (for the first time) deploys deep reinforcement learning for MTL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improvable-gap-balancing-for-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Nonlinear Projections for Reduced-Order Modeling of Dynamical Systems using Constrained Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-projections-for-reduced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To begin to address these issues, we introduce a parametric class of nonlinear projections described by constrained autoencoder neural networks in which both the manifold and the projection fibers are learned from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-nonlinear-projections-for-reduced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differential Evolution Algorithm based Hyper-Parameters Selection of Transformer Neural Network Model for Load Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply several metaheuristics namely Differential Evolution to find the optimal hyperparameters of the Transformer-based Neural Network to produce accurate forecasts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differential-evolution-algorithm-based-hyper</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Learning Behaviour of In-context Learning: A Comparison with Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-learning-behaviour-of-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable capacity for in-context learning (ICL), where learning a new task from just a few training examples is done without being explicitly pre-trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-learning-behaviour-of-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Road to Quality is Paved with Good Revisions: A Detailed Evaluation Methodology for Revision Policies in Incremental Sequence Labelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-road-to-quality-is-paved-with-good</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Incremental dialogue model components produce a sequence of output prefixes based on incoming input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-road-to-quality-is-paved-with-good</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to generate hedges in peer-tutoring interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-generate-hedges-in-peer-tutoring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the application of machine learning techniques to predict where hedging occurs in peer-tutoring interactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-generate-hedges-in-peer-tutoring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is One Epoch All You Need For Multi-Fidelity Hyperparameter Optimization?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-one-epoch-all-you-need-for-multi-fidelity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization (HPO) is crucial for fine-tuning machine learning models but can be computationally expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/is-one-epoch-all-you-need-for-multi-fidelity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-attention Graph Pooling for Efficient Pairwise Graph Interaction Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-attention-graph-pooling-for-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have proven to be effective in processing and learning from graph-structured data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-attention-graph-pooling-for-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From continuous-time formulations to discretization schemes: tensor trains and robust regression for BSDEs and parabolic PDEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-continuous-time-formulations-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The numerical approximation of partial differential equations (PDEs) poses formidable challenges in high dimensions since classical grid-based methods suffer from the so-called curse of dimensionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-continuous-time-formulations-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Data Generation in Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-data-generation-in-vision-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research in language-guided visual navigation has demonstrated a significant demand for the diversity of traversable environments and the quantity of supervision for training generalizable agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-data-generation-in-vision-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAFuser: Towards Omni-Aperture Fusion for Light Field Semantic Segmentation of Road Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oafuser-towards-omni-aperture-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To avoid feature loss during network propagation and simultaneously streamline the redundant information from the light field camera, we present a simple yet very effective Sub-Aperture Fusion Module (SAFM) to embed sub-aperture images into angular features without any additional memory cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oafuser-towards-omni-aperture-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum-noise-limited optical neural networks operating at a few quanta per activation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-noise-limited-optical-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We experimentally demonstrated MNIST classification with a test accuracy of 98% using an optical neural network with a hidden layer operating in the single-photon regime; the optical energy used to perform the classification corresponds to 0. 008 photons per multiply-accumulate (MAC) operation, which is equivalent to 0. 003 attojoules of optical energy per MAC.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-noise-limited-optical-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Backdoor Defense with Non-Adversarial Backdoor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-defense-with-non-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks (DNNs) are vulnerable to backdoor attack, which does not affect the network's performance on clean data but would manipulate the network behavior once a trigger pattern is added.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/backdoor-defense-with-non-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale-aware Test-time Click Adaptation for Pulmonary Nodule and Mass Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-test-time-click-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments on both open-source and in-house datasets consistently demonstrate the effectiveness of the proposed method over some CNN and Transformer-based segmentation methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scale-aware-test-time-click-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attentive Multimodal Fusion for Optical and Scene Flow</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-multimodal-fusion-for-optical-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an investigation into the estimation of optical and scene flow using RGBD information in scenarios where the RGB modality is affected by noise or captured in dark environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attentive-multimodal-fusion-for-optical-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI for Medical Imaging: extending the MONAI Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-for-medical-imaging-extending</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We have implemented these models in a generalisable fashion, illustrating that their results can be extended to 2D or 3D scenarios, including medical images with different modalities (like CT, MRI, and X-Ray data) and from different anatomical areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-ai-for-medical-imaging-extending</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised AI for Efficient Analysis of 3D Pathology Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-ai-for-efficient-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human tissue and its constituent cells form a microenvironment that is fundamentally three-dimensional (3D).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-ai-for-efficient-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take-A-Photo: 3D-to-2D Generative Pre-training of Point Cloud Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-photo-3d-to-2d-generative-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel 3D-to-2D generative pre-training method that is adaptable to any point cloud model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-a-photo-3d-to-2d-generative-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning-powered Pricing of the Multidimensional Passport Option</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-powered-pricing-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These approaches prove to be successful for pricing the passport option in one-dimensional and multi-dimensional uncorrelated BS markets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-powered-pricing-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture of Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose the Gated Self-Supervised Learning method to improve image classification which use more than one transformation as pretext task and uses the Mixture of Expert architecture as a gating network in combining each pretext task so that the model automatically can study and focus more on the most useful augmentations for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Explanations for Graph Classification Through the Lenses of Density</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual examples have emerged as an effective approach to produce simple and understandable post-hoc explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-explanations-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Dynamic Range Imaging via Visual Attention Modules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-imaging-via-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to High Dynamic Range (HDR) imaging methods, the scope of photography has seen profound changes recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-dynamic-range-imaging-via-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training Vision Transformers with Very Limited Synthesized Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vision-transformers-with-very</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior work on FDSL has shown that pre-training vision transformers on such synthetic datasets can yield competitive accuracy on a wide range of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-vision-transformers-with-very</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Natural Language Inference in Arabic using Transformer Models and Linguistically Informed Pre-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-natural-language-inference-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the classification of Arabic text data in the field of Natural Language Processing (NLP), with a particular focus on Natural Language Inference (NLI) and Contradiction Detection (CD).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-natural-language-inference-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taxonomy Adaptive Cross-Domain Adaptation in Medical Imaging via Optimization Trajectory Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-adaptive-cross-domain-adaptation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of automated medical image analysis depends on large-scale and expert-annotated training sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taxonomy-adaptive-cross-domain-adaptation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P2C: Self-Supervised Point Cloud Completion from Single Partial Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2c-self-supervised-point-cloud-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud completion aims to recover the complete shape based on a partial observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p2c-self-supervised-point-cloud-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test Time Adaptation for Blind Image Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-adaptation-for-blind-image-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce two novel quality-relevant auxiliary tasks at the batch and sample levels to enable TTA for blind IQA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/test-time-adaptation-for-blind-image-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Age Estimation Using Structural MRI: A Clustered Federated Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-age-estimation-using-structural-mri-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating brain age based on structural Magnetic Resonance Imaging (MRI) is one of the most challenging and prominent areas of research in recent medical imaging and neuroscience studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-age-estimation-using-structural-mri-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Adapt or Not to Adapt? Real-Time Adaptation for Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-adapt-or-not-to-adapt-real-time-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The goal of Online Domain Adaptation for semantic segmentation is to handle unforeseeable domain changes that occur during deployment, like sudden weather events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/to-adapt-or-not-to-adapt-real-time-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Interaction Paradigm for Complex EDA Software Leveraging GPT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-interaction-paradigm-for-complex-eda</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the rapidly growing field of electronic design automation (EDA), professional software such as KiCad, Cadence , and Altium Designer provide increasingly extensive design functionalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/new-interaction-paradigm-for-complex-eda</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTNet for micro-expression recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-for-micro-expression-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The transformer layer is used to focus on representing local minor muscle movement with local self-attention in each area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-for-micro-expression-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLDiffusion: Learning Degradation Representations in Diffusion Models for Low-Light Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lldiffusion-learning-degradation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this limitation by proposing a degradation-aware learning scheme for LLIE using diffusion models, which effectively integrates degradation and image priors into the diffusion process, resulting in improved image enhancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lldiffusion-learning-degradation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IML-ViT: Image Manipulation Localization by Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iml-vit-image-manipulation-localization-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, artifacts are sensitive to image resolution, amplified under multi-scale features, and massive at the manipulation border.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iml-vit-image-manipulation-localization-by</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
