<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 21:06:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Collapse Inspired Feature-Classifier Alignment for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we deal with this misalignment dilemma in FSCIL inspired by the recently discovered phenomenon named neural collapse, which reveals that the last-layer features of the same class will collapse into a vertex, and the vertices of all classes are aligned with the classifier prototypes, which are formed as a simplex equiangular tight frame (ETF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-collapse-inspired-feature-classifier</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Power Laws for Hyperparameter Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-power-laws-for-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hyperparameter optimization is an important subfield of machine learning that focuses on tuning the hyperparameters of a chosen algorithm to achieve peak performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-power-laws-for-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADAPT: Action-aware Driving Caption Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-action-aware-driving-caption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge the gap, we propose an end-to-end transformer-based architecture, ADAPT (Action-aware Driving cAPtion Transformer), which provides user-friendly natural language narrations and reasoning for each decision making step of autonomous vehicular control and action.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adapt-action-aware-driving-caption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Lexical Borrowings from Dominant Languages in Multilingual Wordlists</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-lexical-borrowings-from-dominant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language contact is a pervasive phenomenon reflected in the borrowing of words from donor to recipient languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-lexical-borrowings-from-dominant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Choice Functions with Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-choice-functions-with-gaussian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Gaussian Process model to learn choice functions from choice-data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-choice-functions-with-gaussian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For the Underrepresented in Gender Bias Research: Chinese Name Gender Prediction with Heterogeneous Graph Attention Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-the-underrepresented-in-gender-bias</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We open-source a more balanced multi-character dataset from an official source together with our code, hoping to help future research promoting gender equality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/for-the-underrepresented-in-gender-bias</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EfficientRep:An Efficient Repvgg-style ConvNets with Hardware-aware Neural Network Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientrep-an-efficient-repvgg-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, how to design a neural network to efficiently use the computing ability and memory bandwidth of hardware is a critical problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficientrep-an-efficient-repvgg-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPLUG-2: A Modularized Multi-modal Foundation Model Across Text, Image and Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-2-a-modularized-multi-modal-foundation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to predominant paradigms of solely relying on sequence-to-sequence generation or encoder-based instance discrimination, mPLUG-2 introduces a multi-module composition network by sharing common universal modules for modality collaboration and disentangling different modality modules to deal with modality entanglement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-2-a-modularized-multi-modal-foundation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stable Target Field for Reduced Variance Score Estimation in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-target-field-for-reduced-variance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that the procedure indeed helps in the challenging intermediate regime by reducing (the trace of) the covariance of training targets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stable-target-field-for-reduced-variance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>W2SAT: Learning to generate SAT instances from Weighted Literal Incidence Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/w2sat-learning-to-generate-sat-instances-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Boolean Satisfiability (SAT) problem stands out as an attractive NP-complete problem in theoretic computer science and plays a central role in a broad spectrum of computing-related applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/w2sat-learning-to-generate-sat-instances-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HunSum-1: an Abstractive Summarization Dataset for Hungarian</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunsum-1-an-abstractive-summarization-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce HunSum-1: a dataset for Hungarian abstractive summarization, consisting of 1. 14M news articles.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunsum-1-an-abstractive-summarization-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An automated, geometry-based method for the analysis of hippocampal thickness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-automated-geometry-based-method-for-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose an automated, geometry-based approach for the unfolding, point-wise correspondence, and local analysis of hippocampal shape features such as thickness and curvature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-automated-geometry-based-method-for-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Generalized Zero-Shot Learners for Open-Domain Image Geolocalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalized-zero-shot-learners-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image geolocalization is the challenging task of predicting the geographic coordinates of origin for a given photo.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalized-zero-shot-learners-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dictionary-based Manifold Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-based-manifold-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a paradigm for interpretable Manifold Learning for scientific data analysis, whereby we parametrize a manifold with $d$ smooth functions from a scientist-provided dictionary of meaningful, domain-related functions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dictionary-based-manifold-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIDE: A Purely Spike-based Method for Training Feedback Spiking Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spide-a-purely-spike-based-method-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study spike-based implicit differentiation on the equilibrium state (SPIDE) that extends the recently proposed training method, implicit differentiation on the equilibrium state (IDE), for supervised learning with purely spike-based computation, which demonstrates the potential for energy-efficient training of SNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spide-a-purely-spike-based-method-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Semantic Perturbations on Grover</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semantic-perturbations-on-grover</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With news and information being as easy to access as they currently are, it is more important than ever to ensure that people are not mislead by what they read.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-semantic-perturbations-on-grover</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deterministic equivalent and error universality of deep random features learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deterministic-equivalent-and-error</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Establishing this result requires proving a deterministic equivalent for traces of the deep random features sample covariance matrices which can be of independent interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deterministic-equivalent-and-error</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uniswap Liquidity Provision: An Online Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniswap-liquidity-provision-an-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Decentralized Exchanges (DEXs) are new types of marketplaces leveraging Blockchain technology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniswap-liquidity-provision-an-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Meta-Learning via Error-based Context Pruning for Implicit Neural Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-meta-learning-via-error-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To implement such context pruning, our technical novelty is three-fold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-meta-learning-via-error-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Learning of Deep Random Networks of Extensive-width</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-learning-of-deep-random-networks-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of learning a target function corresponding to a deep, extensive-width, non-linear neural network with random Gaussian weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-learning-of-deep-random-networks-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthesis-based Imaging-Differentiation Representation Learning for Multi-Sequence 3D/4D MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-based-imaging-differentiation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-sequence MRIs can be necessary for reliable diagnosis in clinical practice due to the complimentary information within sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthesis-based-imaging-differentiation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distillation Policy Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-policy-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Can we design an algorithm that can employ the off-policy data, while exploit the stable learning by sailing along the course of the on-policy walkway?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distillation-policy-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertain Quality-Diversity: Evaluation methodology and new methods for Quality-Diversity in Uncertain Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertain-quality-diversity-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, we propose a new methodology to evaluate Uncertain QD approaches, relying on a new per-generation sampling budget and a set of existing and new metrics specifically designed for Uncertain QD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertain-quality-diversity-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Prompt Tuning with Motion Cues for Open-vocabulary Video Relation Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-prompt-tuning-with-motion-cues</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Without bells and whistles, our RePro achieves a new state-of-the-art performance on two VidVRD benchmarks of not only the base training object and predicate categories, but also the unseen ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-prompt-tuning-with-motion-cues</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Few-Shot Generalization by Exploring and Exploiting Auxiliary Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-generalization-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we focus on Few-shot Learning with Auxiliary Data (FLAD), a training paradigm that assumes access to auxiliary data during few-shot learning in hopes of improving generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-few-shot-generalization-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\rm A^2Q$: Aggregation-Aware Quantization for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-a-2q-aggregation-aware-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through an in-depth analysis of the topology of GNNs, we observe that the topology of the graph leads to significant differences between nodes, and most of the nodes in a graph appear to have a small aggregation value.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rm-a-2q-aggregation-aware-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Message Passing Neural Network for Crystal Material Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-message-passing-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic material discovery with desired properties is a fundamental challenge for material sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-message-passing-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NoiseTransfer: Image Noise Generation with Contrastive Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisetransfer-image-noise-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although several real-world noisy datasets have been presented, the number of train datasets (i. e., pairs of clean and real noisy images) is limited, and acquiring more real noise datasets is laborious and expensive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noisetransfer-image-noise-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRC-RL: A Novel Visual Feature Representation Architecture for Unsupervised Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crc-rl-a-novel-visual-feature-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper addresses the problem of visual feature representation learning with an aim to improve the performance of end-to-end reinforcement learning (RL) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crc-rl-a-novel-visual-feature-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASiam: Efficient Representation Learning using Neural Architecture Search for Siamese Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nasiam-efficient-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we present NASiam, a novel approach that uses for the first time differentiable NAS to improve the multilayer perceptron projector and predictor (encoder/predictor pair) architectures inside siamese-networks-based contrastive learning frameworks (e. g., SimCLR, SimSiam, and MoCo) while preserving the simplicity of previous baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nasiam-efficient-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Counterfactual Collaborative Session-based Recommender System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-counterfactual-collaborative-session-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, COCO-SBRS adopts counterfactual inference to recommend items based on the outputs of the pre-trained recommendation model considering the causalities to alleviate the data sparsity problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-counterfactual-collaborative-session-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring QSAR Models for Activity-Cliff Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-qsar-models-for-activity-cliff</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pairs of similar compounds that only differ by a small structural modification but exhibit a large difference in their binding affinity for a given target are known as activity cliffs (ACs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-qsar-models-for-activity-cliff</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sport Task: Fine Grained Action Detection and Classification of Table Tennis Strokes from Videos for MediaEval 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sport-task-fine-grained-action-detection-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since 2021, the task also provides a stroke detection challenge from unannotated, untrimmed videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sport-task-fine-grained-action-detection-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Touché23-ValueEval Dataset for Identifying Human Values behind Arguments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-touche23-valueeval-dataset-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Touch\'e23-ValueEval Dataset for Identifying Human Values behind Arguments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-touche23-valueeval-dataset-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Hyper-To-Real Space Projections Through Euclidean Norm Meta-Heuristic Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-hyper-to-real-space-projections</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The continuous computational power growth in the last decades has made solving several optimization problems significant to humankind a tractable task; however, tackling some of them remains a challenge due to the overwhelming amount of candidate solutions to be evaluated, even by using sophisticated algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-hyper-to-real-space-projections</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZhichunRoad at Amazon KDD Cup 2022: MultiTask Pre-Training for E-Commerce Product Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zhichunroad-at-amazon-kdd-cup-2022-multitask</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a robust multilingual model to improve the quality of search results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zhichunroad-at-amazon-kdd-cup-2022-multitask</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CaraNet: Context Axial Reverse Attention Network for Segmentation of Small Medical Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caranet-context-axial-reverse-attention-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a Context Axial Reverse Attention Network (CaraNet) to improve the segmentation performance on small objects compared with several recent state-of-the-art models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/caranet-context-axial-reverse-attention-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superhuman Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superhuman-fairness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fairness of machine learning-based decisions has become an increasingly important focus in the design of supervised machine learning methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superhuman-fairness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PADL: Language-Directed Physics-Based Character Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padl-language-directed-physics-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present PADL, which leverages recent innovations in NLP in order to take steps towards developing language-directed controllers for physics-based character animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padl-language-directed-physics-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Flan Collection: Designing Data and Methods for Effective Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-flan-collection-designing-data-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the design decisions of publicly available instruction tuning methods, and break down the development of Flan 2022 (Chung et al., 2022).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-flan-collection-designing-data-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly Segmentation for High-Resolution Remote Sensing Images Based on Pixel Descriptors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-segmentation-for-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anomaly segmentation in high spatial resolution (HSR) remote sensing imagery is aimed at segmenting anomaly patterns of the earth deviating from normal patterns, which plays an important role in various Earth vision applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anomaly-segmentation-for-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NP-Match: Towards a New Probabilistic Model for Semi-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/np-match-towards-a-new-probabilistic-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we adjust neural processes (NPs) to the semi-supervised image classification task, resulting in a new method named NP-Match.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/np-match-towards-a-new-probabilistic-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multicalibration as Boosting for Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multicalibration-as-boosting-for-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this characterization, we give an exceedingly simple algorithm that can be analyzed both as a boosting algorithm for regression and as a multicalibration algorithm for a class H that makes use only of a standard squared error regression oracle for H. We give a weak learning assumption on H that ensures convergence to Bayes optimality without the need to make any realizability assumptions -- giving us an agnostic boosting algorithm for regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multicalibration-as-boosting-for-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Physics-informed Reduced-Order Learning from the First Principles for Simulation of Quantum Nanostructures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-reduced-order-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-dimensional direct numerical simulation (DNS) of the Schr\"odinger equation is needed for design and analysis of quantum nanostructures that offer numerous applications in biology, medicine, materials, electronic/photonic devices, etc.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/physics-informed-reduced-order-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep learning-based lung segmentation and automatic regional template in chest X-ray images for pediatric tuberculosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-lung-segmentation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In clinical practice, experienced physicians assess TB by examining chest X-rays (CXR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-lung-segmentation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey and Benchmark of Automatic Surface Reconstruction from Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-and-benchmark-of-automatic-surface</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We survey and benchmark traditional and novel learning-based algorithms that address the problem of surface reconstruction from point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-and-benchmark-of-automatic-surface</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Bellman Errors for Offline Model Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-bellman-errors-for-offline-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, previous work has struggled to obtain adequate OMS performance with Bellman errors, leading many researchers to abandon the idea.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-bellman-errors-for-offline-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourier series weight in quantum machine learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-series-weight-in-quantum-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we aim to confirm the impact of the Fourier series on the quantum machine learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-series-weight-in-quantum-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attend-and-Excite: Attention-Based Semantic Guidance for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attend-and-excite-attention-based-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent text-to-image generative models have demonstrated an unparalleled ability to generate diverse and creative imagery guided by a target text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attend-and-excite-attention-based-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Shortcut Squeezing: Countering Perturbative Availability Poisons with Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-shortcut-squeezing-countering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perturbative availability poisoning (PAP) adds small changes to images to prevent their use for model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/image-shortcut-squeezing-countering</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
