<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 21:06:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Singer Identity Representation Learning using Self-Supervised Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singer-identity-representation-learning-using-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant strides have been made in creating voice identity representations using speech data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/singer-identity-representation-learning-using-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECC-PolypDet: Enhanced CenterNet with Contrastive Learning for Automatic Polyp Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecc-polypdet-enhanced-centernet-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate polyp detection is critical for early colorectal cancer diagnosis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ecc-polypdet-enhanced-centernet-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning effective good variables from physical data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-effective-good-variables-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assume that a sufficiently large database is available, where a physical property of interest and a number of associated ruling primitive variables or observables are stored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-effective-good-variables-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application of Deep Learning in Blind Motion Deblurring: Current Status and Future Prospects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-deep-learning-in-blind-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a response, blind motion deblurring has emerged, aiming to restore clear and detailed images without prior knowledge of the blur type, fueled by the advancements in deep learning methodologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/application-of-deep-learning-in-blind-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Causal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-causal-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientists often want to learn about cause and effect from hierarchical data, collected from subunits nested inside units.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-causal-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full-frequency dynamic convolution: a physical frequency-dependent convolution for sound event detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-frequency-dynamic-convolution-a-physical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, 2D convolution has been found unqualified in sound event detection (SED).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/full-frequency-dynamic-convolution-a-physical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I am a Strange Dataset: Metalinguistic Tests for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-am-a-strange-dataset-metalinguistic-tests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also provide minimally different metalinguistic non-self-reference examples to complement the main dataset by probing for whether models can handle metalinguistic language at all.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-am-a-strange-dataset-metalinguistic-tests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributed Monitoring for Data Distribution Shifts in Edge-ML Fraud Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-monitoring-for-data-distribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The digital era has seen a marked increase in financial fraud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributed-monitoring-for-data-distribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Based Difficulty Calibration for Enhanced Membership Inference Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-difficulty-calibration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experiment results show that LDC-MIA can improve TPR at low FPR by up to 4x compared to the other difficulty calibration based MIAs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-difficulty-calibration-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HaltingVT: Adaptive Token Halting Transformer for Efficient Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/haltingvt-adaptive-token-halting-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Action recognition in videos poses a challenge due to its high computational cost, especially for Joint Space-Time video transformers (Joint VT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/haltingvt-adaptive-token-halting-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Influence of Reading Sequences on Knowledge Gain during Web Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-influence-of-reading-sequences-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use publicly available study data from a web-based learning task to examine the relationship between our feature set and the participants' test scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-influence-of-reading-sequences-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DualVAE: Dual Disentangled Variational AutoEncoder for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualvae-dual-disentangled-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose a Dual Disentangled Variational AutoEncoder (DualVAE) for collaborative recommendation, which combines disentangled representation learning with variational inference to facilitate the generation of implicit interaction data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dualvae-dual-disentangled-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure from Duplicates: Neural Inverse Graphics from a Pile of Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-from-duplicates-neural-inverse-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our world is full of identical objects (\emphe. g., cans of coke, cars of same model).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-from-duplicates-neural-inverse-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, this is what I was looking for! Towards Multi-modal Medical Consultation Concern Summary Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yes-this-is-what-i-was-looking-for-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past few years, the use of the Internet for healthcare-related tasks has grown by leaps and bounds, posing a challenge in effectively managing and processing information to ensure its efficient utilization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yes-this-is-what-i-was-looking-for-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divide and Conquer for Large Language Models Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-for-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown impressive performance in various reasoning benchmarks with the emergence of Chain-of-Thought (CoT) and its derivative methods, particularly in tasks involving multi-choice questions (MCQs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/divide-and-conquer-for-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASA: Causality-driven Argument Sufficiency Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casa-causality-driven-argument-sufficiency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Motivated by the probability of sufficiency (PS) definition in the causal literature, we propose CASA, a zero-shot causality-driven argument sufficiency assessment framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casa-causality-driven-argument-sufficiency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Hardness Negative Sampling for Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-hardness-negative-sampling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Negative sampling is essential for implicit collaborative filtering to provide proper negative training signals so as to achieve desirable performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-hardness-negative-sampling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Online Sign Language Recognition and Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-online-sign-language-recognition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach comprises three phases: 1) developing a sign language dictionary encompassing all glosses present in a target sign language dataset; 2) training an isolated sign language recognition model on augmented signs using both conventional classification loss and our novel saliency loss; 3) employing a sliding window approach on the input sign sequence and feeding each sign clip to the well-optimized model for online recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-online-sign-language-recognition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MISS: Multiclass Interpretable Scoring Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miss-multiclass-interpretable-scoring-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a novel, machine-learning approach for constructing Multiclass Interpretable Scoring Systems (MISS) - a fully data-driven methodology for generating single, sparse, and user-friendly scoring systems for multiclass classification problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/miss-multiclass-interpretable-scoring-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REACT 2024: the Second Multiple Appropriate Facial Reaction Generation Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react-2024-the-second-multiple-appropriate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In dyadic interactions, humans communicate their intentions and state of mind using verbal and non-verbal cues, where multiple different facial reactions might be appropriate in response to a specific speaker behaviour.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/react-2024-the-second-multiple-appropriate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUTOACT: Automatic Agent Learning from Scratch via Self-Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoact-automatic-agent-learning-from-scratch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language agents have achieved considerable performance on various complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoact-automatic-agent-learning-from-scratch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Test-time Likelihood: The Likelihood Path Principle and Its Application to OOD Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-test-time-likelihood-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, introducing new theoretic tools such as nearly essential support, essential distance and co-Lipschitzness, we obtain non-asymptotic provable OOD detection guarantees for certain distillation of the minimal sufficient statistics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-test-time-likelihood-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inconsistency-Based Data-Centric Active Open-Set Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inconsistency-based-data-centric-active-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The presence of unknown classes in the data can significantly impact the performance of existing active learning methods due to the uncertainty they introduce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inconsistency-based-data-centric-active-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Audio Concepts from Counterfactual Natural Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-audio-concepts-from-counterfactual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional audio classification relied on predefined classes, lacking the ability to learn from free-form text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-audio-concepts-from-counterfactual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Covariance Alignment for Domain Adaptive Remote Sensing Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-covariance-alignment-for-domain-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared with the existing category alignment methods, our CR aims to regularize the correlation between different dimensions of the features and thus performs more robustly when dealing with the divergent category features of imbalanced and inconsistent distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-covariance-alignment-for-domain-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Baseline for Spoken Language to Sign Language Translation with 3D Avatars</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-spoken-language-to-sign</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of this paper is to develop a functional system for translating spoken languages into sign languages, referred to as Spoken2Sign translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-baseline-for-spoken-language-to-sign</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probabilistic emotion and sentiment modelling of patient-reported experiences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-emotion-and-sentiment-modelling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study introduces a novel methodology for modelling patient emotions from online patient experience narratives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probabilistic-emotion-and-sentiment-modelling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-Free Conformal Joint Prediction Regions for Neural Marked Temporal Point Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-free-conformal-joint-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A primary objective is to generate a distribution-free joint prediction region for the arrival time and mark, with a finite-sample marginal coverage guarantee.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-free-conformal-joint-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Robustness of Knowledge-Grounded Dialogue via Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-robustness-of-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge-grounded dialogue (KGD) learns to generate an informative response based on a given dialogue context and external knowledge (\emph{e. g.}, knowledge graphs; KGs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-the-robustness-of-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generic Knowledge Boosted Pre-training For Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-knowledge-boosted-pre-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning models are essential for scene classification, change detection, land cover segmentation, and other remote sensing image understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-knowledge-boosted-pre-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-World Aerial Vision Guidance with Categorical 6D Pose Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-aerial-vision-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the real-world robot task of aerial vision guidance for aerial robotics manipulation, utilizing category-level 6-DoF pose tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-world-aerial-vision-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAMPAT: Low-Rank Adaption for Multilingual Paraphrasing Using Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lampat-low-rank-adaption-for-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Paraphrases are texts that convey the same meaning while using different words or sentence structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lampat-low-rank-adaption-for-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answer Retrieval in Legal Community Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answer-retrieval-in-legal-community-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose LegalQA: a real-world benchmark dataset for evaluating answer retrieval in the legal domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/answer-retrieval-in-legal-community-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-PRIME: Transformer-based Protocol Identification for Machine-learning at the Edge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-prime-transformer-based-protocol</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spectrum sharing allows different protocols of the same standard (e. g., 802. 11 family) or different standards (e. g., LTE and DVB) to coexist in overlapping frequency bands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-prime-transformer-based-protocol</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TechGPT-2.0: A large language model project to solve the task of knowledge graph construction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/techgpt-2-0-a-large-language-model-project-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have exhibited robust performance across diverse natural language processing tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/techgpt-2-0-a-large-language-model-project-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MapAI: Precision in Building Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapai-precision-in-building-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The competition will be held in the fall of 2022.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapai-precision-in-building-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DebugBench: Evaluating Debugging Capability of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debugbench-evaluating-debugging-capability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous evaluations of LLMs' debugging ability are significantly limited by the risk of data leakage, the scale of the dataset, and the variety of tested bugs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/debugbench-evaluating-debugging-capability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iterative Feedback Network for Unsupervised Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-feedback-network-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel Iterative Feedback Network (IFNet) for unsupervised point cloud registration, in which the representation of low-level features is efficiently enriched by rerouting subsequent high-level features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iterative-feedback-network-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sample-and-Bound for Non-Convex Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-and-bound-for-non-convex-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standard approaches for global optimization of non-convex functions, such as branch-and-bound, maintain partition trees to systematically prune the domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sample-and-bound-for-non-convex-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Recursive Feature Machines provably recover low-rank matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-recursive-feature-machines-provably</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A possible explanation is that common training algorithms for neural networks implicitly perform dimensionality reduction - a process called feature learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-recursive-feature-machines-provably</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGNITE: Individualized GeNeration of Imputations in Time-series Electronic health records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignite-individualized-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In IGNITE, we further propose a novel individualized missingness mask (IMM), which helps our model generate values based on the individual's observed data and missingness patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ignite-individualized-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Low-resource finetuning of foundation models beats state-of-the-art in histopathology</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-resource-finetuning-of-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, foundation models in computer vision showed that leveraging huge amounts of data through supervised or self-supervised learning improves feature quality and generalizability for a variety of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/low-resource-finetuning-of-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Editing Can Hurt General Abilities of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-editing-can-hurt-general-abilities-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large language models (LLMs) have opened up new paradigms for accessing the knowledge stored in their parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-editing-can-hurt-general-abilities-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Shot Audio to Audio Emotion Transfer With Speaker Disentanglement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-audio-to-audio-emotion-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The problem of audio-to-audio (A2A) style transfer involves replacing the style features of the source audio with those from the target audio while preserving the content related attributes of the source audio.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-audio-to-audio-emotion-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Adversarial Training at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-at-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, by training on DataComp-1B dataset, our AdvXL empowers a vanilla ViT-g model to substantially surpass the previous records of $l_{\infty}$-, $l_{2}$-, and $l_{1}$-robust accuracy by margins of 11. 4%, 14. 2% and 12. 9%, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-at-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Survival Trees: A Dynamic Programming Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-survival-trees-a-dynamic-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Survival analysis studies and predicts the time of death, or other singular unrepeated events, based on historical data, while the true time of death for some instances is unknown.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-survival-trees-a-dynamic-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUNA: A Framework for Language Understanding and Naturalness Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luna-a-framework-for-language-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The evaluation of Natural Language Generation (NLG) models has gained increased attention, urging the development of metrics that evaluate various aspects of generated text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/luna-a-framework-for-language-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-aware Sampling for Long-tailed Semi-supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-sampling-for-long-tailed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach allows the model to perceive the uncertainty of pseudo-labels at different training stages, thereby adaptively adjusting the selection thresholds for different classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-sampling-for-long-tailed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Critique of Critique</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-critique-of-critique</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we pioneer the critique of critique, termed MetaCritique, which is a framework to evaluate the critique from two aspects, i. e., factuality as precision score and comprehensiveness as recall score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-critique-of-critique</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mix-GENEO: A flexible filtration for multiparameter persistent homology detects digital images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mix-geneo-a-flexible-filtration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Two important problems in the field of Topological Data Analysis are defining practical multifiltrations on objects and showing ability of TDA to detect the geometry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mix-geneo-a-flexible-filtration-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
