<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 09:15:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Panoramic Interests: Stylistic-Content Aware Personalized Headline Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoramic-interests-stylistic-content-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prevailing methods focus on user-oriented content preferences, but most of them overlook the fact that diverse stylistic preferences are integral to users’ panoramic interests, leading to suboptimal personalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/panoramic-interests-stylistic-content-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FoundationStereo: Zero-Shot Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundationstereo-zero-shot-stereo-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tremendous progress has been made in deep stereo matching to excel on benchmark datasets through per-domain fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundationstereo-zero-shot-stereo-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>landmarker: a Toolkit for Anatomical Landmark Localization in 2D/3D Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmarker-a-toolkit-for-anatomical-landmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although many general-purpose tools exist for landmark localization in classical computer vision tasks, such as pose estimation, they lack the specialized features and modularity necessary for anatomical landmark localization applications in the medical domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/landmarker-a-toolkit-for-anatomical-landmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Graph MLP Mixer for Spatio-Temporal Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-mlp-mixer-for-spatio-temporal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spatiotemporal forecasting is critical in applications such as traffic prediction, climate modeling, and environmental monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-graph-mlp-mixer-for-spatio-temporal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-Driven Attribute Recovery for Attribute Missing Graph Learning in Social Internet of Things</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-driven-attribute-recovery-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text Attribute Graphs (TAGs) capture both topological structures and semantic attributes, enhancing the analysis of complex interactions within the SIoT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-driven-attribute-recovery-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete Prior-based Temporal-coherent Content Prediction for Blind Face Video Restoration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-prior-based-temporal-coherent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enhance the temporal coherence of the predicted content, a motion statistics modulation module is designed to adjust the content, based on discrete motion priors in terms of cross-frame mean and variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-prior-based-temporal-coherent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiPruner: Balanced Structure Removal in Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipruner-balanced-structure-removal-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, state-of-the-art approaches for pruning large pre-trained models (LPMs) have demonstrated that the training-free removal of non-critical residual blocks in Transformers is viable for reducing model size, achieving results that outperform previous training-free pruning approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multipruner-balanced-structure-removal-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>X-Dyna: Expressive Dynamic Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-dyna-expressive-dynamic-human-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of our approach is the Dynamics-Adapter, a lightweight module that effectively integrates reference appearance context into the spatial attentions of the diffusion backbone while preserving the capacity of motion modules in synthesizing fluid and intricate dynamic details.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/x-dyna-expressive-dynamic-human-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LWGANet: A Lightweight Group Attention Backbone for Remote Sensing Visual Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwganet-a-lightweight-group-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This article introduces LWGANet, a specialized lightweight backbone network tailored for RS visual tasks, incorporating a novel lightweight group attention (LWGA) module designed to address these specific challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lwganet-a-lightweight-group-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Early Alzheimer Disease Detection with MRI Scans</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-early-alzheimer-disease</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alzheimer's Disease is a neurodegenerative condition characterized by dementia and impairment in neurological function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-early-alzheimer-disease</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Preventing Overreliance on Task-Oriented Conversational AI Through Accountability Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preventing-overreliance-on-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our empirical findings demonstrate that this approach not only enables reliable estimation of AI agent errors but also guides the LLM decoder in generating more accurate actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-preventing-overreliance-on-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FiLo++: Zero-/Few-Shot Anomaly Detection by Fused Fine-Grained Descriptions and Deformable Localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filo-zero-few-shot-anomaly-detection-by-fused</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, their handcrafted generic descriptions fail to capture the diverse range of anomalies that may emerge in different objects, and simple patch-level image-text matching often struggles to localize anomalous regions of varying shapes and sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/filo-zero-few-shot-anomaly-detection-by-fused</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIRCHITECT v2: Learning the Hardware Accelerator Design Space through Unified Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/airchitect-v2-learning-the-hardware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results evaluated on 10^5 real DNN workloads demonstrate that, on average, AIrchitect v2 outperforms existing techniques by 15% in identifying optimal design points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/airchitect-v2-learning-the-hardware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aneumo: A Large-Scale Comprehensive Synthetic Dataset of Aneurysm Hemodynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aneumo-a-large-scale-comprehensive-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although clinical practice is usually based on individual factors and morphological features of the aneurysm, its pathophysiology and hemodynamic mechanisms remain controversial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aneumo-a-large-scale-comprehensive-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Attention Networks for Enhanced Segmentation and Depth Estimation of Subsurface Defects in Pulse Thermography</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-attention-networks-for-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, this work proposes PT-Fusion, a multi-modal attention-based fusion network that fuses both PCA and TSR modalities for defect segmentation and depth estimation of subsurface defects in PT setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-attention-networks-for-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Spatiotemporal Augmentation for Improving Dynamic Graph Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spatiotemporal-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic graph augmentation is used to improve the performance of dynamic GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-spatiotemporal-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSHNet: A Novel Information Asymmetric Image Translation Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cshnet-a-novel-information-asymmetric-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose the CNN-Swin Hybrid Network (CSHNet), which combines two key modules: Swin Embedded CNN (SEC) and CNN Embedded Swin (CES), forming the SEC-CES-Bottleneck (SCB).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cshnet-a-novel-information-asymmetric-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study on a Fast Solver for Combined Field Integral Equations of 3D Conducting Bodies Based on Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/study-on-a-fast-solver-for-combined-field</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a graph neural networks (GNNs)-based fast solver (GraphSolver) for solving combined field integral equations (CFIEs) of 3D conducting bodies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/study-on-a-fast-solver-for-combined-field</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSTS: A Multimodal Safety Test Suite for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msts-a-multimodal-safety-test-suite-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we explore the automation of VLM safety assessments, finding even the best safety classifiers to be lacking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/msts-a-multimodal-safety-test-suite-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FaceXBench: Evaluating Multimodal LLMs on Face Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facexbench-evaluating-multimodal-llms-on-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce FaceXBench, a comprehensive benchmark designed to evaluate MLLMs on complex face understanding tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facexbench-evaluating-multimodal-llms-on-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surface-SOS: Self-Supervised Object Segmentation via Neural Surface Representation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-sos-self-supervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make better use of the above information, we propose Surface representation based Self-supervised Object Segmentation (Surface-SOS), a new framework to segment objects for each view by 3D surface representation from multi-view images of a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surface-sos-self-supervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation and Efficiency Comparison of Evolutionary Algorithms for Service Placement Optimization in Fog Architectures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-and-efficiency-comparison-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study compares three evolutionary algorithms for the problem of fog service placement: weighted sum genetic algorithm (WSGA), non-dominated sorting genetic algorithm II (NSGA-II), and multiobjective evolutionary algorithm based on decomposition (MOEA/D).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-and-efficiency-comparison-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Statistical Inference for Sequential Feature Selection after Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-sequential-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In high-dimensional regression, feature selection methods, such as sequential feature selection (SeqFS), are commonly used to identify relevant features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/statistical-inference-for-sequential-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ComplexFuncBench: Exploring Multi-Step and Constrained Function Calling under Long-Context Scenario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexfuncbench-exploring-multi-step-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, evaluating the function calling abilities of LLMs in real-world scenarios remains under-explored due to the complexity of data collection and evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/complexfuncbench-exploring-multi-step-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoK: Introducing Bag-of-Keywords Loss for Interpretable Dialogue Response Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bok-introducing-bag-of-keywords-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One such auxiliary loss function is Bag-of-Words (BoW) loss, defined as the cross-entropy loss for predicting all the words/tokens of the next utterance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bok-introducing-bag-of-keywords-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Actions for Enhanced Embodied Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-actions-for-enhanced-embodied</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training on diverse, internet-scale data is a key factor in the success of recent large foundation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-actions-for-enhanced-embodied</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PandaSkill -- Player Performance and Skill Rating in Esports: Application to League of Legends</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandaskill-player-performance-and-skill</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To take the esports scene to the next level, we introduce PandaSkill, a framework for assessing player performance and skill rating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pandaskill-player-performance-and-skill</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple but Effective Closed-form Solution for Extreme Multi-label Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-but-effective-closed-form-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many current high-performance XML models are composed of a lot of hyperparameters, which complicates the tuning process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-but-effective-closed-form-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Structure-Informed Machinery Part Segmentation with Foundation Models and Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-structure-informed-machinery-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method's fast training times and effective generalization to real data make it a valuable tool for autonomous systems interacting with machinery and infrastructure, and illustrate the potential of combined and orchestrated foundation models for few-shot segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-structure-informed-machinery-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen it detect machine-generated text?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-it-detect-machine-generated-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the approach of the Unibuc - NLP team in tackling the Coling 2025 GenAI Workshop, Task 1: Binary Multilingual Machine-Generated Text Detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qwen-it-detect-machine-generated-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Continual Forgetting for Pre-trained Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-continual-forgetting-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(ii) For remaining knowledge, the impact brought by the forgetting procedure should be minimal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-continual-forgetting-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpticFusion: Multi-Modal Neural Implicit 3D Reconstruction of Microstructures by Fusing White Light Interferometry and Optical Microscopy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opticfusion-multi-modal-neural-implicit-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, conventional WLI cannot capture the natural color of a sample's surface, which is essential for many microscale research applications that require both 3D geometry and color information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opticfusion-multi-modal-neural-implicit-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Aerial Detection Baseline of Multimodal Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-aerial-detection-baseline-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a simple baseline for applying MLMs to aerial detection for the first time, named LMMRotate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-aerial-detection-baseline-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple Graph Contrastive Learning Framework for Short Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-graph-contrastive-learning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, we directly apply contrastive learning on these embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-graph-contrastive-learning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-task deep-learning for sleep event detection and stage classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-deep-learning-for-sleep-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is complex, for which identification of different types of events involves focusing on different subsets of signals, resulting on an iterative time-consuming process entailing several visual analysis passes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-deep-learning-for-sleep-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predictions as Surrogates: Revisiting Surrogate Outcomes in the Age of AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictions-as-surrogates-revisiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further analyze the benefits of recalibration, both theoretically and numerically, in several common scenarios where machine learning predictions systematically deviate from the outcome of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predictions-as-surrogates-revisiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Scarcity to Capability: Empowering Fake News Detection in Low-Resource Languages with LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-scarcity-to-capability-empowering-fake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This version includes 11, 700 additional, meticulously curated fake news articles validated from credible sources, creating a proportional dataset of 47, 000 authentic and 13, 000 fake news items across 13 categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-scarcity-to-capability-empowering-fake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Learning Informative Trajectory Embeddings for Imitation, Classification and Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-informative-trajectory-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In real-world sequential decision making tasks like autonomous driving, robotics, and healthcare, learning from observed state-action trajectories is critical for tasks like imitation, classification, and clustering.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-learning-informative-trajectory-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Class Incremental Fault Diagnosis under Limited Fault Data via Supervised Contrastive Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-fault-diagnosis-under</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Class-incremental fault diagnosis requires a model to adapt to new fault classes while retaining previous knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/class-incremental-fault-diagnosis-under</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatrixNet: Learning over symmetry groups using learned group representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrixnet-learning-over-symmetry-groups-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Group theory has been used in machine learning to provide a theoretically grounded approach for incorporating known symmetry transformations in tasks from robotics to protein modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matrixnet-learning-over-symmetry-groups-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRE-Conv: Symmetric Rotation Equivariant Convolution for Biomedical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sre-conv-symmetric-rotation-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolutional neural networks (CNNs) are essential tools for computer vision tasks, but they lack traditionally desired properties of extracted features that could further improve model performance, e. g., rotational equivariance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sre-conv-symmetric-rotation-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Wav2Vec2 the Language of the Brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-wav2vec2-the-language-of-the-brain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, labeled data and pre-trained models for the closely related task of speech recognition from audio are widely available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-wav2vec2-the-language-of-the-brain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NS-Gym: Open-Source Simulation Environments and Benchmarks for Non-Stationary Markov Decision Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ns-gym-open-source-simulation-environments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This toolkit is the first effort to develop a set of standardized interfaces and benchmark problems to enable consistent and reproducible evaluation of algorithms under non-stationary conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ns-gym-open-source-simulation-environments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analyzing Continuous Semantic Shifts with Diachronic Word Similarity Matrices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-continuous-semantic-shifts-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address those issues, we propose a simple yet intuitive framework for how semantic shifts occur over multiple time periods by leveraging a similarity matrix between the embeddings of the same word through time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analyzing-continuous-semantic-shifts-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting Short Text Classification with Multi-Source Information Exploration and Dual-Level Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-short-text-classification-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel model named MI-DELIGHT for short text classification in this work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-short-text-classification-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChartInsighter: An Approach for Mitigating Hallucination in Time-series Chart Summary Generation with A Benchmark Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartinsighter-an-approach-for-mitigating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce ChartInsighter, which automatically generates chart summaries of time-series data, effectively reducing hallucinations in chart summary generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chartinsighter-an-approach-for-mitigating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Image-Based Narrative Extraction: A Case Study with Historical Photographic Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-image-based-narrative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings show that the narrative maps approach generally outperforms random sampling for longer timelines (10+ images, p < 0. 05), with expert evaluation confirming the historical accuracy and coherence of the extracted narratives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-image-based-narrative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIXELS: Progressive Image Xemplar-based Editing with Latent Surgery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixels-progressive-image-xemplar-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a novel framework for progressive exemplar-driven editing with off-the-shelf diffusion models, dubbed PIXELS, to enable customization by providing granular control over edits, allowing adjustments at the pixel or region level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixels-progressive-image-xemplar-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-Knots Kolmogorov-Arnold Network: On the Analysis of Spline Knots and Advancing Stability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-knots-kolmogorov-arnold-network-on-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we analyze the behavior of KANs through the lens of spline knots and derive the lower and upper bound for the number of knots in B-spline-based KANs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-knots-kolmogorov-arnold-network-on-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merging Models on the Fly Without Retraining: A Sequential Approach to Scalable Continual Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-models-on-the-fly-without-retraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a training-free projection-based continual merging method that processes models sequentially through orthogonal projections of weight matrices and adaptive scaling mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/merging-models-on-the-fly-without-retraining</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
