<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2023 09:12:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Encoding Multi-Domain Scientific Papers by Ensembling Multiple CLS Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encoding-multi-domain-scientific-papers-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many useful tasks on scientific documents, such as topic classification and citation prediction, involve corpora that span multiple scientific domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/encoding-multi-domain-scientific-papers-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Sufficient Spatial-Frequency Interaction for Gradient-aware Underwater Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-sufficient-spatial-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underwater images suffer from complex and diverse degradation, which inevitably affects the performance of underwater visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-sufficient-spatial-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSPRD: A Financial Policy Retrieval Dataset for Chinese Stock Market</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csprd-a-financial-policy-retrieval-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, great advances in pre-trained language models (PLMs) have sparked considerable research focus and achieved promising performance on the approach of dense passage retrieval, which aims at retrieving relative passages from massive corpus with given questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csprd-a-financial-policy-retrieval-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CenTime: Event-Conditional Modelling of Censoring in Survival Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centime-event-conditional-modelling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that our approach forms a consistent estimator for the event model parameters, even in the absence of uncensored data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/centime-event-conditional-modelling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPU frequency scheduling of real-time applications on embedded devices with temporal encoding-based deep reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpu-frequency-scheduling-of-real-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a reinforcement-learning-based technique with temporal encoding to derive an effective DVFS governor even with the presence of the three system patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cpu-frequency-scheduling-of-real-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoLa: Decoding by Contrasting Layers Improves Factuality in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dola-decoding-by-contrasting-layers-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their impressive capabilities, large language models (LLMs) are prone to hallucinations, i. e., generating content that deviates from facts seen during pretraining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dola-decoding-by-contrasting-layers-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImageBind-LLM: Multi-modality Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagebind-llm-multi-modality-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During training, we adopt a learnable bind network to align the embedding space between LLaMA and ImageBind's image encoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagebind-llm-multi-modality-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Function Interpretation Benchmark for Evaluating Interpretability Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-function-interpretation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Labeling neural network submodules with human-legible descriptions is useful for many downstream tasks: such descriptions can surface failures, guide interventions, and perhaps even explain important model behaviors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-function-interpretation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Anything with Decoupled Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-anything-with-decoupled-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To 'track anything' without training on video data for every individual task, we develop a decoupled video segmentation approach (DEVA), composed of task-specific image-level segmentation and class/task-agnostic bi-directional temporal propagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-anything-with-decoupled-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyGraft: Configurable Generation of Schemas and Knowledge Graphs at Your Fingertips</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-03685</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In some data-sensitive fields such as education or medicine, access to public datasets is even more limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-03685</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating ChatGPT as a Recommender System: A Rigorous Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-chatgpt-as-a-recommender-system-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through thoroughly exploring ChatGPT's abilities in recommender systems, our study aims to contribute to the growing body of research on the versatility and potential applications of large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-chatgpt-as-a-recommender-system-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnthroNet: Conditional Generation of Humans via Anthropometrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anthronet-conditional-generation-of-humans-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel human body model formulated by an extensive set of anthropocentric measurements, which is capable of generating a wide range of human body shapes and poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anthronet-conditional-generation-of-humans-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy-preserving Continual Federated Clustering via Adaptive Resonance Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-continual-federated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the clustering domain, various algorithms with a federated learning framework (i. e., federated clustering) have been actively studied and showed high clustering performance while preserving data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/privacy-preserving-continual-federated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulating room transfer functions between transducers mounted on audio devices using a modified image source method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-room-transfer-functions-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The image source method (ISM) is often used to simulate room acoustics due to its ease of use and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulating-room-transfer-functions-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware 3D Object Localization from Single Calibrated Images: A Study of Basketballs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-3d-object-localization-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately localizing objects in three dimensions (3D) is crucial for various computer vision applications, such as robotics, autonomous driving, and augmented reality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-3d-object-localization-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning continuous-valued treatment effects through representation balancing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-valued-treatment-effects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose CBRNet, a causal machine learning approach to estimate an individual dose response from observational data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-valued-treatment-effects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Natural Gas Consumption Forecasting System for Continual Learning Scenarios based on Hoeffding Trees with Change Point Detection Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-natural-gas-consumption-forecasting-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Forecasting natural gas consumption, considering seasonality and trends, is crucial in planning its supply and consumption and optimizing the cost of obtaining it, mainly by industrial entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-natural-gas-consumption-forecasting-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-Eval: A Benchmark for Cross-Dataset Evaluation of Abdominal Multi-Organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-eval-a-benchmark-for-cross-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these questions, we introduce A-Eval, a benchmark for the cross-dataset Evaluation ('Eval') of Abdominal ('A') multi-organ segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-eval-a-benchmark-for-cross-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution-Aware Prompt Tuning for Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-prompt-tuning-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained vision-language models (VLMs) have shown impressive performance on various downstream tasks by utilizing knowledge learned from large data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-aware-prompt-tuning-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Recharge: UAV Coverage Path Planning through Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-recharge-uav-coverage-path</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coverage path planning (CPP) is a critical problem in robotics, where the goal is to find an efficient path that covers every point in an area of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-recharge-uav-coverage-path</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification in Deep Learning Based Kalman Filters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-deep-learning-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various algorithms combine deep neural networks (DNNs) and Kalman filters (KFs) to learn from data to track in complex dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-deep-learning-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-InvestAR: Enhancing Stock Investment Strategies through Annual Report Analysis with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-investar-enhancing-stock-investment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to simplify the process of assessing Annual Reports of all the firms by leveraging the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-investar-enhancing-stock-investment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGANet: Multi-Scale Edge-Guided Attention Network for Weak Boundary Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meganet-multi-scale-edge-guided-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MEGANet is designed as an end-to-end framework, encompassing three key modules: an encoder, which is responsible for capturing and abstracting the features from the input image, a decoder, which focuses on salient features, and the Edge-Guided Attention module (EGA) that employs the Laplacian Operator to accentuate polyp boundaries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meganet-multi-scale-edge-guided-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResFields: Residual Neural Fields for Spatiotemporal Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural fields, a category of neural networks trained to represent high-frequency signals, have gained significant attention in recent years due to their impressive performance in modeling complex 3D data, especially large neural signed distance (SDFs) or radiance fields (NeRFs) via a single multi-layer perceptron (MLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLN-net: A multi-source medical image segmentation method for clustered microcalcifications using multiple layer normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mln-net-a-multi-source-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments validate the effectiveness of MLN-net in segmenting clustered microcalcifications from different domains and the its segmentation accuracy surpasses state-of-the-art methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mln-net-a-multi-source-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hide and Seek (HaS): A Lightweight Framework for Prompt Privacy Protection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hide-and-seek-has-a-lightweight-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerous companies have started offering services based on large language models (LLM), such as ChatGPT, which inevitably raises privacy concerns as users' prompts are exposed to the model provider.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hide-and-seek-has-a-lightweight-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Risk-reducing design and operations toolkit: 90 strategies for managing risk and uncertainty in decision problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-reducing-design-and-operations-toolkit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper finds more than 90 examples of such strategies falling into six broad categories and argues that they provide an efficient response to decision problems that are seemingly intractable due to high uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/risk-reducing-design-and-operations-toolkit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vote2Cap-DETR++: Decoupling Localization and Describing for End-to-End 3D Dense Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vote2cap-detr-decoupling-localization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we argue that object localization and description generation require different levels of scene understanding, which could be challenging for a shared set of queries to capture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vote2cap-detr-decoupling-localization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetric-Reciprocal-Match Method for Vector Network Analyzer Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-reciprocal-match-method-for-vector</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method involves using multiple symmetric one-port loads, a two-port reciprocal device, and a matched load.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-reciprocal-match-method-for-vector</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRASS: Unified Generation Model for Speech Semantic Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grass-unified-generation-model-for-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the instruction fine-tuning technique for speech semantic understanding by introducing a unified end-to-end (E2E) framework that generates semantic labels conditioned on a task-related prompt for audio data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grass-unified-generation-model-for-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Imperfect Symmetry: a Novel Symmetry-Learning Actor-Critic Extension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-imperfect-symmetry-a-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Symmetry, a fundamental concept to understand our environment, often oversimplifies reality from a mathematical perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-imperfect-symmetry-a-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Multimodal Analysis of Influencer Content on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-analysis-of-influencer-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Influencer marketing involves a wide range of strategies in which brands collaborate with popular content creators (i. e., influencers) to leverage their reach, trust, and impact on their audience to promote and endorse products or services.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-multimodal-analysis-of-influencer-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Large Language Models for Clinical Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-for-clinical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable adaptability, showcasing their capacity to excel in tasks for which they were not explicitly trained.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-large-language-models-for-clinical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Adversarial Implications of Variable-Time Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-adversarial-implications-of-variable-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our examination of the timing side-channel vulnerabilities associated with this algorithm, we identified the potential to enhance decision-based attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-adversarial-implications-of-variable-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INCEPTNET: Precise And Early Disease Detection Application For Medical Images Analyses</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inceptnet-precise-and-early-disease-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a novel deep neural network (DNN), entitled InceptNet, in the scope of medical image processing, for early disease detection and segmentation of medical images in order to enhance precision and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inceptnet-precise-and-early-disease-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FSD: An Initial Chinese Dataset for Fake Song Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsd-an-initial-chinese-dataset-for-fake-song</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we initially construct a Chinese Fake Song Detection (FSD) dataset to investigate the field of song deepfake detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fsd-an-initial-chinese-dataset-for-fake-song</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SyntheWorld: A Large-Scale Synthetic Dataset for Land Cover Mapping and Building Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntheworld-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, when it comes to remote sensing image processing, the creation of synthetic datasets becomes challenging due to the demand for larger-scale and more diverse 3D models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/syntheworld-a-large-scale-synthetic-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeApex: A Bilingual Programming Evaluation Benchmark for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codeapex-a-bilingual-programming-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CodeApex comprises three types of multiple-choice questions: conceptual understanding, commonsense reasoning, and multi-hop reasoning, designed to evaluate LLMs on programming comprehension tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codeapex-a-bilingual-programming-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Aggregation for Hierarchical Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aggregation-for-hierarchical-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hierarchical Agglomerative Clustering (HAC) is likely the earliest and most flexible clustering method, because it can be used with many distances, similarities, and various linkage strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aggregation-for-hierarchical-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MA-VAE: Multi-head Attention-based Variational Autoencoder Approach for Anomaly Detection in Multivariate Time-series Applied to Automotive Endurance Powertrain Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-vae-multi-head-attention-based-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A clear need for automatic anomaly detection applied to automotive testing has emerged as more and more attention is paid to the data recorded and manual evaluation by humans reaches its capacity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ma-vae-multi-head-attention-based-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeisCLIP: A seismology foundation model pre-trained by multi-modal data for multi-purpose seismic feature extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seisclip-a-seismology-foundation-model-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training specific deep learning models for particular tasks is common across various domains within seismology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seisclip-a-seismology-foundation-model-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting File Context for Source Code Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-file-context-for-source-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source code summarization is the task of writing natural language descriptions of source code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-file-context-for-source-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Superclustering by finding statistically significant separable groups of optimal gaussian clusters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superclustering-by-finding-statistically</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper presents the algorithm for clustering a dataset by grouping the optimal, from the point of view of the BIC criterion, number of Gaussian clusters into the optimal, from the point of view of their statistical separability, superclusters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/superclustering-by-finding-statistically</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy-Driven Pathology Detection on Chest X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-driven-pathology-detection-on-chest-x</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pathology detection and delineation enables the automatic interpretation of medical scans such as chest X-rays while providing a high level of explainability to support radiologists in making informed decisions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-driven-pathology-detection-on-chest-x</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>nanoT5: A PyTorch Framework for Pre-training and Fine-tuning T5-style Models with Limited Resources</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nanot5-a-pytorch-framework-for-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art language models like T5 have revolutionized the NLP landscape, but their computational demands hinder a large portion of the research community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nanot5-a-pytorch-framework-for-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeeTLe: A Framework for Linear B-Cell Epitope Prediction and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beetle-a-framework-for-linear-b-cell-epitope</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The process of identifying and characterizing B-cell epitopes, which are the portions of antigens recognized by antibodies, is important for our understanding of the immune system, and for many applications including vaccine development, therapeutics, and diagnostics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beetle-a-framework-for-linear-b-cell-epitope</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lightweight, Rapid and Efficient Deep Convolutional Network for Chest X-Ray Tuberculosis Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-rapid-and-efficient-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose LightTBNet, a novel lightweight, fast and efficient deep convolutional network specially customized to detect TB from CXR images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-lightweight-rapid-and-efficient-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensorization: Creating and Utilising Multidimensional Datasets for Multiway Analysis and Tensorised Deep Neural Networks -- Python Tutorial and Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorization-creating-and-utilising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As the size and complexity of data continue to increase, the need for efficient and effective analysis methods becomes ever more crucial.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensorization-creating-and-utilising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Architectures for Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-architectures-for-language-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent efforts have incorporated large language models (LLMs) with external resources (e. g., the Internet) or internal control flows (e. g., prompt chaining) for tasks requiring grounding or reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-architectures-for-language-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReliTalk: Relightable Talking Portrait Generation from a Single Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relitalk-relightable-talking-portrait</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our key insight is to decompose the portrait's reflectance from implicitly learned audio-driven facial normals and images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relitalk-relightable-talking-portrait</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
