<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 21:08:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ModWaveMLP: MLP-Based Mode Decomposition and Wavelet Denoising Model to Defeat Complex Structures in Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modwavemlp-mlp-based-mode-decomposition-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, when handling traffic data, researchers tend to manually design the model structure based on the data features, which makes the structure of traffic prediction redundant and the model generalizability limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modwavemlp-mlp-based-mode-decomposition-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescaling Large Datasets Based on Validation Outcomes of a Pre-trained Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rescaling-large-datasets-based-on-validation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gathering the lowest-accuracy classes along with the most confused ones can produce a smaller subset with a higher challenge for quick validation of an early network draft.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rescaling-large-datasets-based-on-validation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YuLan: An Open-source Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yulan-an-open-source-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the development of YuLan, a series of open-source LLMs with $12$ billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yulan-an-open-source-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACES: Automatic Cohort Extraction System for Event-Stream Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aces-automatic-cohort-extraction-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reproducibility remains a significant challenge in machine learning (ML) for healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aces-automatic-cohort-extraction-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Odd-One-Out: Anomaly Detection by Comparing with Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odd-one-out-anomaly-detection-by-comparing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel anomaly detection (AD) problem that focuses on identifying `odd-looking' objects relative to the other instances within a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odd-one-out-anomaly-detection-by-comparing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extract More from Less: Efficient Fine-Grained Visual Recognition in Low-Data Regimes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extract-more-from-less-efficient-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emerging task of fine-grained image classification in low-data regimes assumes the presence of low inter-class variance and large intra-class variation along with a highly limited amount of training samples per class.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extract-more-from-less-efficient-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything without Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-without-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By integrating our unsupervised pseudo masks into SA-1B's ground-truth masks and training UnSAM with only 1% of SA-1B, a lightly semi-supervised UnSAM can often segment entities overlooked by supervised SAM, exceeding SAM's AR by over 6. 7% and AP by 3. 9% on SA-1B.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-without-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightStereo: Channel Boost Is All Your Need for Efficient 2D Cost Aggregation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightstereo-channel-boost-is-all-your-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present LightStereo, a cutting-edge stereo-matching network crafted to accelerate the matching process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightstereo-channel-boost-is-all-your-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GM-DF: Generalized Multi-Scenario Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gm-df-generalized-multi-scenario-deepfake</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we elaborately investigate the generalization capacity of deepfake detection models when jointly trained on multiple face forgery detection datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gm-df-generalized-multi-scenario-deepfake</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ToolBeHonest: A Multi-level Hallucination Diagnostic Benchmark for Tool-Augmented Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolbehonest-a-multi-level-hallucination</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we introduce a comprehensive diagnostic benchmark, ToolBH.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolbehonest-a-multi-level-hallucination</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Differentiable Approach to Multi-scale Brain Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-differentiable-approach-to-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage this capability of BrainPy across different brain scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-differentiable-approach-to-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIRONet: Spatial-Frequency Learning and Topological Channel Interaction Network for Vessel Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spironet-spatial-frequency-learning-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic vessel segmentation is paramount for developing next-generation interventional navigation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spironet-spatial-frequency-learning-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Event Stream Super-Resolution with Recursive Multi-Branch Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-event-stream-super-resolution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[FFM is designed for the fusion of contextual information within neighboring event streams, leveraging the coupling relationship between positive and negative events to alleviate the misleading of noises in the respective branches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-event-stream-super-resolution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncovering the hidden core-periphery structure in hyperbolic networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-hidden-core-periphery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hyperbolic network models exhibit very fundamental and essential features, like small-worldness, scale-freeness, high-clustering coefficient, and community structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncovering-the-hidden-core-periphery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CANDY: A Benchmark for Continuous Approximate Nearest Neighbor Search with Dynamic Data Ingestion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/candy-a-benchmark-for-continuous-approximate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although numerous AKNN algorithms and benchmarks have been developed recently to evaluate their effectiveness, the dynamic nature of real-world data presents significant challenges that existing benchmarks fail to address.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/candy-a-benchmark-for-continuous-approximate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVolta: Efficient Multi-modal Models via Stage-wise Visual Context Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llavolta-efficient-multi-modal-models-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While significant advancements have been made in compressed representations for text embeddings in large language models (LLMs), the compression of visual tokens in large multi-modal models (LMMs) has remained a largely overlooked area.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llavolta-efficient-multi-modal-models-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Subtle Differences between Human and Model Languages Using Spectrum of Relative Likelihood</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-subtle-differences-between-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human and model-generated texts can be distinguished by examining the magnitude of likelihood in language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-subtle-differences-between-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Generative Replay for Task-Incremental Segmentation with Concurrent Appearance and Semantic Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-generative-replay-for-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generalist segmentation models are increasingly favored for diverse tasks involving various objects from different image sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-generative-replay-for-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Molecular Facts: Desiderata for Decontextualization in LLM Fact Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-facts-desiderata-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic factuality verification of large language model (LLM) generations is becoming more and more widely used to combat hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/molecular-facts-desiderata-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electrostatics-based particle sampling and approximate inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electrostatics-based-particle-sampling-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A new particle-based sampling and approximate inference method, based on electrostatics and Newton mechanics principles, is introduced with theoretical ground, algorithm design and experimental validation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/electrostatics-based-particle-sampling-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Token Gradient Conflict in Mixture-of-Experts for Large Vision-Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-token-gradient-conflict-in-mixture-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This can lead to severe optimization conflicts between different tokens within an expert.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-token-gradient-conflict-in-mixture-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Precision matters: Precision-aware ensemble for weakly supervised semantic segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-matters-precision-aware-ensemble</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further extend our ensemble method to CAMs from AMN (ResNet-like) and MCTformer (ViT-like) models, achieving performance benefits in advanced WSSS models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/precision-matters-precision-aware-ensemble</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PM-VIS+: High-Performance Video Instance Segmentation without Video Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pm-vis-high-performance-video-instance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This method achieves high video instance segmentation performance without manual video annotations, offering a cost-effective solution and new perspectives for video instance segmentation applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pm-vis-high-performance-video-instance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Impact of Initialization on Intra-subject Pediatric Brain MR Image Registration: A Comparative Analysis between SyN ANTs and Deep Learning-Based Approaches</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-initialization-on-intra-subject</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning-based approaches, with or without linear initializations, exhibit slight superiority over SyN ANTs in terms of Dice scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/impact-of-initialization-on-intra-subject</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web2Code: A Large-scale Webpage-to-Code Dataset and Evaluation Framework for Multimodal LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web2code-a-large-scale-webpage-to-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we propose Web2Code, a benchmark consisting of a new large-scale webpage-to-code dataset for instruction tuning and an evaluation framework for the webpage understanding and HTML code translation abilities of MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/web2code-a-large-scale-webpage-to-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta Learning for Efficient Fine-Tuning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-for-efficient-fine-tuning-of-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The research investigates the application of meta-learning strategies to enhance the adaptability and performance of LLMs with limited computational resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-for-efficient-fine-tuning-of-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PopAlign: Population-Level Alignment for Fair Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popalign-population-level-alignment-for-fair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this limitation, we introduce PopAlign, a novel approach for population-level preference optimization, while standard optimization would prefer entire sets of samples over others.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popalign-population-level-alignment-for-fair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuGSI: Distilling GNNs with Multi-Granularity Structural Information for Graph Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mugsi-distilling-gnns-with-multi-granularity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the second challenge, MuGSI proposes to incorporate a node feature augmentation component, thereby enhancing the expressiveness of the student MLPs and making them more capable learners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mugsi-distilling-gnns-with-multi-granularity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaRA: Supercharging Robot Learning Data for Vision-Language Policy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llara-supercharging-robot-learning-data-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) equipped with extensive world knowledge and strong reasoning skills can tackle diverse tasks across domains, often by posing them as conversation-style instruction-response pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llara-supercharging-robot-learning-data-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROS-LLM: A ROS framework for embodied AI with task feedback and structured reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ros-llm-a-ros-framework-for-embodied-ai-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Key features of the framework include: integration of ROS with an AI agent connected to a plethora of open-source and commercial LLMs, automatic extraction of a behavior from the LLM output and execution of ROS actions/services, support for three behavior modes (sequence, behavior tree, state machine), imitation learning for adding new robot actions to the library of possible actions, and LLM reflection via human and environment feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ros-llm-a-ros-framework-for-embodied-ai-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Instruct: Generated Visual Instructions for Large Multimodal Model Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-instruct-generated-visual-instructions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces MM-Instruct, a large-scale dataset of diverse and high-quality visual instruction data designed to enhance the instruction-following capabilities of large multimodal models (LMMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-instruct-generated-visual-instructions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSAKD: Knowledge Distillation with Cross Self-Attention for Hyperspectral and Multispectral Image Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csakd-knowledge-distillation-with-cross-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a novel knowledge distillation (KD) framework for HR-MSI/LR-HSI fusion to achieve SR of LR-HSI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/csakd-knowledge-distillation-with-cross-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pairwise Difference Learning for Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-difference-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pairwise difference learning (PDL) has recently been introduced as a new meta-learning technique for regression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pairwise-difference-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRACE: Graph-Regularized Attentive Convolutional Entanglement with Laplacian Smoothing for Robust DeepFake Video Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grace-graph-regularized-attentive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As DeepFake video manipulation techniques escalate, posing profound threats, the urgent need to develop efficient detection strategies is underscored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grace-graph-regularized-attentive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeaKR: Self-aware Knowledge Retrieval for Adaptive Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seakr-self-aware-knowledge-retrieval-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Self-aware Knowledge Retrieval (SeaKR), a novel adaptive RAG model that extracts self-aware uncertainty of LLMs from their internal states.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seakr-self-aware-knowledge-retrieval-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CELLO: Causal Evaluation of Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cello-causal-evaluation-of-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work typically focuses on commonsense causality between events and/or actions, which is insufficient for applications like embodied agents and lacks the explicitly defined causal graphs required for formal causal reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cello-causal-evaluation-of-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spiking Convolutional Neural Networks for Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-convolutional-neural-networks-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spiking neural networks (SNNs) offer a promising pathway to implement deep neural networks (DNNs) in a more energy-efficient manner since their neurons are sparsely activated and inferences are event-driven.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spiking-convolutional-neural-networks-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Learning Abductive Reasoning using VSA Distributed Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-abductive-reasoning-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Abductive Rule Learner with Context-awareness (ARLC), a model that solves abstract reasoning tasks based on Learn-VRF.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-learning-abductive-reasoning-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEX-TTS: Diffusion-based EXpressive Text-to-Speech with Style Modeling on Time Variability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-tts-diffusion-based-expressive-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expressive Text-to-Speech (TTS) using reference speech has been studied extensively to synthesize natural speech, but there are limitations to obtaining well-represented styles and improving model generalization ability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dex-tts-diffusion-based-expressive-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suri: Multi-constraint Instruction Following for Long-form Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suri-multi-constraint-instruction-following</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing research on instruction following largely focuses on tasks with simple instructions and short responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/suri-multi-constraint-instruction-following</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Pareto Set for Multi-Objective Continuous Robot Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pareto-set-for-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a control problem with multiple conflicting objectives, there exists a set of Pareto-optimal policies called the Pareto set instead of a single optimal policy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-pareto-set-for-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STBench: Assessing the Ability of Large Language Models in Spatio-Temporal Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stbench-assessing-the-ability-of-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid evolution of large language models (LLMs) holds promise for reforming the methodology of spatio-temporal data mining.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stbench-assessing-the-ability-of-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HUWSOD: Holistic Self-training for Unified Weakly Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huwsod-holistic-self-training-for-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most WSOD methods rely on traditional object proposals to generate candidate regions and are confronted with unstable training, which easily gets stuck in a poor local optimum.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/huwsod-holistic-self-training-for-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Anywhere Pointed: Layout-aware GUI Screen Reading with Tree-of-Lens Grounding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-anywhere-pointed-layout-aware-gui-screen</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Tree-of-Lens (ToL) agent, utilizing a novel ToL grounding mechanism, to address the SPR task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/read-anywhere-pointed-layout-aware-gui-screen</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Biased Selective Labels to Pseudo-Labels: An Expectation-Maximization Framework for Learning from Biased Decisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-biased-selective-labels-to-pseudo-labels</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by causal models of selective labels, we propose Disparate Censorship Expectation-Maximization (DCEM), an algorithm for learning in the presence of disparate censorship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-biased-selective-labels-to-pseudo-labels</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dysca: A Dynamic and Scalable Benchmark for Evaluating Perception Ability of LVLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dysca-a-dynamic-and-scalable-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Besides, these benchmarks merely focus on evaluating LVLMs on the realistic style images and clean scenarios, leaving the multi-stylized images and noisy scenarios unexplored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dysca-a-dynamic-and-scalable-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSP: Self-Supervised Prompting for Cross-Lingual Transfer to Low-Resource Languages using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-prompting-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate their effectiveness for NLP tasks in low-resource languages (LRLs), especially in the setting of zero-labelled cross-lingual transfer (0-CLT), where no labelled training data for the target language is available -- however training data from one or more related medium-resource languages (MRLs) is utilized, alongside the available unlabeled test data for a target language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ssp-self-supervised-prompting-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Factor multivariate stochastic volatility models of high dimension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factor-multivariate-stochastic-volatility</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a two-stage estimation procedure for the fMSV model: the first stage obtains the estimators of the factor model, and the second stage estimates the MSV part using the estimated common factor variables.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/factor-multivariate-stochastic-volatility</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporally Multi-Scale Sparse Self-Attention for Physical Activity Data Imputation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-multi-scale-sparse-self-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wearable sensors enable health researchers to continuously collect data pertaining to the physiological state of individuals in real-world settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporally-multi-scale-sparse-self-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpleFusion: A Simple Fusion Framework for Infrared and Visible Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplefusion-a-simple-fusion-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Integrating visible and infrared images into one high-quality image, also known as visible and infrared image fusion, is a challenging yet critical task for many downstream vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplefusion-a-simple-fusion-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
