<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 09:16:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Study of Machine Unlearning Techniques for Computer Vision and NLP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-of-machine-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine unlearning is an emerging field in machine learning that focuses on efficiently removing the influence of specific data from a trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-study-of-machine-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Performance of TAAF for image classification models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-performance-of-taaf-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the results of testing a custom activation function, The Analog Activation Function (TAAF), on both the MNIST and CIFAR-10 datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-performance-of-taaf-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eidetic Learning: an Efficient and Provable Solution to Catastrophic Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eidetic-learning-an-efficient-and-provable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show with a variety of network architectures and sets of tasks that EideticNets are immune to forgetting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eidetic-learning-an-efficient-and-provable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Potential of Classic GNNs for Graph-level Tasks: Simple Architectures Meet Excellence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-classic-gnns-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Message-passing Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) are often criticized for their limited expressiveness, issues like over-smoothing and over-squashing, and challenges in capturing long-range dependencies, while Graph Transformers (GTs) are considered superior due to their global attention mechanisms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-the-potential-of-classic-gnns-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Stochastic Parrot on LLM's Shoulder: A Summative Assessment of Physical Concept Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stochastic-parrot-on-llm-s-shoulder-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a systematic way, we investigate a widely asked question: Do LLMs really understand what they say?, which relates to the more familiar term Stochastic Parrot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-stochastic-parrot-on-llm-s-shoulder-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Light-A-Video: Training-free Video Relighting via Progressive Light Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-a-video-training-free-video-relighting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Second, leveraging the physical principle of light transport independence, we apply linear blending between the source video's appearance and the relighted appearance, using a Progressive Light Fusion (PLF) strategy to ensure smooth temporal transitions in illumination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/light-a-video-training-free-video-relighting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss Landscape Analysis for Reliable Quantized ML Models for Scientific Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-landscape-analysis-for-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a method to perform empirical analysis of the loss landscape of machine learning (ML) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-landscape-analysis-for-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top-Theta Attention: Sparsifying Transformers by Compensated Thresholding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-theta-attention-sparsifying-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The attention mechanism is essential for the impressive capabilities of transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/top-theta-attention-sparsifying-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Modeling with Bayesian Sample Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-with-bayesian-sample</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We derive a novel generative model from the simple act of Gaussian posterior inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-modeling-with-bayesian-sample</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Robust Framework for Multimodal Hate Detection: A Study on Video vs. Image-based Content</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-robust-framework-for-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a systematic analysis of fusion-based approaches for multimodal hate detection, focusing on their performance across video and image-based content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-robust-framework-for-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JamendoMaxCaps: A Large Scale Music-caption Dataset with Imputed Metadata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamendomaxcaps-a-large-scale-music-caption</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce JamendoMaxCaps, a large-scale music-caption dataset featuring over 200, 000 freely licensed instrumental tracks from the renowned Jamendo platform.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/jamendomaxcaps-a-large-scale-music-caption</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinRL-DeepSeek: LLM-Infused Risk-Sensitive Reinforcement Learning for Trading Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrl-deepseek-llm-infused-risk-sensitive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel risk-sensitive trading agent combining reinforcement learning and large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finrl-deepseek-llm-infused-risk-sensitive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeI/O: Condensing Reasoning Patterns via Code Input-Output Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codei-o-condensing-reasoning-patterns-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning is a fundamental capability of Large Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codei-o-condensing-reasoning-patterns-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Language Model Makes an Effective Long Text Extractor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-language-model-makes-an-effective-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the task of extracting longer entity spans (e. g., awards) from extended texts (e. g., homepages) is barely explored.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-language-model-makes-an-effective-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Capability Discovery via Model Self-Exploration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-capability-discovery-via-model-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Automated Capability Discovery (ACD), a framework that designates one foundation model as a scientist to systematically propose open-ended tasks probing the abilities of a subject model (potentially itself).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-capability-discovery-via-model-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenGrok: Enhancing SNS Data Processing with Distilled Knowledge and Mask-like Mechanisms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengrok-enhancing-sns-data-processing-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report details Lumen Labs' novel approach to processing Social Networking Service (SNS) data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opengrok-enhancing-sns-data-processing-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneity in Sectoral Production and the Macro Effect of Sectoral Shocks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-in-sectoral-production-and-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The effect of a negative sectoral shock on GDP depends on how important the shocked sector is as a direct and indirect supplier and how easily sectors can substitute inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-in-sectoral-production-and-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph RAG-Tool Fusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-rag-tool-fusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we address this limitation by introducing Graph RAG-Tool Fusion, a novel plug-and-play approach that combines the strengths of vector-based retrieval with efficient graph traversal to capture all relevant tools (nodes) along with any nested dependencies (edges) within the predefined tool knowledge graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-rag-tool-fusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-Scale Benchmark for Vietnamese Sentence Paraphrases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-benchmark-for-vietnamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents ViSP, a high-quality Vietnamese dataset for sentence paraphrasing, consisting of 1. 2M original-paraphrase pairs collected from various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-benchmark-for-vietnamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instance-dependent Early Stopping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-dependent-early-stopping</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve the efficiency, we propose an Instance-dependent Early Stopping (IES) method that adapts the early stopping mechanism from the entire training set to the instance level, based on the core principle that once the model has mastered an instance, the training on it should stop.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instance-dependent-early-stopping</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early Stopping Against Label Noise Without Validation Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-stopping-against-label-noise-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Early stopping methods in deep learning face the challenge of balancing the volume of training and validation data, especially in the presence of label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/early-stopping-against-label-noise-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial-Label Learning with Conformal Candidate Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-label-learning-with-conformal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To work around the missing labeled validation set, which is typically required for conformal prediction, we propose a strategy that alternates between training a PLL classifier to label the validation set, leveraging these predicted class labels for calibration, and pruning candidate labels that are not part of the resulting conformal sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-label-learning-with-conformal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linear Transformers as VAR Models: Aligning Autoregressive Attention Mechanisms with Autoregressive Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-transformers-as-var-models-aligning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first show that a single linear attention layer can be interpreted as a dynamic vector autoregressive (VAR) structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linear-transformers-as-var-models-aligning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hallucination, Monofacts, and Miscalibration: An Empirical Investigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-monofacts-and-miscalibration-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent theoretical work by [Kalai and Vempala 2024] proves that a particular notion of hallucination rate in LLMs must be lower bounded by the training data monofact rate (related to the classical Good-Turing missing mass estimator) minus model miscalibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hallucination-monofacts-and-miscalibration-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Efficient RLHF Pipeline: A Unified View from Contextual Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-rlhf-pipeline-a-unified</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning from Human Feedback (RLHF) is a widely used approach for aligning Large Language Models (LLMs) with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-efficient-rlhf-pipeline-a-unified</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPO-Shift: Shifting the Distribution of Direct Preference Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpo-shift-shifting-the-distribution-of-direct</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Direct Preference Optimization (DPO) and its variants have become increasingly popular for aligning language models with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpo-shift-shifting-the-distribution-of-direct</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Document Parsing via Large Margin Feature Matching and Heuristics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-document-parsing-via-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present our solution to the AAAI-25 VRD-IU challenge, achieving first place in the competition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-document-parsing-via-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask-Enhanced Autoregressive Prediction: Pay Less Attention to Learn More</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-enhanced-autoregressive-prediction-pay</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose Mask-Enhanced Autoregressive Prediction (MEAP), a simple yet effective training paradigm that seamlessly integrates Masked Language Modeling (MLM) into Next-Token Prediction (NTP) to enhance the latter's in-context retrieval capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-enhanced-autoregressive-prediction-pay</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BenchMAX: A Comprehensive Multilingual Evaluation Suite for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmax-a-comprehensive-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous multilingual benchmarks focus primarily on simple understanding tasks, but for large language models(LLMs), we emphasize proficiency in instruction following, reasoning, long context understanding, code generation, and so on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmax-a-comprehensive-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LASP-2: Rethinking Sequence Parallelism for Linear Attention and Its Hybrid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasp-2-rethinking-sequence-parallelism-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce LASP-2, a new SP method to enhance both communication and computation parallelism when training linear attention transformer models with very-long input sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lasp-2-rethinking-sequence-parallelism-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Elliptic Curve Based Solution to the Perspective-Three-Point Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-elliptic-curve-based-solution-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Perspective-Three-Point Problem (P3P) is solved by first focusing on determining the directions of the lines through pairs of control points, relative to the camera, rather than the distances from the camera to the control points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-elliptic-curve-based-solution-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RusCode: Russian Cultural Code Benchmark for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ruscode-russian-cultural-code-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The lack of cultural awareness can reduce the generation quality and lead to undesirable consequences such as unintentional insult, and the spread of prejudice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ruscode-russian-cultural-code-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextAtlas5M: A Large-scale Dataset for Dense Text Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textatlas5m-a-large-scale-dataset-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-conditioned image generation has gained significant attention in recent years and are processing increasingly longer and comprehensive text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textatlas5m-a-large-scale-dataset-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Fine-Tuning when Scaling Test-Time Compute: Limiting Confidence Improves Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-fine-tuning-when-scaling-test-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To explore this, we focus on pass@N, a simple test-time strategy that searches for a correct answer in $N$ independent samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-fine-tuning-when-scaling-test-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Can Easily Learn to Reason from Demonstrations Structure, not content, is what matters!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-easily-learn-to-reason-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Perturbations affecting content, such as training on incorrect samples or removing reasoning keywords, have little impact on performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-can-easily-learn-to-reason-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explaining 3D Computed Tomography Classifiers with Counterfactuals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-3d-computed-tomography-classifiers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Counterfactual explanations in medical imaging are critical for understanding the predictions made by deep learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explaining-3d-computed-tomography-classifiers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CASC-AI: Consensus-aware Self-corrective AI Agents for Noise Cell Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casc-ai-consensus-aware-self-corrective-ai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Consensus Matrix defines regions where both the AI and annotators agree on cell and non-cell annotations, which are prioritized with stronger supervision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/casc-ai-consensus-aware-self-corrective-ai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curvature Tuning: Provable Training-free Model Steering From a Single Parameter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-tuning-provable-training-free-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we apply CT to ReLU-based Swin-T/S, improving their generalization on nine downstream datasets by 2. 43\%/3. 33\%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curvature-tuning-provable-training-free-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAT: Contrastive Adversarial Training for Evaluating the Robustness of Protective Perturbations in Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-contrastive-adversarial-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we first reveal that the primary reason adversarial examples are effective as protective perturbations in latent diffusion models is the distortion of their latent representations, as demonstrated through qualitative and quantitative experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cat-contrastive-adversarial-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Task-oriented Nighttime Haze Imaging Enhancer for Vision-driven Measurement Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-oriented-nighttime-haze-imaging</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The MToIE incorporates two key innovative components: First, the network employs a task-oriented node learning mechanism to handle three specific degradation types: day-time haze, low light, and night-time haze conditions, with an embedded self-attention module enhancing its performance in nighttime imaging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-task-oriented-nighttime-haze-imaging</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Ownership Verification in Contrastive Pre-trained Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-ownership-verification-in-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose the first dataset ownership verification method tailored specifically for self-supervised pre-trained models by contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-ownership-verification-in-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CreAgent: Towards Long-Term Evaluation of Recommender System under Platform-Creator Information Asymmetry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creagent-towards-long-term-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous studies have attempted to model creator behavior, they often overlook the role of information asymmetry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creagent-towards-long-term-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color-Quality Invariance for Robust Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-quality-invariance-for-robust-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose two novel techniques to enhance generalization: dynamic color image normalization (DCIN) module and color-quality generalization (CQG) loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/color-quality-invariance-for-robust-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Semantic Drift in Task-Agnostic Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-semantic-drift-in-task-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building on this insight, we propose a novel semantic drift calibration method that incorporates mean shift compensation and covariance calibration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-semantic-drift-in-task-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EIQP: Execution-time-certified and Infeasibility-detecting QP Solver</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiqp-execution-time-certified-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Solving real-time quadratic programming (QP) is a ubiquitous task in control engineering, such as in model predictive control and control barrier function-based QP.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eiqp-execution-time-certified-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Iterative Evaluation and Enhancement of Code Quality Using GPT-4o</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-iterative-evaluation-and-enhancement-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces CodeQUEST, a novel framework leveraging Large Language Models (LLMs) to iteratively evaluate and enhance code quality across multiple dimensions, including readability, maintainability, efficiency, and security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-iterative-evaluation-and-enhancement-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic 1-For-1: Generating One Minute Video Clips within One Minute</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-1-for-1-generating-one-minute-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key idea is simple: factorize the text-to-video generation task into two separate easier tasks for diffusion step distillation, namely text-to-image generation and image-to-video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-1-for-1-generating-one-minute-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space-Aware Instruction Tuning: Dataset and Benchmark for Guide Dog Robots Assisting the Visually Impaired</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/space-aware-instruction-tuning-dataset-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Guide dog robots offer promising solutions to enhance mobility and safety for visually impaired individuals, addressing the limitations of traditional guide dogs, particularly in perceptual intelligence and communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/space-aware-instruction-tuning-dataset-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EgoTextVQA: Towards Egocentric Scene-Text Aware Video Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egotextvqa-towards-egocentric-scene-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce EgoTextVQA, a novel and rigorously constructed benchmark for egocentric QA assistance involving scene text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/egotextvqa-towards-egocentric-scene-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USRNet: Unified Scene Recovery Network for Enhancing Traffic Imaging under Multiple Adverse Weather Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usrnet-unified-scene-recovery-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The USRNet features a sophisticated architecture consisting of a scene encoder, an attention-driven node independent learning mechanism (NILM), an edge decoder, and a scene restoration module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usrnet-unified-scene-recovery-network-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
