<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:08:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>When Do Skills Help Reinforcement Learning? A Theoretical Analysis of Temporal Abstractions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-skills-help-reinforcement-learning-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Skills are temporal abstractions that are intended to improve reinforcement learning (RL) performance through hierarchical RL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-do-skills-help-reinforcement-learning-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Sounds, Missing the Questions: The Challenge of Object Hallucination in Large Audio-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-sounds-missing-the-questions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large audio-language models (LALMs) enhance traditional large language models by integrating audio perception capabilities, allowing them to tackle audio-related tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-sounds-missing-the-questions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It Takes Two: On the Seamlessness between Reward and Policy Model in RLHF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/it-takes-two-on-the-seamlessness-between</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We validate the effectiveness of SEAM in data selection and model augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/it-takes-two-on-the-seamlessness-between</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimSAM: Simple Siamese Representations Based Semantic Affinity Matrix for Unsupervised Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simsam-simple-siamese-representations-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent developments in self-supervised learning (SSL) have made it possible to learn data representations without the need for annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simsam-simple-siamese-representations-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenObj: Open-Vocabulary Object-Level Neural Radiance Fields with Fine-Grained Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openobj-open-vocabulary-object-level-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, there has been a surge of interest in open-vocabulary 3D scene reconstruction facilitated by visual language models (VLMs), which showcase remarkable capabilities in open-set retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openobj-open-vocabulary-object-level-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A novel approach to graph distinction through GENEOs and permutants</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-approach-to-graph-distinction-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The theory of Group Equivariant Non-Expansive Operators (GENEOs) was initially developed in Topological Data Analysis for the geometric approximation of data observers, including their invariances and symmetries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-approach-to-graph-distinction-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMWorld: Towards Multi-discipline Multi-faceted World Model Evaluation in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmworld-towards-multi-discipline-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Language Language Models (MLLMs) demonstrate the emerging abilities of "world models" -- interpreting and reasoning about complex real-world dynamics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmworld-towards-multi-discipline-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding In-Context Learning of LLMs through Quality Estimation for Machine Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-in-context-learning-of-llms-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quality of output from large language models (LLMs), particularly in machine translation (MT), is closely tied to the quality of in-context examples (ICEs) provided along with the query, i. e., the text to translate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-in-context-learning-of-llms-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residual Learning and Context Encoding for Adaptive Offline-to-Online Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-learning-and-context-encoding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In general, these methods assume that the transition dynamics remain the same during both the offline and online phases of training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-learning-and-context-encoding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OmniCorpus: An Unified Multimodal Corpus of 10 Billion-Level Images Interleaved with Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnicorpus-an-unified-multimodal-corpus-of-10</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce OmniCorpus, a 10 billion-scale image-text interleaved dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/omnicorpus-an-unified-multimodal-corpus-of-10</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Interpretable Are Interpretable Graph Neural Networks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-interpretable-are-interpretable-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extracting the desired interpretable subgraph requires an accurate approximation of SubMT, yet we find that the existing XGNNs can have a huge gap in fitting SubMT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-interpretable-are-interpretable-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Max-Min Formulation of Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning: From Theory to a Model-Free Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-max-min-formulation-of-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider multi-objective reinforcement learning, which arises in many real-world problems with multiple optimization goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-max-min-formulation-of-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PixMamba: Leveraging State Space Models in a Dual-Level Architecture for Underwater Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixmamba-leveraging-state-space-models-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Underwater Image Enhancement (UIE) is critical for marine research and exploration but hindered by complex color distortions and severe blurring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixmamba-leveraging-state-space-models-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legend: Leveraging Representation Engineering to Annotate Safety Margin for Preference Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legend-leveraging-representation-engineering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By leveraging this safety direction, Legend can then leverage the semantic distances of paired responses along this direction to annotate margins automatically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legend-leveraging-representation-engineering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConMe: Rethinking Evaluation of Compositional Reasoning for Modern VLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conme-rethinking-evaluation-of-compositional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compositional Reasoning (CR) entails grasping the significance of attributes, relations, and word order.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conme-rethinking-evaluation-of-compositional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech Emotion Recognition with ASR Transcripts: A Comprehensive Study on Word Error Rate and Fusion Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-emotion-recognition-with-asr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text data is commonly utilized as a primary input to enhance Speech Emotion Recognition (SER) performance and reliability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-emotion-recognition-with-asr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset and Lessons Learned from the 2024 SaTML LLM Capture-the-Flag Competition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-and-lessons-learned-from-the-2024</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To study this problem, we organized a capture-the-flag competition at IEEE SaTML 2024, where the flag is a secret string in the LLM system prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-and-lessons-learned-from-the-2024</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Probing Implicit Bias in Semi-gradient Q-learning: Visualizing the Effective Loss Landscapes via the Fokker--Planck Equation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-implicit-bias-in-semi-gradient-q</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-gradient Q-learning is applied in many fields, but due to the absence of an explicit loss function, studying its dynamics and implicit bias in the parameter space is challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/probing-implicit-bias-in-semi-gradient-q</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatial Annealing Smoothing for Efficient Few-shot Neural Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-annealing-smoothing-for-efficient-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce an accurate and efficient few-shot neural rendering method named Spatial Annealing smoothing regularized NeRF (SANeRF), which is specifically designed for a pre-filtering-driven hybrid representation architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatial-annealing-smoothing-for-efficient-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LVBench: An Extreme Long Video Understanding Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvbench-an-extreme-long-video-understanding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we introduce LVBench, a benchmark specifically designed for long video understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvbench-an-extreme-long-video-understanding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Explanation Model for Image Classifiers using Class Association Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-explanation-model-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recombining the individual code of a given sample with altered class-associated code leads to a synthetic real-looking sample with preserved individual characters but modified class-associated features and possibly flipped class assignments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accurate-explanation-model-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing End-to-End Autonomous Driving with Latent World Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-end-to-end-autonomous-driving-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, our framework \textbf{LAW} uses a LAtent World model to predict future latent features based on the predicted ego actions and the latent feature of the current frame.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-end-to-end-autonomous-driving-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning to Disentangle Multiqubit Quantum States from Partial Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-to-disentangle</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a deep reinforcement learning (RL) approach to constructing short disentangling circuits for arbitrary 4-, 5-, and 6-qubit states using an actor-critic algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-to-disentangle</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MWIRSTD: A MWIR Small Target Detection Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mwirstd-a-mwir-small-target-detection-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel mid-wave infrared (MWIR) small target detection dataset (MWIRSTD) comprising 14 video sequences containing approximately 1053 images with annotated targets of three distinct classes of small objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mwirstd-a-mwir-small-target-detection-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better than Random: Reliable NLG Human Evaluation with Constrained Active Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-than-random-reliable-nlg-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human evaluation is viewed as a reliable evaluation method for NLG which is expensive and time-consuming.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/better-than-random-reliable-nlg-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Step Effective Diffusion Network for Real-World Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-effective-diffusion-network-for-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments demonstrate that OSEDiff achieves comparable or even better Real-ISR results, in terms of both objective metrics and subjective evaluations, than previous diffusion model based Real-ISR methods that require dozens or hundreds of steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-effective-diffusion-network-for-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConceptHash: Interpretable Fine-Grained Hashing via Concept Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concepthash-interpretable-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Code at: https://github. com/kamwoh/concepthash.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concepthash-interpretable-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-Supervised Spoken Language Glossification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-spoken-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spoken language glossification (SLG) aims to translate the spoken language text into the sign language gloss, i. e., a written record of sign language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-spoken-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IFTD: Image Feature Triangle Descriptor for Loop Detection in Driving Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iftd-image-feature-triangle-descriptor-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a fast and robust Image Feature Triangle Descriptor (IFTD) based on the STD method, aimed at improving the efficiency and accuracy of place recognition in driving scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iftd-image-feature-triangle-descriptor-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable &amp; Interpretable Model Combination in Dynamic Systems Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-interpretable-model-combination-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the core concepts in science, and something that happens intuitively in every-day dynamic systems modeling, is the combination of models or methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-interpretable-model-combination-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Evaluating Adversarial Robustness of Volumetric Medical Segmentation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-evaluating-adversarial-robustness-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend this investigation across four volumetric segmentation datasets, evaluating robustness under both white box and black box adversarial attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-evaluating-adversarial-robustness-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counteracting Duration Bias in Video Recommendation via Counterfactual Watch Time</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counteracting-duration-bias-in-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In video recommendation, an ongoing effort is to satisfy users' personalized information needs by leveraging their logged watch time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counteracting-duration-bias-in-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Figuratively Speaking: Authorship Attribution via Multi-Task Figurative Language Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figuratively-speaking-authorship-attribution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accordingly, we propose a Multi-task Figurative Language Model (MFLM) that learns to detect multiple FL features in text at once.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/figuratively-speaking-authorship-attribution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GUI Odyssey: A Comprehensive Dataset for Cross-App GUI Navigation on Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gui-odyssey-a-comprehensive-dataset-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Smartphone users often navigate across multiple applications (apps) to complete tasks such as sharing content between social media platforms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gui-odyssey-a-comprehensive-dataset-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small Scale Data-Free Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-scale-data-free-knowledge-distillation-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this line of research, existing methods typically follow an inversion-and-distillation paradigm in which a generative adversarial network on-the-fly trained with the guidance of the pre-trained teacher network is used to synthesize a large-scale sample set for knowledge distillation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/small-scale-data-free-knowledge-distillation-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovering Preference Optimization Algorithms with and for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-preference-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we iteratively prompt an LLM to propose and implement new preference optimization loss functions based on previously-evaluated performance metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovering-preference-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Languages Transferred Within the Encoder: On Representation Transfer in Zero-Shot Multilingual Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/languages-transferred-within-the-encoder-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding representation transfer in multilingual neural machine translation can reveal the representational issue causing the zero-shot translation deficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/languages-transferred-within-the-encoder-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regularizing and Aggregating Clients with Class Distribution for Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-and-aggregating-clients-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized federated learning (PFL) enables customized models for clients with varying data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regularizing-and-aggregating-clients-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nyström Kernel Stein Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nystrom-kernel-stein-discrepancy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kernel methods underpin many of the most successful approaches in data science and statistics, and they allow representing probability measures as elements of a reproducing kernel Hilbert space without loss of information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nystrom-kernel-stein-discrepancy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tell Me What's Next: Textual Foresight for Generic UI Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tell-me-what-s-next-textual-foresight-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mobile app user interfaces (UIs) are rich with action, text, structure, and image content that can be utilized to learn generic UI representations for tasks like automating user commands, summarizing content, and evaluating the accessibility of user interfaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tell-me-what-s-next-textual-foresight-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judging the Judges: A Systematic Investigation of Position Bias in Pairwise Comparative Assessments by LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-a-systematic-investigation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our study investigates this issue by developing a framework to systematically study and quantify position bias using metrics such as repetitional consistency, positional consistency, and positional fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/judging-the-judges-a-systematic-investigation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do we know about Hugging Face? A systematic literature review and quantitative validation of qualitative claims</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-we-know-about-hugging-face-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We successfully test 3 of these claims through a quantitative analysis, and directly compare one with traditional software.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-we-know-about-hugging-face-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KernelWarehouse: Rethinking the Design of Dynamic Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelwarehouse-rethinking-the-design-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dynamic convolution learns a linear mixture of n static kernels weighted with their input-dependent attentions, demonstrating superior performance than normal convolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernelwarehouse-rethinking-the-design-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causality for Tabular Data Synthesis: A High-Order Structure Causal Benchmark Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-for-tabular-data-synthesis-a-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce high-order structural causal information as natural prior knowledge and provide a benchmark framework for the evaluation of tabular synthesis models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causality-for-tabular-data-synthesis-a-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisionLLM v2: An End-to-End Generalist Multimodal Large Language Model for Hundreds of Vision-Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionllm-v2-an-end-to-end-generalist</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It not only allows flexible transmission of task information and gradient feedback between the MLLM and multiple downstream decoders but also effectively resolves training conflicts in multi-tasking scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionllm-v2-an-end-to-end-generalist</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strong and Weak Random Walks on Signed Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-and-weak-random-walks-on-signed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show through a series of experiments on synthetic and empirical networks that the similarity matrix based on weak walks can be used for both unsupervised and semi-supervised clustering, outperforming the same similarity matrix based on strong walks when the graph has more than two communities, or exhibits asymmetry in the density of links.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strong-and-weak-random-walks-on-signed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenCOLE: Towards Reproducible Automatic Graphic Design Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencole-towards-reproducible-automatic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic generation of graphic designs has recently received considerable attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opencole-towards-reproducible-automatic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Patch for 3D Local Feature Extractor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-patch-for-3d-local-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local feature extractors are the cornerstone of many computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adversarial-patch-for-3d-local-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Large Language Models Good Statisticians?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-good-statisticians</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive capabilities across a range of scientific tasks including mathematics, physics, and chemistry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-large-language-models-good-statisticians</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Label-aware Hard Negative Sampling Strategies with Momentum Contrastive Learning for Implicit Hate Speech Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-aware-hard-negative-sampling-strategies</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting implicit hate speech that is not directly hateful remains a challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/label-aware-hard-negative-sampling-strategies</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
