<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2023 09:12:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>VoxelNeXt: Fully Sparse VoxelNet for 3D Object Detection and Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxelnext-fully-sparse-voxelnet-for-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our core insight is to predict objects directly based on sparse voxel features, without relying on hand-crafted proxies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxelnext-fully-sparse-voxelnet-for-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards End-to-End Generative Modeling of Long Videos with Memory-Efficient Bidirectional Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-to-end-generative-modeling-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoregressive transformers have shown remarkable success in video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-to-end-generative-modeling-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Might be Enough: Bridge Real-World Traffic Signal Control Using Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-might-be-enough-bridge-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose: (1) a cyclical offline dataset (COD), designed based on common real-world scenarios to facilitate easy collection; (2) an offline RL model called DataLight, capable of learning satisfactory control strategies from the COD; and (3) a method called Arbitrary To Cyclical (ATC), which can transform most RL-based methods into cyclical signal control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-might-be-enough-bridge-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leapfrog Diffusion Model for Stochastic Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leapfrog-diffusion-model-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of the proposed LED is to leverage a trainable leapfrog initializer to directly learn an expressive multi-modal distribution of future trajectories, which skips a large number of denoising steps, significantly accelerating inference speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leapfrog-diffusion-model-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMC2-Net: Joint Equalization and Modulation Classification based on Constellation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emc2-net-joint-equalization-and-modulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Modulation classification (MC) is the first step performed at the receiver side unless the modulation type is explicitly indicated by the transmitter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emc2-net-joint-equalization-and-modulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M$^{2}$SNet: Multi-scale in Multi-scale Subtraction Network for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-2-snet-multi-scale-in-multi-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, we expand the single-scale SU to the intra-layer multi-scale SU, which can provide the decoder with both pixel-level and structure-level difference information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-2-snet-multi-scale-in-multi-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneity of AI-Induced Societal Harms and the Failure of Omnibus AI Laws</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-of-ai-induced-societal-harms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lastly, for cognitive models, data protection law should be adapted to effectively address privacy, surveillance, and security problems and facilitate governance built on public-private partnerships.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneity-of-ai-induced-societal-harms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imitating Graph-Based Planning with Goal-Conditioned Policies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitating-graph-based-planning-with-goal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, graph-based planning algorithms have gained much attention to solve goal-conditioned reinforcement learning (RL) tasks: they provide a sequence of subgoals to reach the target-goal, and the agents learn to execute subgoal-conditioned policies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitating-graph-based-planning-with-goal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sionna RT: Differentiable Ray Tracing for Radio Propagation Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sionna-rt-differentiable-ray-tracing-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sionna is a GPU-accelerated open-source library for link-level simulations based on TensorFlow.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sionna-rt-differentiable-ray-tracing-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Language Models for Knowledge Base Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-language-models-for-knowledge-base</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a second step, we perform a human evaluation on predictions that are not yet in the KB, as only this provides real insights into the added value over existing KBs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-language-models-for-knowledge-base</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual-stream Time-Delay Neural Network with Dynamic Global Filter for Speaker Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-time-delay-neural-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The time-delay neural network (TDNN) is one of the state-of-the-art models for text-independent speaker verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-stream-time-delay-neural-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Neural Rough Differential Equations for Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-rough-differential-equations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A prevalent approach in the field is to combine graph convolutional networks and recurrent neural networks for the spatio-temporal processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-neural-rough-differential-equations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>k-SALSA: k-anonymous synthetic averaging of retinal images via local style alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-salsa-k-anonymous-synthetic-averaging-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While prior works have explored image de-identification strategies based on synthetic averaging of images in other domains (e. g. facial images), existing techniques face difficulty in preserving both privacy and clinical utility in retinal images, as we demonstrate in our work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/k-salsa-k-anonymous-synthetic-averaging-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF: Interactive Multimodal Fusion Model for Link Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imf-interactive-multimodal-fusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a two-stage multimodal fusion framework to preserve modality-specific knowledge as well as take advantage of the complementarity between different modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imf-interactive-multimodal-fusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sound Localization from Motion: Jointly Learning Sound Direction and Camera Rotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sound-localization-from-motion-jointly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we use these cues to solve a problem we call Sound Localization from Motion (SLfM): jointly estimating camera rotation and localizing sound sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sound-localization-from-motion-jointly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Learning for Multimodal Non-Rigid 3D Shape Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-multimodal-non</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The matching of 3D shapes has been extensively studied for shapes represented as surface meshes, as well as for shapes represented as point clouds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-multimodal-non</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP goes 3D: Leveraging Prompt Tuning for Language Grounded 3D Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-goes-3d-leveraging-prompt-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attempting to train the visual and text encoder to account for this shift results in catastrophic forgetting and a notable decrease in performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clip-goes-3d-leveraging-prompt-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Invertible Neural Networks as Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-invertible-neural-networks-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autoencoders are able to learn useful data representations in an unsupervised matter and have been widely used in various machine learning and computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-invertible-neural-networks-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bimodal SegNet: Instance Segmentation Fusing Events and RGB Frames for Robotic Grasping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bimodal-segnet-instance-segmentation-fusing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object segmentation for robotic grasping under dynamic conditions often faces challenges such as occlusion, low light conditions, motion blur and object size variance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bimodal-segnet-instance-segmentation-fusing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliability in Semantic Segmentation: Are We on the Right Track?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-in-semantic-segmentation-are-we</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze a broad variety of models, spanning from older ResNet-based architectures to novel transformers and assess their reliability based on four metrics: robustness, calibration, misclassification detection and out-of-distribution (OOD) detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reliability-in-semantic-segmentation-are-we</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attribute-preserving Face Dataset Anonymization via Latent Code Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-preserving-face-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By optimizing the latent codes directly, we ensure both that the identity is of a desired distance away from the original (with an identity obfuscation loss), whilst preserving the facial attributes (using a novel feature-matching loss in FaRL's deep feature space).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-preserving-face-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoxelNeXt: Fully Sparse VoxelNet for 3D Object Detection and Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxelnext-fully-sparse-voxelnet-for-3d-object-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our core insight is to predict objects directly based on sparse voxel features, without relying on hand-crafted proxies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voxelnext-fully-sparse-voxelnet-for-3d-object-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LFACon: Introducing Anglewise Attention to No-Reference Quality Assessment in Light Field Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfacon-introducing-anglewise-attention-to-no</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel concept of "anglewise attention" by introducing a multihead self-attention mechanism to the angular domain of an LFI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lfacon-introducing-anglewise-attention-to-no</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VIMI: Vehicle-Infrastructure Multi-view Intermediate Fusion for Camera-based 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vimi-vehicle-infrastructure-multi-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In autonomous driving, Vehicle-Infrastructure Cooperative 3D Object Detection (VIC3D) makes use of multi-view cameras from both vehicles and traffic infrastructure, providing a global vantage point with rich semantic context of road conditions beyond a single vehicle viewpoint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vimi-vehicle-infrastructure-multi-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-semantic-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To that end, the segmentation mask is expressed with a special type of image (dubbed as maskige).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-semantic-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TWINS: A Fine-Tuning Framework for Improved Transferability of Adversarial Robustness and Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twins-a-fine-tuning-framework-for-improved</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To better exploit the potential of pre-trained models in adversarial robustness, this paper focuses on the fine-tuning of an adversarially pre-trained model in various classification tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/twins-a-fine-tuning-framework-for-improved</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long-Term Indoor Localization with Metric-Semantic Mapping using a Floor Plan Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-indoor-localization-with-metric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We exploit 3D object detections from monocular RGB frames for both, the object-based map construction, and for globally localizing in the constructed map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/long-term-indoor-localization-with-metric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascading Hierarchical Networks with Multi-task Balanced Loss for Fine-grained hashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-hierarchical-networks-with-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the retrieval accuracy of fine-grained hashing, we propose a cascaded network to learn compact and highly semantic hash codes, and introduce an attention-guided data augmentation method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascading-hierarchical-networks-with-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explicit Visual Prompting for Low-Level Structure Segmentations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-visual-prompting-for-low-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from the previous visual prompting which is typically a dataset-level implicit embedding, our key insight is to enforce the tunable parameters focusing on the explicit visual content from each individual image, i. e., the features from frozen patch embeddings and the input's high-frequency components.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explicit-visual-prompting-for-low-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeiT: Storage-Efficient Vision Training with Tokens Using 1% of Pixel Storage</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seit-storage-efficient-vision-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We need billion-scale images to achieve more generalizable and ground-breaking vision models, as well as massive dataset storage to ship the images (e. g., the LAION-4B dataset needs 240TB storage space).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seit-storage-efficient-vision-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracker Meets Night: A Transformer Enhancer for UAV Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracker-meets-night-a-transformer-enhancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To realize reliable UAV tracking at night, a spatial-channel Transformer-based low-light enhancer (namely SCT), which is trained in a novel task-inspired manner, is proposed and plugged prior to tracking approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracker-meets-night-a-transformer-enhancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Benthic Classification using Resolution Scaling and SymmNet Unsupervised Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-benthic-classification-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adapt the SymmNet state-of-the-art Unsupervised Domain Adaptation method with an efficient bilinear pooling layer and image scaling to normalise spatial resolution, and show improved classification accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-benthic-classification-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inverse problem regularization with hierarchical variational autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-problem-regularization-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments show that the proposed PnP-HVAE method is competitive with both SOTA denoiser-based PnP approaches, and other SOTA restoration methods based on generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inverse-problem-regularization-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cascaded Latent Diffusion Models for High-Resolution Chest X-ray Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-latent-diffusion-models-for-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recent advances in large-scale foundational models show promising results, their application to the medical domain has not yet been explored in detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cascaded-latent-diffusion-models-for-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EqMotion: Equivariant Multi-agent Motion Prediction with Invariant Interaction Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eqmotion-equivariant-multi-agent-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In motion prediction tasks, maintaining motion equivariance under Euclidean geometric transformations and invariance of agent interaction is a critical and fundamental principle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eqmotion-equivariant-multi-agent-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: Reducing Task and Model Complexity for 3D Point Cloud Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-reducing-task-and-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whilst the availability of 3D LiDAR point cloud data has significantly grown in recent years, annotation remains expensive and time-consuming, leading to a demand for semi-supervised semantic segmentation methods with application domains such as autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-reducing-task-and-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DocRED-FE: A Document-Level Fine-Grained Entity And Relation Extraction Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docred-fe-a-document-level-fine-grained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Joint entity and relation extraction (JERE) is one of the most important tasks in information extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docred-fe-a-document-level-fine-grained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeID-GPT: Zero-shot Medical Text De-Identification by GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deid-gpt-zero-shot-medical-text-de</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The digitization of healthcare has facilitated the sharing and re-using of medical data but has also raised concerns about confidentiality and privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deid-gpt-zero-shot-medical-text-de</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Algorithms for Synthetic Power System Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-algorithms-for-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While power systems research relies on the availability of real-world network datasets, data owners (e. g., system operators) are hesitant to share data due to security and privacy risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-algorithms-for-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EVA-02: A Visual Representation for Neon Genesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-02-a-visual-representation-for-neon</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We launch EVA-02, a next-generation Transformer-based visual representation pre-trained to reconstruct strong and robust language-aligned vision features via masked image modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eva-02-a-visual-representation-for-neon</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partial Network Cloning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-network-cloning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike prior methods that update all or at least part of the parameters in the target network throughout the knowledge transfer process, PNC conducts partial parametric "cloning" from a source network and then injects the cloned module to the target, without modifying its parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/partial-network-cloning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiently Counting Substructures by Subgraph GNNs without Running GNN on Subgraphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-counting-substructures-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among these works, a popular way is to use subgraph GNNs, which decompose the input graph into a collection of subgraphs and enhance the representation of the graph by applying GNN to individual subgraphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiently-counting-substructures-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFSL: Personalized &amp; Fair Split Learning with Data &amp; Label Privacy for thin clients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfsl-personalized-fair-split-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The traditional framework of federated learning (FL) requires each client to re-train their models in every iteration, making it infeasible for resource-constrained mobile devices to train deep-learning (DL) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pfsl-personalized-fair-split-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Uncertainty Quantification of Deep Classifiers via Neighborhood Conformal Prediction: Novel Algorithm and Theoretical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-uncertainty-quantification-of-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Safe deployment of deep neural networks in high-stake real-world applications requires theoretically sound uncertainty quantification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-uncertainty-quantification-of-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRF-LOAM: Neural Implicit Representation for Large-Scale Incremental LiDAR Odometry and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-loam-neural-implicit-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, in this paper, we propose a novel NeRF-based LiDAR odometry and mapping approach, NeRF-LOAM, consisting of three modules neural odometry, neural mapping, and mesh reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nerf-loam-neural-implicit-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle-Infrastructure Cooperative 3D Object Detection via Feature Flow Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vehicle-infrastructure-cooperative-3d-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cooperatively utilizing both ego-vehicle and infrastructure sensor data can significantly enhance autonomous driving perception abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vehicle-infrastructure-cooperative-3d-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer learning method in the problem of binary classification of chest X-rays</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-method-in-the-problem-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The purpose of this study is to determine the best models and implementations of the transfer learning method in the binary classification problem in the presence of a small amount of training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-method-in-the-problem-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Camera Calibration and Beyond: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-camera-calibration-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a comprehensive survey of learning-based camera calibration techniques, by analyzing their strengths and limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-for-camera-calibration-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCTV-Gun: Benchmarking Handgun Detection in CCTV Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cctv-gun-benchmarking-handgun-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a meticulously crafted and annotated benchmark, called \textbf{CCTV-Gun}, which addresses the challenges of detecting handguns in real-world CCTV images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cctv-gun-benchmarking-handgun-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MECPformer: Multi-estimations Complementary Patch with CNN-Transformers for Weakly Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mecpformer-multi-estimations-complementary</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a class, the initial seeds generated based on the transformer may invade regions belonging to other classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mecpformer-multi-estimations-complementary</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
