<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 09:21:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Skip the Middle Layers of Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-skip-the-middle-layers-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conditional computation is a popular strategy to make Transformers more efficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-skip-the-middle-layers-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PsyLite Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psylite-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the rapid development of digital technology, AI-driven psychological counseling has gradually become an important research direction in the field of mental health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/psylite-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Response Quality Assessment for Retrieval-Augmented Generation via Conditional Conformal Factuality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-quality-assessment-for-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to existing RAG auto-evaluation methods, Conformal-RAG offers statistical guarantees on the quality of refined sub-claims, ensuring response reliability without the need for ground truth answers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/response-quality-assessment-for-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DBConformer: Dual-Branch Convolutional Transformer for EEG Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbconformer-dual-branch-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It integrates a temporal Conformer to model long-range temporal dependencies and a spatial Conformer to extract inter-channel interactions, capturing both temporal dynamics and spatial patterns in EEG signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dbconformer-dual-branch-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Good Are Synthetic Requirements ? Evaluating LLM-Generated Datasets for AI4RE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-synthetic-requirements</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate four research questions assessing how prompting strategies, automated prompt optimization, and post-generation curation affect data quality across four classification tasks: defect detection, functional vs. non-functional, quality vs. non-quality, and security vs. non-security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-are-synthetic-requirements</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPTailor: Large Language Model Pruning Through Layer Cutting and Stitching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptailor-large-language-model-pruning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown remarkable capabilities in language understanding and generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptailor-large-language-model-pruning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loss-Aware Automatic Selection of Structured Pruning Criteria for Deep Neural Network Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-aware-automatic-selection-of-structured-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an efficient Loss-Aware Automatic Selection of Structured Pruning Criteria (LAASP) for slimming and accelerating deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/loss-aware-automatic-selection-of-structured-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangled representations of microscopy images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-representations-of-microscopy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Microscopy image analysis is fundamental for different applications, from diagnosis to synthetic engineering and environmental monitoring.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangled-representations-of-microscopy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing EG-IPT and ipt~: a novel electric guitar dataset and a new Max/MSP object for real-time classification of instrumental playing techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-eg-ipt-and-ipt-a-novel-electric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents two key contributions to the real-time classification of Instrumental Playing Techniques (IPTs) in the context of NIME and human-machine interactive systems: the EG-IPT dataset and the ipt∼ Max/MSP object.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/introducing-eg-ipt-and-ipt-a-novel-electric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Distributed Equivariant Graph Neural Networks by Virtual Node Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-distributed-equivariant-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Equivariant Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have achieved remarkable success across diverse scientific applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-distributed-equivariant-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMARTIES: Spectrum-Aware Multi-Sensor Auto-Encoder for Remote Sensing Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smarties-spectrum-aware-multi-sensor-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From optical sensors to microwave radars, leveraging the complementary strengths of remote sensing (RS) sensors is crucial for achieving dense spatio-temporal monitoring of our planet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smarties-spectrum-aware-multi-sensor-auto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CycleDistill: Bootstrapping Machine Translation using LLMs with Cyclical Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycledistill-bootstrapping-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs), despite their ability to perform few-shot machine translation (MT), often lag behind dedicated MT systems trained on parallel corpora, which are crucial for high quality machine translation (MT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cycledistill-bootstrapping-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnalogNAS-Bench: A NAS Benchmark for Analog In-Memory Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analognas-bench-a-nas-benchmark-for-analog-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analog In-memory Computing (AIMC) has emerged as a highly efficient paradigm for accelerating Deep Neural Networks (DNNs), offering significant energy and latency benefits over conventional digital hardware.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analognas-bench-a-nas-benchmark-for-analog-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReasonFlux-PRM: Trajectory-Aware PRMs for Long Chain-of-Thought Reasoning in LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasonflux-prm-trajectory-aware-prms-for-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We adapt ReasonFlux-PRM to support reward supervision under both offline and online settings, including (i) selecting high-quality model distillation data for downstream supervised fine-tuning of smaller models, (ii) providing dense process-level rewards for policy optimization during reinforcement learning, and (iii) enabling reward-guided Best-of-N test-time scaling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasonflux-prm-trajectory-aware-prms-for-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongWriter-Zero: Mastering Ultra-Long Text Generation via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longwriter-zero-mastering-ultra-long-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Ultra-long generation by large language models (LLMs) is a widely demanded scenario, yet it remains a significant challenge due to their maximum generation length limit and overall quality degradation as sequence length increases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longwriter-zero-mastering-ultra-long-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PP-DocBee2: Improved Baselines with Efficient Data for Multimodal Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-docbee2-improved-baselines-with-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report introduces PP-DocBee2, an advanced version of the PP-DocBee, designed to enhance multimodal document understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pp-docbee2-improved-baselines-with-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TAB: Unified Benchmarking of Time Series Anomaly Detection Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tab-unified-benchmarking-of-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series anomaly detection (TSAD) plays an important role in many domains such as finance, transportation, and healthcare.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tab-unified-benchmarking-of-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Music Representations? Evaluating Foundation Models on World Music Corpora</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-music-representations-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models have revolutionized music information retrieval, but questions remain about their ability to generalize across diverse musical traditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-music-representations-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabArena: A Living Benchmark for Machine Learning on Tabular Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabarena-a-living-benchmark-for-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We launch TabArena with a public leaderboard, reproducible code, and maintenance protocols to create a living benchmark available at https://tabarena. ai.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabarena-a-living-benchmark-for-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse-Reg: Improving Sample Complexity in Offline Reinforcement Learning using Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-reg-improving-sample-complexity-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the use of small datasets in the context of offline reinforcement learning (RL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-reg-improving-sample-complexity-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan3D 2.5: Towards High-Fidelity 3D Assets Generation with Ultimate Details</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-5-towards-high-fidelity-3d-assets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present Hunyuan3D 2. 5, a robust suite of 3D diffusion models aimed at generating high-fidelity and detailed textured 3D assets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-5-towards-high-fidelity-3d-assets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show-o2: Improved Native Unified Multimodal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o2-improved-native-unified-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on a language model, autoregressive modeling and flow matching are natively applied to the language head and flow head, respectively, to facilitate text token prediction and image/video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/show-o2-improved-native-unified-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the growing field of research on AI for software testing -- the taxonomy for AI-augmented software testing and an ontology-driven literature survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-growing-field-of-research-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper reviews recent research on AI augmentation in software test automation, from no automation to full automation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/navigating-the-growing-field-of-research-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Learning to Optimize with Theoretical Guarantees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-learning-to-optimize-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on our proposed methodology of aligning OOD problems to InD problems, we also demonstrate that the L2O model's convergence rate in OOD scenarios will deteriorate by an equation of the L2O model's input features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-learning-to-optimize-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xolver: Multi-Agent Reasoning with Holistic Experience Learning Just Like an Olympiad Team</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xolver-multi-agent-reasoning-with-holistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite impressive progress on complex reasoning, current large language models (LLMs) typically operate in isolation - treating each problem as an independent attempt, without accumulating or integrating experiential knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xolver-multi-agent-reasoning-with-holistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RMIT-ADM+S at the SIGIR 2025 LiveRAG Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmit-adm-s-at-the-sigir-2025-liverag</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the RMIT--ADM+S participation in the SIGIR 2025 LiveRAG Challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rmit-adm-s-at-the-sigir-2025-liverag</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lecture Video Visual Objects (LVVO) Dataset: A Benchmark for Visual Object Detection in Educational Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lecture-video-visual-objects-lvvo-dataset-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Lecture Video Visual Objects (LVVO) dataset, a new benchmark for visual object detection in educational video content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lecture-video-visual-objects-lvvo-dataset-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeakWeather: MeteoSwiss Weather Station Measurements for Spatiotemporal Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peakweather-meteoswiss-weather-station</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate weather forecasts are essential for supporting a wide range of activities and decision-making processes, as well as mitigating the impacts of adverse weather events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/peakweather-meteoswiss-weather-station</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arctic Long Sequence Training: Scalable And Efficient Training For Multi-Million Token Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arctic-long-sequence-training-scalable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ALST supports training Meta's Llama 8B model with 500K sequence length on a single H100 GPU, 3. 7M on a single 8xH100 GPU node, and over 15M on a 4 node cluster, an increase of over 400x compared to the 32K baseline for the latter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arctic-long-sequence-training-scalable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZipVoice: Fast and High-Quality Zero-Shot Text-to-Speech with Flow Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipvoice-fast-and-high-quality-zero-shot-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing large-scale zero-shot text-to-speech (TTS) models deliver high speech quality but suffer from slow inference speeds due to massive parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zipvoice-fast-and-high-quality-zero-shot-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stream-Omni: Simultaneous Multimodal Interactions with Large Language-Vision-Speech Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stream-omni-simultaneous-multimodal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of GPT-4o-like large multimodal models (LMMs) has raised the exploration of integrating text, vision, and speech modalities to support more flexible multimodal interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stream-omni-simultaneous-multimodal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vine Copulas as Differentiable Computational Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vine-copulas-as-differentiable-computational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vine copulas are sophisticated models for multivariate distributions and are increasingly used in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vine-copulas-as-differentiable-computational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DETRPose: Real-time end-to-end transformer model for multi-person pose estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrpose-real-time-end-to-end-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The paper presents a family of transformer-based models capable of performing multi-person 2D pose estimation in real-time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detrpose-real-time-end-to-end-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Enhancement for Depth from a Lightweight ToF Sensor with Monocular Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-enhancement-for-depth-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depth map enhancement using paired high-resolution RGB images offers a cost-effective solution for improving low-resolution depth data from lightweight ToF sensors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-enhancement-for-depth-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoVLA: A Vision-Language-Action Model for End-to-End Autonomous Driving with Adaptive Reasoning and Reinforcement Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autovla-a-vision-language-action-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Vision-Language-Action (VLA) models have shown promise for end-to-end autonomous driving by leveraging world knowledge and reasoning capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autovla-a-vision-language-action-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Membership Inference Attacks as Privacy Tools: Reliability, Disparity and Ensemble</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-as-privacy-tools</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Membership inference attacks (MIAs) pose a significant threat to the privacy of machine learning models and are widely used as tools for privacy assessment, auditing, and machine unlearning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/membership-inference-attacks-as-privacy-tools</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vector Ontologies as an LLM world view extraction method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-ontologies-as-an-llm-world-view</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) possess intricate internal representations of the world, yet these latent structures are notoriously difficult to interpret or repurpose beyond the original prediction task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vector-ontologies-as-an-llm-world-view</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAGDA: Open-Source Synthetic Agriculture Data for Africa</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sagda-open-source-synthetic-agriculture-data-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data scarcity in African agriculture hampers machine learning (ML) model performance, limiting innovations in precision agriculture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sagda-open-source-synthetic-agriculture-data-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Risk Management Mechanisms in DeFi Lending Protocols: A Crosschain Comparative Analysis of Aave and Compound</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-risk-management-mechanisms-in-defi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, liquidations in v2 have an insignificant impact, which indicates that the most recent v3 protocols have better risk management than the earlier v2 protocols.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-risk-management-mechanisms-in-defi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focusing on Tracks for Online Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focusing-on-tracks-for-online-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-object tracking (MOT) is a critical task in computer vision, requiring the accurate identification and continuous tracking of multiple objects across video frames.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focusing-on-tracks-for-online-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>M^3-VOS: Multi-Phase, Multi-Transition, and Multi-Scenery Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-vos-multi-phase-multi-transition-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we introduce the concept of phase in segmentation, which categorizes real-world objects based on their visual characteristics and potential morphological and appearance changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/m-3-vos-multi-phase-multi-transition-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BeyondRPC: A Contrastive and Augmentation-Driven Framework for Robust Point Cloud Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyondrpc-a-contrastive-and-augmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust perception of 3D point clouds remains a significant challenge in real-world environments where sensor data is often corrupted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyondrpc-a-contrastive-and-augmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCANet: A Temporal Convolutional Attention Network for Motor Imagery EEG Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcanet-a-temporal-convolutional-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes the Temporal Convolutional Attention Network (TCANet), a novel end-to-end model that hierarchically captures spatiotemporal dependencies by progressively integrating local, fused, and global features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tcanet-a-temporal-convolutional-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Review of the Long Horizon Forecasting Problem in Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-the-long-horizon-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The long horizon forecasting (LHF) problem has come up in the time series literature for over the last 35 years or so.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-review-of-the-long-horizon-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Per-Garment Virtual Try-On with Temporal Consistency for Loose-Fitting Garments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-per-garment-virtual-try-on-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This enhances the robustness of semantic map estimation under loose-fitting garments during garment-specific dataset generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/real-time-per-garment-virtual-try-on-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Clustering of Neural Bandits: Selective Reinitialization for Mitigating Loss of Plasticity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-clustering-of-neural-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Clustering of Bandits (CB) methods enhance sequential decision-making by grouping bandits into clusters based on similarity and incorporating cluster-level contextual information, demonstrating effectiveness and adaptability in applications like personalized streaming recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-clustering-of-neural-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MatchPlant: An Open-Source Pipeline for UAV-Based Single-Plant Detection and Data Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matchplant-an-open-source-pipeline-for-uav</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate identification of individual plants from unmanned aerial vehicle (UAV) images is essential for advancing high-throughput phenotyping and supporting data-driven decision-making in plant breeding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/matchplant-an-open-source-pipeline-for-uav</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlexRAG: A Flexible and Comprehensive Framework for Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexrag-a-flexible-and-comprehensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) plays a pivotal role in modern large language model applications, with numerous existing frameworks offering a wide range of functionalities to facilitate the development of RAG systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexrag-a-flexible-and-comprehensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenUnlearning: Accelerating LLM Unlearning via Unified Benchmarking of Methods and Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openunlearning-accelerating-llm-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Robust unlearning is crucial for safely deploying large language models (LLMs) in environments where data privacy, model safety, and regulatory compliance must be ensured.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openunlearning-accelerating-llm-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Encodings by Maximizing State Distinguishability: Variational Quantum Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-encodings-by-maximizing-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Quantum error correction is crucial for protecting quantum information against decoherence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-encodings-by-maximizing-state</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
