<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 09:11:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Mask: Explore the Intrinsic Out-of-Distribution Detection Capability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-mask-explore-the-intrinsic-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on such insights, we propose a novel method, Unleashing Mask, which aims to restore the OOD discriminative capabilities of the well-trained model with ID data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-mask-explore-the-intrinsic-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schema First! Learn Versatile Knowledge Graph Embeddings by Capturing Semantics with MASCHInE</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-first-learn-versatile-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models learn a vector representation of knowledge graph entities and relations, a. k. a.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-first-learn-versatile-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Manipulating Signals of User-Item Graph: A Jacobi Polynomial-based Graph Collaborative Filtering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-manipulating-signals-of-user-item-graph-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph CF has attracted more and more attention in recent years due to its effectiveness in leveraging high-order information in the user-item bipartite graph for better recommendations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-manipulating-signals-of-user-item-graph-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conditional Diffusion Models for Weakly Supervised Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-diffusion-models-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in denoising diffusion probabilistic models have shown great success in image synthesis tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conditional-diffusion-models-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioBLP: A Modular Framework for Learning on Multimodal Biomedical Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioblp-a-modular-framework-for-learning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We train models using a biomedical KG containing approximately 2 million triples, and evaluate the performance of the resulting entity embeddings on the tasks of link prediction, and drug-protein interaction prediction, comparing against methods that do not take attribute data into account.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bioblp-a-modular-framework-for-learning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FinRED: A Dataset for Relation Extraction in Financial Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finred-a-dataset-for-relation-extraction-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relation extraction models trained on a source domain cannot be applied on a different target domain due to the mismatch between relation sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/finred-a-dataset-for-relation-extraction-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciLit: A Platform for Joint Scientific Literature Discovery, Summarization and Citation Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scilit-a-platform-for-joint-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SciLit, a pipeline that automatically recommends relevant papers, extracts highlights, and suggests a reference sentence as a citation of a paper, taking into consideration the user-provided context and keywords.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scilit-a-platform-for-joint-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CUE: An Uncertainty Interpretation Framework for Text Classifiers Built on Pre-Trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cue-an-uncertainty-interpretation-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then generate text representations by perturbing the latent space which causes fluctuation in predictive uncertainty.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cue-an-uncertainty-interpretation-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial Numeric Extreme Labelling: A Dataset and Benchmarking for XBRL Tagging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/financial-numeric-extreme-labelling-a-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The U. S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) mandates all public companies to file periodic financial statements that should contain numerals annotated with a particular label from a taxonomy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/financial-numeric-extreme-labelling-a-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Expressivity of Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-expressivity-of-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we characterize the expressive power of MPNNs in terms of the tree distance, which is a graph distance based on the concepts of fractional isomorphisms, and substructure counts via tree homomorphisms, showing that these concepts have the same expressive power as the $1$-WL and MPNNs on graphons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-expressivity-of-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mildly Constrained Evaluation Policy for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mildly-constrained-evaluation-policy-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Offline reinforcement learning (RL) methodologies enforce constraints on the policy to adhere closely to the behavior policy, thereby stabilizing value learning and mitigating the selection of out-of-distribution (OOD) actions during test time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mildly-constrained-evaluation-policy-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Information Regularization for Weakly-supervised RGB-D Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-information-regularization-for-weakly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, following the principle of disentangled representation learning, we introduce a mutual information upper bound with a mutual information minimization regularizer to encourage the disentangled representation of each modality for salient object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-information-regularization-for-weakly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Efficient Interaction between an Algorithm Agent and an LLM: A Reinforcement Learning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-interaction-between-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results also suggest that by learning a mediator model to interact with the LLM, the agent's performance becomes more robust against both exploratory and stochastic environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-efficient-interaction-between-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Pitfalls of Test-Time Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-pitfalls-of-test-time-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-Time Adaptation (TTA) has recently emerged as a promising approach for tackling the robustness challenge under distribution shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-pitfalls-of-test-time-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Functional Data Perspective and Baseline On Multi-Layer Out-of-Distribution Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-functional-data-perspective-and-baseline-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key feature of out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is to exploit a trained neural network by extracting statistical patterns and relationships through the multi-layer classifier to detect shifts in the expected input data distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-functional-data-perspective-and-baseline-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the effects of robotic design on learning and neural control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effects-of-robotic-design-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, this dissertation intimates the ability to automatically design robots that are more general purpose than current robots and that can perform various tasks while requiring less computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effects-of-robotic-design-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instructive Feature Enhancement for Dichotomous Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructive-feature-enhancement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks have been widely applied in dichotomous medical image segmentation (DMIS) of many anatomical structures in several modalities, achieving promising performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructive-feature-enhancement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-imperceptible, Machine-recognizable Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-imperceptible-machine-recognizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Massive human-related data is collected to train neural networks for computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-imperceptible-machine-recognizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Model Dynamics for Accumulative Poisoning Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-model-dynamics-for-accumulative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we dive into the perspective of model dynamics and propose a novel information measure, namely, Memorization Discrepancy, to explore the defense via the model-level information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-model-dynamics-for-accumulative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian post-hoc regularization of random forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-post-hoc-regularization-of-random</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Random Forests are powerful ensemble learning algorithms widely used in various machine learning tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-post-hoc-regularization-of-random</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Do or Learning While Doing: Reinforcement Learning and Bayesian Optimisation for Online Continuous Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-do-or-learning-while-doing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Online tuning of real-world plants is a complex optimisation problem that continues to require manual intervention by experienced human operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-do-or-learning-while-doing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Emergence of Essential Sparsity in Large Pre-trained Models: The Weights that Matter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emergence-of-essential-sparsity-in-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained transformers are show-stealer in modern-day deep learning, and it becomes crucial to comprehend the parsimonious patterns that exist within them as they grow in scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-emergence-of-essential-sparsity-in-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CiT-Net: Convolutional Neural Networks Hand in Hand with Vision Transformers for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cit-net-convolutional-neural-networks-hand-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The hybrid architecture of convolutional neural networks (CNNs) and Transformer are very popular for medical image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cit-net-convolutional-neural-networks-hand-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student Classroom Behavior Detection based on Improved YOLOv7</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/student-classroom-behavior-detection-based-on-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurately detecting student behavior in classroom videos can aid in analyzing their classroom performance and improving teaching effectiveness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/student-classroom-behavior-detection-based-on-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciCap+: A Knowledge Augmented Dataset to Study the Challenges of Scientific Figure Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scicap-a-knowledge-augmented-dataset-to-study</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automating figure caption generation helps move model understandings of scientific documents beyond text and will help authors write informative captions that facilitate communicating scientific findings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scicap-a-knowledge-augmented-dataset-to-study</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum-Based Augmented Fourier Domain Adaptation for Robust Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-augmented-fourier-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate and robust medical image segmentation is fundamental and crucial for enhancing the autonomy of computer-aided diagnosis and intervention systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/curriculum-based-augmented-fourier-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient and Interpretable Compressive Text Summarisation with Unsupervised Dual-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-interpretable-compressive-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, compressive text summarisation offers a balance between the conciseness issue of extractive summarisation and the factual hallucination issue of abstractive summarisation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-and-interpretable-compressive-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-Object Interaction Prediction in Videos through Gaze Following</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-object-interaction-prediction-in-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the human-object interactions (HOIs) from a video is essential to fully comprehend a visual scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-object-interaction-prediction-in-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning-Based Heuristic for Combinatorial Optimization of the Minimum Dominating Set Problem using Graph Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-heuristic-for-combinatorial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The minimum dominating set problem seeks to find a dominating set of minimum cardinality and is a well-established NP-hard combinatorial optimization problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-based-heuristic-for-combinatorial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supervised Knowledge May Hurt Novel Class Discovery Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-knowledge-may-hurt-novel-class</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, by using the proposed transfer flow, we conduct various empirical experiments with different levels of semantic similarity, yielding that supervised knowledge may hurt NCD performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supervised-knowledge-may-hurt-novel-class</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAMO: Fast Adaptive Multitask Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/famo-fast-adaptive-multitask-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the grand enduring goals of AI is to create generalist agents that can learn multiple different tasks from diverse data via multitask learning (MTL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/famo-fast-adaptive-multitask-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take the Hint: Improving Arabic Diacritization with Partially-Diacritized Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-the-hint-improving-arabic-diacritization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic Arabic diacritization is useful in many applications, ranging from reading support for language learners to accurate pronunciation predictor for downstream tasks like speech synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-the-hint-improving-arabic-diacritization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Autoencoders are Efficient Continual Federated Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-are-efficient-continual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In parts, federated learning lifts this assumption, as it sets out to solve the real-world challenge of collaboratively learning a shared model from data distributed across clients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-autoencoders-are-efficient-continual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deductive Verification of Chain-of-Thought Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deductive-verification-of-chain-of-thought</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In light of this, we propose to decompose a reasoning verification process into a series of step-by-step subprocesses, each only receiving their necessary context and premises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deductive-verification-of-chain-of-thought</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inference-Time Intervention: Eliciting Truthful Answers from a Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-time-intervention-eliciting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This intervention significantly improves the performance of LLaMA models on the TruthfulQA benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inference-time-intervention-eliciting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Dynamical Systems from Noisy Data with Inverse-Explicit Integrators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dynamical-systems-from-noisy-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the mean inverse integrator (MII), a novel approach to increase the accuracy when training neural networks to approximate vector fields of dynamical systems from noisy data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-dynamical-systems-from-noisy-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine learning in and out of equilibrium</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-in-and-out-of-equilibrium</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an example system where the posterior is exactly known, this SGWORLD algorithm outperforms SGLD, converging to the posterior orders of magnitude faster as a function of the learning rate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-in-and-out-of-equilibrium</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-Based Dual Gaussian Processes for Sequential Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-based-dual-gaussian-processes-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sequential learning with Gaussian processes (GPs) is challenging when access to past data is limited, for example, in continual and active learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-based-dual-gaussian-processes-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ColdNAS: Search to Modulate for User Cold-Start Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coldnas-search-to-modulate-for-user-cold</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of using a fixed modulation function and deciding modulation position by expertise, we propose a modulation framework called ColdNAS for user cold-start problem, where we look for proper modulation structure, including function and position, via neural architecture search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coldnas-search-to-modulate-for-user-cold</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents Explore the Environment Beyond Good Actions to Improve Their Model for Better Decisions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-explore-the-environment-beyond-good</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the planning skills needed to make good decisions, MuZero's agent combines prediction by a network model and planning by a tree search using the predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agents-explore-the-environment-beyond-good</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Difference of BERT-style and CLIP-style Text Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-difference-of-bert-style-and-clip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Masked language modeling (MLM) has been one of the most popular pretraining recipes in natural language processing, e. g., BERT, one of the representative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-difference-of-bert-style-and-clip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Key Points to Key Point Hierarchy: Structured and Expressive Opinion Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-key-points-to-key-point-hierarchy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Key Point Analysis (KPA) has been recently proposed for deriving fine-grained insights from collections of textual comments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-key-points-to-key-point-hierarchy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Cross-Linguistic Pressure for Uniform Information Density in Word Order</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-linguistic-pressure-for-uniform</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we ask whether a pressure for UID may have influenced word order patterns cross-linguistically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-cross-linguistic-pressure-for-uniform</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I'm Afraid I Can't Do That: Predicting Prompt Refusal in Black-Box Generative Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-m-afraid-i-can-t-do-that-predicting-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With this machine-labeled data, we train a prompt classifier to predict whether ChatGPT will refuse a given question, without seeing ChatGPT's response.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-m-afraid-i-can-t-do-that-predicting-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGAT4PASS: Spherical Geometry-Aware Transformer for PAnoramic Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgat4pass-spherical-geometry-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results on Stanford2D3D Panoramic datasets show that SGAT4PASS significantly improves performance and robustness, with approximately a 2% increase in mIoU, and when small 3D disturbances occur in the data, the stability of our performance is improved by an order of magnitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgat4pass-spherical-geometry-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DVIS: Decoupled Video Instance Segmentation Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvis-decoupled-video-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficacy of the decoupling strategy relies on two crucial elements: 1) attaining precise long-term alignment outcomes via frame-by-frame association during tracking, and 2) the effective utilization of temporal information predicated on the aforementioned accurate alignment outcomes during refinement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dvis-decoupled-video-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Alleviating the Object Bias in Prompt Tuning-based Factual Knowledge Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-alleviating-the-object-bias-in-prompt</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many works employed prompt tuning methods to automatically optimize prompt queries and extract the factual knowledge stored in Pretrained Language Models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-alleviating-the-object-bias-in-prompt</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEO-Bench: Toward Foundation Models for Earth Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-bench-toward-foundation-models-for-earth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in self-supervision has shown that pre-training large neural networks on vast amounts of unsupervised data can lead to substantial increases in generalization to downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geo-bench-toward-foundation-models-for-earth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM3D: Segment Anything in 3D Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam3d-segment-anything-in-3d-scenes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose SAM3D, a novel framework that is able to predict masks in 3D point clouds by leveraging the Segment-Anything Model (SAM) in RGB images without further training or finetuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam3d-segment-anything-in-3d-scenes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-Based Counterfactual Causal Discovery on Real World Driver Behaviour</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-counterfactual-causal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Being able to reason about how one's behaviour can affect the behaviour of others is a core skill required of intelligent driving agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-counterfactual-causal</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
