<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 09:13:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FedALA: Adaptive Local Aggregation for Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedala-adaptive-local-aggregation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge in federated learning (FL) is the statistical heterogeneity that impairs the generalization of the global model on each client.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedala-adaptive-local-aggregation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Straight-Through gradients and Soft-Thresholding all you need for Sparse Training?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-straight-through-gradients-and-soft</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Turning the weights to zero when training a neural network helps in reducing the computational complexity at inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-straight-through-gradients-and-soft</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARAS-Net: Scale and Relation Aware Siamese Network for Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saras-net-scale-and-relation-aware-siamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Change detection (CD) aims to find the difference between two images at different times and outputs a change map to represent whether the region has changed or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saras-net-scale-and-relation-aware-siamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepFT: Fault-Tolerant Edge Computing using a Self-Supervised Deep Surrogate Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepft-fault-tolerant-edge-computing-using-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emergence of latency-critical AI applications has been supported by the evolution of the edge computing paradigm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepft-fault-tolerant-edge-computing-using-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SimpleMind adds thinking to deep neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplemind-adds-thinking-to-deep-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The SimpleMind framework brings thinking to DNNs by: (1) providing methods for reasoning with the knowledge base about image content, such as spatial inferencing and conditional reasoning to check DNN outputs; (2) applying process knowledge, in the form of general-purpose software agents, that are chained together to accomplish image preprocessing, DNN prediction, and result post-processing, and (3) performing automatic co-optimization of all knowledge base parameters to adapt agents to specific problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simplemind-adds-thinking-to-deep-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Learnable Attention for Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-learnable-attention-for-single-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Utilizing this finding, we proposed a Global Learnable Attention (GLA) to adaptively modify similarity scores of non-local textures during training instead of only using a fixed similarity scoring function such as the dot product.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-learnable-attention-for-single-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Inverse Learning via Intelligent Localization with Exploratory Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-inverse-learning-via-intelligent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the scope of "AI for Science", solving inverse problems is a longstanding challenge in materials and drug discovery, where the goal is to determine the hidden structures given a set of desirable properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/accelerating-inverse-learning-via-intelligent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PASTA: Proportional Amplitude Spectrum Training Augmentation for Syn-to-Real Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-proportional-amplitude-spectrum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthetic data offers the promise of cheap and bountiful training data for settings where lots of labeled real-world data for tasks is unavailable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pasta-proportional-amplitude-spectrum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe machine learning model release from Trusted Research Environments: The AI-SDC package</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-machine-learning-model-release-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present AI-SDC, an integrated suite of open source Python tools to facilitate Statistical Disclosure Control (SDC) of Machine Learning (ML) models trained on confidential data prior to public release.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safe-machine-learning-model-release-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Simultaneous Machine Translation with Monolingual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-simultaneous-machine-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Preliminary experiments on En-Zh and En-Ja news domain corpora demonstrate that monolingual data can significantly improve translation quality (e. g., +3. 15 BLEU on En-Zh).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-simultaneous-machine-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ripple: Concept-Based Interpretation for Raw Time Series Models in Education</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ripple-concept-based-interpretation-for-raw</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series is the most prevalent form of input data for educational prediction tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ripple-concept-based-interpretation-for-raw</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Domain Graph Anomaly Detection via Anomaly-aware Contrastive Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-graph-anomaly-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In doing so, ACT effectively transfers anomaly-informed knowledge from the source graph to learn the complex node relations of the normal class for GAD on the target graph without any specification of the anomaly distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-graph-anomaly-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model and Data Agreement for Learning with Noisy Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-and-data-agreement-for-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce mean point ensemble to utilize a more robust loss function and more information from unselected samples to reduce error accumulation from the model perspective.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-and-data-agreement-for-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coevolutionary Framework for Generalized Multimodal Multi-objective Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coevolutionary-framework-for-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the above two issues, in this study, a novel coevolutionary framework termed CoMMEA for multimodal multi-objective optimization is proposed to better obtain both global and local PSs, and simultaneously, to improve the convergence performance in dealing with high-dimension MMOPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/coevolutionary-framework-for-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FECAM: Frequency Enhanced Channel Attention Mechanism for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecam-frequency-enhanced-channel-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, use of FT is problematic due to Gibbs phenomenon.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fecam-frequency-enhanced-channel-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIC: Masked Image Consistency for Context-Enhanced Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mic-masked-image-consistency-for-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MIC significantly improves the state-of-the-art performance across the different recognition tasks for synthetic-to-real, day-to-nighttime, and clear-to-adverse-weather UDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mic-masked-image-consistency-for-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UIU-Net: U-Net in U-Net for Infrared Small Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uiu-net-u-net-in-u-net-for-infrared-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RM-DS integrates Residual U-blocks into a deep supervision network to generate deep multi-scale resolution-maintenance features while learning global context information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uiu-net-u-net-in-u-net-for-infrared-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subword-Delimited Downsampling for Better Character-Level Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subword-delimited-downsampling-for-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This new downsampling method not only outperforms existing downsampling methods, showing that downsampling characters can be done without sacrificing quality, but also leads to promising performance compared to subword models for translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/subword-delimited-downsampling-for-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Incremental Learning Approach for Sustainable Region Isolation and Integration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-incremental-learning-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we mimic partitioned learning and memory replay in the human brain and propose an incremental learning approach named SRII, short for sustainable regional isolation and integration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-incremental-learning-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Process regression over discrete probability measures: on the non-stationarity relation between Euclidean and Wasserstein Squared Exponential Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-process-regression-over-discrete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gaussian Process regression is a kernel method successfully adopted in many real-life applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-process-regression-over-discrete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gibbs-Helmholtz Graph Neural Network: capturing the temperature dependency of activity coefficients at infinite dilution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gibbs-helmholtz-graph-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The accurate prediction of physicochemical properties of chemical compounds in mixtures (such as the activity coefficient at infinite dilution $\gamma_{ij}^\infty$) is essential for developing novel and more sustainable chemical processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gibbs-helmholtz-graph-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially Private Adaptive Optimization with Delayed Preconditioners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-adaptive-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Privacy noise may negate the benefits of using adaptive optimizers in differentially private model training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentially-private-adaptive-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biomedical NER for the Enterprise with Distillated BERN2 and the Kazu Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-ner-for-the-enterprise-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to assist the drug discovery/development process, pharmaceutical companies often apply biomedical NER and linking techniques over internal and public corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biomedical-ner-for-the-enterprise-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Principled Multi-Aspect Evaluation Measures of Rankings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-multi-aspect-evaluation-measures</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Information Retrieval evaluation has traditionally focused on defining principled ways of assessing the relevance of a ranked list of documents with respect to a query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/principled-multi-aspect-evaluation-measures</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FoPro: Few-Shot Guided Robust Webly-Supervised Prototypical Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fopro-few-shot-guided-robust-webly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing methods focus on learning noise-robust models from web images while neglecting the performance drop caused by the differences between web domain and real-world domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fopro-few-shot-guided-robust-webly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Linear and Iterative Combinations of Patches for Image Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-linear-and-iterative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a parametric view of non-local two-step denoisers, for which BM3D is a major representative, where quadratic risk minimization is leveraged for unsupervised optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-linear-and-iterative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attribute-based Representations for Accurate and Interpretable Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-based-representations-for-accurate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Surprisingly, we find that this simple representation is sufficient to achieve state-of-the-art performance in ShanghaiTech, the largest and most complex VAD dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribute-based-representations-for-accurate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data-Efficient Finetuning Using Cross-Task Nearest Neighbors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-finetuning-using-cross-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We assume access to a small number (250--1000) of unlabeled target task instances, select their nearest neighbors from a pool of multitask data, and use the retrieved data to train target task-specific models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-efficient-finetuning-using-cross-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AC-Band: A Combinatorial Bandit-Based Approach to Algorithm Configuration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ac-band-a-combinatorial-bandit-based-approach</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the algorithm configuration (AC) problem, in which one seeks to find an optimal parameter configuration of a given target algorithm in an automated way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ac-band-a-combinatorial-bandit-based-approach</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Compatibility between a Neural Network and a Partial Differential Equation for Physics-informed Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-compatibility-between-a-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this pitfall, we prove that a linear PDE up to the $n$-th order can be strictly satisfied by an MLP with $C^n$ activation functions when the weights of its output layer lie on a certain hyperplane, as called the out-layer-hyperplane.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-compatibility-between-a-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do you MEME? Generating Explanations for Visual Semantic Role Labelling in Memes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-you-meme-generating-explanations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we introduce a novel task - EXCLAIM, generating explanations for visual semantic role labeling in memes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-do-you-meme-generating-explanations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GrannGAN: Graph annotation generative adversarial networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granngan-graph-annotation-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The model we propose tackles the problem of generating the data features constrained by the specific graph structure of each data point by splitting the task into two phases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/granngan-graph-annotation-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Fast Unit Commitment Constraint Screening via Learning Cost Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-fast-unit-commitment-constraint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unit commitment (UC) are essential tools to transmission system operators for finding the most economical and feasible generation schedules and dispatch signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enabling-fast-unit-commitment-constraint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Commonsense-Infused Language-Agnostic Learning Framework for Enhancing Prediction of Political Polarity in Multilingual News Headlines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-commonsense-infused-language-agnostic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With attended knowledge in our framework, the same model show an increase in 2. 2% accuracy and F1, and 3. 6% jaccard score.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-commonsense-infused-language-agnostic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analogical Math Word Problems Solving with Enhanced Problem-Solution Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analogical-math-word-problems-solving-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to build a novel MWP solver by leveraging analogical MWPs, which advance the solver's generalization ability across different kinds of MWPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/analogical-math-word-problems-solving-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compositional Learning of Dynamical System Models Using Port-Hamiltonian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-learning-of-dynamical-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Toward the objective of learning composite models of such systems from data, we present i) a framework for compositional neural networks, ii) algorithms to train these models, iii) a method to compose the learned models, iv) theoretical results that bound the error of the resulting composite models, and v) a method to learn the composition itself, when it is not known a prior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/compositional-learning-of-dynamical-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRiT: A Generative Region-to-text Transformer for Object Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-a-generative-region-to-text-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, GRiT consists of a visual encoder to extract image features, a foreground object extractor to localize objects, and a text decoder to generate open-set object descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grit-a-generative-region-to-text-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Robust State Observers using Neural ODEs (longer version)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-state-observers-using-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Relying on recent research results on Neural ODEs, this paper presents a methodology for the design of state observers for nonlinear systems based on Neural ODEs, learning Luenberger-like observers and their nonlinear extension (Kazantzis-Kravaris-Luenberger (KKL) observers) for systems with partially-known nonlinear dynamics and fully unknown nonlinear dynamics, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-robust-state-observers-using-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Zero-Shot Models with Label Distribution Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-models-with-label</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a new approach, CLIPPR (CLIP with Priors), which adapts zero-shot models for regression and classification on unlabelled datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-zero-shot-models-with-label</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Image Restoration Using Denoising Diffusion Null-Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-restoration-using-denoising</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most existing Image Restoration (IR) models are task-specific, which can not be generalized to different degradation operators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-image-restoration-using-denoising</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semiconductor Defect Pattern Classification by Self-Proliferation-and-Attention Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semiconductor-defect-pattern-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel architecture that can perform defect classification in a more efficient way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semiconductor-defect-pattern-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixed Neural Voxels for Fast Multi-view Video Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-neural-voxels-for-fast-multi-view-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a novel method named MixVoxels to better represent the dynamic scenes with fast training speed and competitive rendering qualities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixed-neural-voxels-for-fast-multi-view-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Combinatorial Structures via Markov Random Fields with Sampling through Lovász Local Lemma</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-combinatorial-structures-via-markov</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because of the highly intractable nature of the gradient estimation of the learning objective subject to combinatorial constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-combinatorial-structures-via-markov</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRRGN: An Implicit Relational Reasoning Graph Network for Multi-turn Response Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrgn-an-implicit-relational-reasoning-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[URR aims to implicitly extract dependencies between utterances, as well as utterances and options, and make reasoning with relational graph convolutional networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/irrgn-an-implicit-relational-reasoning-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generate Text-grounded Mask for Open-world Semantic Segmentation from Only Image-Text Pairs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-text-grounded-mask-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing open-world segmentation methods have shown impressive advances by employing contrastive learning (CL) to learn diverse visual concepts and adapting the learned image-level understanding to the segmentation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generate-text-grounded-mask-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Representations Reveal Distinct Modes of Class Fitting in Residual Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-representations-reveal-distinct-modes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we estimate class-conditional density models for representations learned by deep ResNets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-representations-reveal-distinct-modes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PIZZA: A new benchmark for complex end-to-end task-oriented parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pizza-a-new-benchmark-for-complex-end-to-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Much recent work in task-oriented parsing has focused on finding a middle ground between flat slots and intents, which are inexpressive but easy to annotate, and powerful representations such as the lambda calculus, which are expressive but costly to annotate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pizza-a-new-benchmark-for-complex-end-to-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ODPP: A Unified Algorithm Framework for Unsupervised Option Discovery based on Determinantal Point Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odpp-a-unified-algorithm-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning rich skills through temporal abstractions without supervision of external rewards is at the frontier of Reinforcement Learning research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/odpp-a-unified-algorithm-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super-CLEVR: A Virtual Benchmark to Diagnose Domain Robustness in Visual Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-clevr-a-virtual-benchmark-to-diagnose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual Question Answering (VQA) models often perform poorly on out-of-distribution data and struggle on domain generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/super-clevr-a-virtual-benchmark-to-diagnose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EHRSQL: A Practical Text-to-SQL Benchmark for Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrsql-a-practical-text-to-sql-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new text-to-SQL dataset for electronic health records (EHRs), where the utterances are collected from 222 hospital staff—including physicians, nurses, insurance review and health records teams, and more.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ehrsql-a-practical-text-to-sql-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
