<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:15:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Crystal ball: From innovative attacks to attack effectiveness classifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crystal-ball-from-innovative-attacks-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a set of innovative problem-based evasion attacks against well-known Android malware detection systems, which decrease their detection rate by up to 97%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crystal-ball-from-innovative-attacks-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dora: Sampling and Benchmarking for 3D Shape Variational Auto-Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-sampling-and-benchmarking-for-3d-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Dora-VAE, a novel approach that enhances VAE reconstruction through our proposed sharp edge sampling strategy and a dual cross-attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-sampling-and-benchmarking-for-3d-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unity is Strength: Unifying Convolutional and Transformeral Features for Better Person Re-Identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unity-is-strength-unifying-convolutional-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel fusion framework called FusionReID to unify the strengths of CNNs and Transformers for image-based person ReID.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unity-is-strength-unifying-convolutional-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Participation Context Consistency Learning for Semi-supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-participation-context-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised semantic segmentation has attracted considerable attention for its ability to mitigate the reliance on extensive labeled data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-participation-context-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRT-o1: Optimized Deep Reasoning Translation via Long Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drt-o1-optimized-deep-reasoning-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To simulate LLMs' long thought ability in MT, we first mine sentences containing similes or metaphors from existing literature books, and then develop a multi-agent framework to translate these sentences via long thought.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drt-o1-optimized-deep-reasoning-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiered Acquisition for Constrained Bayesian Optimization: An Application to Analog Circuits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiered-acquisition-for-constrained-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analog circuit design can be considered as an optimization problem with the targeted circuit specifications as constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tiered-acquisition-for-constrained-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bi-Directional Multi-Scale Graph Dataset Condensation via Information Bottleneck</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-multi-scale-graph-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main bottleneck of the above paradigms is whether the effective information of the original graph is fully preserved when consenting to the primary sub-scale (the first of multiple scales), which determines the condensation effect and consistency of all scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bi-directional-multi-scale-graph-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just What You Desire: Constrained Timeline Summarization with Self-Reflection for Enhanced Relevance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-what-you-desire-constrained-timeline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an approach that employs a large language model (LLM) to summarize news articles according to a specified constraint and cluster them to identify key events to include in a constrained timeline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/just-what-you-desire-constrained-timeline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bivariate Matrix-valued Linear Regression (BMLR): Finite-sample performance under Identifiability and Sparsity Assumptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bivariate-matrix-valued-linear-regression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the estimation of parameters in a matrix-valued linear regression model, where the $T$ responses $(Y_t)_{t=1}^T \in \mathbb{R}^{n \times p}$ and predictors $(X_t)_{t=1}^T \in \mathbb{R}^{m \times q}$ satisfy the relationship $Y_t = A^* X_t B^* + E_t$ for all $t = 1, \ldots, T$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bivariate-matrix-valued-linear-regression</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Experimental Evaluation of Japanese Tokenizers for Sentiment-Based Text Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-experimental-evaluation-of-japanese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates the performance of three popular tokenization tools: MeCab, Sudachi, and SentencePiece, when applied as a preprocessing step for sentiment-based text classification of Japanese texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-experimental-evaluation-of-japanese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeV: Issue Resolving with Visual Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codev-issue-resolving-with-visual-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have advanced rapidly in recent years, with their applications in software engineering expanding to more complex repository-level tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codev-issue-resolving-with-visual-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chumor 2.0: Towards Benchmarking Chinese Humor Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chumor-2-0-towards-benchmarking-chinese-humor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing humor datasets and evaluations predominantly focus on English, leaving limited resources for culturally nuanced humor in non-English languages like Chinese.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chumor-2-0-towards-benchmarking-chinese-humor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMAC-Hard: Enabling Mixed Opponent Strategy Script and Self-play on SMAC</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smac-hard-enabling-mixed-opponent-strategy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SMAC-HARD supports customizable opponent strategies, randomization of adversarial policies, and interfaces for MARL self-play, enabling agents to generalize to varying opponent behaviors and improve model stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smac-hard-enabling-mixed-opponent-strategy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenario-Wise Rec: A Multi-Scenario Recommendation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scenario-wise-rec-a-multi-scenario</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi Scenario Recommendation (MSR) tasks, referring to building a unified model to enhance performance across all recommendation scenarios, have recently gained much attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scenario-wise-rec-a-multi-scenario</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGONITE: Iterative Retrieval on Induced Databases and Verbalized RDF for Conversational QA over KGs with RAG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragonite-iterative-retrieval-on-induced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational question answering (ConvQA) is a convenient means of searching over RDF knowledge graphs (KGs), where a prevalent approach is to translate natural language questions to SPARQL queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragonite-iterative-retrieval-on-induced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian penalized empirical likelihood and MCMC sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-penalized-empirical-likelihood-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach has two primary objectives: (i) to enhance the inherent flexibility of EL in accommodating diverse model conditions, and (ii) to facilitate the use of well-established Markov Chain Monte Carlo (MCMC) sampling schemes as a convenient alternative to the complex optimization typically required for statistical inference using EL.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-penalized-empirical-likelihood-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous Federated Learning: A Scalable Approach for Decentralized Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-federated-learning-a-scalable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, traditional FL approaches often face limitations in scalability and efficiency due to their reliance on synchronous client updates, which can result in significant delays and increased communication overhead, particularly in heterogeneous and dynamic environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-federated-learning-a-scalable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dual-Perspective Metaphor Detection Framework Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-perspective-metaphor-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Metaphor detection, a critical task in natural language processing, involves identifying whether a particular word in a sentence is used metaphorically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dual-perspective-metaphor-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comprehensive Multi-Modal Prototypes are Simple and Effective Classifiers for Vast-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-multi-modal-prototypes-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enabling models to recognize vast open-world categories has been a longstanding pursuit in object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comprehensive-multi-modal-prototypes-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Cross-Lingual Sentiment Analysis through Emoji Interpretation: A Multimodal Generative AI Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-cross-lingual-sentiment-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our analysis reveals that the accuracy of LLM-based emoji-conveyed sentiment is 81. 43%, underscoring emojis' significant potential to serve as a universal sentiment marker.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlocking-cross-lingual-sentiment-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S-INF: Towards Realistic Indoor Scene Synthesis via Scene Implicit Neural Field</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-inf-towards-realistic-indoor-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It disentangles the multimodal relationships into scene layout relationships and detailed object relationships, fusing them later through implicit neural fields (INFs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s-inf-towards-realistic-indoor-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Generalization Ability of Machine-Generated Text Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalization-ability-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rise of large language models (LLMs) has raised concerns about machine-generated text (MGT), including ethical and practical issues like plagiarism and misinformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-generalization-ability-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resource-Aware Arabic LLM Creation: Model Adaptation, Integration, and Multi-Domain Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-aware-arabic-llm-creation-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach to fine-tuning the Qwen2-1. 5B model for Arabic language processing using Quantized Low-Rank Adaptation (QLoRA) on a system with only 4GB VRAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resource-aware-arabic-llm-creation-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResearchTown: Simulator of Human Research Community</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/researchtown-simulator-of-human-research</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments reveal three key findings: (1) ResearchTown can provide a realistic simulation of collaborative research activities, including paper writing and review writing; (2) ResearchTown can maintain robust simulation with multiple researchers and diverse papers; (3) ResearchTown can generate interdisciplinary research ideas that potentially inspire novel research directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/researchtown-simulator-of-human-research</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient fine-tuning methodology of text embedding models for information retrieval: contrastive learning penalty (clp)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fine-tuning-methodology-of-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text embedding models play a crucial role in natural language processing, particularly in information retrieval, and their importance is further highlighted with the recent utilization of RAG (Retrieval- Augmented Generation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-fine-tuning-methodology-of-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Conditioned Motion Diffusion for Pose-Based Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-conditioned-motion-diffusion-for-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address pose-based video anomaly detection and introduce a novel framework called Dual Conditioned Motion Diffusion (DCMD), which enjoys the advantages of both approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-conditioned-motion-diffusion-for-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Generative AI Models for Deep Learning Test Input Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-generative-ai-models-for-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test Input Generators (TIGs) are crucial to assess the ability of Deep Learning (DL) image classifiers to provide correct predictions for inputs beyond their training and test sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-generative-ai-models-for-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LegalAgentBench: Evaluating LLM Agents in Legal Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legalagentbench-evaluating-llm-agents-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose LegalAgentBench, a comprehensive benchmark specifically designed to evaluate LLM Agents in the Chinese legal domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/legalagentbench-evaluating-llm-agents-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B-STaR: Monitoring and Balancing Exploration and Exploitation in Self-Taught Reasoners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/b-star-monitoring-and-balancing-exploration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the absence of extensive human-annotated data for complex reasoning tasks, self-improvement -- where models are trained on their own outputs -- has emerged as a primary method for enhancing performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/b-star-monitoring-and-balancing-exploration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YuLan-Mini: An Open Data-efficient Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yulan-mini-an-open-data-efficient-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective pre-training of large language models (LLMs) has been challenging due to the immense resource demands and the complexity of the technical processes involved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yulan-mini-an-open-data-efficient-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interweaving Memories of a Siamese Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interweaving-memories-of-a-siamese-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A promising approach to mitigate this issue is to recall prior memories based on the original knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interweaving-memories-of-a-siamese-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modality-Aware Shot Relating and Comparing for Video Scene Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-aware-shot-relating-and-comparing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving this requires meticulously correlating multi-modal cues, $\it{e. g.}$ visual entity and place modalities, among shots and comparing semantic changes around each shot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modality-aware-shot-relating-and-comparing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel-Aware Graph Prompt Learning for Few-Shot Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-aware-graph-prompt-learning-for-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, a kernel-aware hierarchical graph is built by taking the different layer features focusing on anomalous regions of different sizes as nodes, meanwhile, the relationships between arbitrary pairs of nodes stand for the edges of the graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-aware-graph-prompt-learning-for-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>xPatch: Dual-Stream Time Series Forecasting with Exponential Seasonal-Trend Decomposition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpatch-dual-stream-time-series-forecasting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we design eXponential Patch (xPatch for short), a novel dual-stream architecture that utilizes exponential decomposition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xpatch-dual-stream-time-series-forecasting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Models to Microtheories: Distilling a Model's Topical Knowledge for Grounded Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-models-to-microtheories-distilling-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that, when added to a general corpus (e. g., Wikipedia), microtheories can supply critical, topical information not necessarily present in the corpus, improving both a model's ability to ground its answers to verifiable knowledge (i. e., show how answers are systematically entailed by documents in the corpus, fully grounding up to +8% more answers), and the accuracy of those grounded answers (up to +8% absolute).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-models-to-microtheories-distilling-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ActiveGS: Active Scene Reconstruction using Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activegs-active-scene-reconstruction-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of our framework is an effective confidence modelling technique for the Gaussian splatting map to identify under-reconstructed areas, while utilising spatial information from the voxel map to target unexplored areas and assist in collision-free path planning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/activegs-active-scene-reconstruction-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPE-P: Evidence-based Parameter-efficient Prompting for Multimodal Learning with Missing Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epe-p-evidence-based-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods for managing missing modalities often require the design of separate prompts for each modality or missing case, leading to complex designs and a substantial increase in the number of parameters to be learned.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epe-p-evidence-based-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Pareto Set Learning for Expensive Multi-objective Optimization via Stein Variational Hypernetworks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-pareto-set-learning-for-expensive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through extensive experiments across both synthetic and real-world MOO benchmarks, we demonstrate that SVH-PSL significantly improves the quality of the learned Pareto set, offering a promising solution for expensive multi-objective optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-pareto-set-learning-for-expensive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating the Search for Artificial Life with Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-search-for-artificial-life</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent Nobel Prize awarded for radical advances in protein discovery, foundation models (FMs) for exploring large combinatorial spaces promise to revolutionize many scientific fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-search-for-artificial-life</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generating Completions for Fragmented Broca's Aphasic Sentences Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-completions-for-fragmented-broca-s</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first generate synthetic Broca's aphasic data using a rule-based system designed to mirror the linguistic characteristics of Broca's aphasic speech.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generating-completions-for-fragmented-broca-s</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-View Referring Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-referring-multi-object-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It introduces the cross-view to obtain the appearances of objects from multiple views, avoiding the problem of the invisible appearances of objects in RMOT task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-referring-multi-object-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friends-MMC: A Dataset for Multi-modal Multi-party Conversation Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/friends-mmc-a-dataset-for-multi-modal-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this Friends-MMC dataset, we further study two fundamental MMC tasks: conversation speaker identification and conversation response prediction, both of which have the multi-party nature with the video or image as visual context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/friends-mmc-a-dataset-for-multi-modal-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Cancer Gene Identification through Graph Anomaly Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-cancer-gene-identification-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph neural networks (GNNs) have shown promise in integrating protein-protein interaction (PPI) networks for identifying cancer genes in recent studies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-cancer-gene-identification-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VarAD: Lightweight High-Resolution Image Anomaly Detection via Visual Autoregressive Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varad-lightweight-high-resolution-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle HRIAD, this paper translates image anomaly detection into visual token prediction and proposes VarAD based on visual autoregressive modeling for token prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/varad-lightweight-high-resolution-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VidTwin: Video VAE with Decoupled Structure and Dynamics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidtwin-video-vae-with-decoupled-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in video autoencoders (Video AEs) have significantly improved the quality and efficiency of video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vidtwin-video-vae-with-decoupled-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power- and Fragmentation-aware Online Scheduling for GPU Datacenters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-and-fragmentation-aware-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A recent scheduling policy, Fragmentation Gradient Descent (FGD), leverages a fragmentation metric to address this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/power-and-fragmentation-aware-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Reconstruction-Based Out-of-Distribution Detection in Brain MRI with Model and Metric Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reconstruction-based-out-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is crucial for safely deploying automated medical image analysis systems, as abnormal patterns in images could hamper their performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-reconstruction-based-out-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards An Unsupervised Learning Scheme for Efficiently Solving Parameterized Mixed-Integer Programs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-unsupervised-learning-scheme-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe a novel unsupervised learning scheme for accelerating the solution of a family of mixed integer programming (MIP) problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-an-unsupervised-learning-scheme-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guided Real Image Dehazing using YCbCr Color Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-real-image-dehazing-using-ycbcr-color</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image dehazing, particularly with learning-based methods, has gained significant attention due to its importance in real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guided-real-image-dehazing-using-ycbcr-color</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QTSeg: A Query Token-Based Architecture for Efficient 2D Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qtseg-a-query-token-based-architecture-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversely, transformer architectures leverage attention mechanisms to excel in handling long-range dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qtseg-a-query-token-based-architecture-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
