<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:09:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Improved transferability of self-supervised learning models through batch normalization finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-transferability-of-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At a cost of extra training of only 0. 16% model parameters, in case of ResNet-50, we acquire a proxy task that (i) has a stronger correlation with end-to-end finetuned performance, (ii) improves the linear probing performance in the many- and few-shot learning regimes and (iii) in some cases, outperforms both linear probing and end-to-end finetuning, reaching the state-of-the-art performance on a pathology dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-transferability-of-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Platform Video Person ReID: A New Benchmark Dataset and Adaptation Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-platform-video-person-reid-a-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we construct a large-scale benchmark dataset for Ground-to-Aerial Video-based person Re-Identification, named G2A-VReID, which comprises 185, 907 images and 5, 576 tracklets, featuring 2, 788 distinct identities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-platform-video-person-reid-a-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Few-shot Self-explaining Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-few-shot-self-explaining-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, the predictor mimics the decision-making process, which makes predictions based on the generated explanation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-few-shot-self-explaining-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabularBench: Benchmarking Adversarial Robustness for Tabular Deep Learning in Real-world Use-cases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularbench-benchmarking-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to our open benchmark (https://github. com/serval-uni-lu/tabularbench) where we welcome submissions of new models and defenses, we implement 7 robustification mechanisms inspired by state-of-the-art defenses in computer vision and propose the largest benchmark of robust tabular deep learning over 200 models across five critical scenarios in finance, healthcare and security.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabularbench-benchmarking-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Basis Function Selection for Computationally Efficient Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-basis-function-selection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Basis Function (BF) expansions are a cornerstone of any engineer's toolbox for computational function approximation which shares connections with both neural networks and Gaussian processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-basis-function-selection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aquila2 Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aquila2-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces the Aquila2 series, which comprises a wide range of bilingual models with parameter sizes of 7, 34, and 70 billion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aquila2-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LiPCoT: Linear Predictive Coding based Tokenizer for Self-supervised Learning of Time Series Data via Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipcot-linear-predictive-coding-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we utilize LiPCoT to encode EEG data into a small vocabulary of tokens and then use BERT for self-supervised learning and the downstream task of PD classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipcot-linear-predictive-coding-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Triple Attention Network: A Decoupled Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-triple-attention-network-a-decoupled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, we propose a high-level decoupled perspective of GTs, breaking them down into three components and two interaction levels: positional attention, structural attention, and attribute attention, alongside local and global interaction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-triple-attention-network-a-decoupled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>q-exponential family for policy optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-exponential-family-for-policy-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider a broader policy family that remains tractable: the $q$-exponential family.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/q-exponential-family-for-policy-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domain-invariant Representation Learning via Segment Anything Model for Blood Cell Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-invariant-representation-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we propose a novel framework of domain-invariant representation learning (DoRL) via segment anything model (SAM) for blood cell classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/domain-invariant-representation-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alignment-Enhanced Decoding:Defending via Token-Level Adaptive Refining of Probability Distributions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-enhanced-decoding-defending-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models are susceptible to jailbreak attacks, which can result in the generation of harmful content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alignment-enhanced-decoding-defending-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRIF-DM: Generation of Rich Impression Fonts using Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grif-dm-generation-of-rich-impression-fonts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a diffusion-based method, termed \ourmethod, to generate fonts that vividly embody specific impressions, utilizing an input consisting of a single letter and a set of descriptive impression keywords.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grif-dm-generation-of-rich-impression-fonts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Merging in LLMs, MLLMs, and Beyond: Methods, Theories, Applications and Opportunities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-merging-in-llms-mllms-and-beyond</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging is an efficient empowerment technique in the machine learning community that does not require the collection of raw training data and does not require expensive computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-merging-in-llms-mllms-and-beyond</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimising Dynamic Traffic Distribution for Urban Networks with Answer Set Programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-dynamic-traffic-distribution-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Answer Set Programming (ASP) has demonstrated its potential as an effective tool for concisely representing and reasoning about real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimising-dynamic-traffic-distribution-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaSeg: MetaFormer-based Global Contexts-aware Network for Efficient Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaseg-metaformer-based-global-contexts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a powerful semantic segmentation network, MetaSeg, which leverages the Metaformer architecture from the backbone to the decoder.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaseg-metaformer-based-global-contexts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNN-JEPA: Self-Supervised Pretraining Convolutional Neural Networks Using Joint Embedding Predictive Architecture</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnn-jepa-self-supervised-pretraining</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-supervised learning (SSL) has become an important approach in pretraining large neural networks, enabling unprecedented scaling of model and dataset sizes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnn-jepa-self-supervised-pretraining</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Step Diffusion-based Super-Resolution with Time-Aware Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-diffusion-based-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we introduce a novel score distillation strategy to align the data distribution between the outputs of the student and teacher models after minor noise perturbation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-step-diffusion-based-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeriodWave: Multi-Period Flow Matching for High-Fidelity Waveform Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/periodwave-multi-period-flow-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we utilize a multi-period estimator that avoids overlaps to capture different periodic features of waveform signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/periodwave-multi-period-flow-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Data Efficient Neural Networks with Hybrid Concept-based Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-data-efficient-neural-networks-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most datasets used for supervised machine learning consist of a single label per data point.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/achieving-data-efficient-neural-networks-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Stereo Matching Network For VHR Remote Sensing Images Based On Error Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-stereo-matching-network-for-vhr</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, unsupervised learning methods can leverage the increasing availability of very-high-resolution (VHR) remote sensing images, offering considerable potential in the realm of stereo matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-stereo-matching-network-for-vhr</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Near-Duplicate Face Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-near-duplicate-face-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Near-duplicate images are often generated when applying repeated photometric and geometric transformations that produce imperceptible variants of the original image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-near-duplicate-face-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ensemble architecture in polyp segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-architecture-in-polyp-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this research, we revisit the architecture of semantic segmentation and evaluate the models excelling in polyp segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ensemble-architecture-in-polyp-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Distillation with Refined Logits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-with-refined-logits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent research on knowledge distillation has increasingly focused on logit distillation because of its simplicity, effectiveness, and versatility in model compression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-distillation-with-refined-logits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Semi-supervised Multimodal Medical Image Segmentation via Cross Modality Collaboration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semi-supervised-multimodal-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a channel-wise semantic consistency loss, our framework ensures alignment of modality-independent information from a feature-wise perspective across modalities, thereby fortifying it against misalignments in multimodal scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-semi-supervised-multimodal-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wasserstein Gradient Flows of MMD Functionals with Distance Kernel and Cauchy Problems on Quantile Functions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-gradient-flows-of-mmd-functionals</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We give a comprehensive description of Wasserstein gradient flows of maximum mean discrepancy (MMD) functionals $\mathcal F_\nu := \text{MMD}_K^2(\cdot, \nu)$ towards given target measures $\nu$ on the real line, where we focus on the negative distance kernel $K(x, y) := -|x-y|$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wasserstein-gradient-flows-of-mmd-functionals</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BadMerging: Backdoor Attacks Against Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badmerging-backdoor-attacks-against-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Considering that a merged model may incorporate tasks from different domains, BadMerging can jointly compromise the tasks provided by the adversary (on-task attack) and other contributors (off-task attack) and solve the corresponding unique challenges with novel attack designs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/badmerging-backdoor-attacks-against-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Spitting Image: Modular Superpixel Tokenization in Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spitting-image-modular-superpixel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision Transformer (ViT) architectures traditionally employ a grid-based approach to tokenization independent of the semantic content of an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-spitting-image-modular-superpixel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge in Superposition: Unveiling the Failures of Lifelong Knowledge Editing for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-in-superposition-unveiling-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, this is the first study to investigate knowledge editing from the perspective of superposition and provides a comprehensive observation of superposition across numerous real-world language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-in-superposition-unveiling-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pattern-Matching Dynamic Memory Network for Dual-Mode Traffic Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pattern-matching-dynamic-memory-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PM-DMNet employs a novel dynamic memory network to capture traffic pattern features with only O(N) complexity, significantly reducing computational overhead while achieving excellent performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pattern-matching-dynamic-memory-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sum-Product-Set Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sum-product-set-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Daily internet communication relies heavily on tree-structured graphs, embodied by popular data formats such as XML and JSON.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sum-product-set-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAPLe: Backdoor Attacks on Medical Foundational Models using Prompt Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baple-backdoor-attacks-on-medical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by the latest developments in learnable prompts, this work introduces a method to embed a backdoor into the medical foundation model during the prompt learning phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/baple-backdoor-attacks-on-medical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SigmaRL: A Sample-Efficient and Generalizable Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning Framework for Motion Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sigmarl-a-sample-efficient-and-generalizable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most RL agents exhibit a limited capacity to generalize, often focusing narrowly on specific scenarios, and are usually evaluated in similar or even the same scenarios seen during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sigmarl-a-sample-efficient-and-generalizable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whitening Consistently Improves Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whitening-consistently-improves-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose incorporating ZCA whitening as the final layer of the encoder in self-supervised learning to enhance the quality of learned features by normalizing and decorrelating them.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/whitening-consistently-improves-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesion-aware network for diabetic retinopathy diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-network-for-diabetic-retinopathy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a CNN-based DR diagnosis network with attention mechanism involved, termed lesion-aware network, to better capture lesion information from imbalanced data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lesion-aware-network-for-diabetic-retinopathy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved 3D Whole Heart Geometry from Sparse CMR Slices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-3d-whole-heart-geometry-from-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we explore the combination of Slice Shifting Algorithm (SSA), Spatial Transformer Network (STN), and Label Transformer Network (LTN) to: 1) correct respiratory motion between segmented slices, and 2) transform sparse segmentation data into dense segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-3d-whole-heart-geometry-from-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Real-time Video Compressive Sensing on Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-video-compressive-sensing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The fast evolving mobile devices and existing high-performance video SCI reconstruction algorithms motivate us to develop mobile reconstruction methods for real-world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-real-time-video-compressive-sensing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRFormer: Grouped Residual Self-Attention for Lightweight Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grformer-grouped-residual-self-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The code is available at \url{https://github. com/sisrformer/GRFormer}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/grformer-grouped-residual-self-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReCLIP++: Learn to Rectify the Bias of CLIP for Unsupervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reclip-learn-to-rectify-the-bias-of-clip-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to explicitly model and rectify the bias existing in CLIP to facilitate the unsupervised semantic segmentation task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reclip-learn-to-rectify-the-bias-of-clip-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flexible 3D Lane Detection by Hierarchical Shape MatchingFlexible 3D Lane Detection by Hierarchical Shape Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-3d-lane-detection-by-hierarchical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As one of the basic while vital technologies for HD map construction, 3D lane detection is still an open problem due to varying visual conditions, complex typologies, and strict demands for precision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flexible-3d-lane-detection-by-hierarchical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Synthetic Image Detection Towards Generalization: An Image Transformation Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-synthetic-image-detection-towards</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we re-examine the SID problem and identify two prevalent biases in current training paradigms, i. e., weakened artifact features and overfitted artifact features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-synthetic-image-detection-towards</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified-IoU: For High-Quality Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-iou-for-high-quality-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the loss function dynamically shifts the model's attention from low-quality prediction boxes to high-quality prediction boxes in a novel way to enhance the model's detection performance on high-precision or intensive datasets and achieve a balance in training speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-iou-for-high-quality-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AquilaMoE: Efficient Training for MoE Models with Scale-Up and Scale-Out Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aquilamoe-efficient-training-for-moe-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present AquilaMoE, a cutting-edge bilingual 8*16B Mixture of Experts (MoE) language model that has 8 experts with 16 billion parameters each and is developed using an innovative training methodology called EfficientScale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aquilamoe-efficient-training-for-moe-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integration of Genetic Algorithms and Deep Learning for the Generation and Bioactivity Prediction of Novel Tyrosine Kinase Inhibitors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integration-of-genetic-algorithms-and-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The intersection of artificial intelligence and bioinformatics has enabled significant advancements in drug discovery, particularly through the application of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/integration-of-genetic-algorithms-and-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The News Comment Gap and Algorithmic Agenda Setting in Online Forums</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-news-comment-gap-and-algorithmic-agenda</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is thus important to understand journalist vs reader comment preferences and how these are served by various comment ranking algorithms that represent discussions differently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-news-comment-gap-and-algorithmic-agenda</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Continuous Control with Generative Flow Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-continuous-control-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Flow Networks (GFlowNets) aim to generate diverse trajectories from a distribution in which the final states of the trajectories are proportional to the reward, serving as a powerful alternative to reinforcement learning for exploratory control tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-agent-continuous-control-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Cross-Domain Single Blood Cell Image Classification via Large-Scale LoRA-based Segment Anything Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-domain-single-blood-cell-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate classification of blood cells plays a vital role in hematological analysis as it aids physicians in diagnosing various medical conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-cross-domain-single-blood-cell-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenResearcher: Unleashing AI for Accelerated Scientific Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openresearcher-unleashing-ai-for-accelerated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid growth of scientific literature imposes significant challenges for researchers endeavoring to stay updated with the latest advancements in their fields and delve into new areas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openresearcher-unleashing-ai-for-accelerated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLGait: A Global-Local Temporal Receptive Field Network for Gait Recognition in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glgait-a-global-local-temporal-receptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, some Convolution Neural Networks (ConvNets) based methods have been proposed to address the issue of gait recognition in the wild.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glgait-a-global-local-temporal-receptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Agent based on Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-agent-based-on-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the tools module, the causal agent applies causal methods to align tabular data with natural language.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-agent-based-on-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDRGS: High Dynamic Range Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdrgs-high-dynamic-range-gaussian-splatting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Gaussian Splatting-a recent, high-quality, real-time 3D reconstruction technique-into this domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hdrgs-high-dynamic-range-gaussian-splatting</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
