<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 09:13:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards End-to-end Semi-supervised Learning for One-stage Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-to-end-semi-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to this challenge, we also reveal two key issues in one-stage SSOD, which are low-quality pseudo-labeling and multi-task optimization conflict, respectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-end-to-end-semi-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Speech Enhancement and Separation with Gradient Modulation for End-to-End Noise-Robust Speech Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-speech-enhancement-and-separation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To alleviate this problem, we propose a novel network to unify speech enhancement and separation with gradient modulation to improve noise-robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-speech-enhancement-and-separation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distribution Normalization: An "Effortless" Test-Time Augmentation for Contrastively Learned Visual-language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-normalization-an-effortless-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in the field of visual-language contrastive learning have made it possible for many downstream applications to be carried out efficiently and accurately by simply taking the dot product between image and text representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distribution-normalization-an-effortless-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Error Estimation for Random Fourier Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-estimation-for-random-fourier-features</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Three key advantages of this approach are: (1) The error estimates are specific to the problem at hand, avoiding the pessimism of worst-case bounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/error-estimation-for-random-fourier-features</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distributionally Robust Recourse Action</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-robust-recourse-action-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To redress this shortcoming, we propose the Distributionally Robust Recourse Action (DiRRAc) framework, which generates a recourse action that has a high probability of being valid under a mixture of model shifts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distributionally-robust-recourse-action-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KS-DETR: Knowledge Sharing in Attention Learning for Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ks-detr-knowledge-sharing-in-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a triple-attention module in which the first attention is a plain scaled dot-product attention, the second/third attention generates high-quality weights/values (with the assistance of GT Fg-Bg Mask) and shares the values/weights with the first attention to improve the quality of values/weights.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ks-detr-knowledge-sharing-in-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gradient Remedy for Multi-Task Learning in End-to-End Noise-Robust Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-remedy-for-multi-task-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a simple yet effective approach called gradient remedy (GR) to solve interference between task gradients in noise-robust speech recognition, from perspectives of both angle and magnitude.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gradient-remedy-for-multi-task-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modal Audio-visual Co-learning for Text-independent Speaker Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-audio-visual-co-learning-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visual speech (i. e., lip motion) is highly related to auditory speech due to the co-occurrence and synchronization in speech production.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-audio-visual-co-learning-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feasible Recourse Plan via Diverse Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasible-recourse-plan-via-diverse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that our method produces a set of recourses that are close to the data manifold while delivering a better cost-diversity trade-off than existing approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feasible-recourse-plan-via-diverse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asynchronous Trajectory Matching-Based Multimodal Maritime Data Fusion for Vessel Traffic Surveillance in Inland Waterways</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-trajectory-matching-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further improve vessel traffic surveillance, it becomes necessary to fuse the AIS and video data to simultaneously capture the visual features, identity and dynamic information for the vessels of interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asynchronous-trajectory-matching-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAD: Towards Principled Adversarial Malware Detection Against Evasion Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pad-towards-principled-adversarial-malware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine Learning (ML) techniques facilitate automating malicious software (malware for short) detection, but suffer from evasion attacks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pad-towards-principled-adversarial-malware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Energy-Based Test Sample Adaptation for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-test-sample-adaptation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose energy-based sample adaptation at test time for domain generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/energy-based-test-sample-adaptation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GTRL: An Entity Group-Aware Temporal Knowledge Graph Representation Learning Method</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gtrl-an-entity-group-aware-temporal-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[GTRL is the first work that incorporates the entity group modeling to capture the correlation between entities by stacking only a finite number of layers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gtrl-an-entity-group-aware-temporal-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BUAA_BIGSCity: Spatial-Temporal Graph Neural Network for Wind Power Forecasting in Baidu KDD CUP 2022</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buaa-bigscity-spatial-temporal-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, organizers provide a wind power dataset containing historical data from 134 wind turbines and launch the Baidu KDD Cup 2022 to examine the limitations of current methods for wind power forecasting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/buaa-bigscity-spatial-temporal-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Generalize Provably in Learning to Optimize</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-provably-in-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the optimizer generalization has been recently studied, the optimizee generalization (or learning to generalize) has not been rigorously studied in the L2O context, which is the aim of this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-generalize-provably-in-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The DeepCAR Method: Forecasting Time-Series Data That Have Change Points</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-deepcar-method-forecasting-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many methods for time-series forecasting are known in classical statistics, such as autoregression, moving averages, and exponential smoothing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-deepcar-method-forecasting-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploration by self-supervised exploitation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-by-self-supervised-exploitation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning can solve decision-making problems and train an agent to behave in an environment according to a predesigned reward function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-by-self-supervised-exploitation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust and Explainable Contextual Anomaly Detection using Quantile Regression Forests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-explainable-contextual-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional anomaly detection methods aim to identify objects that deviate from most other objects by treating all features equally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-and-explainable-contextual-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNG: Taxonomy Expansion by Exploring the Intrinsic Directed Structure on Non-Gaussian Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dng-taxonomy-expansion-by-exploring-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the inherited feature originates from "parent" nodes and is weighted by an inheritance factor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dng-taxonomy-expansion-by-exploring-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from Multiple Sources for Data-to-Text and Text-to-Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-multiple-sources-for-data-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our model is designed to handle the tasks of D2T and T2D jointly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-multiple-sources-for-data-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-SwinUNet: Spatio-temporal Deep Learning Framework for VFSS Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-swinunet-spatio-temporal-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a deep learning framework for medical video segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-swinunet-spatio-temporal-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining a $k$-nearest neighbor graph for a computationally efficient spectral clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-a-k-nearest-neighbor-graph-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We proposed a refined version of $k$-nearest neighbor graph, in which we keep data points and aggressively reduce number of edges for computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refining-a-k-nearest-neighbor-graph-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASSET: Robust Backdoor Data Detection Across a Multiplicity of Deep Learning Paradigms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asset-robust-backdoor-data-detection-across-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, we lack a thorough understanding of the applicability of existing detection methods across a variety of learning settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/asset-robust-backdoor-data-detection-across-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Visual Appearance and Geometry for Multi-modality 6DoF Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-visual-appearance-and-geometry-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a multi-modality tracker that fuses information from visual appearance and geometry to estimate object poses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusing-visual-appearance-and-geometry-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Probabilistic Models for Graph-Structured Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a variational expectation maximization algorithm to train our DPM in the semi-supervised setting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-probabilistic-models-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimax-Bayes Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-bayes-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the Bayesian decision-theoretic framework offers an elegant solution to the problem of decision making under uncertainty, one question is how to appropriately select the prior distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-bayes-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CADIS: Handling Cluster-skewed Non-IID Data in Federated Learning with Clustered Aggregation and Knowledge DIStilled Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cadis-handling-cluster-skewed-non-iid-data-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By performing an in-depth analysis of the behavior of a classification model's penultimate layer, we introduce a metric that quantifies the similarity between two clients' data distributions without violating their privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cadis-handling-cluster-skewed-non-iid-data-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT: Jack of all trades, master of none</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-jack-of-all-trades-master-of-none</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our comparison of its results with available State-of-the-Art (SOTA) solutions showed that the average loss in quality of the ChatGPT model was about 25% for zero-shot and few-shot evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-jack-of-all-trades-master-of-none</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memory-augmented Online Video Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-augmented-online-video-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to understand the surrounding scene is of paramount importance for Autonomous Vehicles (AVs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memory-augmented-online-video-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Privacy Preferences for Smart Devices as Norms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-privacy-preferences-for-smart</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Smart devices, such as smart speakers, are becoming ubiquitous, and users expect these devices to act in accordance with their preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-privacy-preferences-for-smart</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Calibrating Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-calibrating-diffusion-probabilistic-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we observe that the stochastic reverse process of data scores is a martingale, from which concentration bounds and the optional stopping theorem for data scores can be derived.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-calibrating-diffusion-probabilistic-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SF2Former: Amyotrophic Lateral Sclerosis Identification From Multi-center MRI Data Using Spatial and Frequency Fusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sf2former-amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, a majority voting scheme has been employed to those coronal slices of a particular subject to produce the final classification decision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sf2former-amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Infomin Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-infomin-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of infomin learning aims to learn a representation with high utility while being uninformative about a specified target, with the latter achieved by minimising the mutual information between the representation and the target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-infomin-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FrankenSplit: Saliency Guided Neural Feature Compression with Shallow Variational Bottleneck Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frankensplit-saliency-guided-neural-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lightweight neural networks exchange fast inference for predictive strength.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frankensplit-saliency-guided-neural-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Discretization using Voronoi Trees for Continuous POMDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-discretization-using-voronoi-trees-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ADVT uses the estimated diameters of the cells to form an upper-confidence bound on the action value function within the cell, guiding the Monte Carlo Tree Search expansion and further discretization of the action space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-discretization-using-voronoi-trees-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-Driven Recognition of Semantic Consistency via the Fusion of Transformer and HowNet Sememes Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-driven-recognition-of-semantic-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-level encoding of internal sentence structures via data-driven is carried out firstly by Transformer, sememes knowledge base HowNet is introduced for knowledge-driven to model the semantic knowledge association among sentence pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-driven-recognition-of-semantic-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Social Explanations for Stochastic Sequential Multi-Agent Decision-Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-social-explanations-for-stochastic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel framework to generate causal explanations for the decisions of agents in stochastic sequential multi-agent environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-social-explanations-for-stochastic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Policy Learning for Aggregation Optimization in Graph Neural Network-based Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-policy-learning-for-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework adaptively determines high-order connectivity to aggregate users and items using dual policy learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-policy-learning-for-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On ML-Based Program Translation: Perils and Promises</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-ml-based-program-translation-perils-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the future, we envision an end-to-end program translation tool where programming domain knowledge can be embedded into an ML-based translation pipeline using pre- and post-processing steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-ml-based-program-translation-perils-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap between ANNs and SNNs by Calibrating Offset Spikes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-anns-and-snns-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that our proposed method achieves state-of-the-art performance on CIFAR-10, CIFAR-100, and ImageNet datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-anns-and-snns-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Inductive Biases for Machine Learning in Data Constrained Settings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-inductive-biases-for-machine-learning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[More precisely, we study the problem of safe sample screening, i. e, executing simple tests to discard uninformative samples from a dataset even before fitting a machine learning model, without affecting the optimal model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-inductive-biases-for-machine-learning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EC-SfM: Efficient Covisibility-based Structure-from-Motion for Both Sequential and Unordered Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ec-sfm-efficient-covisibility-based-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this general image connection, we propose a unified framework to efficiently reconstruct sequential images, unordered images, and the mixture of these two.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ec-sfm-efficient-covisibility-based-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LU-Net: Invertible Neural Networks Based on Matrix Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lu-net-invertible-neural-networks-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, the computation of the determinant of the Jacobian matrix of such layers is cheap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lu-net-invertible-neural-networks-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Domain Gap for Continual Domain Adaptation in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-domain-gap-for-continual-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure reliable object detection in autonomous systems, the detector must be able to adapt to changes in appearance caused by environmental factors such as time of day, weather, and seasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-domain-gap-for-continual-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PointFISH -- learning point cloud representations for RNA localization patterns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointfish-learning-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subcellular RNA localization is a critical mechanism for the spatial control of gene expression.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pointfish-learning-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting the Power of Kernel Two-Sample Tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-power-of-kernel-two-sample-tests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The kernel two-sample test based on the maximum mean discrepancy (MMD) is one of the most popular methods for detecting differences between two distributions over general metric spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-power-of-kernel-two-sample-tests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Scene Text Image Super-Resolution via Dual Prior Modulation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-scene-text-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene text image super-resolution (STISR) aims to simultaneously increase the resolution and legibility of the text images, and the resulting images will significantly affect the performance of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-scene-text-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable Rendering with Reparameterized Volume Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-rendering-with-reparameterized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To generate a pixel of a novel view, it marches a ray through the pixel and computes a weighted sum of radiance emitted from a dense set of ray points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-rendering-with-reparameterized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusion of Global and Local Knowledge for Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-of-global-and-local-knowledge-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Personalized federated learning, as a variant of federated learning, trains customized models for clients using their heterogeneously distributed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fusion-of-global-and-local-knowledge-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mean Parity Fair Regression in RKHS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-parity-fair-regression-in-rkhs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the fair regression problem under the notion of Mean Parity (MP) fairness, which requires the conditional mean of the learned function output to be constant with respect to the sensitive attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-parity-fair-regression-in-rkhs</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
