<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 21:07:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MoE-LLaVA: Mixture of Experts for Large Vision-Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moe-llava-mixture-of-experts-for-large-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel training strategy MoE-tuning for LVLMs, which can constructing a sparse model with an outrageous number of parameter but a constant computational cost, and effectively addresses the performance degradation typically associated with multi-modal learning and model sparsity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moe-llava-mixture-of-experts-for-large-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for a better fit? An Incremental Learning Multimodal Object Referencing Framework adapting to Individual Drivers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-better-fit-an-incremental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid advancement of the automotive industry towards automated and semi-automated vehicles has rendered traditional methods of vehicle interaction, such as touch-based and voice command systems, inadequate for a widening range of non-driving related tasks, such as referencing objects outside of the vehicle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/looking-for-a-better-fit-an-incremental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternLM-XComposer2: Mastering Free-form Text-Image Composition and Comprehension in Vision-Language Large Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-mastering-free-form-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce InternLM-XComposer2, a cutting-edge vision-language model excelling in free-form text-image composition and comprehension.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internlm-xcomposer2-mastering-free-form-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continual Learning with Pre-Trained Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-pre-trained-models-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, real-world applications often face streaming data, which requires the learning system to absorb new knowledge as data evolves.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/continual-learning-with-pre-trained-models-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of pseudo-healthy image reconstruction for anomaly detection with deep generative models: Application to brain FDG PET</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-pseudo-healthy-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past years, pseudo-healthy reconstruction for unsupervised anomaly detection has gained in popularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-pseudo-healthy-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeFlow: Decoder of Scene Flow Network in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deflow-decoder-of-scene-flow-network-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene flow estimation determines a scene's 3D motion field, by predicting the motion of points in the scene, especially for aiding tasks in autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deflow-decoder-of-scene-flow-network-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BooleanOCT: Optimal Classification Trees based on multivariate Boolean Rules</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/booleanoct-optimal-classification-trees-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While existing optimal classification trees substantially enhance accuracy over greedy-based tree models like CART, they still fall short when compared to the more complex black-box models, such as random forests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/booleanoct-optimal-classification-trees-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The McCormick martingale optimal transport</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mccormick-martingale-optimal-transport</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Martingale optimal transport (MOT) often yields broad price bounds for options, constraining their practical applicability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-mccormick-martingale-optimal-transport</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-training and Diagnosing Knowledge Base Completion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-and-diagnosing-knowledge-base</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The method works for both canonicalized knowledge bases and uncanonicalized or open knowledge bases, i. e., knowledge bases where more than one copy of a real-world entity or relation may exist.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pre-training-and-diagnosing-knowledge-base</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SupplyGraph: A Benchmark Dataset for Supply Chain Planning using Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supplygraph-a-benchmark-dataset-for-supply</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there is a noticeable absence of research on applying GNNs to supply chain networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/supplygraph-a-benchmark-dataset-for-supply</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Neural Topic Models: Methods, Applications, and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-neural-topic-models-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a comprehensive survey on neural topic models concerning methods, applications, and challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-neural-topic-models-methods</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiHop-RAG: Benchmarking Retrieval-Augmented Generation for Multi-Hop Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multihop-rag-benchmarking-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope MultiHop-RAG will be a valuable resource for the community in developing effective RAG systems, thereby facilitating greater adoption of LLMs in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multihop-rag-benchmarking-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Airavata: Introducing Hindi Instruction-tuned LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/airavata-introducing-hindi-instruction-tuned</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We announce the initial release of "Airavata," an instruction-tuned LLM for Hindi.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/airavata-introducing-hindi-instruction-tuned</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TA-RNN: an Attention-based Time-aware Recurrent Neural Network Architecture for Electronic Health Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ta-rnn-an-attention-based-time-aware</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For interpretability, we propose employing a dual-level attention mechanism that operates between visits and features within each visit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ta-rnn-an-attention-based-time-aware</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Space Adaptive Filter: Integrating Graph Topology and Node Attributes for Alleviating the Over-smoothing Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-space-adaptive-filter-integrating-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, various methods have been proposed to create an adaptive filter by incorporating an extra filter (e. g., a high-pass filter) extracted from the graph topology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-space-adaptive-filter-integrating-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personality Perception in Human Videos Altered by Motion Transfer Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personality-perception-in-human-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We follow five different cases to study the influence of motion and appearance on personality perception.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/personality-perception-in-human-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOAt: Explaining Graph Neural Networks via Graph Output Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goat-explaining-graph-neural-networks-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the decision-making process of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) is crucial to their interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/goat-explaining-graph-neural-networks-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Local Control Barrier Functions for Safety Control of Hybrid Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-local-control-barrier-functions-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach is computationally efficient, minimally invasive to any reference controller, and applicable to large-scale systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-local-control-barrier-functions-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Universal Predictors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-universal-predictors</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta-learning has emerged as a powerful approach to train neural networks to learn new tasks quickly from limited data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-universal-predictors</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endowing Protein Language Models with Structural Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endowing-protein-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Drawing from recent advances in graph transformers, our approach refines the self-attention mechanisms of pretrained language transformers by integrating structural information with structure extractor modules.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/endowing-protein-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pLitterStreet: Street Level Plastic Litter Detection and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plitterstreet-street-level-plastic-litter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dataset is open-source and more details about the dataset and trained models can be found at https://github. com/gicait/pLitter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plitterstreet-street-level-plastic-litter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrecognizable Yet Identifiable: Image Distortion with Preserved Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrecognizable-yet-identifiable-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of security applications, biometric authentication systems play a crucial role, yet one often encounters challenges concerning privacy and security while developing one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrecognizable-yet-identifiable-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>F-Eval: Asssessing Fundamental Abilities with Refined Evaluation Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-eval-asssessing-fundamental-abilities-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these evaluation benchmarks are limited to assessing the instruction-following capabilities, overlooking the fundamental abilities that emerge during the pre-training stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/f-eval-asssessing-fundamental-abilities-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROXYQA: An Alternative Framework for Evaluating Long-Form Text Generation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxyqa-an-alternative-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMs are prompted to generate extensive content in response to these meta-questions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proxyqa-an-alternative-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masked Pre-trained Model Enables Universal Zero-shot Denoiser</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-pre-trained-model-enables-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we observe that the model, which is trained on vast general images using masking strategy, has been naturally embedded with the distribution knowledge regarding natural images, and thus spontaneously attains the underlying potential for strong image denoising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masked-pre-trained-model-enables-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conserve-Update-Revise to Cure Generalization and Robustness Trade-off in Adversarial Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conserve-update-revise-to-cure-generalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial training improves the robustness of neural networks against adversarial attacks, albeit at the expense of the trade-off between standard and robust generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conserve-update-revise-to-cure-generalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Particle-MALA and Particle-mGRAD: Gradient-based MCMC methods for high-dimensional state-space models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-mala-and-particle-mgrad-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In experiments, for both highly and weakly informative prior dynamics, our methods substantially improve upon both CSMC and sophisticated 'classical' MCMC approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/particle-mala-and-particle-mgrad-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PARSAC: Accelerating Robust Multi-Model Fitting with Parallel Sample Consensus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parsac-accelerating-robust-multi-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a real-time method for robust estimation of multiple instances of geometric models from noisy data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parsac-accelerating-robust-multi-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Image Inpainting via Global Structure-Guided Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-image-inpainting-via-global-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the global structure of the text as a prior, the proposed GSDM develops an efficient diffusion model to recover clean texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-image-inpainting-via-global-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inferring Data Preconditions from Deep Learning Models for Trustworthy Prediction in Deployment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-data-preconditions-from-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel technique that uses rules derived from neural network computations to infer data preconditions for a DNN model to determine the trustworthiness of its predictions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/inferring-data-preconditions-from-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residual Quantization with Implicit Neural Codebooks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-quantization-with-implicit-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose QINCo, a neural RQ variant which predicts specialized codebooks per vector using a neural network that is conditioned on the approximation of the vector from previous steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-quantization-with-implicit-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annotated Hands for Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotated-hands-for-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These annotations provide additional structure that coax the generative model to produce higher quality hand images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/annotated-hands-for-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Domain Generalization: A Noise Robustness Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-domain-generalization-a-noise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the rapid development of machine learning algorithms for domain generalization (DG), there is no clear empirical evidence that the existing DG algorithms outperform the classic empirical risk minimization (ERM) across standard benchmarks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/understanding-domain-generalization-a-noise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Independent Communication in Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-independent-communication-in-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning (MARL) comprises a broad area of research within the field of multi-agent systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-independent-communication-in-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Macro Graph Neural Networks for Online Billion-Scale Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macro-graph-neural-networks-for-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Predicting Click-Through Rate (CTR) in billion-scale recommender systems poses a long-standing challenge for Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) due to the overwhelming computational complexity involved in aggregating billions of neighbors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/macro-graph-neural-networks-for-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EAGLE: Speculative Sampling Requires Rethinking Feature Uncertainty</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-speculative-sampling-requires</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As of the submission of this paper, EAGLE is the fastest known framework within the speculative sampling family.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eagle-speculative-sampling-requires</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusion Stochastic Optimization for Min-Max Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-stochastic-optimization-for-min-max</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The optimistic gradient method is useful in addressing minimax optimization problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusion-stochastic-optimization-for-min-max</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientific Large Language Models: A Survey on Biological &amp; Chemical Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scientific-large-language-models-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have emerged as a transformative power in enhancing natural language comprehension, representing a significant stride toward artificial general intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scientific-large-language-models-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PL-FSCIL: Harnessing the Power of Prompts for Few-Shot Class-Incremental Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pl-fscil-harnessing-the-power-of-prompts-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach called Prompt Learning for FSCIL (PL-FSCIL), which harnesses the power of prompts in conjunction with a pre-trained Vision Transformer (ViT) model to address the challenges of FSCIL effectively.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pl-fscil-harnessing-the-power-of-prompts-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off-Policy Primal-Dual Safe Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-primal-dual-safe-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results on benchmark tasks show that our method not only achieves an asymptotic performance comparable to state-of-the-art on-policy methods while using much fewer samples, but also significantly reduces constraint violation during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/off-policy-primal-dual-safe-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-Rex: Text-assisted Retrosynthesis Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-rex-text-assisted-retrosynthesis-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a fundamental task in computational chemistry, retrosynthesis prediction aims to identify a set of reactants to synthesize a target molecule.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-rex-text-assisted-retrosynthesis-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SliceGPT: Compress Large Language Models by Deleting Rows and Columns</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slicegpt-compress-large-language-models-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models have become the cornerstone of natural language processing, but their use comes with substantial costs in terms of compute and memory resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slicegpt-compress-large-language-models-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAM: Diffusion Activation Maximization for 3D Global Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-diffusion-activation-maximization-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, the performance of point cloud models has been rapidly improved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dam-diffusion-activation-maximization-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unitxt: Flexible, Shareable and Reusable Data Preparation and Evaluation for Generative AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitxt-flexible-shareable-and-reusable-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the dynamic landscape of generative NLP, traditional text processing pipelines limit research flexibility and reproducibility, as they are tailored to specific dataset, task, and model combinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitxt-flexible-shareable-and-reusable-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comparative Analysis of Noise Reduction Methods in Sentiment Analysis on Noisy Bengali Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-noise-reduction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a dataset (NC-SentNoB) that we annotated manually to identify ten different types of noise found in a pre-existing sentiment analysis dataset comprising of around 15K noisy Bengali texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comparative-analysis-of-noise-reduction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>True Knowledge Comes from Practice: Aligning LLMs with Embodied Environments via Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/true-knowledge-comes-from-practice-aligning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the impressive performance across numerous tasks, large language models (LLMs) often fail in solving simple decision-making tasks due to the misalignment of the knowledge in LLMs with environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/true-knowledge-comes-from-practice-aligning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Design of Input Condition Invariant Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-design-of-input-condition-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we propose novel architectures to improve the input condition invariant SE model so that performance in simulated conditions remains competitive while real condition degradation is much mitigated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-design-of-input-condition-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Active Learning in the Era of Vision Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-active-learning-in-the-era-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation vision or vision-language models are trained on large unlabeled or noisy data and learn robust representations that can achieve impressive zero- or few-shot performance on diverse tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-active-learning-in-the-era-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Quality of DermaMNIST and Fitzpatrick17k Dermatological Image Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-quality-of-dermamnist-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The remarkable progress of deep learning in dermatological tasks has brought us closer to achieving diagnostic accuracies comparable to those of human experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-quality-of-dermamnist-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Manipulate Artistic Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-manipulate-artistic-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancement in computer vision has significantly lowered the barriers to artistic creation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-manipulate-artistic-images</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
