<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 09:12:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Scaffolding a Student to Instill Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaffolding-a-student-to-instill-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel knowledge distillation (KD) method to selectively instill teacher knowledge into a student model motivated by situations where the student's capacity is significantly smaller than that of the teachers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaffolding-a-student-to-instill-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskPrompter: Spatial-Channel Multi-Task Prompting for Dense Scene Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskprompter-spatial-channel-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Each task prompt learns task-specific representation for one task, while all the prompts can jointly contribute to the learning of the shared image token representations, and the interactions between different task prompts model the cross-task relationship.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskprompter-spatial-channel-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIMPLE: Specialized Model-Sample Matching for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-specialized-model-sample-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, our method is highly efficient and achieves more than 1000 times training speedup compared to the conventional DG methods with fine-tuning a pretrained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simple-specialized-model-sample-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Edge Inference by Selective Query</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-edge-inference-by-selective-query</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training a hybrid learner is difficult since we lack annotations of hard edge-examples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-edge-inference-by-selective-query</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stable and Scalable Method for Solving Initial Value PDEs with Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stable-and-scalable-method-for-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unlike conventional grid and mesh based methods for solving partial differential equations (PDEs), neural networks have the potential to break the curse of dimensionality, providing approximate solutions to problems where using classical solvers is difficult or impossible.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-stable-and-scalable-method-for-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA-Adapter V2: Parameter-Efficient Visual Instruction Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-v2-parameter-efficient-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This strategy effectively alleviates the interference between the two tasks of image-text alignment and instruction following and achieves strong multi-modal reasoning with only a small-scale image-text and instruction dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-v2-parameter-efficient-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Enhanced Model for Live Video Comment Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-model-for-live-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Live video commenting is popular on video media platforms, as it can create a chatting atmosphere and provide supplementary information for users while watching videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-enhanced-model-for-live-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Multimodal Model Merging</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-multimodal-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model merging (e. g., via interpolation or task arithmetic) fuses multiple models trained on different tasks to generate a multi-task solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-multimodal-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cost-Sensitive Self-Training for Optimizing Non-Decomposable Metrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-sensitive-self-training-for-optimizing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the proposed CSST framework, we obtain practical self-training methods (for both vision and NLP tasks) for optimizing different non-decomposable metrics using deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cost-sensitive-self-training-for-optimizing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuralKG-ind: A Python Library for Inductive Knowledge Graph Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralkg-ind-a-python-library-for-inductive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Since the dynamic characteristics of knowledge graphs, many inductive knowledge graph representation learning (KGRL) works have been proposed in recent years, focusing on enabling prediction over new entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuralkg-ind-a-python-library-for-inductive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musical Voice Separation as Link Prediction: Modeling a Musical Perception Task as a Multi-Trajectory Tracking Problem</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musical-voice-separation-as-link-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our approach builds a graph from a musical piece, by creating one node for every note, and separates the melodic trajectories by predicting a link between two notes if they are consecutive in the same voice/stream.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musical-voice-separation-as-link-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Knowledge Graph Entity Alignment with Graph Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knowledge-graph-entity-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity alignment (EA) which links equivalent entities across different knowledge graphs (KGs) plays a crucial role in knowledge fusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-knowledge-graph-entity-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A feature selection method based on Shapley values robust to concept shift in regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-selection-method-based-on-shapley-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Feature selection is one of the most relevant processes in any methodology for creating a statistical learning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-feature-selection-method-based-on-shapley-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local-Global Transformer Enhanced Unfolding Network for Pan-sharpening</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-transformer-enhanced-unfolding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we customize a Local-Global Transformer (LGT) to simultaneously model local and global dependencies, and further formulate an LGT-based prior module for image denoising.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/local-global-transformer-enhanced-unfolding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are the Best Multilingual Document Embeddings simply Based on Sentence Embeddings?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-best-multilingual-document-embeddings</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that while a simple sentence average results in a strong baseline for classification tasks, more complex combinations are necessary for semantic tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/are-the-best-multilingual-document-embeddings</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-refined Denoising Network for Robust Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-refined-denoising-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Knowledge graph (KG), which contains rich side information, becomes an essential part to boost the recommendation performance and improve its explainability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-refined-denoising-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HQP: A Human-Annotated Dataset for Detecting Online Propaganda</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hqp-a-human-annotated-dataset-for-detecting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[(3) To address the cost of labeling, we extend our work to few-shot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hqp-a-human-annotated-dataset-for-detecting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGAligner : 3D Scene Alignment with Scene Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgaligner-3d-scene-alignment-with-scene</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SGAligner, the first method for aligning pairs of 3D scene graphs that is robust to in-the-wild scenarios (ie, unknown overlap -- if any -- and changes in the environment).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sgaligner-3d-scene-alignment-with-scene</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synergy of Machine and Deep Learning Models for Multi-Painter Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-of-machine-and-deep-learning-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The growing availability of digitized art collections has created the need to manage, analyze and categorize large amounts of data related to abstract concepts, highlighting a demanding problem of computer science and leading to new research perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synergy-of-machine-and-deep-learning-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Made of Steel? Learning Plausible Materials for Components in the Vehicle Repair Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/made-of-steel-learning-plausible-materials</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel approach to learn domain-specific plausible materials for components in the vehicle repair domain by probing Pretrained Language Models (PLMs) in a cloze task style setting to overcome the lack of annotated datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/made-of-steel-learning-plausible-materials</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Perturbation to Improve Goodness-of-Fit Tests based on Kernelized Stein Discrepancy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-perturbation-to-improve-goodness-of-fit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Kernelized Stein discrepancy (KSD) is a score-based discrepancy widely used in goodness-of-fit tests.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-perturbation-to-improve-goodness-of-fit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Redundancy and Biases in Public Document Information Extraction Benchmarks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-redundancy-and-biases-in-public</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in the Visually-rich Document Understanding (VrDU) field and particularly the Key-Information Extraction (KIE) task are marked with the emergence of efficient Transformer-based approaches such as the LayoutLM models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-redundancy-and-biases-in-public</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CED: Catalog Extraction from Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ced-catalog-extraction-from-documents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we build a large manually annotated corpus, which is the first dataset for the Catalog Extraction from Documents (CED) task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ced-catalog-extraction-from-documents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let the Chart Spark: Embedding Semantic Context into Chart with Text-to-Image Generative Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-chart-spark-embedding-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pictorial visualization seamlessly integrates data and semantic context into visual representation, conveying complex information in a manner that is both engaging and informative.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-the-chart-spark-embedding-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dense Hybrid Proposal Modulation for Lane Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-hybrid-proposal-modulation-for-lane</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to the shape and location constraints, we design a quality-aware classification loss to adaptively supervise each positive proposal so that the discriminative power can be further boosted.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dense-hybrid-proposal-modulation-for-lane</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Structure Analysis of the FRP Rebar Using Computer Vision Techniques</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-analysis-of-the-frp-rebar-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present a method to analyze the inner structure of the composite FRP rebar, namely the shift of the real center of gravity with a respect to the geometrical center of rebar and changes of cross-sectional characteristics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/structure-analysis-of-the-frp-rebar-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pushing the Boundaries of Tractable Multiperspective Reasoning: A Deduction Calculus for Standpoint EL+</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-boundaries-of-tractable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Standpoint EL is a multi-modal extension of the popular description logic EL that allows for the integrated representation of domain knowledge relative to diverse standpoints or perspectives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pushing-the-boundaries-of-tractable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Inductive Bias in Transformer for Point Cloud Classification and Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inductive-bias-in-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Discovering inter-point connection for efficient high-dimensional feature extraction from point coordinate is a key challenge in processing point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-inductive-bias-in-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Modular Approach for Multilingual Timex Detection and Normalization using Deep Learning and Grammar-based methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-approach-for-multilingual-timex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting and normalizing temporal expressions is an essential step for many NLP tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-modular-approach-for-multilingual-timex</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaMini-LM: A Diverse Herd of Distilled Models from Large-Scale Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamini-lm-a-diverse-herd-of-distilled-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we carefully develop a large set of 2. 58M instructions based on both existing and newly-generated instructions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamini-lm-a-diverse-herd-of-distilled-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Density Invariant Contrast Maximization for Neuromorphic Earth Observations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-invariant-contrast-maximization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is to ensure that the contrast is only high around the correct motion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/density-invariant-contrast-maximization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLAC: Fairness-Aware Representation Learning by Suppressing Attribute-Class Associations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flac-fairness-aware-representation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, this work introduces FLAC, a methodology that minimizes mutual information between the features extracted by the model and a protected attribute, without the use of attribute labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flac-fairness-aware-representation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Efficient and Comprehensive Urban Spatial-Temporal Prediction: A Unified Library and Performance Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-comprehensive-urban-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As deep learning technology advances and more urban spatial-temporal data accumulates, an increasing number of deep learning models are being proposed to solve urban spatial-temporal prediction problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-efficient-and-comprehensive-urban-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SweCTRL-Mini: a data-transparent Transformer-based large language model for controllable text generation in Swedish</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swectrl-mini-a-data-transparent-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SweCTRL-Mini, a large Swedish language model that can be used for inference and fine-tuning on a single consumer-grade GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swectrl-mini-a-data-transparent-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We're Afraid Language Models Aren't Modeling Ambiguity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-re-afraid-language-models-aren-t-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the task remains extremely challenging, including for the recent GPT-4, whose generated disambiguations are considered correct only 32% of the time in human evaluation, compared to 90% for disambiguations in our dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/we-re-afraid-language-models-aren-t-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIMS-OS: An automation software to implement a closed loop between artificial intelligence and robotic experiments in materials science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nims-os-an-automation-software-to-implement-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Newly created modules for AI and robotic experiments can be added easily to extend the functionality of the system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nims-os-an-automation-software-to-implement-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entity-Level Sentiment Analysis (ELSA): An exploratory task survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-level-sentiment-analysis-elsa-an-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that sentiment in our dataset is expressed not only with an entity mention as target, but also towards targets with a sentiment-relevant relation to a volitional entity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entity-level-sentiment-analysis-elsa-an-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViMQ: A Vietnamese Medical Question Dataset for Healthcare Dialogue System Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vimq-a-vietnamese-medical-question-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing medical text datasets usually take the form of ques- tion and answer pairs that support the task of natural language gener- ation, but lacking the composite annotations of the medical terms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vimq-a-vietnamese-medical-question-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting People in Their Place: Affordance-Aware Human Insertion into Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-people-in-their-place-affordance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given a scene image with a marked region and an image of a person, we insert the person into the scene while respecting the scene affordances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-people-in-their-place-affordance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight, Pre-trained Transformers for Remote Sensing Timeseries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-pre-trained-transformers-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Presto can be used for transfer learning or as a feature extractor for simple models, enabling efficient deployment at scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-pre-trained-transformers-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>string2string: A Modern Python Library for String-to-String Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It includes traditional algorithmic solutions as well as recent advanced neural approaches to tackle various problems in string alignment, distance measurement, lexical and semantic search, and similarity analysis -- along with several helpful visualization tools and metrics to facilitate the interpretation and analysis of these methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Probabilistic Attention Model with Occlusion-aware Texture Regression for 3D Hand Reconstruction from a Single RGB Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-attention-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results demonstrate our probabilistic model's state-of-the-art accuracy in 3D hand and texture reconstruction from a single image in both training schemes, including in the presence of severe occlusions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-probabilistic-attention-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SeqTrack: Sequence to Sequence Learning for Visual Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqtrack-sequence-to-sequence-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new sequence-to-sequence learning framework for visual tracking, dubbed SeqTrack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seqtrack-sequence-to-sequence-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Aware Neural Network from Similarity and Sensitivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-neural-network-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the proposed NN training method for UQ, first, we train a shallow NN for the point prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-neural-network-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distinguishing a planetary transit from false positives: a Transformer-based classification for planetary transit signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-a-planetary-transit-from-false</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Models, such as the Transformer architecture, were recently proposed for sequential data with successful results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distinguishing-a-planetary-transit-from-false</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Conformer: Incorporating Convolutions into Vision Transformer Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-conformer-incorporating-convolutions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers are popular neural network models that use layers of self-attention and fully-connected nodes with embedded tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-conformer-incorporating-convolutions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models Are State-of-the-Art Evaluators of Code Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-state-of-the-art-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Token-matching-based metrics, such as BLEU, have demonstrated weak correlations with human practitioners in code generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-are-state-of-the-art-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SparseFusion: Fusing Multi-Modal Sparse Representations for Multi-Sensor 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsefusion-fusing-multi-modal-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, given that objects occupy only a small part of a scene, finding dense candidates and generating dense representations is noisy and inefficient.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsefusion-fusing-multi-modal-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of Robust Spectral Shape Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-robust-spectral</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast, building upon recent insights about the relation between functional maps and point-wise maps, we propose a novel unsupervised loss to couple the functional maps and point-wise maps, and thereby directly obtain point-wise maps without any post-processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-robust-spectral</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moderately Distributional Exploration for Domain Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moderately-distributional-exploration-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that MODE can endow models with provable generalization performance on unknown target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moderately-distributional-exploration-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
