<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 21:09:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing person re-identification via Uncertainty Feature Fusion Method and Auto-weighted Measure Combination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-person-re-identification-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the Occluded-DukeMTMC dataset, our method increases Rank@1 by 22. 0% and mAP by 18. 4%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-person-re-identification-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedMLLM: Federated Fine-tuning MLLM on Multimodal Heterogeneity Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmllm-federated-fine-tuning-mllm-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Fine-tuning MLLMs with Federated Learning (FL) allows for expanding the training data scope by including private data sources, thereby enhancing their practical applicability in privacy-sensitive domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedmllm-federated-fine-tuning-mllm-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Multi-modal Models Can Interpret Features in Large Multi-modal Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-multi-modal-models-can-interpret</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in Large Multimodal Models (LMMs) lead to significant breakthroughs in both academia and industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-multi-modal-models-can-interpret</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmological Analysis with Calibrated Neural Quantile Estimation and Approximate Simulators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmological-analysis-with-calibrated-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major challenge in extracting information from current and upcoming surveys of cosmological Large-Scale Structure (LSS) is the limited availability of computationally expensive high-fidelity simulations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmological-analysis-with-calibrated-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Pre-Aligned Method with Global and Local Information for Remote-Sensing Image and Text Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-pre-aligned-method-with-global</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, challenges remain in effectively integrating global and local information due to variations in remote sensing imagery and ensuring proper feature pre-alignment before modal fusion, which affects retrieval accuracy and efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-pre-aligned-method-with-global</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Speaker Identification with Minimal Dataset and Constrained Resources using 1D-Convolution Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-speaker-identification-with-minimal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Voice recognition and speaker identification are vital for applications in security and personal assistants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-speaker-identification-with-minimal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Vision Transformer Models for Visual Quality Control in Industrial Manufacturing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-vision-transformer-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the most promising use-cases for machine learning in industrial manufacturing is the early detection of defective products using a quality control system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-vision-transformer-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionDrive: Truncated Diffusion Model for End-to-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondrive-truncated-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the numerous denoising steps in the robotic diffusion policy and the more dynamic, open-world nature of traffic scenes pose substantial challenges for generating diverse driving actions at a real-time speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondrive-truncated-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many happy returns: machine learning to support platelet issuing and waste reduction in hospital blood banks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-happy-returns-machine-learning-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efforts to reduce platelet wastage in hospital blood banks have focused on ordering policies, but the predominant practice of issuing the oldest unit first may not be optimal when some units are returned unused.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/many-happy-returns-machine-learning-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leapfrog Latent Consistency Model (LLCM) for Medical Images Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leapfrog-latent-consistency-model-llcm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a Leapfrog Latent Consistency Model (LLCM) that is distilled from a retrained diffusion model based on the collected MedImgs dataset, which enables our model to generate real-time high-resolution images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leapfrog-latent-consistency-model-llcm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPAC-Net: Rethinking Point Cloud Completion with Structural Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spac-net-rethinking-point-cloud-completion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud completion aims to infer a complete shape from its partial observation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spac-net-rethinking-point-cloud-completion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Foundation Models Fine-Tuning for Cytology Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-foundation-models-fine-tuning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Cytology slides are essential tools in diagnosing and staging cancer, but their analysis is time-consuming and costly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-foundation-models-fine-tuning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recursive Gaussian Process State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-gaussian-process-state-space-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning dynamical models from data is not only fundamental but also holds great promise for advancing principle discovery, time-series prediction, and controller design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recursive-gaussian-process-state-space-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOCUS: Knowledge-enhanced Adaptive Visual Compression for Few-shot Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-knowledge-enhanced-adaptive-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce the knowledge-enhanced adaptive visual compression framework, dubbed FOCUS, which uniquely combines pathology FMs with language prior knowledge to enable a focused analysis of diagnostically relevant regions by prioritizing discriminative WSI patches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focus-knowledge-enhanced-adaptive-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordinal Multiple-instance Learning for Ulcerative Colitis Severity Estimation with Selective Aggregated Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ordinal-multiple-instance-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Patient-level diagnosis of severity in ulcerative colitis (UC) is common in real clinical settings, where the most severe score in a patient is recorded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ordinal-multiple-instance-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-granularity Interest Retrieval and Refinement Network for Long-Term User Behavior Modeling in CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-interest-retrieval-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements have shown that modeling rich user behaviors can significantly improve the performance of CTR prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-granularity-interest-retrieval-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEXGen: a Generative Diffusion Model for Mesh Textures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texgen-a-generative-diffusion-model-for-mesh</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we focus on the fundamental problem of learning in the UV texture space itself.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texgen-a-generative-diffusion-model-for-mesh</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Benchmark Dataset for Collaborative SLAM in Service Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-dataset-for-collaborative-slam-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[C-SLAM, as a fundamental technique for multiple service robots, needs to handle diverse challenges such as homogeneous scenes and dynamic objects to ensure that robots operate smoothly and perform their tasks safely.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-benchmark-dataset-for-collaborative-slam-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OminiControl: Minimal and Universal Control for Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ominicontrol-minimal-and-universal-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce OminiControl, a highly versatile and parameter-efficient framework that integrates image conditions into pre-trained Diffusion Transformer (DiT) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ominicontrol-minimal-and-universal-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ScribeAgent: Towards Specialized Web Agents Using Production-Scale Workflow Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribeagent-towards-specialized-web-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Model (LLM) agents are rapidly improving to handle increasingly complex web-based tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scribeagent-towards-specialized-web-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Way: Kronecker-Factored Approximate Curvature Deep Hedging and its Benefits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-way-kronecker-factored-approximate</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper advances the computational efficiency of Deep Hedging frameworks through the novel integration of Kronecker-Factored Approximate Curvature (K-FAC) optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-way-kronecker-factored-approximate</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locating the Leading Edge of Cultural Change</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locating-the-leading-edge-of-cultural-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Measures of textual similarity and divergence are increasingly used to study cultural change.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locating-the-leading-edge-of-cultural-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learnable Activation Functions in Physics-Informed Neural Networks for Solving Partial Differential Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-activation-functions-in-physics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate the use of learnable activation functions in Physics-Informed Neural Networks (PINNs) for solving Partial Differential Equations (PDEs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learnable-activation-functions-in-physics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can GNNs Learn Link Heuristics? A Concise Review and Evaluation of Link Prediction Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gnns-learn-link-heuristics-a-concise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores the ability of Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) in learning various forms of information for link prediction, alongside a brief review of existing link prediction methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-gnns-learn-link-heuristics-a-concise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Convex Splatting: Radiance Field Rendering with 3D Smooth Convexes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-convex-splatting-radiance-field-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results highlight the potential of 3D Convex Splatting to become the new standard for high-quality scene reconstruction and novel view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-convex-splatting-radiance-field-rendering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AttriBoT: A Bag of Tricks for Efficiently Approximating Leave-One-Out Context Attribution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribot-a-bag-of-tricks-for-efficiently</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The influence of contextual input on the behavior of large language models (LLMs) has prompted the development of context attribution methods that aim to quantify each context span's effect on an LLM's generations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attribot-a-bag-of-tricks-for-efficiently</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiset Transformer: Advancing Representation Learning in Persistence Diagrams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiset-transformer-advancing-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve persistence diagram representation learning, we propose Multiset Transformer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiset-transformer-advancing-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparative Analysis of nnUNet and MedNeXt for Head and Neck Tumor Segmentation in MRI-guided Radiotherapy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-nnunet-and-mednext</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We utilized the HNTS-MRG2024 dataset, which consists of 150 MRI scans from patients diagnosed with HNC, including original and registered pre-RT and mid-RT T2-weighted images with corresponding segmentation masks for GTVp and GTVn.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comparative-analysis-of-nnunet-and-mednext</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geminio: Language-Guided Gradient Inversion Attacks in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geminio-language-guided-gradient-inversion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is achieved by leveraging a pretrained VLM to guide the optimization of a malicious global model that, when shared with and optimized by a victim, retains only gradients of samples that match the attacker-specified query.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geminio-language-guided-gradient-inversion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FairAdapter: Detecting AI-generated Images with Improved Fairness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairadapter-detecting-ai-generated-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The high-quality, realistic images generated by generative models pose significant challenges for exposing them. So far, data-driven deep neural networks have been justified as the most efficient forensics tools for the challenges.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fairadapter-detecting-ai-generated-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Human Artifacts from Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-human-artifacts-from-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address this challenge by curating Human Artifact Dataset (HAD), the first large-scale dataset specifically designed to identify and localize human artifacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-human-artifacts-from-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Robustness of Analogical Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-analogical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For each domain we test humans and GPT models on robustness to variants of the original analogy problems that test the same abstract reasoning abilities but are likely dissimilar from tasks in the pre-training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-analogical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Regression for Socio-Economic Estimation via Multi-View Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-regression-for-socio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, much of this research has primarily focused on daytime satellite imagery due to the limitation that most pre-trained models are trained on 3-band RGB images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-regression-for-socio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching MLPs to Master Heterogeneous Graph-Structured Knowledge for Efficient and Accurate Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-mlps-to-master-heterogeneous-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous Graph Neural Networks (HGNNs) have achieved promising results in various heterogeneous graph learning tasks, owing to their superiority in capturing the intricate relationships and diverse relational semantics inherent in heterogeneous graph structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-mlps-to-master-heterogeneous-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemiKong: Curating, Training, and Evaluating A Semiconductor Industry-Specific Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semikong-curating-training-and-evaluating-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated the potential to address some issues within the semiconductor industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semikong-curating-training-and-evaluating-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer Pruning with Consensus: A Triple-Win Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-pruning-with-consensus-a-triple-win</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Layer pruning offers a promising alternative to standard structured pruning, effectively reducing computational costs, latency, and memory footprint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-pruning-with-consensus-a-triple-win</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Formally Verified Neural Network for Autonomous Navigation: An Experience Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-a-formally-verified-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increased reliance of self-driving vehicles on neural networks opens up the challenge of their verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-a-formally-verified-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMGenBench: Evaluating the Limits of LMMs from the Text-to-Image Generation Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmgenbench-evaluating-the-limits-of-lmms-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we introduce MMGenBench-Test, a comprehensive benchmark developed to evaluate LMMs across 13 distinct image patterns, and MMGenBench-Domain, targeting the performance evaluation of LMMs within the generative image domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmgenbench-evaluating-the-limits-of-lmms-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification in Working Memory via Moment Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-working-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study applies moment neural networks (MNNs) to explore the neural mechanism of uncertainty quantification in working memory (WM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-working-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Cooperate with Humans using Generative Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-cooperate-with-humans-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By sampling from the latent space, we can use the generative model to produce different partners to train Cooperator agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-cooperate-with-humans-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Aspect-Based Summarization of Climate Change Reports with Small Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-aspect-based-summarization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of Natural Language Processing (NLP) for helping decision-makers with Climate Change action has recently been highlighted as a use case aligning with a broader drive towards NLP technologies for social good.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-aspect-based-summarization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataset for Evaluating Online Anomaly Detection Approaches for Discrete Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-evaluating-online-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To cater for both unsupervised and semi-supervised anomaly detection settings, as well as time series generation and forecasting, we make different versions of the dataset available, where training and test subsets are offered in contaminated and clean versions, depending on the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-evaluating-online-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stereo Anything: Unifying Stereo Matching with Large-Scale Mixed Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-anything-unifying-stereo-matching-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enrich the model's ability to generalize across different conditions, we introduce a novel synthetic dataset that complements existing data by adding variability in baselines, camera angles, and scene types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-anything-unifying-stereo-matching-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Low-Light Image Enhancement via Joint Frequency Domain Priors Guided Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-low-light-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we will propose a new zero-shot low-light enhancement method to compensate for the lack of light and structural information in the diffusion sampling process by effectively combining the wavelet and Fourier frequency domains to construct rich a priori information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-low-light-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugging Rain Man: A Novel Facial Action Units Dataset for Analyzing Atypical Facial Expressions in Children with Autism Spectrum Disorder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugging-rain-man-a-novel-facial-action-units</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Children with Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) often exhibit atypical facial expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugging-rain-man-a-novel-facial-action-units</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RV4Chatbot: Are Chatbots Allowed to Dream of Electric Sheep?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rv4chatbot-are-chatbots-allowed-to-dream-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formalise expected behaviours as interaction protocols between the user and the chatbot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rv4chatbot-are-chatbots-allowed-to-dream-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Integration of Convolution and Attention for Vision Backbone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-integration-of-convolution-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in each layer, we use two different ways to represent an image: a fine-grained regular grid and a coarse-grained set of semantic slots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-integration-of-convolution-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARLearn: Weather-Adaptive Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warlearn-weather-adaptive-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the in-variance principal used in Barlow Twins, we demonstrate the capability to port the existing models initially trained on clear weather data to effectively handle adverse weather conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warlearn-weather-adaptive-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring applications of topological data analysis in stock index movement prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-applications-of-topological-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topological Data Analysis (TDA) has recently gained significant attention in the field of financial prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-applications-of-topological-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised learning for radio-astronomy source classification: a benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-radio-astronomy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the application of SSL to radio astronomy, comparing the performance of SSL-trained models with that of traditional models pretrained on natural images, evaluating the importance of data curation for SSL, and assessing the potential benefits of self-supervision to different domain-specific radio astronomy datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-radio-astronomy</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
