<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 21:08:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing person re-identification via Uncertainty Feature Fusion Method and Auto-weighted Measure Combination</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-person-re-identification-via-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the Occluded-DukeMTMC dataset, our method increases Rank@1 by 22. 0% and mAP by 18. 4%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-person-re-identification-via-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-Aided Policy Tuning for Black-Box Robot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-aided-policy-tuning-for-black-box</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of the algorithm, a probabilistic model learns the dependence of the policy parameters and the robot learning objective not only by performing experiments on the robot, but also by leveraging data from a simulator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-aided-policy-tuning-for-black-box</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Cooperate with Humans using Generative Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-cooperate-with-humans-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By sampling from the latent space, we can use the generative model to produce different partners to train Cooperator agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-cooperate-with-humans-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GASP: Efficient Black-Box Generation of Adversarial Suffixes for Jailbreaking LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gasp-efficient-black-box-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have shown impressive proficiency across a range of natural language processing tasks yet remain vulnerable to adversarial prompts, known as jailbreak attacks, carefully designed to elicit harmful responses from LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gasp-efficient-black-box-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic brain tumor segmentation in 2D intra-operative ultrasound images using MRI tumor annotations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-brain-tumor-segmentation-in-2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This shows that MRI tumor annotations can be used as a substitute for US tumor annotations to train a deep learning model for automatic brain tumor segmentation in intra-operative ultrasound images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-brain-tumor-segmentation-in-2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised learning for radio-astronomy source classification: a benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-radio-astronomy</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the application of SSL to radio astronomy, comparing the performance of SSL-trained models with that of traditional models pretrained on natural images, evaluating the importance of data curation for SSL, and assessing the potential benefits of self-supervision to different domain-specific radio astronomy datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-for-radio-astronomy</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HARP: A Large-Scale Higher-Order Ambisonic Room Impulse Response Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harp-a-large-scale-higher-order-ambisonic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This contribution introduces a dataset of 7th-order Ambisonic Room Impulse Responses (HOA-RIRs), created using the Image Source Method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harp-a-large-scale-higher-order-ambisonic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugging Rain Man: A Novel Facial Action Units Dataset for Analyzing Atypical Facial Expressions in Children with Autism Spectrum Disorder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugging-rain-man-a-novel-facial-action-units</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Children with Autism Spectrum Disorder (ASD) often exhibit atypical facial expressions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hugging-rain-man-a-novel-facial-action-units</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Human Artifacts from Text-to-Image Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-human-artifacts-from-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we address this challenge by curating Human Artifact Dataset (HAD), the first large-scale dataset specifically designed to identify and localize human artifacts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-human-artifacts-from-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating the Robustness of Analogical Reasoning in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-analogical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For each domain we test humans and GPT models on robustness to variants of the original analogy problems that test the same abstract reasoning abilities but are likely dissimilar from tasks in the pre-training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-the-robustness-of-analogical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sli2Vol+: Segmenting 3D Medical Images Based on an Object Estimation Guided Correspondence Flow Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sli2vol-segmenting-3d-medical-images-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these challenges, in this work, we propose a new SSF, called \proposed, {for segmenting any anatomical structures in 3D medical images using only a single annotated slice per training and testing volume.}]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sli2vol-segmenting-3d-medical-images-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Aspect-Based Summarization of Climate Change Reports with Small Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-aspect-based-summarization-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The use of Natural Language Processing (NLP) for helping decision-makers with Climate Change action has recently been highlighted as a use case aligning with a broader drive towards NLP technologies for social good.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-aspect-based-summarization-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring applications of topological data analysis in stock index movement prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-applications-of-topological-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topological Data Analysis (TDA) has recently gained significant attention in the field of financial prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-applications-of-topological-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dataset for Evaluating Online Anomaly Detection Approaches for Discrete Multivariate Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-evaluating-online-anomaly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To cater for both unsupervised and semi-supervised anomaly detection settings, as well as time series generation and forecasting, we make different versions of the dataset available, where training and test subsets are offered in contaminated and clean versions, depending on the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dataset-for-evaluating-online-anomaly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching MLPs to Master Heterogeneous Graph-Structured Knowledge for Efficient and Accurate Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-mlps-to-master-heterogeneous-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Heterogeneous Graph Neural Networks (HGNNs) have achieved promising results in various heterogeneous graph learning tasks, owing to their superiority in capturing the intricate relationships and diverse relational semantics inherent in heterogeneous graph structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/teaching-mlps-to-master-heterogeneous-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentiable SVD based on Moore-Penrose Pseudoinverse for Inverse Imaging Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-svd-based-on-moore-penrose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a differentiable SVD based on the Moore-Penrose pseudoinverse to address this issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/differentiable-svd-based-on-moore-penrose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WARLearn: Weather-Adaptive Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warlearn-weather-adaptive-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging the in-variance principal used in Barlow Twins, we demonstrate the capability to port the existing models initially trained on clear weather data to effectively handle adverse weather conditions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/warlearn-weather-adaptive-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RV4Chatbot: Are Chatbots Allowed to Dream of Electric Sheep?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rv4chatbot-are-chatbots-allowed-to-dream-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We formalise expected behaviours as interaction protocols between the user and the chatbot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rv4chatbot-are-chatbots-allowed-to-dream-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NewsInterview: a Dataset and a Playground to Evaluate LLMs' Ground Gap via Informational Interviews</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newsinterview-a-dataset-and-a-playground-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive capabilities in generating coherent text but often struggle with grounding language and strategic dialogue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/newsinterview-a-dataset-and-a-playground-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REFOL: Resource-Efficient Federated Online Learning for Traffic Flow Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refol-resource-efficient-federated-online</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a novel method named Resource-Efficient Federated Online Learning (REFOL) for TFF, which guarantees prediction performance in a communication-lightweight and computation-efficient way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/refol-resource-efficient-federated-online</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Detection of Watermarks for Large Language Models Under Human Edits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-detection-of-watermarks-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We prove that the Tr-GoF test achieves optimality in robust detection of the Gumbel-max watermark in a certain asymptotic regime of substantial text modifications and vanishing watermark signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-detection-of-watermarks-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out-Of-Distribution Detection with Diversification (Provably)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out-of-distribution (OOD) detection is crucial for ensuring reliable deployment of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/out-of-distribution-detection-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Persistent Homology for Structural Characterization in Disordered Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistent-homology-for-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a unified framework based on persistent homology (PH) to characterize both local and global structures in disordered systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/persistent-homology-for-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRPruning: Efficient Large Language Model Pruning through Distributionally Robust Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drpruning-efficient-large-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we propose DRPruning, which incorporates distributionally robust optimization to restore balanced performance across domains, along with further improvements to enhance robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drpruning-efficient-large-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RestorerID: Towards Tuning-Free Face Restoration with ID Preservation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restorerid-towards-tuning-free-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[RestorerID is a diffusion model-based method that restores low-quality images with varying levels of degradation by using a single reference image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restorerid-towards-tuning-free-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-Aware Regression for Socio-Economic Estimation via Multi-View Remote Sensing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-regression-for-socio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, much of this research has primarily focused on daytime satellite imagery due to the limitation that most pre-trained models are trained on 3-band RGB images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-aware-regression-for-socio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnifiedCrawl: Aggregated Common Crawl for Affordable Adaptation of LLMs on Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifiedcrawl-aggregated-common-crawl-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) under-perform on low-resource languages due to limited training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifiedcrawl-aggregated-common-crawl-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stereo Anything: Unifying Stereo Matching with Large-Scale Mixed Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-anything-unifying-stereo-matching-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To further enrich the model's ability to generalize across different conditions, we introduce a novel synthetic dataset that complements existing data by adding variability in baselines, camera angles, and scene types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stereo-anything-unifying-stereo-matching-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Low-Light Image Enhancement via Joint Frequency Domain Priors Guided Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-low-light-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we will propose a new zero-shot low-light enhancement method to compensate for the lack of light and structural information in the diffusion sampling process by effectively combining the wavelet and Fourier frequency domains to construct rich a priori information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-low-light-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting the Integration of Convolution and Attention for Vision Backbone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-integration-of-convolution-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, in each layer, we use two different ways to represent an image: a fine-grained regular grid and a coarse-grained set of semantic slots.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-the-integration-of-convolution-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FunctionChat-Bench: Comprehensive Evaluation of Language Models' Generative Capabilities in Korean Tool-use Dialogs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functionchat-bench-comprehensive-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study investigates language models' generative capabilities in tool-use dialogs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/functionchat-bench-comprehensive-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POS-tagging to highlight the skeletal structure of sentences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pos-tagging-to-highlight-the-skeletal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents the development of a part-of-speech (POS) tagging model to extract the skeletal structure of sentences using transfer learning with the BERT architecture for token classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pos-tagging-to-highlight-the-skeletal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiscriminate Disruption of Conditional Inference on Multivariate Gaussians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indiscriminate-disruption-of-conditional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The multivariate Gaussian distribution underpins myriad operations-research, decision-analytic, and machine-learning models (e. g., Bayesian optimization, Gaussian influence diagrams, and variational autoencoders).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indiscriminate-disruption-of-conditional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIPer: Hierarchically Improving Spatial Representation of CLIP for Open-Vocabulary Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliper-hierarchically-improving-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed CLIPer includes an early-layer fusion module and a fine-grained compensation module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cliper-hierarchically-improving-spatial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating a Formally Verified Neural Network for Autonomous Navigation: An Experience Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-a-formally-verified-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increased reliance of self-driving vehicles on neural networks opens up the challenge of their verification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/creating-a-formally-verified-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MMGenBench: Evaluating the Limits of LMMs from the Text-to-Image Generation Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmgenbench-evaluating-the-limits-of-lmms-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we introduce MMGenBench-Test, a comprehensive benchmark developed to evaluate LMMs across 13 distinct image patterns, and MMGenBench-Domain, targeting the performance evaluation of LMMs within the generative image domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mmgenbench-evaluating-the-limits-of-lmms-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemiKong: Curating, Training, and Evaluating A Semiconductor Industry-Specific Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semikong-curating-training-and-evaluating-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated the potential to address some issues within the semiconductor industry.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semikong-curating-training-and-evaluating-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer Pruning with Consensus: A Triple-Win Solution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-pruning-with-consensus-a-triple-win</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Layer pruning offers a promising alternative to standard structured pruning, effectively reducing computational costs, latency, and memory footprint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-pruning-with-consensus-a-triple-win</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification in Working Memory via Moment Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-working-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study applies moment neural networks (MNNs) to explore the neural mechanism of uncertainty quantification in working memory (WM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-in-working-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regional Attention for Shadow Removal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regional-attention-for-shadow-removal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Shadow, as a natural consequence of light interacting with objects, plays a crucial role in shaping the aesthetics of an image, which however also impairs the content visibility and overall visual quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/regional-attention-for-shadow-removal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenScholar: Synthesizing Scientific Literature with Retrieval-augmented LMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openscholar-synthesizing-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific progress depends on researchers' ability to synthesize the growing body of literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openscholar-synthesizing-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dealing with Synthetic Data Contamination in Online Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-synthetic-data-contamination-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Also, we propose Entropy Selection with Real-synthetic similarity Maximization (ESRM), a method to alleviate the performance deterioration caused by synthetic images when training online CL models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dealing-with-synthetic-data-contamination-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insight-V: Exploring Long-Chain Visual Reasoning with Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insight-v-exploring-long-chain-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Insight-V, an early effort to 1) scalably produce long and robust reasoning data for complex multi-modal tasks, and 2) an effective training pipeline to enhance the reasoning capabilities of multi-modal large language models (MLLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/insight-v-exploring-long-chain-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BERT-Based Approach for Automating Course Articulation Matrix Construction with Explainable AI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bert-based-approach-for-automating-course</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work demonstrates the potential of utilizing transfer learning with BERT-based models for the automated generation of CAMs, offering high performance and interpretability in educational outcome assessment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bert-based-approach-for-automating-course</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Autoregressive Pre-training of Large Vision Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-autoregressive-pre-training-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel method for pre-training of large-scale vision encoders.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-autoregressive-pre-training-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Static Images Using Generative Models for Video Salient Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-static-images-using-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This ability allows the model to generate plausible optical flows, preserving semantic integrity while reflecting the independent motion of scene elements.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transforming-static-images-using-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuromorphic Attitude Estimation and Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromorphic-attitude-estimation-and-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the real drone the perception-to-control SNN tracks attitude commands with an average error of $3$ degrees, compared to $2. 5$ degrees for the regular flight stack.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuromorphic-attitude-estimation-and-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global and Local Attention-Based Transformer for Hyperspectral Image Change Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-attention-based-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The global attention component employs global attention on downsampled feature maps to capture low-frequency information, while the local attention component focuses on high-frequency details using non-overlapping window-based local attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-and-local-attention-based-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedRAV: Hierarchically Federated Region-Learning for Traffic Object Classification of Autonomous Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedrav-hierarchically-federated-region</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, considering the complicated traffic environments and driving scenarios, deploying federated learning for autonomous vehicles is inevitably challenged by non-independent and identically distributed (Non-IID) data of vehicles, which may lead to failed convergence and low training accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedrav-hierarchically-federated-region</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do language models perform worse for morphologically complex languages?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-do-language-models-perform-worse-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose and test three possible causes for this performance gap: morphological alignment of tokenizers, tokenization quality, and disparities in dataset sizes and measurement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-do-language-models-perform-worse-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
