<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 09:24:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Explaining Distribution Shifts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-distribution-shifts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We derive our interpretable mappings from a relaxation of the optimal transport problem, where the candidate mappings are restricted to a set of interpretable mappings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-explaining-distribution-shifts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Targeted Adversarial Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-adversarial-self-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel targeted adversarial training method for the SSL frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/targeted-adversarial-self-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Should Adversarial Perturbations be Imperceptible? Rethink the Research Paradigm in Adversarial NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-should-adversarial-perturbations-be</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We discuss the deficiencies in previous work and propose our suggestions that the research on the Security-oriented adversarial NLP (SoadNLP) should: (1) evaluate their methods on security tasks to demonstrate the real-world concerns; (2) consider real-world attackers' goals, instead of developing impractical methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-should-adversarial-perturbations-be</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSV-Cities: Toward Appropriate Supervised Visual Place Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsv-cities-toward-appropriate-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to investigate representation learning for large scale visual place recognition, which consists of determining the location depicted in a query image by referring to a database of reference images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gsv-cities-toward-appropriate-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canary in a Coalmine: Better Membership Inference with Ensembled Adversarial Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canary-in-a-coalmine-better-membership</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As industrial applications are increasingly automated by machine learning models, enforcing personal data ownership and intellectual property rights requires tracing training data back to their rightful owners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/canary-in-a-coalmine-better-membership</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayesian Emulation for Computer Models with Multiple Partial Discontinuities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-emulation-for-computer-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer models are widely used across a range of scientific disciplines to describe various complex physical systems, however to perform full uncertainty quantification we often need to employ emulators.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bayesian-emulation-for-computer-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Tracking Using Weakly Supervised Human Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-tracking-using-weakly-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-view approaches to people-tracking have the potential to better handle occlusions than single-view ones in crowded scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-tracking-using-weakly-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Sonar Image Simulation with Various Seabed Conditions for Automatic Target Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-sonar-image-simulation-with-various</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method to generate underwater object imagery that is acoustically compliant with that generated by side-scan sonar using the Unreal Engine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synthetic-sonar-image-simulation-with-various</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Discover and Detect Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-discover-and-detect-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a two-stage object detection network Region-based NCDL (RNCDL), that uses a region proposal network to localize object candidates and is trained to classify each candidate, either as one of the known classes, seen in the source dataset, or one of the extended set of novel classes, with a long-tail distribution constraint on the class assignments, reflecting the natural frequency of classes in the real world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-discover-and-detect-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Devil in Linear Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-in-linear-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we examine existing kernel-based linear transformers and identify two key issues that lead to such performance gaps: 1) unbounded gradients in the attention computation adversely impact the convergence of linear transformer models; 2) attention dilution which trivially distributes attention scores over long sequences while neglecting neighbouring structures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-devil-in-linear-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two-level Data Augmentation for Calibrated Multi-view Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-level-data-augmentation-for-calibrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data augmentation has proven its usefulness to improve model generalization and performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-level-data-augmentation-for-calibrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian-Bernoulli RBMs Without Tears</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-bernoulli-rbms-without-tears</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We revisit the challenging problem of training Gaussian-Bernoulli restricted Boltzmann machines (GRBMs), introducing two innovations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-bernoulli-rbms-without-tears</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propagating Variational Model Uncertainty for Bioacoustic Call Label Smoothing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagating-variational-model-uncertainty-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We focus on using the predictive uncertainty signal calculated by Bayesian neural networks to guide learning in the self-same task the model is being trained on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagating-variational-model-uncertainty-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Decomposition: Quantifying the Dependency and Correlation of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-decomposition-quantifying-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A goodness-of-fit metric for LMD similar to the coefficient of determination is defined and used to measure the linear dependency of a set of LMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-decomposition-quantifying-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online LiDAR-Camera Extrinsic Parameters Self-checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-lidar-camera-extrinsic-parameters-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This calibration task is multi-modal, where the rich color and texture information captured by the camera and the accurate three-dimensional spatial information from the LiDAR is incredibly significant for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-lidar-camera-extrinsic-parameters-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Detoxification with Attribute-Discriminative Latent Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-detoxification-with-attribute</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we project the latent space of an original Transformer LM to a discriminative latent space on which the texts are well-separated by their attributes, with the help of a projection block and a discriminator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-detoxification-with-attribute</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Chinese Story Generation via Awareness of Syntactic Dependencies and Semantics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-chinese-story-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In spite of the success of prior works with the application of pre-trained models, current neural models for Chinese stories still struggle to generate high-quality long text narratives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-chinese-story-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Accurate Subgraph Similarity Computation via Neural Graph Pruning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-subgraph-similarity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we convert graph pruning to a problem of node relabeling and then relax it to a differentiable problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-subgraph-similarity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIAMBRA Arena: a New Reinforcement Learning Platform for Research and Experimentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diambra-arena-a-new-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Results confirm the utility of DIAMBRA Arena as a reinforcement learning research tool, providing environments designed to study some of the most challenging topics in the field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diambra-arena-a-new-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Temporal Action Segmentation: An Analysis of Modern Technique</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-action-segmentation-an-analysis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal action segmentation from videos aims at the dense labeling of video frames with multiple action classes in minutes-long videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/temporal-action-segmentation-an-analysis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Learning for Analyzing Political Campaigns on Facebook</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-learning-for-analyzing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Social media platforms are currently the main channel for political messaging, allowing politicians to target specific demographics and adapt based on their reactions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-learning-for-analyzing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robustness of Demonstration-based Learning Under Limited Data Scenario</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-of-demonstration-based-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Demonstration-based learning has shown great potential in stimulating pretrained language models' ability under limited data scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustness-of-demonstration-based-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphCSPN: Geometry-Aware Depth Completion via Dynamic GCNs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphcspn-geometry-aware-depth-completion-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, unlike previous methods, we leverage convolution neural networks as well as graph neural networks in a complementary way for geometric representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphcspn-geometry-aware-depth-completion-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioGPT: Generative Pre-trained Transformer for Biomedical Text Generation and Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biogpt-generative-pre-trained-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained language models have attracted increasing attention in the biomedical domain, inspired by their great success in the general natural language domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biogpt-generative-pre-trained-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>p$^3$VAE: a physics-integrated generative model. Application to the semantic segmentation of optical remote sensing images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-3-vae-a-physics-integrated-generative-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our experiments on a simulated data set demonstrated the benefits of our hybrid model against conventional machine learning models in terms of extrapolation capabilities and interpretability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/p-3-vae-a-physics-integrated-generative-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spatio-channel Attention Blocks for Cross-modal Crowd Counting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-channel-attention-blocks-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Crowd counting research has made significant advancements in real-world applications, but it remains a formidable challenge in cross-modal settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spatio-channel-attention-blocks-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PoseGPT: Quantization-based 3D Human Motion Generation and Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posegpt-quantization-based-3d-human-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The discrete and compressed nature of the latent space allows the GPT-like model to focus on long-range signal, as it removes low-level redundancy in the input signal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/posegpt-quantization-based-3d-human-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Feasibility of Cross-Task Transfer with Model-Based Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-feasibility-of-cross-task-transfer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Model-Based Cross-Task Transfer (XTRA), a framework for sample-efficient online RL with scalable pretraining and finetuning of learned world models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-feasibility-of-cross-task-transfer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NGEP: A Graph-based Event Planning Framework for Story Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ngep-a-graph-based-event-planning-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To improve the performance of long text generation, recent studies have leveraged automatically planned event structures (i. e. storylines) to guide story generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ngep-a-graph-based-event-planning-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Fairness in Prediction-Based Decision Making: From Moral Assessment to Implementation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-fairness-in-prediction-based-decision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a step-by-step procedure integrating three elements: (a) a framework for the moral assessment of what fairness means in a given context, based on the recently proposed general principle of "Fair equality of chances" (FEC) (b) a mapping of the assessment's results to established statistical group fairness criteria, and (c) a method for integrating the thus-defined fairness into optimal decision making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/group-fairness-in-prediction-based-decision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TOIST: Task Oriented Instance Segmentation Transformer with Noun-Pronoun Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toist-task-oriented-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, we study the challenging problem of task oriented detection, which aims to find objects that best afford an action indicated by verbs like sit comfortably on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toist-task-oriented-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Aspect Sentiment Quad Prediction via Template-Order Data Augmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-aspect-sentiment-quad-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By fine-tuning the pre-trained language model with these template orders, our approach improves the performance of quad prediction, and outperforms state-of-the-art methods significantly in low-resource settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-aspect-sentiment-quad-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Realistic Low-resource Relation Extraction: A Benchmark with Empirical Baseline Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-realistic-low-resource-relation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents an empirical study to build relation extraction systems in low-resource settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-realistic-low-resource-relation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Graph Conversion for Robust Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quick-graph-conversion-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Implicit feedback plays a huge role in recommender systems, but its high noise characteristic seriously reduces its effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quick-graph-conversion-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When to Ask for Help: Proactive Interventions in Autonomous Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-ask-for-help-proactive-interventions</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A long-term goal of reinforcement learning is to design agents that can autonomously interact and learn in the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-to-ask-for-help-proactive-interventions</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schema-aware Reference as Prompt Improves Data-Efficient Relational Triple and Event Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-aware-reference-as-prompt-improves</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel approach of schema-aware Reference As Prompt (RAP), which dynamically leverage schema and knowledge inherited from global (few-shot) training data for each sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schema-aware-reference-as-prompt-improves</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Graph Masking Pre-training for Graph-to-Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-graph-masking-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale pre-trained language models (PLMs) have advanced Graph-to-Text (G2T) generation by processing the linearised version of a graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-graph-masking-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Stability of Fine-Tuning Pretrained Language Models via Component-Wise Gradient Norm Clipping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-stability-of-fine-tuning-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its superior performance, such fine-tuning can be unstable, resulting in significant variance in performance and potential risks for practical applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-stability-of-fine-tuning-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning from the Dictionary: Heterogeneous Knowledge Guided Fine-tuning for Chinese Spell Checking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-the-dictionary-heterogeneous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Chinese Spell Checking (CSC) aims to detect and correct Chinese spelling errors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-from-the-dictionary-heterogeneous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Provably Convergent Plug &amp; Play Linearized ADMM, applied to Deblurring Spatially Varying Kernels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-convergent-plug-play-linearized-admm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Plug & Play methods combine proximal algorithms with denoiser priors to solve inverse problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/provably-convergent-plug-play-linearized-admm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forging Multiple Training Objectives for Pre-trained Language Models via Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forging-multiple-training-objectives-for-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multiple pre-training objectives fill the vacancy of the understanding capability of single-objective language modeling, which serves the ultimate purpose of pre-trained language models (PrLMs), generalizing well on a mass of scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forging-multiple-training-objectives-for-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Few-shot Transferable Robust Representation Learning via Bilevel Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-transferable-robust-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, learning transferable robust representations for unseen domains is a difficult problem even with a large amount of data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/few-shot-transferable-robust-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Type-supervised sequence labeling based on the heterogeneous star graph for named entity recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/type-supervised-sequence-labeling-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named entity recognition is a fundamental task in natural language processing, identifying the span and category of entities in unstructured texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/type-supervised-sequence-labeling-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Entity Detection with Proposer and Regressor</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-entity-detection-with-proposer-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Named entity recognition is a traditional task in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-entity-detection-with-proposer-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linguistic Rules-Based Corpus Generation for Native Chinese Grammatical Error Correction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-rules-based-corpus-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments and detailed analyses not only demonstrate that the training data constructed by our method effectively improves the performance of CGEC models, but also reflect that our benchmark is an excellent resource for further development of the CGEC field.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/linguistic-rules-based-corpus-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniNL: Aligning Representation Learning with Scoring Function for OOD Detection via Unified Neighborhood Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uninl-aligning-representation-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design a K-nearest neighbor contrastive learning (KNCL) objective for representation learning and introduce a KNN-based scoring function for OOD detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uninl-aligning-representation-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Procedural Fairness: Uncovering Biases in How a Toxic Language Classifier Uses Sentiment Information</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-procedural-fairness-uncovering-biases</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a multi-class toxic language classifier, we leverage a concept-based explanation framework to calculate the sensitivity of the model to the concept of sentiment, which has been used before as a salient feature for toxic language detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-procedural-fairness-uncovering-biases</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-to-speech translation for a real-world unwritten language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-to-speech-translation-for-a-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use English-Taiwanese Hokkien as a case study, and present an end-to-end solution from training data collection, modeling choices to benchmark dataset release.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-to-speech-translation-for-a-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised Heterogeneous Graph Pre-training Based on Structural Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-heterogeneous-graph-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The two modules can effectively utilize and enhance each other, promoting the model to learn discriminative embeddings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-heterogeneous-graph-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consistent Multiclass Algorithms for Complex Metrics and Constraints</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-multiclass-algorithms-for-complex</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present consistent algorithms for multiclass learning with complex performance metrics and constraints, where the objective and constraints are defined by arbitrary functions of the confusion matrix.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/consistent-multiclass-algorithms-for-complex</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
