<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2022 09:21:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GLSO: Grammar-guided Latent Space Optimization for Sample-efficient Robot Design Automation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glso-grammar-guided-latent-space-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Grammar-guided Latent Space Optimization (GLSO), a framework that transforms design automation into a low-dimensional continuous optimization problem by training a graph variational autoencoder (VAE) to learn a mapping between the graph-structured design space and a continuous latent space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glso-grammar-guided-latent-space-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Hashing with Semantic Concept Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hashing-with-semantic-concept</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, to improve the unsupervised image retrieval performance, plenty of unsupervised hashing methods have been proposed by designing a semantic similarity matrix, which is based on the similarities between image features extracted by a pre-trained CNN model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hashing-with-semantic-concept</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensor-Based Multi-Modality Feature Selection and Regression for Alzheimer's Disease Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-multi-modality-feature-selection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The assessment of Alzheimer's Disease (AD) and Mild Cognitive Impairment (MCI) associated with brain changes remains a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tensor-based-multi-modality-feature-selection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I-SPLIT: Deep Network Interpretability for Split Computing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-split-deep-network-interpretability-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A neuron is important if its gradient with respect to the correct class decision is high.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/i-split-deep-network-interpretability-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Neural Model for Regular Grammar Induction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-model-for-regular-grammar-induction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Grammatical inference is a classical problem in computational learning theory and a topic of wider influence in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-neural-model-for-regular-grammar-induction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly Supervised Two-Stage Training Scheme for Deep Video Fight Detection Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-two-stage-training-scheme</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a simple but effective method that solves the task from a new perspective: we design the fight detection model as a composition of an action-aware feature extractor and an anomaly score generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-two-stage-training-scheme</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking Performance Gains in Image Dehazing Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-performance-gains-in-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image dehazing is an active topic in low-level vision, and many image dehazing networks have been proposed with the rapid development of deep learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-performance-gains-in-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Efficient Reinforcement Learning for Full-length Game of StarCraft II</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate a set of RL techniques for the full-length game of StarCraft II.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-efficient-reinforcement-learning-for-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion Guided Deep Dynamic 3D Garments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-guided-deep-dynamic-3d-garments</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Technically, we model garment dynamics, driven using the input character motion, by predicting per-frame local displacements in a canonical state of the garment that is enriched with frame-dependent skinning weights to bring the garment to the global space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/motion-guided-deep-dynamic-3d-garments</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantile-constrained Wasserstein projections for robust interpretability of numerical and machine learning models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-constrained-wasserstein-projections</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Numerical experiments on real case studies, from the UQ and ML fields, highlight the computational feasibility of such studies and provide local and global insights on the robustness of black-box models to input perturbations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-constrained-wasserstein-projections</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Frame Rate Agnostic Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-frame-rate-agnostic-multi-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a Frame Rate Agnostic MOT framework with Periodic training Scheme (FAPS) to tackle the FraMOT problem for the first time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-frame-rate-agnostic-multi-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ET5: A Novel End-to-end Framework for Conversational Machine Reading Comprehension</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/et5-a-novel-end-to-end-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational machine reading comprehension (CMRC) aims to assist computers to understand an natural language text and thereafter engage in a multi-turn conversation to answer questions related to the text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/et5-a-novel-end-to-end-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Lake: a Lakehouse for Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-lake-a-lakehouse-for-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional data lakes provide critical data infrastructure for analytical workloads by enabling time travel, running SQL queries, ingesting data with ACID transactions, and visualizing petabyte-scale datasets on cloud storage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-lake-a-lakehouse-for-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Aware Hand Mesh Estimation and Personalization from RGB Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-aware-hand-mesh-estimation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an identity-aware hand mesh estimation model, which can incorporate the identity information represented by the intrinsic shape parameters of the subject.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identity-aware-hand-mesh-estimation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poisson Flow Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisson-flow-generative-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We interpret the data points as electrical charges on the $z=0$ hyperplane in a space augmented with an additional dimension $z$, generating a high-dimensional electric field (the gradient of the solution to Poisson equation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/poisson-flow-generative-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DIG: Draping Implicit Garment over the Human Body</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dig-draping-implicit-garment-over-the-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing data-driven methods for draping garments over posed human bodies, despite being effective, cannot handle garments of arbitrary topology and are typically not end-to-end differentiable.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dig-draping-implicit-garment-over-the-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look at Learned Optimization: Stability, Robustness, and Inductive Biases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-learned-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We apply the resulting learned optimizer to a variety of neural network training tasks, where it outperforms the current state of the art learned optimizer -- at matched optimizer computational overhead -- with regard to optimization performance and meta-training speed, and is capable of generalization to tasks far different from those it was meta-trained on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-at-learned-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simulation-based inference of Bayesian hierarchical models while checking for model misspecification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-inference-of-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents recent methodological advances to perform simulation-based inference (SBI) of a general class of Bayesian hierarchical models (BHMs), while checking for model misspecification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simulation-based-inference-of-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Bibliographic View on Constrained Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bibliographic-view-on-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A keyword search on constrained clustering on Web-of-Science returned just under 3, 000 documents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-bibliographic-view-on-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Challenges in Visual Anomaly Detection for Mobile Robots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-visual-anomaly-detection-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the task of detecting anomalies for autonomous mobile robots based on vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/challenges-in-visual-anomaly-detection-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EventNet: Detecting Events in EEG</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventnet-detecting-events-in-eeg</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an end-to-end event detection approach (EventNet), based on deep learning, that directly works with events as learning targets, stepping away from ad-hoc postprocessing schemes to turn model outputs into events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eventnet-detecting-events-in-eeg</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NamedMask: Distilling Segmenters from Complementary Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/namedmask-distilling-segmenters-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, termed NamedMask, begins by using CLIP to construct category-specific archives of images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/namedmask-distilling-segmenters-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MonoByte: A Pool of Monolingual Byte-level Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monobyte-a-pool-of-monolingual-byte-level</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The zero-shot cross-lingual ability of models pretrained on multilingual and even monolingual corpora has spurred many hypotheses to explain this intriguing empirical result.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monobyte-a-pool-of-monolingual-byte-level</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equivariant Transduction through Invariant Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-transduction-through-invariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to generalize compositionally is key to understanding the potentially infinite number of sentences that can be constructed in a human language from only a finite number of words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/equivariant-transduction-through-invariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proximal Point Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-point-imitation-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thanks to PPM, we avoid nested policy evaluation and cost updates for online IL appearing in the prior literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proximal-point-imitation-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCALES: From Fairness Principles to Constrained Decision-Making</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scales-from-fairness-principles-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes SCALES, a general framework that translates well-established fairness principles into a common representation based on the Constraint Markov Decision Process (CMDP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scales-from-fairness-principles-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantically Consistent Data Augmentation for Neural Machine Translation via Conditional Masked Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-consistent-data-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, to enhance diversity, we incorporate the idea of soft word substitution for data augmentation which replaces a word with a probabilistic distribution over the vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantically-consistent-data-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Differential Privacy, There is Truth: On Vote Leakage in Ensemble Private Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-differential-privacy-there-is-truth-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When learning from sensitive data, care must be taken to ensure that training algorithms address privacy concerns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-differential-privacy-there-is-truth-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Good Is Neural Combinatorial Optimization?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-is-neural-combinatorial-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional solvers for tackling combinatorial optimization (CO) problems are usually designed by human experts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-good-is-neural-combinatorial-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recurrence-free Survival Prediction under the Guidance of Automatic Gross Tumor Volume Segmentation for Head and Neck Cancers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrence-free-survival-prediction-under-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For Head and Neck Cancers (HNC) patient management, automatic gross tumor volume (GTV) segmentation and accurate pre-treatment cancer recurrence prediction are of great importance to assist physicians in designing personalized management plans, which have the potential to improve the treatment outcome and quality of life for HNC patients.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrence-free-survival-prediction-under-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Investigation of the Bias-Variance Tradeoff in Meta-Gradients</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-the-bias-variance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Meta-gradients provide a general approach for optimizing the meta-parameters of reinforcement learning (RL) algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-investigation-of-the-bias-variance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLGWSC-1: The first Machine Learning Gravitational-Wave Search Mock Data Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlgwsc-1-the-first-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The final of the 4 provided datasets contained real noise from the O3a observing run and signals up to a duration of 20 seconds with the inclusion of precession effects and higher order modes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlgwsc-1-the-first-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Few-Shot Learning Without Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-few-shot-learning-without-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This simple framework requires no prompts or verbalizers, and achieves high accuracy with orders of magnitude less parameters than existing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-few-shot-learning-without-prompts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptation of domain-specific transformer models with text oversampling for sentiment analysis of social media posts on Covid-19 vaccines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-domain-specific-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Covid-19 has spread across the world and several vaccines have been developed to counter its surge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptation-of-domain-specific-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting pairwise preferences between TTS audio stimuli using parallel ratings data and anti-symmetric twin neural networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-pairwise-preferences-between-tts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While previous work has focused on predicting listeners' ratings (mean opinion scores) of individual stimuli, we focus on the simpler task of predicting subjective preference given two speech stimuli for the same text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-pairwise-preferences-between-tts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAMRI Loss: Improving Recall of a Specific Class without Sacrificing Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camri-loss-improving-recall-of-a-specific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a loss function that can improve the separation of the important class by setting the margin only for the important class, called Class-sensitive Additive Angular Margin Loss (CAMRI Loss).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/camri-loss-improving-recall-of-a-specific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated head and neck tumor segmentation from 3D PET/CT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-head-and-neck-tumor-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Head and neck tumor segmentation challenge (HECKTOR) 2022 offers a platform for researchers to compare their solutions to segmentation of tumors and lymph nodes from 3D CT and PET images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automated-head-and-neck-tumor-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homophone Reveals the Truth: A Reality Check for Speech2Vec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homophone-reveals-the-truth-a-reality-check</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There is no indication that these embeddings are generated by the Speech2Vec model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/homophone-reveals-the-truth-a-reality-check</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Response Recovery Using Ambient Synchrophasor Data: A Synthetic Texas Interconnection Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-response-recovery-using-ambient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Wide-area dynamic studies are of paramount importance to ensure the stability and reliability of power grids.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynamic-response-recovery-using-ambient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Information Minimization Based Contrastive Learning Model for Unsupervised Sentence Embeddings Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-information-minimization-based-contrastive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this problem, we present an information minimization based contrastive learning (InforMin-CL) model to retain the useful information and discard the redundant information by maximizing the mutual information and minimizing the information entropy between positive instances meanwhile for unsupervised sentence representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-information-minimization-based-contrastive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DLUNet: Semi-supervised Learning based Dual-Light UNet for Multi-organ Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlunet-semi-supervised-learning-based-dual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the training phase, it consists of two light UNets, which make full use of label and unlabeled data simultaneously by using consistent-based learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dlunet-semi-supervised-learning-based-dual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing and Experimenting with Diffusion Models for Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementing-and-experimenting-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this thesis, we aim to contribute by firstly reviewing the different approaches and techniques used by these models, and then by proposing our own implementation of a text-to-image model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementing-and-experimenting-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capsule Network based Contrastive Learning of Unsupervised Visual Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capsule-network-based-contrastive-learning-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Capsule Networks have shown tremendous advancement in the past decade, outperforming the traditional CNNs in various task due to it's equivariant properties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/capsule-network-based-contrastive-learning-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMGAN: Conformer-Based Metric-GAN for Monaural Speech Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmgan-conformer-based-metric-gan-for-monaural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Convolution-augmented transformers (Conformers) are recently proposed in various speech-domain applications, such as automatic speech recognition (ASR) and speech separation, as they can capture both local and global dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmgan-conformer-based-metric-gan-for-monaural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Concept Activation Regions: A Generalized Framework For Concept-Based Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-activation-regions-a-generalized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further demonstrate empirically that CARs offer (1) more accurate descriptions of how concepts are scattered in the DNN's latent space; (2) global explanations that are closer to human concept annotations and (3) concept-based feature importance that meaningfully relate concepts with each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/concept-activation-regions-a-generalized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layer Freezing &amp; Data Sieving: Missing Pieces of a Generic Framework for Sparse Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-freezing-data-sieving-missing-pieces-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we analyze the feasibility and potentiality of using the layer freezing technique in sparse training and find it has the potential to save considerable training costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/layer-freezing-data-sieving-missing-pieces-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AcroFOD: An Adaptive Method for Cross-domain Few-shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acrofod-an-adaptive-method-for-cross-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under the domain shift, cross-domain few-shot object detection aims to adapt object detectors in the target domain with a few annotated target data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acrofod-an-adaptive-method-for-cross-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VToonify: Controllable High-Resolution Portrait Video Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although a series of successful portrait image toonification models built upon the powerful StyleGAN have been proposed, these image-oriented methods have obvious limitations when applied to videos, such as the fixed frame size, the requirement of face alignment, missing non-facial details and temporal inconsistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropic Descent Archetypal Analysis for Blind Hyperspectral Unmixing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-descent-archetypal-analysis-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce a new algorithm based on archetypal analysis for blind hyperspectral unmixing, assuming linear mixing of endmembers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/entropic-descent-archetypal-analysis-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGTR: End-to-End Mutual Gaze Detection with Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtr-end-to-end-mutual-gaze-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[People's looking at each other or mutual gaze is ubiquitous in our daily interactions, and detecting mutual gaze is of great significance for understanding human social scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mgtr-end-to-end-mutual-gaze-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
