<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 09:16:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>CENSOR: Defense Against Gradient Inversion via Orthogonal Subspace Bayesian Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-defense-against-gradient-inversion-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing gradient inversion attacks can exploit this vulnerability to recover private training instances from a client's gradient vectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censor-defense-against-gradient-inversion-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Quantum Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quantum-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benchmarking and establishing proper statistical validation metrics for reinforcement learning (RL) remain ongoing challenges, where no consensus has been established yet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-quantum-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upside Down Reinforcement Learning with Policy Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upside-down-reinforcement-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method, dubbed Upside Down Reinforcement Learning with Policy Generators (UDRLPG), streamlines comparable techniques by removing the need for an evaluator or critic to update the weights of the generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/upside-down-reinforcement-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mixture-of-Mamba: Enhancing Multi-Modal State-Space Models with Modality-Aware Sparsity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-mamba-enhancing-multi-modal-state</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the Chameleon setting, Mixture-of-Mamba reaches similar image loss with just 42. 50% of the FLOPs at the 1. 4B scale, and similar text loss with just 65. 40% of the FLOPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mixture-of-mamba-enhancing-multi-modal-state</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UDBE: Unsupervised Diffusion-based Brightness Enhancement in Underwater Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udbe-unsupervised-diffusion-based-brightness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A major challenge in this domain is the depth at which images are captured, with increasing depth resulting in a darker environment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/udbe-unsupervised-diffusion-based-brightness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Formal Verification of Markov Processes with Learned Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-verification-of-markov-processes-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the problem of formally verifying properties of Markov processes where the parameters are the output of machine learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/formal-verification-of-markov-processes-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-View Attention Syntactic Enhanced Graph Convolutional Network for Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-attention-syntactic-enhanced-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis (ABSA) is the task aimed at predicting the sentiment polarity of aspect words within sentences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-attention-syntactic-enhanced-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Diverse Perspectives: A Multi-Agent Framework for Enhanced Error Detection in Knowledge Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diverse-perspectives-a-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For specific industrial scenarios, our framework can facilitate the training of specialized agents using domain-specific knowledge graphs for error detection, which highlights the potential industrial application value of our framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-diverse-perspectives-a-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficiency Bottlenecks of Convolutional Kolmogorov-Arnold Networks: A Comprehensive Scrutiny with ImageNet, AlexNet, LeNet and Tabular Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-bottlenecks-of-convolutional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Algorithmic level developments like Convolutional Neural Networks, transformers, attention mechanism, Retrieval Augmented Generation and so on have changed Artificial Intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficiency-bottlenecks-of-convolutional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-powered Multi-agent Framework for Goal-oriented Learning in Intelligent Tutoring System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-powered-multi-agent-framework-for-goal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After identifying the skill gap, it schedules an efficient learning path using an evolving optimization approach, driven by a comprehensive and dynamic profile of learners' multifaceted status.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-powered-multi-agent-framework-for-goal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPECIAL: Zero-shot Hyperspectral Image Classification With CLIP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/special-zero-shot-hyperspectral-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although deep learning-based HSI classification methods have achieved significant advancements, existing methods still rely on manually labeled data for training, which is both time-consuming and labor-intensive. To address this limitation, we introduce a novel zero-shot hyperspectral image classification framework based on CLIP (SPECIAL), aiming to eliminate the need for manual annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/special-zero-shot-hyperspectral-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCTG Bench: LLM Controlled Text Generation Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lctg-bench-llm-controlled-text-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LCTG Bench provides a unified framework for assessing control performance, enabling users to select the most suitable model for their use cases based on controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lctg-bench-llm-controlled-text-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-view Structural Convolution Network for Domain-Invariant Point Cloud Recognition of Autonomous Vehicles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-structural-convolution-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present the Multi-View Structural Convolution Network (MSCN) designed for domain-invariant point cloud recognition.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-view-structural-convolution-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Attention-Sharing Information Distillation Transformer for Lightweight Single Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-sharing-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this challenge, we propose the Attention-Sharing Information Distillation (ASID) network, a lightweight SR network that integrates attention-sharing and an information distillation structure specifically designed for Transformer-based SR methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-attention-sharing-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWIFT: Mapping Sub-series with Wavelet Decomposition Improves Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-mapping-sub-series-with-wavelet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose $\textit{SWIFT}$, a lightweight model that is not only powerful, but also efficient in deployment and inference for Long-term Time Series Forecasting (LTSF).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/swift-mapping-sub-series-with-wavelet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-Retinal V2: Transfer an Elite Knowledge Spark into Fundus Vision-Language Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-v2-transfer-an-elite-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Vision-language pretraining (VLP) has been investigated to generalize across diverse downstream tasks for fundus image analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-retinal-v2-transfer-an-elite-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Tropical Cyclone Forecasting With Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tropical-cyclone-forecasting-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tropical cyclone (TC) forecasting is crucial for disaster preparedness and mitigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-tropical-cyclone-forecasting-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing Out-of-Label Hazard Detection in Dashcam Videos: Insights from the COOOL Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-out-of-label-hazard-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach for hazard analysis in dashcam footage, addressing the detection of driver reactions to hazards, the identification of hazardous objects, and the generation of descriptive captions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/addressing-out-of-label-hazard-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LUCY: Linguistic Understanding and Control Yielding Early Stage of Her</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucy-linguistic-understanding-and-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The film Her features Samantha, a sophisticated AI audio agent who is capable of understanding both linguistic and paralinguistic information in human speech and delivering real-time responses that are natural, informative and sensitive to emotional subtleties.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lucy-linguistic-understanding-and-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parametric Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce Parametric retrieval-augmented generation (Parametric RAG), a new RAG paradigm that integrates external knowledge directly into the parameters of feed-forward networks (FFN) of an LLM through document parameterization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parametric-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD-Lamba: Boosting Remote Sensing Change Detection via a Cross-Temporal Locally Adaptive State Space Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-lamba-boosting-remote-sensing-change</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing remote sensing change detection (RSCD) approaches based on Mamba frequently struggle to effectively perceive the inherent locality of change regions as they direct flatten and scan RS images (i. e., the features of the same region of changes are not distributed continuously within the sequence but are mixed with features from other regions throughout the sequence).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cd-lamba-boosting-remote-sensing-change</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GaussianToken: An Effective Image Tokenizer with 2D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussiantoken-an-effective-image-tokenizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose GaussianToken: An Effective Image Tokenizer with 2D Gaussian Splatting as a solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussiantoken-an-effective-image-tokenizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNIDOOR: A Universal Framework for Action-Level Backdoor Attacks in Deep Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidoor-a-universal-framework-for-action</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning (DRL) is widely applied to safety-critical decision-making scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unidoor-a-universal-framework-for-action</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Information Consistent Pruning: How to Efficiently Search for Sparse Networks?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-consistent-pruning-how-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Iterative magnitude pruning methods (IMPs), proven to be successful in reducing the number of insignificant nodes in over-parameterized deep neural networks (DNNs), have been getting an enormous amount of attention with the rapid deployment of DNNs into cutting-edge technologies with computation and memory constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/information-consistent-pruning-how-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guaranteed Multidimensional Time Series Prediction via Deterministic Tensor Completion Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guaranteed-multidimensional-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we develop a deterministic tensor completion theory and introduce the Temporal Convolutional Tensor Nuclear Norm (TCTNN) model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guaranteed-multidimensional-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Survey on Self-Interpretable Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-self-interpretable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural networks have achieved remarkable success across various fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-comprehensive-survey-on-self-interpretable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ARWKV: Pretrain is not what we need, an RNN-Attention-Based Language Model Born from Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arwkv-pretrain-is-not-what-we-need-an-rnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As is known, hybrid quadratic and subquadratic attention models in multi-head architectures have surpassed both Transformer and Linear RNN models , with these works primarily focusing on reducing KV complexity and improving efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arwkv-pretrain-is-not-what-we-need-an-rnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Approximate Message Passing for Bayesian Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-message-passing-for-bayesian</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, our framework is the first MP method that handles convolutional neural networks and avoids double-counting training data, a limitation of previous MP methods that causes overconfidence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/approximate-message-passing-for-bayesian</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iFormer: Integrating ConvNet and Transformer for Mobile Application</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iformer-integrating-convnet-and-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, iFormer achieves an impressive Top-1 accuracy of 80. 4\% on ImageNet-1k with a latency of only 1. 10 ms on an iPhone 13, surpassing the recently proposed MobileNetV4 under similar latency constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iformer-integrating-convnet-and-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Radiologist-in-the-Loop Self-Training for Generalizable CT Metal Artifact Reduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiologist-in-the-loop-self-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these limitations, we propose a novel Radiologist-In-the-loop SElf-training framework for MAR, termed RISE-MAR, which can integrate radiologists' feedback into the semi-supervised learning process, progressively improving the quality and quantity of pseudo ground-truths for enhanced generalization on real clinical CT images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/radiologist-in-the-loop-self-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BoKDiff: Best-of-K Diffusion Alignment for Target-Specific 3D Molecule Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bokdiff-best-of-k-diffusion-alignment-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address alignment challenges, we introduce a method that relocates the center of mass of generated ligands to their docking poses, enabling accurate sub-component extraction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bokdiff-best-of-k-diffusion-alignment-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MimicGait: A Model Agnostic approach for Occluded Gait Recognition using Correlational Knowledge Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimicgait-a-model-agnostic-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Gait recognition is an important biometric technique over large distances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mimicgait-a-model-agnostic-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking External Slow-Thinking: From Snowball Errors to Probability of Correct Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-external-slow-thinking-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Test-time scaling, which is also often referred to as \textit{slow-thinking}, has been demonstrated to enhance multi-step reasoning in large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-external-slow-thinking-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCP-116K: A High-Quality Problem-Solution Dataset and a Generalized Pipeline for Automated Extraction in the Higher Education Science Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scp-116k-a-high-quality-problem-solution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent breakthroughs in large language models (LLMs) exemplified by the impressive mathematical and scientific reasoning capabilities of the o1 model have spotlighted the critical importance of high-quality training data in advancing LLM performance across STEM disciplines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scp-116k-a-high-quality-problem-solution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overview of the Amphion Toolkit (v0.2)</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-the-amphion-toolkit-v0-2</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Amphion is an open-source toolkit for Audio, Music, and Speech Generation, designed to lower the entry barrier for junior researchers and engineers in these fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/overview-of-the-amphion-toolkit-v0-2</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Generation Without Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-generation-without-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It retains the same maximum likelihood objective as CFG and differs mainly in the parameterization of conditional models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-generation-without-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaOcc: Surround-View 4D Radar and Camera Fusion Framework for 3D Occupancy Prediction with Dual Training Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaocc-surround-view-4d-radar-and-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Temporal alignment and fusion module is employed to further aggregate historical feature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metaocc-surround-view-4d-radar-and-camera</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Modal Transfer from Memes to Videos: Addressing Data Scarcity in Hateful Video Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-transfer-from-memes-to-videos</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Detecting hate speech in online content is essential to ensuring safer digital spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-transfer-from-memes-to-videos</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TdAttenMix: Top-Down Attention Guided Mixup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdattenmix-top-down-attention-guided-mixup</link>
      <description><![CDATA[CutMix is a data augmentation strategy that cuts and pastes image patches to mixup training data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tdattenmix-top-down-attention-guided-mixup</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Image Restoration Pre-training via Degradation Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-image-restoration-pre-training-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Subsequently, a lightweight decoder, such as ResNet18, is leveraged to classify the degradation type of the input image solely based on the features extracted in the first stage, without utilizing the input image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-image-restoration-pre-training-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyLLaVA-Video: A Simple Framework of Small-scale Large Multimodal Models for Video Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllava-video-a-simple-framework-of-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the TinyLLaVA-Video, a video understanding model with parameters not exceeding 4B that processes video sequences in a simple manner, without the need for complex architectures, supporting both fps sampling and uniform frame sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllava-video-a-simple-framework-of-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SedarEval: Automated Evaluation using Self-Adaptive Rubrics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sedareval-automated-evaluation-using-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the same training data, our evaluator LM achieves a higher concordance rate with human grading results than other paradigms, including GPT-4, highlighting the superiority and efficiency of our approach.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sedareval-automated-evaluation-using-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kernel-Based Anomaly Detection Using Generalized Hyperbolic Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-based-anomaly-detection-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel approach to anomaly detection by integrating Generalized Hyperbolic (GH) processes into kernel-based methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kernel-based-anomaly-detection-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoPure: Diffusion-based Adversarial Purification for Video Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopure-diffusion-based-adversarial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given an adversarial example, we first employ temporal DDIM inversion to transform the input distribution into a temporally consistent and trajectory-defined distribution, covering adversarial noise while preserving more video structure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopure-diffusion-based-adversarial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDEval: Evaluating and Enhancing Markdown Awareness in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdeval-evaluating-and-enhancing-markdown</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are expected to offer structured Markdown responses for the sake of readability in web chatbots (e. g., ChatGPT).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mdeval-evaluating-and-enhancing-markdown</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpikSSD: Better Extraction and Fusion for Object Detection with Spiking Neuron Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikssd-better-extraction-and-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, efficiently conducting feature extraction and fusion under the spiking characteristics of SNNs for object detection remains a pressing challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spikssd-better-extraction-and-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Galaxy Images Across Ultraviolet, Visible and Infrared Bands Using Generative Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-galaxy-images-across-ultraviolet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that generative deep learning can translate galaxy observations across ultraviolet, visible, and infrared photometric bands.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-galaxy-images-across-ultraviolet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFT-RAG: An Entity Tree Based Retrieval Augmented Generation Algorithm With Cuckoo Filter</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cft-rag-an-entity-tree-based-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although retrieval-augmented generation(RAG) significantly improves generation quality by retrieving external knowledge bases and integrating generated content, it faces computational efficiency bottlenecks, particularly in knowledge retrieval tasks involving hierarchical structures for Tree-RAG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cft-rag-an-entity-tree-based-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Killing it with Zero-Shot: Adversarially Robust Novelty Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/killing-it-with-zero-shot-adversarially</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating robust pretrained features into the k-NN algorithm, we establish a new standard for performance and robustness in the field of robust ND.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/killing-it-with-zero-shot-adversarially</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Retrieval-Augmented Generation through Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-retrieval-augmented-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we present MMOA-RAG, a Multi-Module joint Optimization Algorithm for RAG, which employs multi-agent reinforcement learning to harmonize all agents' goals towards a unified reward, such as the F1 score of the final answer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-retrieval-augmented-generation</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
