<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:14:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Text-to-Image Diffusion Models for Visual Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-text-to-image-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose VPD (Visual Perception with a pre-trained Diffusion model), a new framework that exploits the semantic information of a pre-trained text-to-image diffusion model in visual perception tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-text-to-image-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting Adversarial Training for ImageNet: Architectures, Training and Generalization across Threat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-for-imagenet</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While adversarial training has been extensively studied for ResNet architectures and low resolution datasets like CIFAR, much less is known for ImageNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-adversarial-training-for-imagenet</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking White Blood Cell Classification Under Domain Shift</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-white-blood-cell-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recognizing the types of white blood cells (WBCs) in microscopic images of human blood smears is a fundamental task in the fields of pathology and hematology.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-white-blood-cell-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prompt, Generate, then Cache: Cascade of Foundation Models makes Strong Few-shot Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-generate-then-cache-cascade-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our CaFo incorporates CLIP's language-contrastive knowledge, DINO's vision-contrastive knowledge, DALL-E's vision-generative knowledge, and GPT-3's language-generative knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prompt-generate-then-cache-cascade-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NovPhy: A Testbed for Physical Reasoning in Open-world Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novphy-a-testbed-for-physical-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[But is it enough to only have physical reasoning capabilities to operate in a real physical environment?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novphy-a-testbed-for-physical-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing Text-to-Image Diffusion Models for Visual Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-text-to-image-diffusion-models-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose VPD (Visual Perception with a pre-trained Diffusion model), a new framework that exploits the semantic information of a pre-trained text-to-image diffusion model in visual perception tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unleashing-text-to-image-diffusion-models-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When does Privileged Information Explain Away Label Noise?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-does-privileged-information-explain-away</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Leveraging privileged information (PI), or features available during training but not at test time, has recently been shown to be an effective method for addressing label noise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/when-does-privileged-information-explain-away</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Multi-Object Tracking Based on Uncertainty-Guided Data Association</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-multi-object-tracking-based-on-uncertainty</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the existing literature, most 3D multi-object tracking algorithms based on the tracking-by-detection framework employed deterministic tracks and detections for similarity calculation in the data association stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-multi-object-tracking-based-on-uncertainty</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSH-Det3D: Improving 3D Object Detection with BEV Shape Heatmap</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsh-det3d-improving-3d-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we design the Pillar-based Shape Completion (PSC) module to predict the probability of occupancy whether a pillar contains object shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bsh-det3d-improving-3d-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Permutation-Invariant Embeddings for Description Logic Concepts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-permutation-invariant-embeddings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We reformulate the learning problem as a multi-label classification problem and propose a neural embedding model (NERO) that learns permutation-invariant embeddings for sets of examples tailored towards predicting $F_1$ scores of pre-selected description logic concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-permutation-invariant-embeddings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Common Rationale to Improve Self-Supervised Representation for Fine-Grained Visual Recognition Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-common-rationale-to-improve-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we fit the GradCAM with a branch with limited fitting capacity, which allows the branch to capture the common rationales and discard the less common discriminative patterns.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-common-rationale-to-improve-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CONTAIN: A Community-based Algorithm for Network Immunization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contain-a-community-based-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Within the network analysis field, network immunization refers to the task of protecting a network from some arbitrary diffusion that tries to infect it.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contain-a-community-based-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T360RRD: A dataset for 360 degree rotated rectangular box table detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t360rrd-a-dataset-for-360-degree-rotated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the problem of scarcity and high annotation costs of rotated image table detection datasets, this chapter proposes a method for building a rotated image table detection dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t360rrd-a-dataset-for-360-degree-rotated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRUSformer: Improving Prostate Cancer Detection from Micro-Ultrasound Using Attention and Self-Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trusformer-improving-prostate-cancer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We analyze this method using a dataset of micro-ultrasound acquired from 578 patients who underwent prostate biopsy, and compare our model to baseline models and other large-scale studies in the literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trusformer-improving-prostate-cancer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Energy Conserving Dynamics Efficiently with Hamiltonian Gaussian Processes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-conserving-dynamics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hamiltonian mechanics is one of the cornerstones of natural sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-energy-conserving-dynamics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the LiDAR Sim-to-Real Domain Shift: A Detailed Investigation Using Object Detectors and Analyzing Point Clouds at Target-Level</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-lidar-sim-to-real-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additional experiments reveal that this domain shift can be lowered by introducing a simple noise model in simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-lidar-sim-to-real-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discovery and Recognition of Formula Concepts using Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovery-and-recognition-of-formula-concepts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our long-term goal is to generalize citation-based IR methods and apply this generalized method to both classical references and mathematical concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discovery-and-recognition-of-formula-concepts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Diffusions in Augmented Spaces: A Complete Recipe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-diffusions-in-augmented-spaces-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Score-based Generative Models (SGMs) have achieved state-of-the-art synthesis results on diverse tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-diffusions-in-augmented-spaces-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DWFormer: Dynamic Window transFormer for Speech Emotion Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwformer-dynamic-window-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Self-attention mechanism is applied within windows for capturing temporal important information locally in a fine-grained way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwformer-dynamic-window-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAGE: A Position-Aware Graph-Based Model for Emotion Cause Entailment in Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/page-a-position-aware-graph-based-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conversational Causal Emotion Entailment (C2E2) is a task that aims at recognizing the causes corresponding to a target emotion in a conversation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/page-a-position-aware-graph-based-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparsity May Cry: Let Us Fail (Current) Sparse Neural Networks Together!</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-may-cry-let-us-fail-current-sparse</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In pursuit of a more general evaluation and unveiling the true potential of sparse algorithms, we introduce "Sparsity May Cry" Benchmark (SMC-Bench), a collection of carefully-curated 4 diverse tasks with 10 datasets, that accounts for capturing a wide range of domain-specific and sophisticated knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparsity-may-cry-let-us-fail-current-sparse</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Translation Performance of a Large Multilingual Language Model: the Case of BLOOM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-translation-performance-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The NLP community recently saw the release of a new large open-access multilingual language model, BLOOM (BigScience et al., 2022) covering 46 languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/investigating-the-translation-performance-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Depth-based 6DoF Object Pose Estimation using Swin Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-based-6dof-object-pose-estimation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, we propose a novel framework called SwinDePose, that uses only geometric information from depth images to achieve accurate 6D pose estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/depth-based-6dof-object-pose-estimation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POPGym: Benchmarking Partially Observable Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popgym-benchmarking-partially-observable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real world applications of Reinforcement Learning (RL) are often partially observable, thus requiring memory.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/popgym-benchmarking-partially-observable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Detection Outcome: A Metric for Pathology Detection in Medical Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-detection-outcome-a-metric-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this problem, we propose Robust Detection Outcome (RoDeO); a novel metric for evaluating algorithms for pathology detection in medical images, especially in chest X-rays.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-detection-outcome-a-metric-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chemically Transferable Generative Backmapping of Coarse-Grained Proteins</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemically-transferable-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Coarse-graining (CG) accelerates molecular simulations of protein dynamics by simulating sets of atoms as singular beads.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chemically-transferable-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ACL-SPC: Adaptive Closed-Loop system for Self-Supervised Point Cloud Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acl-spc-adaptive-closed-loop-system-for-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Point cloud completion addresses filling in the missing parts of a partial point cloud obtained from depth sensors and generating a complete point cloud.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/acl-spc-adaptive-closed-loop-system-for-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending against Adversarial Audio via Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-adversarial-audio-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an adversarial purification-based defense pipeline, AudioPure, for acoustic systems via off-the-shelf diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-adversarial-audio-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less is More: Mitigate Spurious Correlations for Open-Domain Dialogue Response Generation Models by Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-mitigate-spurious-correlations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct the first study on spurious correlations for open-domain response generation models based on a corpus CGDIALOG curated in our work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-is-more-mitigate-spurious-correlations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeer: Interactive RNN Explanation and Debugging via State Abstraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseer-interactive-rnn-explanation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The core of DeepSeer is a state abstraction method that bundles semantically similar hidden states in an RNN model and abstracts the model as a finite state machine.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseer-interactive-rnn-explanation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLANet: Multi-Level Attention Network with Sub-instruction for Continuous Vision-and-Language Navigation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlanet-multi-level-attention-network-with-sub</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For a better performance in continuous VLN, we design a multi-level instruction understanding procedure and propose a novel model, Multi-Level Attention Network (MLANet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mlanet-multi-level-attention-network-with-sub</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConTEXTual Net: A Multimodal Vision-Language Model for Segmentation of Pneumothorax</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-net-a-multimodal-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a vision-language model for the task of pneumothorax segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-net-a-multimodal-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepLens: Interactive Out-of-distribution Data Detection in NLP Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplens-interactive-out-of-distribution-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose DeepLens, an interactive system that helps users detect and explore OOD issues in massive text corpora.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeplens-interactive-out-of-distribution-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse MoE as the New Dropout: Scaling Dense and Self-Slimmable Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-moe-as-the-new-dropout-scaling-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite their remarkable achievement, gigantic transformers encounter significant drawbacks, including exorbitant computational and memory footprints during training, as well as severe collapse evidenced by a high degree of parameter redundancy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-moe-as-the-new-dropout-scaling-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHAP-IQ: Unified Approximation of any-order Shapley Interactions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-iq-unified-approximation-of-any-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SHAP-IQ is based on a novel representation and, in contrast to existing methods, we provide theoretical guarantees for its approximation quality, as well as estimates for the variance of the point estimates.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shap-iq-unified-approximation-of-any-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Specformer: Spectral Graph Neural Networks Meet Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specformer-spectral-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle these issues, we introduce Specformer, which effectively encodes the set of all eigenvalues and performs self-attention in the spectral domain, leading to a learnable set-to-set spectral filter.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/specformer-spectral-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discrete-time Competing-Risks Regression with or without Penalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-time-competing-risks-regression-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we showcase the utility of our procedure by estimating a survival model for the length of stay of patients hospitalized in the intensive care unit, considering three competing events: discharge to home, transfer to another medical facility, and in-hospital death.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/discrete-time-competing-risks-regression-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Geometric Visual Similarity Learning in 3D Medical Image Self-supervised Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-visual-similarity-learning-in-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel visual similarity learning paradigm, Geometric Visual Similarity Learning, which embeds the prior of topological invariance into the measurement of the inter-image similarity for consistent representation of semantic regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geometric-visual-similarity-learning-in-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperparameter Tuning and Model Evaluation in Causal Effect Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-and-model-evaluation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also find hyperparameter tuning and model evaluation are much more important than causal estimators and ML methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperparameter-tuning-and-model-evaluation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STUNT: Few-shot Tabular Learning with Self-generated Tasks from Unlabeled Tables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stunt-few-shot-tabular-learning-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning with few labeled tabular samples is often an essential requirement for industrial machine learning applications as varieties of tabular data suffer from high annotation costs or have difficulties in collecting new samples for novel tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stunt-few-shot-tabular-learning-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can BERT Refrain from Forgetting on Sequential Tasks? A Probing Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bert-refrain-from-forgetting-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained language models help to achieve state of the art on a variety of natural language processing (NLP) tasks, nevertheless, they still suffer from forgetting when incrementally learning a sequence of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-bert-refrain-from-forgetting-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical Network Acceleration with Tiny Sets: Hypothesis, Theory, and Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-network-acceleration-with-tiny-sets-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For 22% latency reduction, it surpasses previous methods by on average 7 percentage points on ImageNet-1k.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/practical-network-acceleration-with-tiny-sets-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Variety Identification with True Labels</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-variety-identification-with-true</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research has shown that this is a problematic assumption, particularly in the case of very similar languages (e. g., Croatian and Serbian) and national language varieties (e. g., Brazilian and European Portuguese), where texts may contain no distinctive marker of the particular language or variety.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-variety-identification-with-true</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning Guided Multi-Objective Exam Paper Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-guided-multi-objective</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the repetitive and complex work of instructors, exam paper generation (EPG) technique has become a salient topic in the intelligent education field, which targets at generating high-quality exam paper automatically according to instructor-specified assessment criteria.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-guided-multi-objective</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pay Less But Get More: A Dual-Attention-based Channel Estimation Network for Massive MIMO Systems with Low-Density Pilots</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-less-but-get-more-a-dual-attention-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, with the proposed transfer learning approach, the DACEN-based method with ultra-low-density pilots ($\rho_L^\prime=2/52$) achieves higher estimation accuracy than the existing methods with low-density pilots, thereby demonstrating the effectiveness and the superiority of the proposed method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pay-less-but-get-more-a-dual-attention-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict-Based Cross-View Consistency for Semi-Supervised Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conflict-based-cross-view-consistency-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a new conflict-based cross-view consistency (CCVC) method based on a two-branch co-training framework for semi-supervised semantic segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/conflict-based-cross-view-consistency-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning-Based Software Testing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-based-software-testing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Reasoning-Based Software Testing (RBST), a new way of thinking at the testing problem as a causal reasoning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-based-software-testing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAVA: Disentangling Adversarial Variational Autoencoder</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dava-disentangling-adversarial-variational</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare DAVA to models with optimal hyperparameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dava-disentangling-adversarial-variational</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MuscleMap: Towards Video-based Activated Muscle Group Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musclemap-towards-video-based-activated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we tackle the new task of video-based Activated Muscle Group Estimation (AMGE) aiming at identifying currently activated muscular regions of humans performing a specific activity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musclemap-towards-video-based-activated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why (and When) does Local SGD Generalize Better than SGD?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-and-when-does-local-sgd-generalize-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local SGD is a communication-efficient variant of SGD for large-scale training, where multiple GPUs perform SGD independently and average the model parameters periodically.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/why-and-when-does-local-sgd-generalize-better</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
