<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 09:11:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Quantigraphic Image Enhancement via Comparametric Equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quantigraphic-image-enhancement-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most recent methods of deep image enhancement can be generally classified into two types: decompose-and-enhance and illumination estimation-centric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-quantigraphic-image-enhancement-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industrial Anomaly Detection with Domain Shift: A Real-world Dataset and Masked Multi-scale Reconstruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industrial-anomaly-detection-with-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, to bridge this gap, we propose the Aero-engine Blade Anomaly Detection (AeBAD) dataset, consisting of two sub-datasets: the single-blade dataset and the video anomaly detection dataset of blades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/industrial-anomaly-detection-with-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Compare Longitudinal Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compare-longitudinal-images</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For example, normalizing for nuisance variation might be hard in settings where there are a lot of idiosyncratic changes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compare-longitudinal-images</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Segment Anything (SA) project: a new task, model, and dataset for image segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation of ChatGPT Family of Models for Biomedical Reasoning and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first task is classifying whether statements of clinical and policy recommendations in scientific literature constitute health advice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluation-of-chatgpt-family-of-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting and Grounding Multi-Modal Media Manipulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-grounding-multi-modal-media</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we highlight a new research problem for multi-modal fake media, namely Detecting and Grounding Multi-Modal Media Manipulation (DGM^4).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/detecting-and-grounding-multi-modal-media</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EigenFold: Generative Protein Structure Prediction with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenfold-generative-protein-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Protein structure prediction has reached revolutionary levels of accuracy on single structures, yet distributional modeling paradigms are needed to capture the conformational ensembles and flexibility that underlie biological function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eigenfold-generative-protein-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dynamic Bayesian optimized active recommender system for curiosity-driven Human-in-the-loop automated experiments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-bayesian-optimized-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimization of experimental materials synthesis and characterization through active learning methods has been growing over the last decade, with examples ranging from measurements of diffraction on combinatorial alloys at synchrotrons, to searches through chemical space with automated synthesis robots for perovskites.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dynamic-bayesian-optimized-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS3D: Leveraging Multiple Detectors for Unsupervised Domain Adaptation in 3D Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms3d-leveraging-multiple-detectors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our proposed Kernel-Density Estimation (KDE) Box Fusion method fuses box proposals from multiple domains to obtain pseudo-labels that surpass the performance of the best source domain detectors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ms3d-leveraging-multiple-detectors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-annotator Deep Learning: A Probabilistic Framework for Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-annotator-deep-learning-a-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Training standard deep neural networks leads to subpar performances in such multi-annotator supervised learning settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-annotator-deep-learning-a-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Impact of Voice Anonymization on Speech-Based COVID-19 Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-voice-anonymization-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With advances seen in deep learning, voice-based applications are burgeoning, ranging from personal assistants, affective computing, to remote disease diagnostics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-impact-of-voice-anonymization-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Validation in Structure from Motion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-validation-in-structure-from-motion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, semantic labels on input images are used for the removal of objects associated with motion in the output SfM models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-validation-in-structure-from-motion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Distillation for Gaussian Process Regression and Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-for-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose two approaches to extend the notion of knowledge distillation to Gaussian Process Regression (GPR) and Gaussian Process Classification (GPC); data-centric and distribution-centric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-distillation-for-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selecting Features by their Resilience to the Curse of Dimensionality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-features-by-their-resilience-to-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Real-world datasets are often of high dimension and effected by the curse of dimensionality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/selecting-features-by-their-resilience-to-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BiFormer: Learning Bilateral Motion Estimation via Bilateral Transformer for 4K Video Frame Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-learning-bilateral-motion-estimation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, in global motion estimation, we predict symmetric bilateral motion fields at a coarse scale.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biformer-learning-bilateral-motion-estimation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiGA: Distil to Generalize and then Adapt for Domain Adaptive Semantic Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diga-distil-to-generalize-and-then-adapt-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Domain adaptive semantic segmentation methods commonly utilize stage-wise training, consisting of a warm-up and a self-training stage.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diga-distil-to-generalize-and-then-adapt-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HNeRV: A Hybrid Neural Representation for Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnerv-a-hybrid-neural-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Such embedding largely limits the regression capacity and internal generalization for video interpolation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hnerv-a-hybrid-neural-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to choose your best allies for a transferable attack?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-choose-your-best-allies-for-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The transferability of adversarial examples is a key issue in the security of deep neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-to-choose-your-best-allies-for-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantifying the Roles of Visual, Linguistic, and Visual-Linguistic Complexity in Verb Acquisition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-roles-of-visual-linguistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these results, we conclude that verb acquisition is influenced by all three sources of complexity, but that the variability of visual structure poses the most significant challenge for verb learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantifying-the-roles-of-visual-linguistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoocRadar: A Fine-grained and Multi-aspect Knowledge Repository for Improving Cognitive Student Modeling in MOOCs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Student modeling, the task of inferring a student's learning characteristics through their interactions with coursework, is a fundamental issue in intelligent education.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/moocradar-a-fine-grained-and-multi-aspect</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Garment Designer: Human-Centric Latent Diffusion Models for Fashion Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-garment-designer-human-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the lack of existing datasets suitable for the task, we also extend two existing fashion datasets, namely Dress Code and VITON-HD, with multimodal annotations collected in a semi-automatic manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-garment-designer-human-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form-NLU: Dataset for the Form Language Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/form-nlu-dataset-for-the-form-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to general document analysis tasks, form document structure understanding and retrieval are challenging.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/form-nlu-dataset-for-the-form-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MM-BSN: Self-Supervised Image Denoising for Real-World with Multi-Mask based on Blind-Spot Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bsn-self-supervised-image-denoising-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our MM-BSN can be used to address the problem of large-noise denoising, which cannot be efficiently handled by other BSN methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mm-bsn-self-supervised-image-denoising-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waving Goodbye to Low-Res: A Diffusion-Wavelet Approach for Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwa-differential-wavelet-amplifier-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel Diffusion-Wavelet (DiWa) approach for Single-Image Super-Resolution (SISR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dwa-differential-wavelet-amplifier-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arrhythmia Classifier Based on Ultra-Lightweight Binary Neural Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arrhythmia-classifier-based-on-ultra</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the development of deep learning, numerous ECG classification algorithms based on deep learning have emerged.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arrhythmia-classifier-based-on-ultra</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Aware Neural Architecture Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aware-neural-architecture-search</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in the case of resource constrained Machine Learning, one single metric is not enough to evaluate a NN architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-aware-neural-architecture-search</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Practical Framework for Unsupervised Structure Preservation Medical Image Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-framework-for-unsupervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a framework for practical unsupervised medical image enhancement that includes (1) a non-reference objective evaluation of structure preservation for medical image enhancement tasks called Laplacian structural similarity index measure (LaSSIM), which is based on SSIM and the Laplacian pyramid, and (2) a novel unsupervised GAN-based method called Laplacian medical image enhancement (LaMEGAN) to support the improvement of both originality and quality from LQ images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-practical-framework-for-unsupervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DCANet: Dual Convolutional Neural Network with Attention for Image Blind Denoising</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcanet-dual-convolutional-neural-network-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a new dual convolutional neural network (CNN) with attention for image blind denoising, named as the DCANet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dcanet-dual-convolutional-neural-network-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Learning with a Geometry-Adaptive Preconditioner</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-a-geometry-adaptive</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose Geometry-Adaptive Preconditioned gradient descent (GAP) that can overcome the limitations in MAML; GAP can efficiently meta-learn a preconditioner that is dependent on task-specific parameters, and its preconditioner can be shown to be a Riemannian metric.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-learning-with-a-geometry-adaptive</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGClass: Text Classification with Extremely Weak Supervision via Mutually-Enhancing Text Granularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megclass-text-classification-with-extremely</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, MEGClass constructs class-oriented sentence and class representations based on keywords for performing a sentence-level confidence-weighted label ensemble in order to estimate a document's initial class distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megclass-text-classification-with-extremely</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Level Contrastive Learning for Dense Prediction Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-contrastive-learning-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We extend our pretext task to supervised pre-training, which achieves a similar performance to self-supervised learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-level-contrastive-learning-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A differentiable programming framework for spin models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-differentiable-programming-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Spin systems are a powerful tool for modeling a wide range of physical systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-differentiable-programming-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Supervision and Shuffle Data Augmentation for 3D Semi-Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-supervision-and-shuffle-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art 3D object detectors are usually trained on large-scale datasets with high-quality 3D annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-supervision-and-shuffle-data</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping Degeneration Meets Label Evolution: Learning Infrared Small Target Detection with Single Point Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-degeneration-meets-label-evolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, during the training phase supervised by point labels, we discover that CNNs first learn to segment a cluster of pixels near the targets, and then gradually converge to predict groundtruth point labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mapping-degeneration-meets-label-evolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AToMiC: An Image/Text Retrieval Test Collection to Support Multimedia Content Creation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-an-image-text-retrieval-test</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents the AToMiC (Authoring Tools for Multimedia Content) dataset, designed to advance research in image/text cross-modal retrieval.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atomic-an-image-text-retrieval-test</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fully Convolutional Networks for Dense Water Flow Intensity Prediction in Swedish Catchment Areas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-convolutional-networks-for-dense-water</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To the best of our knowledge, we are the first to tackle the task of dense water flow intensity prediction; earlier works have considered predicting flow intensities at a sparse set of locations at a time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fully-convolutional-networks-for-dense-water</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap between Model Explanations in Partially Annotated Multi-label Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-model-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on these findings, we propose to boost the attribution scores of the model trained with partial labels to make its explanation resemble that of the model trained with full labels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-model-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM-Adapters: An Adapter Family for Parameter-Efficient Fine-Tuning of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-adapters-an-adapter-family-for-parameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To enable further research on PEFT methods of LLMs, this paper presents LLM-Adapters, an easy-to-use framework that integrates various adapters into LLMs and can execute these adapter-based PEFT methods of LLMs for different tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-adapters-an-adapter-family-for-parameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against Patch-based Backdoor Attacks on Self-Supervised Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-patch-based-backdoor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It was shown that an adversary can poison a small part of the unlabeled data so that when a victim trains an SSL model on it, the final model will have a backdoor that the adversary can exploit.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/defending-against-patch-based-backdoor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SportsPose -- A Dynamic 3D sports pose dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportspose-a-dynamic-3d-sports-pose-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate 3D human pose estimation is essential for sports analytics, coaching, and injury prevention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sportspose-a-dynamic-3d-sports-pose-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-modulated Few-shot Image Generation for Colorectal Tissue Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modulated-few-shot-image-generation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a few-shot colorectal tissue image generation method for addressing the scarcity of histopathological training data for rare cancer tissues.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modulated-few-shot-image-generation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>\emph{MEnsA}: Mix-up Ensemble Average for Unsupervised Multi Target Domain Adaptation on 3D Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emph-mensa-mix-up-ensemble-average-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised domain adaptation (UDA) addresses the problem of distribution shift between the unlabeled target domain and labelled source domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emph-mensa-mix-up-ensemble-average-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploration of Lightweight Single Image Denoising with Transformers and Truly Fair Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-lightweight-single-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As multimedia content often contains noise from intrinsic defects of digital devices, image denoising is an important step for high-level vision recognition tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploration-of-lightweight-single-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Comprehension: Language Models with Compiled Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-comprehension-language-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models have achieved impressive results in natural language processing tasks, but their ability to perform symbolic operations and arithmetic operations, remains limited, which attribute to their learn the rules implicitly from data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-comprehension-language-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FakET: Simulating Cryo-Electron Tomograms with Neural Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faket-simulating-cryo-electron-tomograms-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key shortcoming of these supervised learning methods is their need for large training data sets, typically generated from particle models in conjunction with complex numerical forward models simulating the physics of transmission electron microscopes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/faket-simulating-cryo-electron-tomograms-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Avatar Stream: a cost-down approach to the Metaverse experience</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-avatar-stream-a-cost-down-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Metaverse through VR headsets is a rapidly growing concept, but the high cost of entry currently limits access for many users.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/virtual-avatar-stream-a-cost-down-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GlueStick: Robust Image Matching by Sticking Points and Lines Together</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gluestick-robust-image-matching-by-sticking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Line segments are powerful features complementary to points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gluestick-robust-image-matching-by-sticking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-space-frequency feature Fusion for 3-channel motor imagery classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-space-frequency-feature-fusion-for-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TSFF-Net comprises four main components: time-frequency representation, time-frequency feature extraction, time-space feature extraction, and feature fusion and classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-space-frequency-feature-fusion-for-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Algorithm-Dependent Bounds for Representation Learning of Multi-Source Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithm-dependent-bounds-for-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further provide algorithm-dependent generalization bounds for these two settings, where the generalization is characterized by the mutual information between the parameters and the data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/algorithm-dependent-bounds-for-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learned Tree Search for Long-Horizon Social Robot Navigation in Shared Airspace</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-tree-search-for-long-horizon-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose Social Robot Tree Search (SoRTS), an algorithm for the safe navigation of mobile robots in social domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learned-tree-search-for-long-horizon-social</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
