<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 21:06:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>StyleID: Identity Disentanglement for Anonymizing Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleid-identity-disentanglement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Privacy of machine learning models is one of the remaining challenges that hinder the broad adoption of Artificial Intelligent (AI).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styleid-identity-disentanglement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TiG-BEV: Multi-view BEV 3D Object Detection via Target Inner-Geometry Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tig-bev-multi-view-bev-3d-object-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the learning scheme of Target Inner-Geometry from the LiDAR modality into camera-based BEV detectors for both dense depth and BEV features, termed as TiG-BEV.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tig-bev-multi-view-bev-3d-object-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable and Lightweight Model for COVID-19 Detection Using Chest Radiology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-lightweight-model-for-covid</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning (DL) analysis of Chest X-ray (CXR) and Computed tomography (CT) images has garnered a lot of attention in recent times due to the COVID-19 pandemic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-and-lightweight-model-for-covid</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Generalizability of Deep Learning Models Using Indian-COVID-19 CT Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generalizability-of-deep-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the major concerns in using ma-chine learning (ML) approaches for automatic processing of CT scan images in clinical setting is that these methods are trained on limited and biased sub-sets of publicly available COVID-19 data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-generalizability-of-deep-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynCLay: Interactive Synthesis of Histology Images from Bespoke Cellular Layouts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synclay-interactive-synthesis-of-histology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tissue image generation based on bespoke cellular layouts through the proposed framework allows users to generate different histological patterns from arbitrary topological arrangement of different types of cells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synclay-interactive-synthesis-of-histology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part-guided Relational Transformers for Fine-grained Visual Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-guided-relational-transformers-for-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework, namely PArt-guided Relational Transformers (PART), is proposed to learn the discriminative part features with an automatic part discovery module, and to explore the intrinsic correlations with a feature transformation module by adapting the Transformer models from the field of natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/part-guided-relational-transformers-for-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Clustering-guided Contrastive Fusion for Multi-view Representation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clustering-guided-contrastive-fusion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we utilize a deep fusion network to fuse view-specific representations into the view-common representation, extracting high-level semantics for obtaining robust representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-clustering-guided-contrastive-fusion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anxolotl, an Anxiety Companion App -- Stress Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anxolotl-an-anxiety-companion-app-stress</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stress has a great effect on people's lives that can not be understated.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anxolotl-an-anxiety-companion-app-stress</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cramming: Training a Language Model on a Single GPU in One Day</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cramming-training-a-language-model-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent trends in language modeling have focused on increasing performance through scaling, and have resulted in an environment where training language models is out of reach for most researchers and practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cramming-training-a-language-model-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature learning in neural networks and kernel machines that recursively learn features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-learning-in-neural-networks-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we isolate the key mechanism driving feature learning in fully connected neural networks by connecting neural feature learning to the average gradient outer product.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-learning-in-neural-networks-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Detect Noisy Labels Using Model-Based Features</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-noisy-labels-using-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Label noise is ubiquitous in various machine learning scenarios such as self-labeling with model predictions and erroneous data annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-detect-noisy-labels-using-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Graph Contrastive Learning with Meta-path Contexts and Weighted Negative Samples</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-contrastive-learning-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We take node embeddings in the coarse view as anchors, and construct positive and negative samples from the fine-grained view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-graph-contrastive-learning-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shape-Aware Fine-Grained Classification of Erythroid Cells</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-fine-grained-classification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[BMEC contains 5, 666 images of individual erythroid cells, each of which is extracted from the bone marrow erythroid cell smears and professionally annotated to one of the four types of erythroid cells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/shape-aware-fine-grained-classification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End-to-End Modeling Hierarchical Time Series Using Autoregressive Transformer and Conditional Normalizing Flow based Reconciliation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-modeling-hierarchical-time-series</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate time series forecasting with hierarchical structure is pervasive in real-world applications, demanding not only predicting each level of the hierarchy, but also reconciling all forecasts to ensure coherency, i. e., the forecasts should satisfy the hierarchical aggregation constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/end-to-end-modeling-hierarchical-time-series</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Recognition and Classification of Future Work Sentences from Academic Articles in a Specific Domain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-recognition-and-classification-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents methods to automatically extract FWS from academic papers and classify them according to the different future directions embodied in the paper's content.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-recognition-and-classification-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lexicographic Multi-Objective Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicographic-multi-objective-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we introduce reinforcement learning techniques for solving lexicographic multi-objective problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lexicographic-multi-objective-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MVTN: Learning Multi-View Transformations for 3D Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvtn-learning-multi-view-transformations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-view projection techniques have shown themselves to be highly effective in achieving top-performing results in the recognition of 3D shapes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mvtn-learning-multi-view-transformations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepCuts: Single-Shot Interpretability based Pruning for BERT</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepcuts-single-shot-interpretability-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also analyze our pruning masks and find them to be significantly different from the ones obtained using standard metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepcuts-single-shot-interpretability-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Forward-Forward Algorithm: Some Preliminary Investigations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-forward-forward-algorithm-some-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The aim of this paper is to introduce a new learning procedure for neural networks and to demonstrate that it works well enough on a few small problems to be worth further investigation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-forward-forward-algorithm-some-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AER: Auto-Encoder with Regression for Time Series Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aer-auto-encoder-with-regression-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then propose AER (Auto-encoder with Regression), a joint model that combines a vanilla auto-encoder and an LSTM regressor to incorporate the successes and address the limitations of each method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aer-auto-encoder-with-regression-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Single-Visit to Multi-Visit Image-Based Models: Single-Visit Models are Enough to Predict Obstructive Hydronephrosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-single-visit-to-multi-visit-image-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Previous work has shown the potential of deep learning to predict renal obstruction using kidney ultrasound images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-single-visit-to-multi-visit-image-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-supervised learning paradigm with conditional generative adversarial networks for sample-efficient classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-supervised-learning-paradigm-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classification using supervised learning requires annotating a large amount of classes-balanced data for model training and testing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-supervised-learning-paradigm-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variance Reduction for Score Functions Using Optimal Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduction-for-score-functions-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although we show that there exist examples where the optimal baseline may be arbitrarily better than a value function baseline, we find that the value function baseline usually performs similarly to an optimal baseline in terms of variance reduction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/variance-reduction-for-score-functions-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Resolution Flow Propagation for Foveated Video Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-resolution-flow-propagation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Cross-Resolution Flow Propagation (CRFP) for FVSR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-resolution-flow-propagation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeRN -- Learning Neural Representations for Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nern-learning-neural-representations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural Representations have recently been shown to effectively reconstruct a wide range of signals from 3D meshes and shapes to images and videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nern-learning-neural-representations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Infusing Definiteness into Randomness: Rethinking Composition Styles for Deep Image Matting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infusing-definiteness-into-randomness</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by this, we introduce a novel composition style that binds the source and combined foregrounds in a definite triplet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infusing-definiteness-into-randomness</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise-aware Learning from Web-crawled Image-Text Data for Image Captioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-aware-learning-from-web-crawled-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the filtering strategy can effectively remove noisy data, however, it leads to a decrease in learnable knowledge and sometimes brings about a new problem of data deficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/noise-aware-learning-from-web-crawled-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Generalization of ViT/MLP-Mixer to Graphs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalization-of-vit-mlp-mixer-to-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph Neural Networks (GNNs) have shown great potential in the field of graph representation learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-generalization-of-vit-mlp-mixer-to-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Models for River Classification at Sub-Meter Resolutions from Multispectral and Panchromatic Commercial Satellite Imagery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-models-for-river-classification</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In a novel approach, we then use results from the multispectral model to generate training data for FCN that only require panchromatic imagery, of which considerably more is available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-models-for-river-classification</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MultiSpider: Towards Benchmarking Multilingual Text-to-SQL Semantic Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multispider-towards-benchmarking-multilingual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-SQL semantic parsing is an important NLP task, which greatly facilitates the interaction between users and the database and becomes the key component in many human-computer interaction systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multispider-towards-benchmarking-multilingual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strangeness-driven Exploration in Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strangeness-driven-exploration-in-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficient exploration strategy is one of essential issues in cooperative multi-agent reinforcement learning (MARL) algorithms requiring complex coordination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/strangeness-driven-exploration-in-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantile Risk Control: A Flexible Framework for Bounding the Probability of High-Loss Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-risk-control-a-flexible-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a flexible framework to produce a family of bounds on quantiles of the loss distribution incurred by a predictor.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantile-risk-control-a-flexible-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAE-Former: Dual Attention-guided Efficient Transformer for Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dae-former-dual-attention-guided-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Transformers have recently gained attention in the computer vision domain due to their ability to model long-range dependencies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dae-former-dual-attention-guided-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Complex Knowledge Base Question Answering via Question-to-Action and Question-to-Question Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-complex-knowledge-base-question</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Complex knowledge base question answering can be achieved by converting questions into sequences of predefined actions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-complex-knowledge-base-question</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orientation-Shared Convolution Representation for CT Metal Artifact Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-shared-convolution-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During X-ray computed tomography (CT) scanning, metallic implants carrying with patients often lead to adverse artifacts in the captured CT images and then impair the clinical treatment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/orientation-shared-convolution-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simultaneously Optimizing Perturbations and Positions for Black-box Adversarial Patch Attacks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneously-optimizing-perturbations-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments are conducted on the Face Recognition (FR) task, and results on four representative FR models show that our method can significantly improve the attack success rate and query efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/simultaneously-optimizing-perturbations-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMMix: Self-Motivated Image Mixing for Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smmix-self-motivated-image-mixing-for-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the subtle designs of the self-motivated paradigm, our SMMix is significant in its smaller training overhead and better performance than other CutMix variants.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smmix-self-motivated-image-mixing-for-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Representation Learning from Pre-trained Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-representation-learning-from-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These imply that the gap corresponds to the lost information of the image, and we can reconstruct the image by filling the gap.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-representation-learning-from-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fewer is More: Efficient Object Detection in Large Aerial Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewer-is-more-efficient-object-detection-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current mainstream object detection methods for large aerial images usually divide large images into patches and then exhaustively detect the objects of interest on all patches, no matter whether there exist objects or not.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fewer-is-more-efficient-object-detection-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Link-level simulator for 5G localization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-level-simulator-for-5g-localization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Channel-state-information-based localization in 5G networks has been a promising way to obtain highly accurate positions compared to previous communication networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/link-level-simulator-for-5g-localization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Self-Supervised Learning-Based Anomaly Node Detection Method Based on an Autoencoder in Wireless Sensor Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-self-supervised-learning-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the issue that existing wireless sensor network (WSN)-based anomaly detection methods only consider and analyze temporal features, in this paper, a self-supervised learning-based anomaly node detection method based on an autoencoder is designed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-self-supervised-learning-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saliency-Augmented Memory Completion for Continual Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-augmented-memory-completion-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we innovatively propose to store the part of the image most important to the tasks in episodic memory by saliency map extraction and memory encoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/saliency-augmented-memory-completion-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Kernel Alignment Regret Bound for Online Kernel Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-kernel-alignment-regret-bound-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[If the eigenvalues of the kernel matrix decay exponentially, then our algorithm enjoys a regret of $O(\sqrt{\mathcal{A}_T})$ at a computational complexity of $O(\ln^2{T})$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-kernel-alignment-regret-bound-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Generalizable Representations for Reinforcement Learning via Adaptive Meta-learner of Behavioral Similarities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalizable-representations-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[How to learn an effective reinforcement learning-based model for control tasks from high-level visual observations is a practical and challenging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-generalizable-representations-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skit-S2I: An Indian Accented Speech to Intent dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skit-s2i-an-indian-accented-speech-to-intent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conventional conversation assistants extract text transcripts from the speech signal using automatic speech recognition (ASR) and then predict intent from the transcriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skit-s2i-an-indian-accented-speech-to-intent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextBox 2.0: A Text Generation Library with Pre-trained Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textbox-2-0-a-text-generation-library-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To facilitate research on text generation, this paper presents a comprehensive and unified library, TextBox 2. 0, focusing on the use of pre-trained language models (PLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textbox-2-0-a-text-generation-library-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closed-form control with spike coding networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-control-with-spike-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The neuroscience theory of Spike Coding Networks (SCNs) offers a fully analytical solution for implementing dynamical systems in recurrent spiking neural networks -- while maintaining irregular, sparse, and robust spiking activity -- but it's not clear how to directly apply it to control problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/closed-form-control-with-spike-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GAE-ISumm: Unsupervised Graph-Based Summarization of Indian Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gae-isumm-unsupervised-graph-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, we experiment with the most publicly available Indian language summarization datasets to investigate the effectiveness of GAE-ISumm on other Indian languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gae-isumm-unsupervised-graph-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-Supervised Deep Learning Model for Prostate Cancer Diagnosis and Gleason Grading of Histopathology Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-deep-learning-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[One of the prognostic features in prostate cancer is the Gleason grading of histopathology images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-deep-learning-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable AI for Bioinformatics: Methods, Tools, and Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-ai-for-bioinformatics-methods</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explainable artificial intelligence (XAI) is an emerging field that aims to mitigate the opaqueness of black-box models and make it possible to interpret how AI systems make their decisions with transparency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/explainable-ai-for-bioinformatics-methods</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
