<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 09:13:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>EC-SfM: Efficient Covisibility-based Structure-from-Motion for Both Sequential and Unordered Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ec-sfm-efficient-covisibility-based-structure</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this general image connection, we propose a unified framework to efficiently reconstruct sequential images, unordered images, and the mixture of these two.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ec-sfm-efficient-covisibility-based-structure</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boosting the Power of Kernel Two-Sample Tests</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-power-of-kernel-two-sample-tests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The kernel two-sample test based on the maximum mean discrepancy (MMD) is one of the most popular methods for detecting differences between two distributions over general metric spaces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/boosting-the-power-of-kernel-two-sample-tests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Self-Supervised Learning for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-self-supervised-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The online emergence of multi-modal sharing platforms (eg, TikTok, Youtube) is powering personalized recommender systems to incorporate various modalities (eg, visual, textual and acoustic) into the latent user representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-self-supervised-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight-Yet-Efficient: Revitalizing Ball-Tree for Point-to-Hyperplane Nearest Neighbor Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-yet-efficient-revitalizing-ball</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finding the nearest neighbor to a hyperplane (or Point-to-Hyperplane Nearest Neighbor Search, simply P2HNNS) is a new and challenging problem with applications in many research domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-yet-efficient-revitalizing-ball</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Scene Text Image Super-Resolution via Dual Prior Modulation Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-scene-text-image-super-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scene text image super-resolution (STISR) aims to simultaneously increase the resolution and legibility of the text images, and the resulting images will significantly affect the performance of downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-scene-text-image-super-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valid Inference for Machine Learning Model Parameters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valid-inference-for-machine-learning-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, this can come with the risk of overtraining; in order for the model to generalize well, it is of great importance that we are able to find the optimal parameter for the model on the entire population -- not only on the given training sample.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/valid-inference-for-machine-learning-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generic Dependency Modeling for Multi-Party Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-dependency-modeling-for-multi-party</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To model the dependencies between utterances in multi-party conversations, we propose a simple and generic framework based on the dependency parsing results of utterances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generic-dependency-modeling-for-multi-party</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CADIS: Handling Cluster-skewed Non-IID Data in Federated Learning with Clustered Aggregation and Knowledge DIStilled Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cadis-handling-cluster-skewed-non-iid-data-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By performing an in-depth analysis of the behavior of a classification model's penultimate layer, we introduce a metric that quantifies the similarity between two clients' data distributions without violating their privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cadis-handling-cluster-skewed-non-iid-data-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assessing Domain Gap for Continual Domain Adaptation in Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-domain-gap-for-continual-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To ensure reliable object detection in autonomous systems, the detector must be able to adapt to changes in appearance caused by environmental factors such as time of day, weather, and seasons.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assessing-domain-gap-for-continual-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mean Parity Fair Regression in RKHS</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-parity-fair-regression-in-rkhs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the fair regression problem under the notion of Mean Parity (MP) fairness, which requires the conditional mean of the learned function output to be constant with respect to the sensitive attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mean-parity-fair-regression-in-rkhs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Efficient Two-stage Gradient Boosting Framework for Short-term Traffic State Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-two-stage-gradient-boosting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we present an efficient two-stage gradient boosting framework for short-term traffic state estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-efficient-two-stage-gradient-boosting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimax-Bayes Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-bayes-reinforcement-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the Bayesian decision-theoretic framework offers an elegant solution to the problem of decision making under uncertainty, one question is how to appropriately select the prior distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minimax-bayes-reinforcement-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Calibrating Diffusion Probabilistic Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-calibrating-diffusion-probabilistic-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we observe that the stochastic reverse process of data scores is a martingale, from which concentration bounds and the optional stopping theorem for data scores can be derived.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-calibrating-diffusion-probabilistic-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On ML-Based Program Translation: Perils and Promises</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-ml-based-program-translation-perils-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the future, we envision an end-to-end program translation tool where programming domain knowledge can be embedded into an ML-based translation pipeline using pre- and post-processing steps.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-ml-based-program-translation-perils-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT: Jack of all trades, master of none</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-jack-of-all-trades-master-of-none</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our comparison of its results with available State-of-the-Art (SOTA) solutions showed that the average loss in quality of the ChatGPT model was about 25% for zero-shot and few-shot evaluation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatgpt-jack-of-all-trades-master-of-none</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FrankenSplit: Saliency Guided Neural Feature Compression with Shallow Variational Bottleneck Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frankensplit-saliency-guided-neural-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Lightweight neural networks exchange fast inference for predictive strength.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/frankensplit-saliency-guided-neural-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap between ANNs and SNNs by Calibrating Offset Spikes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-anns-and-snns-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The experimental results show that our proposed method achieves state-of-the-art performance on CIFAR-10, CIFAR-100, and ImageNet datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bridging-the-gap-between-anns-and-snns-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Discretization using Voronoi Trees for Continuous POMDPs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-discretization-using-voronoi-trees-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[ADVT uses the estimated diameters of the cells to form an upper-confidence bound on the action value function within the cell, guiding the Monte Carlo Tree Search expansion and further discretization of the action space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-discretization-using-voronoi-trees-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dual Policy Learning for Aggregation Optimization in Graph Neural Network-based Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-policy-learning-for-aggregation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This framework adaptively determines high-order connectivity to aggregate users and items using dual policy learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dual-policy-learning-for-aggregation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Co-Driven Recognition of Semantic Consistency via the Fusion of Transformer and HowNet Sememes Knowledge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-driven-recognition-of-semantic-consistency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-level encoding of internal sentence structures via data-driven is carried out firstly by Transformer, sememes knowledge base HowNet is introduced for knowledge-driven to model the semantic knowledge association among sentence pairs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/co-driven-recognition-of-semantic-consistency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Infomin Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-infomin-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of infomin learning aims to learn a representation with high utility while being uninformative about a specified target, with the latter achieved by minimising the mutual information between the representation and the target.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-infomin-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecFNO: a resolution-invariant flow and heat field reconstruction method from sparse observations via Fourier neural operator</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recfno-a-resolution-invariant-flow-and-heat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The MLP embedding is propitious to more sparse input, while the others benefit from spatial information preservation and perform better with the increase of observation data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recfno-a-resolution-invariant-flow-and-heat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Escaping limit cycles: Global convergence for constrained nonconvex-nonconcave minimax problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-limit-cycles-global-convergence-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a new extragradient-type algorithm for a class of nonconvex-nonconcave minimax problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/escaping-limit-cycles-global-convergence-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Asymptotic Optimality: Sequential Unsupervised Regression of Density Ratio for Early Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-asymptotic-optimality-sequential</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Theoretically-inspired sequential density ratio estimation (SDRE) algorithms are proposed for the early classification of time series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-asymptotic-optimality-sequential</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nyström $M$-Hilbert-Schmidt Independence Criterion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nystrom-m-hilbert-schmidt-independence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to alleviate the quadratic computational bottleneck in large-scale applications, multiple HSIC approximations have been proposed, however these estimators are restricted to $M=2$ random variables, do not extend naturally to the $M\ge 2$ case, and lack theoretical guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nystrom-m-hilbert-schmidt-independence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Unbounded Machine Unlearning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unbounded-machine-unlearning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep machine unlearning is the problem of removing the influence of a cohort of data from the weights of a trained deep model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-unbounded-machine-unlearning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A DNN based Normalized Time-frequency Weighted Criterion for Robust Wideband DoA Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dnn-based-normalized-time-frequency</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the best-performing design of T-F weights is criterion-dependent in general.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-dnn-based-normalized-time-frequency</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can discrete information extraction prompts generalize across language models?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-discrete-information-extraction-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study whether automatically-induced prompts that effectively extract information from a language model can also be used, out-of-the-box, to probe other language models for the same information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-discrete-information-extraction-prompts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens before and after: Multi-Event Commonsense in Event Coreference Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-happens-before-and-after-multi-event</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event coreference models cluster event mentions pertaining to the same real-world event.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/what-happens-before-and-after-multi-event</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo Label-Guided Model Inversion Attack via Conditional Generative Adversarial Network</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-label-guided-model-inversion-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At first, a top-n selection strategy is proposed to provide pseudo-labels for public data, and use pseudo-labels to guide the training of the cGAN.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-label-guided-model-inversion-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiagent Inverse Reinforcement Learning via Theory of Mind Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiagent-inverse-reinforcement-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To understand how people interact with each other in collaborative settings, especially in situations where individuals know little about their teammates, Multiagent Inverse Reinforcement Learning (MIRL) aims to infer the reward functions guiding the behavior of each individual given trajectories of a team's behavior during task performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multiagent-inverse-reinforcement-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Sparse Gaussian Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sparse-gaussian-process</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Next, to make the model inference as simple as possible, we propose updating a single inducing point of the sparse GP model together with the remaining model parameters every time a new sample arrives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-sparse-gaussian-process</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving User Controlled Table-To-Text Generation Robustness</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-controlled-table-to-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work we study user controlled table-to-text generation where users explore the content in a table by selecting cells and reading a natural language description thereof automatically produce by a natural language generator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-user-controlled-table-to-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstration-Guided Reinforcement Learning with Efficient Exploration for Task Automation of Surgical Robot</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstration-guided-reinforcement-learning-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Task automation of surgical robot has the potentials to improve surgical efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstration-guided-reinforcement-learning-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Because Every Sensor Is Unique, so Is Every Pair: Handling Dynamicity in Traffic Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/because-every-sensor-is-unique-so-is-every</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further analysis also shows that each pair of sensors also has a unique dynamic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/because-every-sensor-is-unique-so-is-every</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-domain Compositing with Pretrained Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-compositing-with-pretrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have enabled high-quality, conditional image editing capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-compositing-with-pretrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composer: Creative and Controllable Image Synthesis with Composable Conditions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composer-creative-and-controllable-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent large-scale generative models learned on big data are capable of synthesizing incredible images yet suffer from limited controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/composer-creative-and-controllable-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iQPP: A Benchmark for Image Query Performance Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iqpp-a-benchmark-for-image-query-performance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To date, query performance prediction (QPP) in the context of content-based image retrieval remains a largely unexplored task, especially in the query-by-example scenario, where the query is an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iqpp-a-benchmark-for-image-query-performance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantastic Rewards and How to Tame Them: A Case Study on Reward Learning for Task-oriented Dialogue Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-rewards-and-how-to-tame-them-a-case</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior works mainly focus on adopting advanced RL techniques to train the ToD agents, while the design of the reward function is not well studied.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fantastic-rewards-and-how-to-tame-them-a-case</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation of DNN Based Data Detector for QPSK Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-of-dnn-based-data-detector-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this system, a deep learning based detector was proposed and implemented alongside the conventional method.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/implementation-of-dnn-based-data-detector-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metropolis Theorem and Its Applications in Single Image Detail Enhancement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metropolis-theorem-and-its-applications-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional image detail enhancement is local filter-based or global filter-based.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metropolis-theorem-and-its-applications-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Face Masks and Emotion Recognition from the Body: Insights from a Deep Learning Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-face-masks-and-emotion-recognition</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This face occlusion can strongly irritate emotional reading from the face and urges us to incorporate the whole body for emotion recognition, as it needs to play a more major role, despite its complementary nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/medical-face-masks-and-emotion-recognition</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take Me Home: Reversing Distribution Shifts using Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-me-home-reversing-distribution-shifts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To aid in our estimates of Wasserstein distance, we employ dimensionality reduction through orthonormal projection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/take-me-home-reversing-distribution-shifts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heterogeneous Social Event Detection via Hyperbolic Graph Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-social-event-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This model addresses the heterogeneity of social media, and, with this graph, the information in social media can be used to capture structural information based on the properties of hyperbolic space.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/heterogeneous-social-event-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incremental Few-Shot Object Detection via Simple Fine-Tuning Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-few-shot-object-detection-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we explore incremental few-shot object detection (iFSD), which incrementally learns novel classes using only a few examples without revisiting base classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-few-shot-object-detection-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Face Video Coding: A Generative Compression Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-face-video-coding-a-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel framework for Interactive Face Video Coding (IFVC), which allows humans to interact with the intrinsic visual representations instead of the signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interactive-face-video-coding-a-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Novel Collaborative Self-Supervised Learning Method for Radiomic Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-collaborative-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compared our proposed method with other state-of-the-art self-supervised learning methods on a simulation study and two independent datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-novel-collaborative-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian processes at the Helm(holtz): A more fluid model for ocean currents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-processes-at-the-helm-holtz-a-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Oceanographers are interested in predicting ocean currents and identifying divergences in a current vector field based on sparse observations of buoy velocities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-processes-at-the-helm-holtz-a-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTNet: Human Topology Aware Network for 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-human-topology-aware-network-for-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D human pose estimation errors would propagate along the human body topology and accumulate at the end joints of limbs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/htnet-human-topology-aware-network-for-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CMVAE: Causal Meta VAE for Unsupervised Meta-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmvae-causal-meta-vae-for-unsupervised-meta</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Unsupervised meta-learning aims to learn the meta knowledge from unlabeled data and rapidly adapt to novel tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cmvae-causal-meta-vae-for-unsupervised-meta</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
