<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 21:06:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Differential Privacy on Recommendation Accuracy and Popularity Bias</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-differential-privacy-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we study how DP impacts recommendation accuracy and popularity bias, when applied to the training data of state-of-the-art recommendation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-impact-of-differential-privacy-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved motif-scaffolding with SE(3) flow matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-motif-scaffolding-with-se-3-flow</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The first is motif amortization, in which FrameFlow is trained with the motif as input using a data augmentation strategy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improved-motif-scaffolding-with-se-3-flow</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Large-scale Empirical Study on Improving the Fairness of Deep Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-study-on-improving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we target the widely-used application scenario of image classification, and utilized three different datasets and five commonly-used performance metrics to assess in total 13 methods from diverse categories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-large-scale-empirical-study-on-improving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using reinforcement learning to improve drone-based inference of greenhouse gas fluxes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-reinforcement-learning-to-improve-drone</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate mapping of greenhouse gas fluxes at the Earth's surface is essential for the validation and calibration of climate models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-reinforcement-learning-to-improve-drone</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anatomy of Neural Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-of-neural-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative AI and transfer learning fields have experienced remarkable advancements in recent years especially in the domain of Natural Language Processing (NLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anatomy-of-neural-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>scDiffusion: conditional generation of high-quality single-cell data using diffusion model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scdiffusion-conditional-generation-of-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments showed that scDiffusion can generate single-cell gene expression data closely resembling real scRNA-seq data, surpassing state-of-the-art models in multiple metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scdiffusion-conditional-generation-of-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechAgents: Human-Communication Simulation with Multi-Modal Multi-Agent Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechagents-human-communication-simulation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose SpeechAgents, a multi-modal LLM based multi-agent system designed for simulating human communication.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechagents-human-communication-simulation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reproducibility Analysis and Enhancements for Multi-Aspect Dense Retriever with Aspect Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-analysis-and-enhancements-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[MADRAL was evaluated on proprietary data and its code was not released, making it challenging to validate its effectiveness on other datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reproducibility-analysis-and-enhancements-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextMachina: Seamless Generation of Machine-Generated Text Datasets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textmachina-seamless-generation-of-machine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have led to high-quality Machine-Generated Text (MGT), giving rise to countless new use cases and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/textmachina-seamless-generation-of-machine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Content-Based Novelty Measure for Scholarly Publications: A Proof of Concept</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-content-based-novelty-measure-for-scholarly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Novelty, akin to gene mutation in evolution, opens possibilities for scientific advancement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-content-based-novelty-measure-for-scholarly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty Quantification on Clinical Trial Outcome Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-on-clinical-trial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Selective classification, encompassing a spectrum of methods for uncertainty quantification, empowers the model to withhold decision-making in the face of samples marked by ambiguity or low confidence, thereby amplifying the accuracy of predictions for the instances it chooses to classify.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-quantification-on-clinical-trial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Efficient and Effective OpenQA Systems for Low-Resource Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-efficient-and-effective-openqa</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SQuAD-TR, a machine translation of SQuAD2. 0, and we build our OpenQA system by adapting ColBERT-QA for Turkish.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/building-efficient-and-effective-openqa</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Benchmarks for Optical Turbulence Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-benchmarks-for-optical-turbulence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Effective modeling of optical turbulence strength is critical for the development and deployment of these systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-benchmarks-for-optical-turbulence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See360: Novel Panoramic View Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/see360-novel-panoramic-view-interpolation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present See360, which is a versatile and efficient framework for 360 panoramic view interpolation using latent space viewpoint estimation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/see360-novel-panoramic-view-interpolation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiarizationLM: Speaker Diarization Post-Processing with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diarizationlm-speaker-diarization-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce DiarizationLM, a framework to leverage large language models (LLM) to post-process the outputs from a speaker diarization system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diarizationlm-speaker-diarization-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAPTAIN at COLIEE 2023: Efficient Methods for Legal Information Retrieval and Entailment Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/captain-at-coliee-2023-efficient-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Competition on Legal Information Extraction/Entailment (COLIEE) is held annually to encourage advancements in the automatic processing of legal texts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/captain-at-coliee-2023-efficient-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Transferability of Network Intrusion Detection in a Federated Learning Setup</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transferability-of-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Network Intrusion Detection Systems (IDS) aim to detect the presence of an intruder by analyzing network packets arriving at an internet connected device.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-transferability-of-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Modal Representation Learning for Molecular Property Prediction: Sequence, Graph, Geometry</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-representation-learning-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a novel data augmentation technique that modifies the topology of the molecular graph to generate augmented data with the same molecular connectivity index as the original data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-modal-representation-learning-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Global Prediction of COVID-19 Variant Emergence Using Dynamics-Informed Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-prediction-of-covid-19-variant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The current methods for predicting the spread of new variants rely on statistical modeling, however, these methods work only when the new variant has already arrived in the region of interest and has a significant prevalence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/global-prediction-of-covid-19-variant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedTGP: Trainable Global Prototypes with Adaptive-Margin-Enhanced Contrastive Learning for Data and Model Heterogeneity in Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedtgp-trainable-global-prototypes-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce the high communication cost of transmitting model parameters, a major challenge in HtFL, prototype-based HtFL methods are proposed to solely share class representatives, a. k. a, prototypes, among heterogeneous clients while maintaining the privacy of clients' models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedtgp-trainable-global-prototypes-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fair Sampling in Diffusion Models through Switching Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-sampling-in-diffusion-models-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have shown their effectiveness in generation tasks by well-approximating the underlying probability distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fair-sampling-in-diffusion-models-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dawn After the Dark: An Empirical Study on Factuality Hallucination in Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dawn-after-the-dark-an-empirical-study-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the LLM hallucination, three key questions should be well studied: how to detect hallucinations (detection), why do LLMs hallucinate (source), and what can be done to mitigate them (mitigation).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-dawn-after-the-dark-an-empirical-study-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picky Eaters Make For Better Raters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picky-eaters-make-for-better-raters</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It has been established in the literature that the number of ratings and the scores restaurants obtain on online rating systems (ORS) significantly impact their revenue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/picky-eaters-make-for-better-raters</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLLM-Protector: Ensuring MLLM's Safety without Hurting Performance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllm-protector-ensuring-mllm-s-safety-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The deployment of multimodal large language models (MLLMs) has brought forth a unique vulnerability: susceptibility to malicious attacks through visual inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mllm-protector-ensuring-mllm-s-safety-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identification of 4FGL uncertain sources at Higher Resolutions with Inverse Discrete Wavelet Transform</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-4fgl-uncertain-sources-at</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the forthcoming era of big astronomical data, it is a burden to find out target sources from ground-based and space-based telescopes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/identification-of-4fgl-uncertain-sources-at</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reading Between the Frames: Multi-Modal Depression Detection in Videos from Non-Verbal Cues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-between-the-frames-multi-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Depression, a prominent contributor to global disability, affects a substantial portion of the population.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reading-between-the-frames-multi-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Image Demoireing from Unpaired Real Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-image-demoireing-from-unpaired-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method, referred to as Unpaired Demoireing (UnDeM), synthesizes pseudo moire images from unpaired datasets, generating pairs with clean images for training demoireing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-image-demoireing-from-unpaired-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrisisViT: A Robust Vision Transformer for Crisis Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisisvit-a-robust-vision-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We leverage the new Incidents1M crisis image dataset to develop a range of new transformer-based image classification models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/crisisvit-a-robust-vision-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let's Get It Started: Fostering the Discoverability of New Releases on Deezer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-get-it-started-fostering-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents our recent initiatives to foster the discoverability of new releases on the music streaming service Deezer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/let-s-get-it-started-fostering-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Verifying Relational Explanations: A Probabilistic Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-relational-explanations-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Explanations on relational data are hard to verify since the explanation structures are more complex (e. g. graphs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/verifying-relational-explanations-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Vocabulary SAM: Segment and Recognize Twenty-thousand Classes Interactively</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-sam-segment-and-recognize</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The CLIP and Segment Anything Model (SAM) are remarkable vision foundation models (VFMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-sam-segment-and-recognize</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffBody: Diffusion-based Pose and Shape Editing of Human Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbody-diffusion-based-pose-and-shape</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Because this initial textured body model has artifacts due to occlusion and the inaccurate body shape, the rendered image undergoes a diffusion-based refinement, in which strong noise destroys body structure and identity whereas insufficient noise does not help.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbody-diffusion-based-pose-and-shape</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AST-T5: Structure-Aware Pretraining for Code Generation and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ast-t5-structure-aware-pretraining-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have made significant advancements in code-related tasks, yet many LLMs treat code as simple sequences, neglecting its structured nature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ast-t5-structure-aware-pretraining-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeFoMed: Parameter Efficient Fine-tuning on Multimodal Large Language Models for Medical Visual Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pefomed-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal large language models (MLLMs) represent an evolutionary expansion in the capabilities of traditional large language models, enabling them to tackle challenges that surpass the scope of purely text-based applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pefomed-parameter-efficient-fine-tuning-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FED-NeRF: Achieve High 3D Consistency and Temporal Coherence for Face Video Editing on Dynamic NeRF</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed-nerf-achieve-high-3d-consistency-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, achieving simultaneously multi-view consistency and temporal coherence while editing video sequences remains a formidable challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fed-nerf-achieve-high-3d-consistency-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dagma-DCE: Interpretable, Non-Parametric Differentiable Causal Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagma-dce-interpretable-non-parametric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Dagma-DCE, an interpretable and model-agnostic scheme for differentiable causal discovery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dagma-dce-interpretable-non-parametric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locally Adaptive Neural 3D Morphable Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-neural-3d-morphable-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Locally Adaptive Morphable Model (LAMM), a highly flexible Auto-Encoder (AE) framework for learning to generate and manipulate 3D meshes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/locally-adaptive-neural-3d-morphable-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AG-ReID.v2: Bridging Aerial and Ground Views for Person Re-identification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ag-reid-v2-bridging-aerial-and-ground-views</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we introduce AG-ReID. v2, a dataset specifically designed for person Re-ID in mixed aerial and ground scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ag-reid-v2-bridging-aerial-and-ground-views</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the numerical reliability of nonsmooth autodiff: a MaxPool case study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-numerical-reliability-of-nonsmooth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using SGD for the training process, we study the impact of different choices of the nonsmooth Jacobian for the MaxPool function on the precision of 16 and 32 bits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-numerical-reliability-of-nonsmooth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedNS: A Fast Sketching Newton-Type Algorithm for Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedns-a-fast-sketching-newton-type-algorithm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide convergence analysis based on statistical learning for the federated Newton sketch approaches.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedns-a-fast-sketching-newton-type-algorithm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Text Embedding Clustering Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/german-text-embedding-clustering-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work introduces a benchmark assessing the performance of clustering German text embeddings in different domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/german-text-embedding-clustering-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHGCN: Dynamic Hop Graph Convolution Network for Self-supervised Point Cloud Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhgcn-dynamic-hop-graph-convolution-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent works attempt to extend Graph Convolution Networks (GCNs) to point clouds for classification and segmentation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dhgcn-dynamic-hop-graph-convolution-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Credence: Augmenting Datacenter Switch Buffer Sharing with ML Predictions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credence-augmenting-datacenter-switch-buffer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This suggests that augmenting drop-tail algorithms with predictions about the future arrivals has the potential to significantly improve performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/credence-augmenting-datacenter-switch-buffer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing targeted transferability via feature space fine-tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-targeted-transferability-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Adversarial examples (AEs) have been extensively studied due to their potential for privacy protection and inspiring robust neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-targeted-transferability-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised hard Negative Augmentation for contrastive learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hard-negative-augmentation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Unsupervised hard Negative Augmentation (UNA), a method that generates synthetic negative instances based on the term frequency-inverse document frequency (TF-IDF) retrieval model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-hard-negative-augmentation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing 3D-Air Signature by Pen Tip Tail Trajectory Awareness: Dataset and Featuring by Novel Spatio-temporal CNN</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-3d-air-signature-by-pen-tip-tail</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We proposed SliT-CNN, a novel 2D spatial-temporal convolutional neural network (CNN) for better featuring of the air signature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-3d-air-signature-by-pen-tip-tail</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics and prevalence of fake social media profiles with AI-generated faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristics-and-prevalence-of-fake-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying this method to a random sample of active Twitter users, we estimate a lower bound for the prevalence of profiles using GAN-generated faces between 0. 021% and 0. 044% -- around 10K daily active accounts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/characteristics-and-prevalence-of-fake-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnetTSF: A Better Performance Linear Complexity Time Series Prediction Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unettsf-a-better-performance-linear</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Out of 32 testing projects, 31 achieved the best results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unettsf-a-better-performance-linear</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latte: Latent Diffusion Transformer for Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latte-latent-diffusion-transformer-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel Latent Diffusion Transformer, namely Latte, for video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latte-latent-diffusion-transformer-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling and Masking: A New Paradigm of Data Sampling for Image and Video Quality Assessment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-and-masking-a-new-paradigm-of-data</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, instead of stacking up models, a more elegant data sampling method (named as SAMA, scaling and masking) is explored, which compacts both the local and global content in a regular input size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-and-masking-a-new-paradigm-of-data</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
