<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 21:06:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Put Your Money Where Your Mouth Is: Evaluating Strategic Planning and Execution of LLM Agents in an Auction Arena</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-your-money-where-your-mouth-is-evaluating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, even our most advanced models (GPT-4) are occasionally surpassed by heuristic baselines and human agents, highlighting the potential for further improvements in the design of LLM agents and the important role that our simulation environment can play in further testing and refining agent architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/put-your-money-where-your-mouth-is-evaluating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate-sensitive Urban Planning through Optimization of Tree Placements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climate-sensitive-urban-planning-through</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show the efficacy of our approach across a wide spectrum of study areas and time scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/climate-sensitive-urban-planning-through</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language Model Beats Diffusion -- Tokenizer is Key to Visual Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-beats-diffusion-tokenizer-is</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Large Language Models (LLMs) are the dominant models for generative tasks in language, they do not perform as well as diffusion models on image and video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-model-beats-diffusion-tokenizer-is</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffCPS: Diffusion Model based Constrained Policy Search for Offline Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffcps-diffusion-model-based-constrained</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Constrained policy search (CPS) is a fundamental problem in offline reinforcement learning, which is generally solved by advantage weighted regression (AWR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffcps-diffusion-model-based-constrained</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AbCD: A Component-wise Adjustable Framework for Dynamic Optimization Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abcd-a-component-wise-adjustable-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using this framework, we investigate components that were proposed in several popular DOP algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/abcd-a-component-wise-adjustable-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast and Robust Early-Exiting Framework for Autoregressive Language Models with Synchronized Parallel Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-early-exiting-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle the high inference latency exhibited by autoregressive language models, previous studies have proposed an early-exiting framework that allocates adaptive computation paths for each token based on the complexity of generating the subsequent token.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-and-robust-early-exiting-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XAL: EXplainable Active Learning Makes Classifiers Better Low-resource Learners</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xal-explainable-active-learning-makes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During the selection of unlabeled data, we combine the predictive uncertainty of the encoder and the explanation score of the decoder to acquire informative data for annotation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/xal-explainable-active-learning-makes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Long-form Text Generation in Mental Health\\ with Task-adaptive Tokenization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-long-form-text-generation-in-mental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose task-adaptive tokenization as a way to adapt the generation pipeline to the specifics of a downstream task and enhance long-form generation in mental health.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-long-form-text-generation-in-mental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem-Solving Guide: Predicting the Algorithm Tags and Difficulty for Competitive Programming Problems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solving-guide-predicting-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, we also consider predicting the difficulty levels of algorithm problems, which can be used as useful guidance to calculate the required time to solve that problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/problem-solving-guide-predicting-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NEFTune: Noisy Embeddings Improve Instruction Finetuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neftune-noisy-embeddings-improve-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that language model finetuning can be improved, sometimes dramatically, with a simple augmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neftune-noisy-embeddings-improve-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larth: Dataset and Machine Translation for Etruscan</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larth-dataset-and-machine-translation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Etruscan is an ancient language spoken in Italy from the 7th century BC to the 1st century AD.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/larth-dataset-and-machine-translation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Closer Look into Automatic Evaluation Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-automatic-evaluation-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we analyze LLM evaluation (Chiang and Lee, 2023) and G-Eval (Liu et al., 2023), and we discuss how those details in the evaluation process change how well the ratings given by LLMs correlate with human ratings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-closer-look-into-automatic-evaluation-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Language Models with Human Preferences via a Bayesian Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For this alignment, current popular methods leverage a reinforcement learning (RL) approach with a reward model trained on feedback from humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffuSeq-v2: Bridging Discrete and Continuous Text Spaces for Accelerated Seq2Seq Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffuseq-v2-bridging-discrete-and-continuous</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models have gained prominence in generating high-quality sequences of text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffuseq-v2-bridging-discrete-and-continuous</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humanoid Agents: Platform for Simulating Human-like Generative Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanoid-agents-platform-for-simulating-human</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Just as computational simulations of atoms, molecules and cells have shaped the way we study the sciences, true-to-life simulations of human-like agents can be valuable tools for studying human behavior.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/humanoid-agents-platform-for-simulating-human</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Multi-modal Entity Alignment via Iteratively Fusing Modality Similarity Paths</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-multi-modal-entity-alignment-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The objective of Entity Alignment (EA) is to identify equivalent entity pairs from multiple Knowledge Graphs (KGs) and create a more comprehensive and unified KG.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/universal-multi-modal-entity-alignment-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Judge for Evaluating Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-judge-for-evaluating-alignment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The rapid development of Large Language Models (LLMs) has substantially expanded the range of tasks they can address.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-judge-for-evaluating-alignment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ParFam -- Symbolic Regression Based on Continuous Global Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parfam-symbolic-regression-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present our new method ParFam that utilizes parametric families of suitable symbolic functions to translate the discrete symbolic regression problem into a continuous one, resulting in a more straightforward setup compared to current state-of-the-art methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parfam-symbolic-regression-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentence-level Prompts Benefit Composed Image Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-level-prompts-benefit-composed-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Composed image retrieval (CIR) is the task of retrieving specific images by using a query that involves both a reference image and a relative caption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sentence-level-prompts-benefit-composed-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Optimal Timing Strategies for Time Series</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optimal-timing-strategies-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deciding the best future execution time is a critical task in many business activities while evolving time series forecasting, and optimal timing strategy provides such a solution, which is driven by observed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-optimal-timing-strategies-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query and Response Augmentation Cannot Help Out-of-domain Math Reasoning Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-and-response-augmentation-cannot-help</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we conduct an investigation for such data augmentation in math reasoning and are intended to answer: (1) What strategies of data augmentation are more effective; (2) What is the scaling relationship between the amount of augmented data and model performance; and (3) Can data augmentation incentivize generalization to out-of-domain mathematical reasoning tasks?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/query-and-response-augmentation-cannot-help</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphLLM: Boosting Graph Reasoning Ability of Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphllm-boosting-graph-reasoning-ability-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This synergy equips LLMs with the ability to proficiently interpret and reason on graph data, harnessing the superior expressive power of graph learning models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphllm-boosting-graph-reasoning-ability-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained Audio-Visual Joint Representations for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-audio-visual-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Audio-visual large language models (LLM) have drawn significant attention, yet the fine-grained combination of both input streams is rather under-explored, which is challenging but necessary for LLMs to understand general video inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fine-grained-audio-visual-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quantum Bayesian Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-bayesian-optimization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Various BO algorithms have been theoretically shown to enjoy upper bounds on their cumulative regret which are sub-linear in the number T of iterations, and a regret lower bound of Omega(sqrt(T)) has been derived which represents the unavoidable regrets for any classical BO algorithm.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quantum-bayesian-optimization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Cadenza Signal Processing Challenge: Improving Music for Those With a Hearing Loss</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-cadenza-signal-processing-challenge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Cadenza project aims to improve the audio quality of music for those who have a hearing loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-first-cadenza-signal-processing-challenge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal structure learning with momentum: Sampling distributions over Markov Equivalence Classes of DAGs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-structure-learning-with-momentum</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the context of inferring a Bayesian network structure (directed acyclic graph, DAG for short), we devise a non-reversible continuous time Markov chain, the "Causal Zig-Zag sampler", that targets a probability distribution over classes of observationally equivalent (Markov equivalent) DAGs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-structure-learning-with-momentum</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InterroLang: Exploring NLP Models and Datasets through Dialogue-based Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interrolang-exploring-nlp-models-and-datasets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While recently developed NLP explainability methods let us open the black box in various ways (Madsen et al., 2022), a missing ingredient in this endeavor is an interactive tool offering a conversational interface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interrolang-exploring-nlp-models-and-datasets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Scalable Meta Learning Practical</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-scalable-meta-learning-practical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite its flexibility to learn diverse inductive biases in machine learning programs, meta learning (i. e., learning to learn) has long been recognized to suffer from poor scalability due to its tremendous compute/memory costs, training instability, and a lack of efficient distributed training support.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/making-scalable-meta-learning-practical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchor-Intermediate Detector: Decoupling and Coupling Bounding Boxes for Accurate Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchor-intermediate-detector-decoupling-and-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The corner-aware head is able to score the corners of each bounding box to facilitate the coupling between corner points.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/anchor-intermediate-detector-decoupling-and-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Care3D: An Active 3D Object Detection Dataset of Real Robotic-Care Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care3d-an-active-3d-object-detection-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As labor shortage increases in the health sector, the demand for assistive robotics grows.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/care3d-an-active-3d-object-detection-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simple and Robust Framework for Cross-Modality Medical Image Segmentation applied to Vision Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-robust-framework-for-cross</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a simple framework to achieve fair image segmentation of multiple modalities using a single conditional model that adapts its normalization layers based on the input type, trained with non-registered interleaved mixed data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-simple-and-robust-framework-for-cross</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SocialCircle: Learning the Angle-based Social Interaction Representation for Pedestrian Trajectory Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialcircle-learning-the-angle-based-social</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Analyzing and forecasting trajectories of agents like pedestrians and cars in complex scenes has become more and more significant in many intelligent systems and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/socialcircle-learning-the-angle-based-social</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uni3DETR: Unified 3D Detection Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3detr-unified-3d-detection-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Uni3DETR, a unified 3D detector that addresses indoor and outdoor 3D detection within the same framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uni3detr-unified-3d-detection-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Large Language Models for Healthcare: from Data, Technology, and Applications to Accountability and Ethics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This shift encompasses a move from discriminative AI approaches to generative AI approaches, as well as a shift from model-centered methodologies to datacentered methodologies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mBBC: Exploring the Multilingual Maze</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbbc-exploring-the-multilingual-maze</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Using the self-supervised task of next token prediction, we assess their performance across a diverse set of languages, with a focus on understanding the impact of resource availability, word order, language family, and script type on model accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mbbc-exploring-the-multilingual-maze</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perceptual Artifacts Localization for Image Synthesis Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-artifacts-localization-for-image-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in deep generative models have facilitated the creation of photo-realistic images across various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perceptual-artifacts-localization-for-image-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Full-Convolutional Siamese Tracker</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-full-convolutional-siamese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, existing lightweight trackers only achieve balance between 2-3 points in terms of parameters, performance, Flops and FPS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightweight-full-convolutional-siamese</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ExIFFI and EIF+: Interpretability and Enhanced Generalizability to Extend the Extended Isolation Forest</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exiffi-and-eif-interpretability-and-enhanced</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we present ExIFFI, a novel approach that equips Extended Isolation Forest with interpretability features, specifically feature rankings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exiffi-and-eif-interpretability-and-enhanced</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZooPFL: Exploring Black-box Foundation Models for Personalized Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoopfl-exploring-black-box-foundation-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[When personalized federated learning (FL) meets large foundation models, new challenges arise from various limitations in resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zoopfl-exploring-black-box-foundation-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toolink: Linking Toolkit Creation and Using through Chain-of-Solving on Open-Source Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolink-linking-toolkit-creation-and-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first validate the efficacy of Toolink in harnessing the model's creativity and CoS ability on ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toolink-linking-toolkit-creation-and-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model (LLM) as a System of Multiple Expert Agents: An Approach to solve the Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus (ARC) Challenge</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-llm-as-a-system-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We attempt to solve the Abstraction and Reasoning Corpus (ARC) Challenge using Large Language Models (LLMs) as a system of multiple expert agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-llm-as-a-system-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiIns: A High-Quality Dataset for Controlled Text Editing by Natural Language Instruction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikiins-a-high-quality-dataset-for-controlled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study the problem of controlled text editing by natural language instruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wikiins-a-high-quality-dataset-for-controlled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OV-PARTS: Towards Open-Vocabulary Part Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-parts-towards-open-vocabulary-part</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Secondly, part segmentation introduces an open granularity challenge due to the diverse and often ambiguous definitions of parts in the open world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ov-parts-towards-open-vocabulary-part</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hieros: Hierarchical Imagination on Structured State Space Sequence World Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hieros-hierarchical-imagination-on-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Due to the special properties of S5 layers, our method can train in parallel and predict next world states iteratively during imagination.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hieros-hierarchical-imagination-on-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepQTest: Testing Autonomous Driving Systems with Reinforcement Learning and Real-world Weather Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepqtest-testing-autonomous-driving-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, existing ADS testing techniques have limited effectiveness in ensuring the realism of test scenarios, especially the realism of weather conditions and their changes over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepqtest-testing-autonomous-driving-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GSLB: The Graph Structure Learning Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gslb-the-graph-structure-learning-benchmark</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we systematically analyze the performance of GSL in different scenarios and develop a comprehensive Graph Structure Learning Benchmark (GSLB) curated from 20 diverse graph datasets and 16 distinct GSL algorithms.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gslb-the-graph-structure-learning-benchmark</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEAR: A GPU-Centric Experience Replay System for Large Reinforcement Learning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-a-gpu-centric-experience-replay-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces a distributed, GPU-centric experience replay system, GEAR, designed to perform scalable reinforcement learning (RL) with large sequence models (such as transformers).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gear-a-gpu-centric-experience-replay-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Data to Dialogue: Leveraging the Structure of Knowledge Graphs for Conversational Exploratory Search</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-data-to-dialogue-leveraging-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Exploratory search is an open-ended information retrieval process that aims at discovering knowledge about a topic or domain rather than searching for a specific answer or piece of information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/from-data-to-dialogue-leveraging-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOD: A Benchmark Dataset for Harmful Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hod-a-benchmark-dataset-for-harmful-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a new benchmark dataset for harmful object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hod-a-benchmark-dataset-for-harmful-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast-DetectGPT: Efficient Zero-Shot Detection of Machine-Generated Text via Conditional Probability Curvature</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-detectgpt-efficient-zero-shot-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have shown the ability to produce fluent and cogent content, presenting both productivity opportunities and societal risks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-detectgpt-efficient-zero-shot-detection</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
