<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 09:18:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>HARRIS: Hybrid Ranking and Regression Forests for Algorithm Selection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harris-hybrid-ranking-and-regression-forests</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is well known that different algorithms perform differently well on an instance of an algorithmic problem, motivating algorithm selection (AS): Given an instance of an algorithmic problem, which is the most suitable algorithm to solve it?]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harris-hybrid-ranking-and-regression-forests</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree Detection and Diameter Estimation Based on Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-detection-and-diameter-estimation-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tree perception is an essential building block toward autonomous forestry operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-detection-and-diameter-estimation-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-Time Attention for Sparse Rewards Multi-Agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-time-attention-for-sparse-rewards-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sparse and delayed rewards pose a challenge to single agent reinforcement learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-time-attention-for-sparse-rewards-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAD-RCNN:A Powerful Tool for Livestock Face Detection and Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lad-rcnn-a-powerful-tool-for-livestock-face</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, there is no study on normalizing of the animal face image with arbitrary directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lad-rcnn-a-powerful-tool-for-livestock-face</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Max Pooling with Vision Transformers reconciles class and shape in weakly supervised semantic segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/max-pooling-with-vision-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On the other hand, WSSS methods based on Vision Transformers (ViT) have not yet explored valid alternatives to CAM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/max-pooling-with-vision-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effective Cross-Task Transfer Learning for Explainable Natural Language Inference with T5</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-cross-task-transfer-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We compare sequential fine-tuning with a model for multi-task learning in the context where we are interested in boosting performance on two tasks, one of which depends on the other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/effective-cross-task-transfer-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 Ways to Bake a Cookie: Mapping the Landscape of Procedural Texts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/50-ways-to-bake-a-cookie-mapping-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The web is full of guidance on a wide variety of tasks, from changing the oil in your car to baking an apple pie.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/50-ways-to-bake-a-cookie-mapping-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PAGE: Prototype-Based Model-Level Explanations for Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/page-prototype-based-model-level-explanations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Aside from graph neural networks (GNNs) catching significant attention as a powerful framework revolutionizing graph representation learning, there has been an increasing demand for explaining GNN models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/page-prototype-based-model-level-explanations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoK: Modeling Explainability in Security Monitoring for Trust, Privacy, and Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-modeling-explainability-in-security</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Security operations centers have a number of security monitoring tools that analyze logs and generate threat alerts which security analysts inspect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sok-modeling-explainability-in-security</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do Charge Prediction Models Learn Legal Theory?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-charge-prediction-models-learn-legal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The charge prediction task aims to predict the charge for a case given its fact description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/do-charge-prediction-models-learn-legal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IITD at the WANLP 2022 Shared Task: Multilingual Multi-Granularity Network for Propaganda Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iitd-at-the-wanlp-2022-shared-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to finding the techniques, Subtask 2 further asks to identify the textual span for each instance of each technique that is present in the tweet; the task can be modeled as a sequence tagging problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/iitd-at-the-wanlp-2022-shared-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Temporal Generalization of Pre-trained Language Models with Lexical Semantic Change</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-temporal-generalization-of-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing methods mainly perform continual training to mitigate such a misalignment.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-temporal-generalization-of-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Optimize Permutation Flow Shop Scheduling via Graph-based Imitation Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-optimize-permutation-flow-shop</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the state-of-the-art reinforcement learning method, our model's network parameters are reduced to only 37\% of theirs, and the solution gap of our model towards the expert solutions decreases from 6. 8\% to 1. 3\% on average.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-optimize-permutation-flow-shop</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emotional Brain State Classification on fMRI Data Using Deep Residual and Convolutional Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-brain-state-classification-on-fmri</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We then developed two distinct Convolution-based approaches to decode emotional brain states using only spatial information from single, minimally pre-processed (slice timing and realignment) fMRI volumes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emotional-brain-state-classification-on-fmri</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPTQ: Accurate Post-Training Quantization for Generative Pre-trained Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptq-accurate-post-training-quantization-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Pre-trained Transformer (GPT) models set themselves apart through breakthrough performance across complex language modelling tasks, but also by their extremely high computational and storage costs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gptq-accurate-post-training-quantization-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Information Bottleneck: Learning Minimal Sufficient Unimodal and Multimodal Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-information-bottleneck-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce the multimodal information bottleneck (MIB), aiming to learn a powerful and sufficient multimodal representation that is free of redundancy and to filter out noisy information in unimodal representations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-information-bottleneck-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Text Classification with Self-Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-classification-with-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in large pretrained language models have increased attention to zero-shot text classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-classification-with-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unified Optimal Transport Framework for Universal Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-optimal-transport-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, UniOT is the first method with the capability to automatically discover and recognize private categories in the target domain for UniDA.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unified-optimal-transport-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Supervised Hierarchical Metrical Structure Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-hierarchical-metrical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel method to model hierarchical metrical structures for both symbolic music and audio signals in a self-supervised manner with minimal domain knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-hierarchical-metrical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Selection of the Optimal Strategy to Improve Precision and Power in Randomized Trials</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-selection-of-the-optimal-strategy-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Benkeser et al. demonstrate how adjustment for baseline covariates in randomized trials can meaningfully improve precision for a variety of outcome types, including binary, ordinal, and time-to-event.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adaptive-selection-of-the-optimal-strategy-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lipschitz regularized gradient flows and latent generative particles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipschitz-regularized-gradient-flows-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For empirical measures, the Lipschitz regularization on gradient flows induces a numerically stable transporter/discriminator particle algorithm, where the generative particles are transported along the gradient of the discriminator.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lipschitz-regularized-gradient-flows-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L-GreCo: An Efficient and General Framework for Layerwise-Adaptive Gradient Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-greco-an-efficient-and-general-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data-parallel distributed training of deep neural networks (DNN) has gained very widespread adoption, but can still experience communication bottlenecks due to gradient transmission.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-greco-an-efficient-and-general-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPS: Genetic Prompt Search for Efficient Few-shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gps-genetic-prompt-search-for-efficient-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prompt-based techniques have demostrated great potential for improving the few-shot generalization of pretrained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gps-genetic-prompt-search-for-efficient-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Open MatSci ML Toolkit: A Flexible Framework for Machine Learning in Materials Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-open-matsci-ml-toolkit-a-flexible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Open MatSci ML Toolkit: a flexible, self-contained, and scalable Python-based framework to apply deep learning models and methods on scientific data with a specific focus on materials science and the OpenCatalyst Dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-open-matsci-ml-toolkit-a-flexible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lila: A Unified Benchmark for Mathematical Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lila-a-unified-benchmark-for-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mathematical reasoning skills are essential for general-purpose intelligent systems to perform tasks from grocery shopping to climate modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lila-a-unified-benchmark-for-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reduce Catastrophic Forgetting of Dense Retrieval Training with Teleportation Negatives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-catastrophic-forgetting-of-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we investigate the instability in the standard dense retrieval training, which iterates between model training and hard negative selection using the being-trained model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reduce-catastrophic-forgetting-of-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleviating the Sample Selection Bias in Few-shot Learning by Removing Projection to the Centroid</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-the-sample-selection-bias-in-few</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we find that this problem usually occurs when the positions of support samples are in the vicinity of task centroid -- the mean of all class centroids in the task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alleviating-the-sample-selection-bias-in-few</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forget Embedding Layers: Representation Learning for Cold-start in Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-embedding-layers-representation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present FELRec, a large embedding network that refines the existing representations of users and items in a recursive manner, as new information becomes available.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forget-embedding-layers-representation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Swin U-Net: Cross-Contextual Attention Mechanism for Skin Lesion Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-swin-u-net-cross-contextual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that the classical concatenation operation utilized in the skip connection path can be further improved by incorporating an attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-swin-u-net-cross-contextual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpretable Geometric Deep Learning via Learnable Randomness Injection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-geometric-deep-learning-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LRI-induced models, once being trained, can detect the points in the point cloud data that carry information indicative of the prediction label.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpretable-geometric-deep-learning-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameter-Efficient Tuning Makes a Good Classification Head</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-tuning-makes-a-good</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we find that parameter-efficient tuning makes a good classification head, with which we can simply replace the randomly initialized heads for a stable performance gain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parameter-efficient-tuning-makes-a-good</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FI-ODE: Certified and Robust Forward Invariance in Neural ODEs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fi-ode-certified-and-robust-forward</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study how to certifiably enforce forward invariance properties in neural ODEs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fi-ode-certified-and-robust-forward</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlas: Automate Online Service Configuration in Network Slicing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atlas-automate-online-service-configuration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[First, we design a learning-based simulator to reduce the sim-to-real discrepancy, which is accomplished by a new parameter searching method based on Bayesian optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/atlas-automate-online-service-configuration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dataset Distillation via Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-via-factorization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we study \xw{dataset distillation (DD)}, from a novel perspective and introduce a \emph{dataset factorization} approach, termed \emph{HaBa}, which is a plug-and-play strategy portable to any existing DD baseline.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dataset-distillation-via-factorization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Bilingual Lexicon Induction with Cross-Encoder Reranking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-bilingual-lexicon-induction-with-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This crucial step is done via 1) creating a word similarity dataset, comprising positive word pairs (i. e., true translations) and hard negative pairs induced from the original CLWE space, and then 2) fine-tuning an mPLM (e. g., mBERT or XLM-R) in a cross-encoder manner to predict the similarity scores.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-bilingual-lexicon-induction-with-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Data Augmentation via Perspective Transition for Open-Domain Dialogues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-data-augmentation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dialogue data admits a wide variety of responses for a given dialogue history, especially responses with different semantics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-data-augmentation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Micro and Macro Level Graph Modeling for Graph Variational Auto-Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micro-and-macro-level-graph-modeling-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We utilize the micro-macro objective to improve graph generation with a GraphVAE, a well-established model based on graph-level latent variables, that provides fast training and generation time for medium-sized graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/micro-and-macro-level-graph-modeling-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Context-to-Vector with Graph Retrofitting to Improve Word Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-context-to-vector-with-graph-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although contextualized embeddings generated from large-scale pre-trained models perform well in many tasks, traditional static embeddings (e. g., Skip-gram, Word2Vec) still play an important role in low-resource and lightweight settings due to their low computational cost, ease of deployment, and stability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-context-to-vector-with-graph-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FatNet: High Resolution Kernels for Classification Using Fully Convolutional Optical Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatnet-high-resolution-kernels-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes the transformation of a traditional in-silico classification network into an optical fully convolutional neural network with high-resolution feature maps and kernels.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fatnet-high-resolution-kernels-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exemplar Guided Deep Neural Network for Spatial Transcriptomics Analysis of Gene Expression Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exemplar-guided-deep-neural-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an Exemplar Guided Network (EGN) to accurately and efficiently predict gene expression directly from each window of a tissue slide image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exemplar-guided-deep-neural-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitigating Unfairness via Evolutionary Multi-objective Ensemble Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-unfairness-via-evolutionary-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the literature of mitigating unfairness in machine learning, many fairness measures are designed to evaluate predictions of learning models and also utilised to guide the training of fair models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mitigating-unfairness-via-evolutionary-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Learning of Structured Representations via Closed-Loop Transcription</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-structured</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes an unsupervised method for learning a unified representation that serves both discriminative and generative purposes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-learning-of-structured</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CAD 3D Model classification by Graph Neural Networks: A new approach based on STEP format</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad-3d-model-classification-by-graph-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Among the various CAD formats, we consider the widely used STEP extension, which represents a standard for product manufacturing information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cad-3d-model-classification-by-graph-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Compare Nodes in Branch and Bound with Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compare-nodes-in-branch-and-bound</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Branch-and-bound approaches in integer programming require ordering portions of the space to explore next, a problem known as node comparison.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-compare-nodes-in-branch-and-bound</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QuEst: Graph Transformer for Quantum Circuit Reliability Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quest-graph-transformer-for-quantum-circuit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, the TorchQuantum library also supports using data-driven ML models to solve problems in quantum system research, such as predicting the impact of quantum noise on circuit fidelity and improving the quantum circuit compilation efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/quest-graph-transformer-for-quantum-circuit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time-rEversed diffusioN tEnsor Transformer: A new TENET of Few-Shot Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-reversed-diffusion-tensor-transformer-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address these drawbacks, we propose a Time-rEversed diffusioN tEnsor Transformer (TENET), which i) forms high-order tensor representations that capture multi-way feature occurrences that are highly discriminative, and ii) uses a transformer that dynamically extracts correlations between the query image and the entire support set, instead of a single average-pooled support embedding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/time-reversed-diffusion-tensor-transformer-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate, Discriminate and Contrast: A Semi-Supervised Sentence Representation Learning Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-discriminate-and-contrast-a-semi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Most sentence embedding techniques heavily rely on expensive human-annotated sentence pairs as the supervised signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generate-discriminate-and-contrast-a-semi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ViTASD: Robust Vision Transformer Baselines for Autism Spectrum Disorder Facial Diagnosis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitasd-robust-vision-transformer-baselines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research progress in the field of ASD facial analysis in pediatric patients has been hindered due to a lack of well-established baselines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vitasd-robust-vision-transformer-baselines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nonlinear Causal Discovery via Kernel Anchor Regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-causal-discovery-via-kernel-anchor</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Anchor regression has been developed to address this problem for a large class of causal graphical models, though the relationships between the variables are assumed to be linear.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nonlinear-causal-discovery-via-kernel-anchor</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model-Free Learning of Optimal Beamformers for Passive IRS-Assisted Sumrate Maximization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-learning-of-optimal-beamformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although Intelligent Reflective Surfaces (IRSs) are a cost-effective technology promising high spectral efficiency in future wireless networks, obtaining optimal IRS beamformers is a challenging problem with several practical limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-free-learning-of-optimal-beamformers</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
