<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 09:16:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Re4: Learning to Re-contrast, Re-attend, Re-construct for Multi-interest Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re4-learning-to-re-contrast-re-attend-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, Re4 encapsulates three backward flows, i. e., 1) Re-contrast, which drives each interest embedding to be distinct from other interests using contrastive learning; 2) Re-attend, which ensures the interest-item correlation estimation in the forward flow to be consistent with the criterion used in final recommendation; and 3) Re-construct, which ensures that each interest embedding can semantically reflect the information of representative items that relate to the corresponding interest.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/re4-learning-to-re-contrast-re-attend-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brain Topography Adaptive Network for Satisfaction Modeling in Interactive Information Access System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-topography-adaptive-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore the effectiveness of BTA for satisfaction modeling in two popular information access scenarios, i. e., search and recommendation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/brain-topography-adaptive-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paint2Pix: Interactive Painting based Progressive Image Synthesis and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint2pix-interactive-painting-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose a novel approach paint2pix, which learns to predict (and adapt) "what a user wants to draw" from rudimentary brushstroke inputs, by learning a mapping from the manifold of incomplete human paintings to their realistic renderings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint2pix-interactive-painting-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Conversational Short-phrase Speaker Diarization (CSSD) Task: Dataset, Evaluation Metric and Baselines</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-conversational-short-phrase-speaker</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the metric aspect, we design the new conversational DER (CDER) evaluation metric, which calculates the SD accuracy at the utterance level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-conversational-short-phrase-speaker</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme-scale Talking-Face Video Upsampling with Audio-Visual Priors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extreme-scale-talking-face-video-upsampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that when we process this $8\times8$ video with the right set of audio and image priors, we can obtain a full-length, $256\times256$ video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extreme-scale-talking-face-video-upsampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Learning with Deterministic Labeling and Large Margin Projection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-with-deterministic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The centrality and diversity of the labeled data are very influential to the performance of semi-supervised learning (SSL), but most SSL models select the labeled data randomly.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-learning-with-deterministic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Heads are Better than One: Robust Learning Meets Multi-branch Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-heads-are-better-than-one-robust-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to all methods that do not use additional data for training, our models achieve 67. 3% and 41. 5% robust accuracy on CIFAR-10 and CIFAR-100 (improving upon the state-of-the-art by +7. 23% and +9. 07%).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/two-heads-are-better-than-one-robust-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning Enabled Time-Lapse 3D Cell Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-enabled-time-lapse-3d-cell</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a method for time-lapse 3D cell analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-enabled-time-lapse-3d-cell</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoCapDeform: Monocular 3D Human Motion Capture in Deformable Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mocapdeform-monocular-3d-human-motion-capture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D human motion capture from monocular RGB images respecting interactions of a subject with complex and possibly deformable environments is a very challenging, ill-posed and under-explored problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mocapdeform-monocular-3d-human-motion-capture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-TransUNet: Temporally Blended Vision Transformer for CT VFSS Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-transunet-temporally-blended-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our findings suggest that the proposed model can indeed enhance the TransUNet architecture via exploiting temporal information and improving segmentation performance by a significant margin.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-transunet-temporally-blended-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Hybrid SFANC-FxNLMS Algorithm for Active Noise Control based on Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-sfanc-fxnlms-algorithm-for-active</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Owing to the effective combination of the two algorithms, experimental results show that the hybrid SFANC-FxNLMS algorithm can achieve a rapid response time, a low noise reduction error, and a high degree of robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-hybrid-sfanc-fxnlms-algorithm-for-active</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-segmentation of Hip Joints using MultiPlanar UNet with Transfer learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-segmentation-of-hip-joints-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Accurate geometry representation is essential in developing finite element models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/auto-segmentation-of-hip-joints-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal foundation models are better simulators of the human brain</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-foundation-models-are-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Further, from the perspective of neural encoding (based on our foundation model), we find that both visual and lingual encoders trained multimodally are more brain-like compared with unimodal ones.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-foundation-models-are-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning-Based Discrete Calibrated Survival Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-discrete-calibrated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep neural networks for survival prediction outper-form classical approaches in discrimination, which is the ordering of patients according to their time-of-event.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-learning-based-discrete-calibrated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which Factors Drive Open Access Publishing? A Springer Nature Case Study</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-factors-drive-open-access-publishing-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Employing statistical methods, we describe the relationship between authors affiliated with countries from different income levels, their choice of publishing (OA or closed access), and the citation impact of their papers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/which-factors-drive-open-access-publishing-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCN-Transformer Feature Fusion for Polyp Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcn-transformer-feature-fusion-for-polyp</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The resulting features from both branches are then fused for final prediction of a $h\times w$ segmentation map.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fcn-transformer-feature-fusion-for-polyp</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Incomplete Multi-view Clustering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, in practical applications, such as disease diagnosis, multimedia analysis, and recommendation system, it is common to observe that not all views of samples are available in many cases, which leads to the failure of the conventional multi-view clustering methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-incomplete-multi-view-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Scalable and Extensible Approach to Benchmarking NL2Code for 18 Programming Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-scalable-and-extensible-approach-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe a general approach for easily adding support for new benchmarks and languages to MultiPL-E.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-scalable-and-extensible-approach-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incremental 3D Scene Completion for Safe and Efficient Exploration Mapping and Planning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-3d-scene-completion-for-safe-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We further present an informative path planning method, leveraging the capabilities of our mapping approach and a novel scene-completion-aware information gain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/incremental-3d-scene-completion-for-safe-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-aware Structure Learning for Graph Topology-imbalance by Relieving Under-reaching and Over-squashing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-structure-learning-for-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Topology-imbalance is a graph-specific imbalance problem caused by the uneven topology positions of labeled nodes, which significantly damages the performance of GNNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-aware-structure-learning-for-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer Encoder for Social Science</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-encoder-for-social-science</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a compact pretrained deep neural network, Transformer Encoder for Social Science (TESS), explicitly designed to tackle text processing tasks in social science research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-encoder-for-social-science</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study on the Membership Inference Attack against Tabular Data Synthesis Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-membership</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We conduct experiments on 4 state-of-the-art tabular data synthesis models under two attack scenarios (i. e., one black-box and one white-box attack), and find that the membership inference attack can seriously jeopardize these models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-on-the-membership</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPA-1: Pretraining of Attention-based Deep Potential Model for Molecular Simulation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpa-1-pretraining-of-attention-based-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine learning assisted modeling of the inter-atomic potential energy surface (PES) is revolutionizing the field of molecular simulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpa-1-pretraining-of-attention-based-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mask and Reason: Pre-Training Knowledge Graph Transformers for Complex Logical Queries</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-and-reason-pre-training-knowledge-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present the Knowledge Graph Transformer (kgTransformer) with masked pre-training and fine-tuning strategies.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mask-and-reason-pre-training-knowledge-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised domain adaptation semantic segmentation of high-resolution remote sensing imagery with invariant domain-level context memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study proposes a novel unsupervised domain adaptation semantic segmentation network (MemoryAdaptNet) for the semantic segmentation of HRS imagery.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unsupervised-domain-adaptation-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novel algorithm to generate shortest edit script using Levenshtein distance algorithm</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-algorithm-to-generate-shortest-edit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[String similarity, longest common subsequence and shortest edit scripts are the triplets of problem that related to each other.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/novel-algorithm-to-generate-shortest-edit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal detection with dynamic programming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/signal-detection-with-dynamic-programming</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper studies the classical problem of detecting the locations of signal occurrences in a one-dimensional noisy measurement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/signal-detection-with-dynamic-programming</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Language-guided Semantic Style Transfer of 3D Indoor Scenes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-semantic-style-transfer-of-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the new problem of language-guided semantic style transfer of 3D indoor scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/language-guided-semantic-style-transfer-of-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CorpusBrain: Pre-train a Generative Retrieval Model for Knowledge-Intensive Language Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corpusbrain-pre-train-a-generative-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that a strong generative retrieval model can be learned with a set of adequately designed pre-training tasks, and be adopted to improve a variety of downstream KILT tasks with further fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/corpusbrain-pre-train-a-generative-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TexPrax: A Messaging Application for Ethical, Real-time Data Collection and Annotation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texprax-a-messaging-application-for-ethical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We evaluate TexPrax in a user-study with German factory employees who ask their colleagues for solutions on problems that arise during their daily work.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texprax-a-messaging-application-for-ethical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counterfactual Supervision-based Information Bottleneck for Out-of-Distribution Generalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-supervision-based-information</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Along this line, a recent study (Arjovsky et al., 2019) has made a first step and proposes a learning principle of information bottleneck based invariant risk minimization (IB-IRM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/counterfactual-supervision-based-information</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Discovery via Contrastive Learning for Weakly Supervised Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-discovery-via-contrastive-learning-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Weakly Supervised Object Detection (WSOD) is a task that detects objects in an image using a model trained only on image-level annotations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-discovery-via-contrastive-learning-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Estimating Appearance Models for Image Segmentation via Tensor Factorization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-appearance-models-for-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Image Segmentation is one of the core tasks in Computer Vision and solving it often depends on modeling the image appearance data via the color distributions of each it its constituent regions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/estimating-appearance-models-for-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Your Hair: Latent Optimization for Pose-Invariant Hairstyle Transfer via Local-Style-Aware Hair Alignment</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-your-hair-latent-optimization-for-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Editing hairstyle is unique and challenging due to the complexity and delicacy of hairstyle.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-your-hair-latent-optimization-for-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVS-Inspired Signal Degradation Network for Just Noticeable Difference Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvs-inspired-signal-degradation-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, they have a major drawback that the generated JND is assessed in the real-world signal domain instead of in the perceptual domain in the human brain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hvs-inspired-signal-degradation-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context-Aware Streaming Perception in Dynamic Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-streaming-perception-in-dynamic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These works evaluate accuracy offline, one image at a time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/context-aware-streaming-perception-in-dynamic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge-Injected Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-injected-federated-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning is an emerging technique for training models from decentralized data sets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-injected-federated-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncertainty-guided Source-free Domain Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-source-free-domain</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Source-free domain adaptation (SFDA) aims to adapt a classifier to an unlabelled target data set by only using a pre-trained source model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uncertainty-guided-source-free-domain</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRAGON: Decentralized Fault Tolerance in Edge Federations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragon-decentralized-fault-tolerance-in-edge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Edge Federation is a new computing paradigm that seamlessly interconnects the resources of multiple edge service providers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragon-decentralized-fault-tolerance-in-edge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training Latent Variable Models with Auto-encoding Variational Bayes: A Tutorial</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-latent-variable-models-with-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Auto-encoding Variational Bayes (AEVB) is a powerful and general algorithm for fitting latent variable models (a promising direction for unsupervised learning), and is well-known for training the Variational Auto-Encoder (VAE).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-latent-variable-models-with-auto</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-dimensional topological loss for cortical plate segmentation in fetal brain MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-topological-loss-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, CP growth and folding patterns are key indicator in the assessment of the brain development and maturation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-dimensional-topological-loss-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleFaceV: Face Video Generation via Decomposing and Recomposing Pretrained StyleGAN3</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylefacev-face-video-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, StyleFaceV is capable of generating realistic $1024\times1024$ face videos even without high-resolution training videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylefacev-face-video-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConTextual Mask Auto-Encoder for Dense Passage Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-mask-auto-encoder-for-dense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Dense passage retrieval aims to retrieve the relevant passages of a query from a large corpus based on dense representations (i. e., vectors) of the query and the passages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contextual-mask-auto-encoder-for-dense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning-Based Test Smell Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-based-test-smell-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Objective: We propose the design and experimentation of a novel test smell detection approach based on machine learning to detect four test smells.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/machine-learning-based-test-smell-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TRoVE: Transforming Road Scene Datasets into Photorealistic Virtual Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trove-transforming-road-scene-datasets-into</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show that using annotations and visual cues from existing datasets, we can facilitate automated multi-modal data generation, mimicking real scene properties with high-fidelity, along with mechanisms to diversify samples in a physically meaningful way.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/trove-transforming-road-scene-datasets-into</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A unifying partially-interpretable framework for neural network-based extreme quantile regression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unifying-partially-interpretable-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a new methodological framework for performing extreme quantile regression using artificial neutral networks, which are able to capture complex non-linear relationships and scale well to high-dimensional data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-unifying-partially-interpretable-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM.int8(): 8-bit Matrix Multiplication for Transformers at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-int8-8-bit-matrix-multiplication-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a procedure for Int8 matrix multiplication for feed-forward and attention projection layers in transformers, which cut the memory needed for inference by half while retaining full precision performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-int8-8-bit-matrix-multiplication-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pyramidal Predictive Network: A Model for Visual-frame Prediction Based on Predictive Coding Theory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramidal-predictive-network-a-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main innovation of our model is that the update frequency of neural units on each of the layer decreases with the increasing of network levels, which results in the model appears like a pyramid from the perspective of time dimension, so we call it the Pyramid Predictive Network (PPNet).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyramidal-predictive-network-a-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SynKB: Semantic Search for Synthetic Procedures</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synkb-semantic-search-for-synthetic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper we present SynKB, an open-source, automatically extracted knowledge base of chemical synthesis protocols.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/synkb-semantic-search-for-synthetic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Task-Oriented Dialogue Systems with Response Selection as an Auxiliary Task</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-task-oriented-dialogue-systems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The adoption of pre-trained language models in task-oriented dialogue systems has resulted in significant enhancements of their text generation abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-task-oriented-dialogue-systems-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
