<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 09:12:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Semiring-Weighted Earley Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-semiring-weighted-earley-parsing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper provides a reference description, in the form of a deduction system, of Earley's (1970) context-free parsing algorithm with various speed-ups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-semiring-weighted-earley-parsing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transfer Learning for the Efficient Detection of COVID-19 from Smartphone Audio Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-the-efficient-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The efficacy of this solution mainly depends on the performances of AI algorithms applied to the collected data and their possible implementation directly on the users' mobile devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transfer-learning-for-the-efficient-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computable Stability for Persistence Rank Function Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computable-stability-for-persistence-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we revisit the persistent homology rank function -- an invariant measure of ``shape" that was introduced before barcodes and persistence diagrams and captures the same information in a form that is more amenable to data and computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/computable-stability-for-persistence-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Disentangled Representations in Signed Directed Graphs without Social Assumptions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-disentangled-representations-in-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose DINES, a novel method for learning disentangled node representations in signed directed graphs without social assumptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-disentangled-representations-in-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLEURT Has Universal Translations: An Analysis of Automatic Metrics by Minimum Risk Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bleurt-has-universal-translations-an-analysis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we systematically analyze and compare various mainstream and cutting-edge automatic metrics from the perspective of their guidance for training machine translation systems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bleurt-has-universal-translations-an-analysis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALPCAH: Sample-wise Heteroscedastic PCA with Tail Singular Value Regularization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpcah-sample-wise-heteroscedastic-pca-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Other methods such as Weighted PCA (WPCA) assume the noise variances are known, which may be difficult to know in practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpcah-sample-wise-heteroscedastic-pca-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proto-CLIP: Vision-Language Prototypical Network for Few-Shot Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proto-clip-vision-language-prototypical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The two encoders are used to compute prototypes of image classes for classification.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/proto-clip-vision-language-prototypical</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecallM: An Architecture for Temporal Context Understanding and Question Answering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recallm-an-architecture-for-temporal-context</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ideal long-term memory mechanism for Large Language Model (LLM) based chatbots, would lay the foundation for continual learning, complex reasoning and allow sequential and temporal dependencies to be learnt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recallm-an-architecture-for-temporal-context</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Solve Tasks with Exploring Prior Behaviours</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-solve-tasks-with-exploring-prior</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method can endow agents with the ability to explore and acquire the required prior behaviours and then connect to the task-specific behaviours in the demonstration to solve sparse-reward tasks without requiring additional demonstration of the prior behaviours.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-solve-tasks-with-exploring-prior</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Censored Sampling of Diffusion Models Using 3 Minutes of Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censored-sampling-of-diffusion-models-using-3</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sometimes, however, a pre-trained diffusion model exhibits partial misalignment in the sense that the model can generate good images, but it sometimes outputs undesirable images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/censored-sampling-of-diffusion-models-using-3</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEO: Learning Efficient Orderings for Multiobjective Binary Decision Diagrams</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leo-learning-efficient-orderings-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show how the configuration space can be efficiently explored using black-box optimization, circumventing the curse of dimensionality (in the number of variables and objectives), and finding good orderings that reduce the PF enumeration time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/leo-learning-efficient-orderings-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Distilling Large Vision-Language Model with Out-of-Distribution Generalizability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-large-vision-language-model-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Model distillation, the process of creating smaller, faster models that maintain the performance of larger models, is a promising direction towards the solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/distilling-large-vision-language-model-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Curves for Heterogeneous Feature-Subsampled Ridge Ensembles</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-curves-for-heterogeneous-feature</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study an ensemble of linear predictors, each fit using ridge regression on a subset of the available features.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-curves-for-heterogeneous-feature</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KoRC: Knowledge oriented Reading Comprehension Benchmark for Deep Text Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/korc-knowledge-oriented-reading-comprehension</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these benchmarks have encountered two major limitations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/korc-knowledge-oriented-reading-comprehension</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused Transformer: Contrastive Training for Context Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-transformer-contrastive-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This novel approach enhances the structure of the (key, value) space, enabling an extension of the context length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-transformer-contrastive-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Role of Subgroup Separability in Group-Fair Medical Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-subgroup-separability-in-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate performance disparities in deep classifiers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-role-of-subgroup-separability-in-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Retrieval-Augmented Large Language Models via Data Importance Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-retrieval-augmented-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[There are exponentially many terms in the multilinear extension, and one key contribution of this paper is a polynomial time algorithm that computes exactly, given a retrieval-augmented model with an additive utility function and a validation set, the data importance of data points in the retrieval corpus using the multilinear extension of the model's utility function.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-retrieval-augmented-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Evaluation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-evaluation-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are gaining increasing popularity in both academia and industry, owing to their unprecedented performance in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-evaluation-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepOnto: A Python Package for Ontology Engineering with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeponto-a-python-package-for-ontology</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applying deep learning techniques, particularly language models (LMs), in ontology engineering has raised widespread attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deeponto-a-python-package-for-ontology</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generalizing Backpropagation for Gradient-Based Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-backpropagation-for-gradient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many popular feature-attribution methods for interpreting deep neural networks rely on computing the gradients of a model's output with respect to its inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generalizing-backpropagation-for-gradient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BaBE: Enhancing Fairness via Estimation of Latent Explaining Variables</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/babe-enhancing-fairness-via-estimation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We consider the problem of unfair discrimination between two groups and propose a pre-processing method to achieve fairness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/babe-enhancing-fairness-via-estimation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Through the Fairness Lens: Experimental Analysis and Evaluation of Entity Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/through-the-fairness-lens-experimental</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Entity matching (EM) is a challenging problem studied by different communities for over half a century.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/through-the-fairness-lens-experimental</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Domain Adaptation of Sentence Embeddings using Adapters</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-domain-adaptation-of-sentence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead, we only train a small number of additional parameters while keeping the weights of the underlying sentence embedding model fixed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-domain-adaptation-of-sentence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semi-supervised Domain Adaptive Medical Image Segmentation through Consistency Regularized Disentangled Contrastive Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptive-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we investigate relatively less explored semi-supervised domain adaptation (SSDA) for medical image segmentation, where access to a few labeled target samples can improve the adaptation performance substantially.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semi-supervised-domain-adaptive-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active Learning with Contrastive Pre-training for Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-contrastive-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Even though some prior works have focused on reducing the need for large amounts of labelled data using different unsupervised methods, another promising approach called active learning is barely explored in the context of FER.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/active-learning-with-contrastive-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Test-Time Adaptation against Distribution Shifts in Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-test-time-adaptation-against</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To implement this benchmark, we have developed a unified framework in PyTorch, which allows for consistent evaluation and comparison of the TTA methods across the different datasets and network architectures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/benchmarking-test-time-adaptation-against</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFSum: A Coarse-to-Fine Contribution Network for Multimodal Summarization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfsum-a-coarse-to-fine-contribution-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Therefore, we propose a novel Coarse-to-Fine contribution network for multimodal Summarization (CFSum) to consider different contributions of images for summarization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfsum-a-coarse-to-fine-contribution-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-supervised learning via inter-modal reconstruction and feature projection networks for label-efficient 3D-to-2D segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-via-inter-modal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, the proposed SSL method allows further improvement of this performance by up to 23%, and we show that the SSL is beneficial regardless of the network architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-supervised-learning-via-inter-modal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T-MARS: Improving Visual Representations by Circumventing Text Feature Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-mars-improving-visual-representations-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, naively removing all such data could also be wasteful, as it throws away images that contain visual features (in addition to overlapping text).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/t-mars-improving-visual-representations-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fourier-Net+: Leveraging Band-Limited Representation for Efficient 3D Medical Image Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-net-leveraging-band-limited</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Instead of directly predicting a full-resolution displacement field, our Fourier-Net learns a low-dimensional representation of the displacement field in the band-limited Fourier domain which our model-driven decoder converts to a full-resolution displacement field in the spatial domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fourier-net-leveraging-band-limited</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Zero-Shot Digital Human Quality Assessment through Text-Prompted Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-zero-shot-digital-human-quality</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this gap, we propose SJTU-H3D, a subjective quality assessment database specifically designed for full-body digital humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advancing-zero-shot-digital-human-quality</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards accurate instance segmentation in large-scale LiDAR point clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-instance-segmentation-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Panoptic segmentation is the combination of semantic and instance segmentation: assign the points in a 3D point cloud to semantic categories and partition them into distinct object instances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-accurate-instance-segmentation-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your spouse needs professional help: Determining the Contextual Appropriateness of Messages through Modeling Social Relationships</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-spouse-needs-professional-help</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a new dataset of contextually-situated judgments of appropriateness and show that large language models can readily incorporate relationship information to accurately identify appropriateness in a given context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/your-spouse-needs-professional-help</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Privacy-Preserving Walk in the Latent Space of Generative Models for Medical Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-privacy-preserving-walk-in-the-latent-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative Adversarial Networks (GANs) have demonstrated their ability to generate synthetic samples that match a target distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-privacy-preserving-walk-in-the-latent-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ContainerGym: A Real-World Reinforcement Learning Benchmark for Resource Allocation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/containergym-a-real-world-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is sufficiently versatile to evaluate reinforcement learning algorithms on any real-world problem that fits our resource allocation framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/containergym-a-real-world-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge Graph Self-Supervised Rationalization for Recommendation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By masking important knowledge with high rational scores, KGRec is trained to rebuild and highlight useful knowledge connections that serve as rationales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/knowledge-graph-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Known Reality: Exploiting Counterfactual Explanations for Medical Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-known-reality-exploiting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The results demonstrate the promising potential of counterfactual explanations to enhance trust and acceptance of AI-driven methods in clinical settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beyond-known-reality-exploiting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deductive Additivity for Planning of Natural Language Proofs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we evaluate whether embedding spaces exhibit a property we call deductive additivity: the sum of premise statement embeddings should be close to embeddings of conclusions based on those premises.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/natural-language-deduction-with-incomplete-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multilingual Controllable Transformer-Based Lexical Simplification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-controllable-transformer-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, further evaluation of our approach on the part of the recent TSAR-2022 multilingual LS shared-task dataset shows that our model performs competitively when compared with the participating systems for English LS and even outperforms the GPT-3 model on several metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multilingual-controllable-transformer-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modelling Spontaneous Firing Activity of the Motor Cortex in a Spiking Neural Network with Random and Local Connectivity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-spontaneous-firing-activity-of-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A local connectivity scheme was implemented to introduce more physiological plausibility to the cortex model, and the effect on the rates, distributions and irregularity of neuronal firing was compared to the original random connectivity method and experimental data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modelling-spontaneous-firing-activity-of-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety Shielding under Delayed Observation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-shielding-under-delayed-observation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose synthesis algorithms to compute \emph{delay-resilient shields} that guarantee safety under worst-case assumptions on the delays of the input signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/safety-shielding-under-delayed-observation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-Domain Hierarchical Event Schema Induction by Incremental Prompting and Verification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-domain-hierarchical-event-schema</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Event schemas are a form of world knowledge about the typical progression of events.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-domain-hierarchical-event-schema</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PULSAR at MEDIQA-Sum 2023: Large Language Models Augmented by Synthetic Dialogue Convert Patient Dialogues to Medical Records</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulsar-at-mediqa-sum-2023-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper describes PULSAR, our system submission at the ImageClef 2023 MediQA-Sum task on summarising patient-doctor dialogues into clinical records.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pulsar-at-mediqa-sum-2023-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAE-DFER: Efficient Masked Autoencoder for Self-supervised Dynamic Facial Expression Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mae-dfer-efficient-masked-autoencoder-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by recent unprecedented success of masked autoencoders (e. g., VideoMAE), this paper proposes MAE-DFER, a novel self-supervised method which leverages large-scale self-supervised pre-training on abundant unlabeled data to advance the development of DFER.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mae-dfer-efficient-masked-autoencoder-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flacuna: Unleashing the Problem Solving Power of Vicuna using FLAN Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flacuna-unleashing-the-problem-solving-power</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, despite being introduced four years ago, T5-based LLMs, such as FLAN-T5, continue to outperform the latest decoder-based LLMs, such as LLAMA and VICUNA, on tasks that require general problem-solving skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flacuna-unleashing-the-problem-solving-power</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DARE: Towards Robust Text Explanations in Biomedical and Healthcare Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dare-towards-robust-text-explanations-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This results in our DomainAdaptiveAREstimator (DARE) attribution robustness estimator, allowing us to properly characterize the domain-specific robustness of faithful explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dare-towards-robust-text-explanations-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Graph Contrastive Topic Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-topic-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on it, we propose the graph contrastive topic model (GCTM), which conducts graph contrastive learning (GCL) using informative positive and negative samples that are generated by the graph-based sampling strategy leveraging in-depth correlation and irrelevance among documents and words.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graph-contrastive-topic-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Discovery with Language Models as Imperfect Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-with-language-models-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Understanding the causal relationships that underlie a system is a fundamental prerequisite to accurate decision-making.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-discovery-with-language-models-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Speech Synthesis from MRI-Based Articulatory Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-speech-synthesis-from-mri-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, through a series of ablations, we show that the proposed MRI representation is more comprehensive than EMA and identify the most suitable MRI feature subset for articulatory synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-speech-synthesis-from-mri-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Prediction using Transformer Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoji-prediction-using-transformer-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We fine-tuned BERT on a large corpus of text containing both text and emojis to predict the most appropriate emoji for a given text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/emoji-prediction-using-transformer-models</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
