<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Latest (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 21:07:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>tntorch: Tensor Network Learning with PyTorch</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tntorch-tensor-network-learning-with-pytorch</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present tntorch, a tensor learning framework that supports multiple decompositions (including Candecomp/Parafac, Tucker, and Tensor Train) under a unified interface.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tntorch-tensor-network-learning-with-pytorch</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgical-VQA: Visual Question Answering in Surgical Scenes using Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqa-visual-question-answering-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This overload often limits their time answering questionnaires from patients, medical students or junior residents related to surgical procedures.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/surgical-vqa-visual-question-answering-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Type Clustering using Markov Directly-Follow Multigraph in Object-Centric Process Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-type-clustering-using-markov-directly</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This graph is used to calculate a similarity matrix for discovering clusters of similar case notions based on a threshold.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-type-clustering-using-markov-directly</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>reStructured Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restructured-pre-training</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, we test our model in the 2022 College Entrance Examination English that happened a few days ago (2022. 06. 08), and it gets a total score of 134 (v. s.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/restructured-pre-training</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoccerCPD: Formation and Role Change-Point Detection in Soccer Matches Using Spatiotemporal Tracking Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soccercpd-formation-and-role-change-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In fluid team sports such as soccer and basketball, analyzing team formation is one of the most intuitive ways to understand tactics from domain participants' point of view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soccercpd-formation-and-role-change-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid Physical Metric For 6-DoF Grasp Pose Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-physical-metric-for-6-dof-grasp-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[6-DoF grasp pose detection of multi-grasp and multi-object is a challenge task in the field of intelligent robot.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybrid-physical-metric-for-6-dof-grasp-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenXAI: Towards a Transparent Evaluation of Model Explanations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openxai-towards-a-transparent-evaluation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[OpenXAI comprises of the following key components: (i) a flexible synthetic data generator and a collection of diverse real-world datasets, pre-trained models, and state-of-the-art feature attribution methods, (ii) open-source implementations of twenty-two quantitative metrics for evaluating faithfulness, stability (robustness), and fairness of explanation methods, and (iii) the first ever public XAI leaderboards to benchmark explanations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openxai-towards-a-transparent-evaluation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-based Graph Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-based-graph-neural-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AgentNet is inspired by sublinear algorithms, featuring a computational complexity that is independent of the graph size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-based-graph-neural-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Vocabulary Object Detection with Proposal Mining and Prediction Equalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-object-detection-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open-vocabulary object detection (OVD) aims to scale up vocabulary size to detect objects of novel categories beyond the training vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-vocabulary-object-detection-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-LexSum: Real-World Summaries of Civil Rights Lawsuits at Multiple Granularities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-lexsum-real-world-summaries-of-civil</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advent of large language models, methods for abstractive summarization have made great strides, creating potential for use in applications to aid knowledge workers processing unwieldy document collections.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-lexsum-real-world-summaries-of-civil</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Langevin Monte Carlo for Contextual Bandits</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-monte-carlo-for-contextual-bandits</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing Thompson sampling-based algorithms need to construct a Laplace approximation (i. e., a Gaussian distribution) of the posterior distribution, which is inefficient to sample in high dimensional applications for general covariance matrices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/langevin-monte-carlo-for-contextual-bandits</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$\texttt{FedBC}$: Calibrating Global and Local Models via Federated Learning Beyond Consensus</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texttt-fedbc-calibrating-global-and-local</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In federated learning (FL), the objective of collaboratively learning a global model through aggregation of model updates across devices tends to oppose the goal of personalization via local information.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/texttt-fedbc-calibrating-global-and-local</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A view of mini-batch SGD via generating functions: conditions of convergence, phase transitions, benefit from negative momenta</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-view-of-mini-batch-sgd-via-generating</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Mini-batch SGD with momentum is a fundamental algorithm for learning large predictive models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-view-of-mini-batch-sgd-via-generating</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near-optimal control of dynamical systems with neural ordinary differential equations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-control-of-dynamical-systems</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimal control problems naturally arise in many scientific applications where one wishes to steer a dynamical system from a certain initial state $\mathbf{x}_0$ to a desired target state $\mathbf{x}^*$ in finite time $T$.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/near-optimal-control-of-dynamical-systems</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diagnostic Tool for Out-of-Sample Model Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnostic-tool-for-out-of-sample-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Assessment of model fitness is an important step in many problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diagnostic-tool-for-out-of-sample-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical Context Tagging for Utterance Rewriting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-tagging-for-utterance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[HCT (i) tags the source string with token-level edit actions and slotted rules and (ii) fills in the resulting rule slots with spans from the dialogue context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hierarchical-context-tagging-for-utterance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Emergent Lexicon Formation with a Self-Reinforcing Stochastic Process</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-emergent-lexicon-formation-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce FiLex, a self-reinforcing stochastic process which models finite lexicons in emergent language experiments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/modeling-emergent-lexicon-formation-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVoRT: Iterative Transformer for Slice-to-Volume Registration in Fetal Brain MRI</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svort-iterative-transformer-for-slice-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experiments with real-world MRI data are also performed to demonstrate the ability of the proposed model to improve the quality of 3D reconstruction under severe fetal motion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svort-iterative-transformer-for-slice-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bregman Power k-Means for Clustering Exponential Family Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bregman-power-k-means-for-clustering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in center-based clustering algorithms combats poor local minima by implicit annealing, using a family of generalized means.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bregman-power-k-means-for-clustering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S2TNet: Spatio-Temporal Transformer Networks for Trajectory Prediction in Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2tnet-spatio-temporal-transformer-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To safely and rationally participate in dense and heterogeneous traffic, autonomous vehicles require to sufficiently analyze the motion patterns of surrounding traffic-agents and accurately predict their future trajectories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/s2tnet-spatio-temporal-transformer-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecting a French Dictionary from the Beginning of the 20th Century to Wikidata</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-a-french-dictionary-from-the</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we describe a new lexical resource, where we connected all the dictionary entries of the history and geography part to current data sources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/connecting-a-french-dictionary-from-the</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DaisyRec 2.0: Benchmarking Recommendation for Rigorous Evaluation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daisyrec-2-0-benchmarking-recommendation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, one critical issue looms large in the field of recommender systems -- there are no effective benchmarks for rigorous evaluation -- which consequently leads to unreproducible evaluation and unfair comparison.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/daisyrec-2-0-benchmarking-recommendation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imitation Learning for Generalizable Self-driving Policy with Sim-to-real Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-learning-for-generalizable-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Imitation Learning uses the demonstrations of an expert to uncover the optimal policy and it is suitable for real-world robotics tasks as well.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitation-learning-for-generalizable-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpA-Former: Transformer image shadow detection and removal via spatial attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spa-former-transformer-image-shadow-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose an end-to-end SpA-Former to recover a shadow-free image from a single shaded image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/spa-former-transformer-image-shadow-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototypical Contrastive Language Image Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-contrastive-language-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show a representation grouping effect during this process: the InfoNCE objective indirectly groups semantically similar representations together via randomly emerged within-modal anchors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prototypical-contrastive-language-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Resolution, Multi-Horizon Distributed Solar PV Power Forecasting with Forecast Combinations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-multi-horizon-distributed</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a forecast combination approach based on particle swarm optimization (PSO) that will enable a forecaster to produce accurate forecasts for the task at hand by weighting the forecasts produced by individual models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-resolution-multi-horizon-distributed</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Transformers: Cloning $k$ modes with one stone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-transformers-cloning-k-modes-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present Behavior Transformer (BeT), a new technique to model unlabeled demonstration data with multiple modes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-transformers-cloning-k-modes-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Re-calibration based MIL for Whole Slide Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-re-calibration-based-mil-for-whole</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Whole slide image (WSI) classification is a fundamental task for the diagnosis and treatment of diseases; but, curation of accurate labels is time-consuming and limits the application of fully-supervised methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-re-calibration-based-mil-for-whole</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisFIS: Visual Feature Importance Supervision with Right-for-the-Right-Reason Objectives</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visfis-visual-feature-importance-supervision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that model FI supervision can meaningfully improve VQA model accuracy as well as performance on several Right-for-the-Right-Reason (RRR) metrics by optimizing for four key model objectives: (1) accurate predictions given limited but sufficient information (Sufficiency); (2) max-entropy predictions given no important information (Uncertainty); (3) invariance of predictions to changes in unimportant features (Invariance); and (4) alignment between model FI explanations and human FI explanations (Plausibility).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visfis-visual-feature-importance-supervision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polar Parametrization for Vision-based Surround-View 3D Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polar-parametrization-for-vision-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on Polar Parametrization, we propose a surround-view 3D DEtection TRansformer, named PolarDETR.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/polar-parametrization-for-vision-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>POGEMA: Partially Observable Grid Environment for Multiple Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pogema-partially-observable-grid-environment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce POGEMA (https://github. com/AIRI-Institute/pogema) a sandbox for challenging partially observable multi-agent pathfinding (PO-MAPF) problems .]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pogema-partially-observable-grid-environment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Symmetric Network with Spatial Relationship Modeling for Natural Language-based Vehicle Retrieval</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-network-with-spatial-relationship</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Natural language (NL) based vehicle retrieval aims to search specific vehicle given text description.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/symmetric-network-with-spatial-relationship</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust SDE-Based Variational Formulations for Solving Linear PDEs via Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sde-based-variational-formulations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The combination of Monte Carlo methods and deep learning has recently led to efficient algorithms for solving partial differential equations (PDEs) in high dimensions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-sde-based-variational-formulations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Propagation of Measurement and Model Uncertainties through Multiline TRL Calibration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagation-of-measurement-and-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed method is in accordance with the ISO Guide to the Expression of Uncertainty in Measurement (GUM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propagation-of-measurement-and-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformer-Based Multi-modal Proposal and Re-Rank for Wikipedia Image-Caption Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multi-modal-proposal-and-re</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the increased accessibility of web and online encyclopedias, the amount of data to manage is constantly increasing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformer-based-multi-modal-proposal-and-re</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vicinity Vision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vicinity-vision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this observation, we present a Vicinity Attention that introduces a locality bias to vision transformers with linear complexity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vicinity-vision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward Unpaired Multi-modal Medical Image Segmentation via Learning Structured Semantic Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unpaired-multi-modal-medical-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from previous methods which adopted both modality-specific and modality-shared modules to accommodate the appearance variance of different modalities while extracting the common semantic information, our method is based on a single Transformer with a carefully designed External Attention Module (EAM) to learn the structured semantic consistency (i. e. semantic class representations and their correlations) between modalities in the training phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/toward-unpaired-multi-modal-medical-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KTN: Knowledge Transfer Network for Learning Multi-person 2D-3D Correspondences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ktn-knowledge-transfer-network-for-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human densepose estimation, aiming at establishing dense correspondences between 2D pixels of human body and 3D human body template, is a key technique in enabling machines to have an understanding of people in images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ktn-knowledge-transfer-network-for-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EdgeNeXt: Efficiently Amalgamated CNN-Transformer Architecture for Mobile Vision Applications</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgenext-efficiently-amalgamated-cnn</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our EdgeNeXt model with 1. 3M parameters achieves 71. 2\% top-1 accuracy on ImageNet-1K, outperforming MobileViT with an absolute gain of 2. 2\% with 28\% reduction in FLOPs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edgenext-efficiently-amalgamated-cnn</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Continuous Rotation Canonicalization with Radial Beam Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-rotation-canonicalization</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inductive biases inherent to convolutional neural networks allow for translation equivariance through kernels acting parallely to the horizontal and vertical axes of the pixel grid.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-continuous-rotation-canonicalization</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitivity of Average Precision to Bounding Box Perturbations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-of-average-precision-to-bounding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Here, we quantify the sensitivity of AP to bounding box perturbations and show that AP is very sensitive to small translations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sensitivity-of-average-precision-to-bounding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position-prior Clustering-based Self-attention Module for Knee Cartilage Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-prior-clustering-based-self</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The morphological changes in knee cartilage (especially femoral and tibial cartilages) are closely related to the progression of knee osteoarthritis, which is expressed by magnetic resonance (MR) images and assessed on the cartilage segmentation results.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-prior-clustering-based-self</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using the Polar Transform for Efficient Deep Learning-Based Aorta Segmentation in CTA Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-polar-transform-for-efficient-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present a general approach to improving the semantic segmentation performance of neural networks in these tasks and validate our approach on the task of aorta segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/using-the-polar-transform-for-efficient-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Object Structural Points Representation for Graph-based Semantic Monocular Localization and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-structural-points-representation-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose the use of an efficient representation, based on structural points, for the geometry of objects to be used as landmarks in a monocular semantic SLAM system based on the pose-graph formulation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/object-structural-points-representation-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KE-RCNN: Unifying Knowledge based Reasoning into Part-level Attribute Parsing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ke-rcnn-unifying-knowledge-based-reasoning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this article, we propose a Knowledge Embedded RCNN (KE-RCNN) to identify attributes by leveraging rich knowledges, including implicit knowledge (e. g., the attribute ``above-the-hip'' for a shirt requires visual/geometry relations of shirt-hip) and explicit knowledge (e. g., the part of ``shorts'' cannot have the attribute of ``hoodie'' or ``lining'').]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ke-rcnn-unifying-knowledge-based-reasoning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EnvPool: A Highly Parallel Reinforcement Learning Environment Execution Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envpool-a-highly-parallel-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On a high-end machine, EnvPool achieves 1 million frames per second for the environment execution on Atari environments and 3 million frames per second on MuJoCo environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/envpool-a-highly-parallel-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Controllable Product Copywriting for E-Commerce</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-controllable-product-copywriting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Automatic product description generation for e-commerce has witnessed significant advancement in the past decade.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automatic-controllable-product-copywriting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Moving Horizon Estimation for Robust Flight Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-moving-horizon-estimation-for-robust</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Estimating and reacting to external disturbances is crucial for robust flight control of quadrotors.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-moving-horizon-estimation-for-robust</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predicting Parking Lot Availability by Graph-to-Sequence Model: A Case Study with SmartSantander</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-parking-lot-availability-by-graph</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nowadays, so as to improve services and urban areas livability, multiple smart city initiatives are being carried out throughout the world.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/predicting-parking-lot-availability-by-graph</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fluctuation-driven initialization for spiking neural network training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluctuation-driven-initialization-for-spiking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus fluctuation-driven initialization provides a practical, versatile, and easy-to-implement strategy for improving SNN training performance on diverse tasks in neuromorphic engineering and computational neuroscience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fluctuation-driven-initialization-for-spiking</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
