<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 21:08:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Open Deep Search: Democratizing Search with Open-source Reasoning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open Search Tool is a novel web search tool that outperforms proprietary counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TripoSG: High-Fidelity 3D Shape Synthesis using Large-Scale Rectified Flow Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triposg-high-fidelity-3d-shape-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose: 1) A large-scale rectified flow transformer for 3D shape generation, achieving state-of-the-art fidelity through training on extensive, high-quality data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triposg-high-fidelity-3d-shape-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easi3R: Estimating Disentangled Motion from DUSt3R Without Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easi3r-estimating-disentangled-motion-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advances in DUSt3R have enabled robust estimation of dense point clouds and camera parameters of static scenes, leveraging Transformer network architectures and direct supervision on large-scale 3D datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easi3r-estimating-disentangled-motion-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dolphin: A Large-Scale Automatic Speech Recognition Model for Eastern Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dolphin-a-large-scale-automatic-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report introduces Dolphin, a large-scale multilingual automatic speech recognition (ASR) model that extends the Whisper architecture to support a wider range of languages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dolphin-a-large-scale-automatic-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Agent: A Survey on Methodology, Applications and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-agent-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The era of intelligent agents is upon us, driven by revolutionary advancements in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-agent-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGGT: Visual Geometry Grounded Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present VGGT, a feed-forward neural network that directly infers all key 3D attributes of a scene, including camera parameters, point maps, depth maps, and 3D point tracks, from one, a few, or hundreds of its views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KBLaM: Knowledge Base augmented Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kblam-knowledge-base-augmented-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Knowledge Base augmented Language Model (KBLaM), a new method for augmenting Large Language Models (LLMs) with external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kblam-knowledge-base-augmented-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiniteYou: Flexible Photo Recrafting While Preserving Your Identity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving flexible and high-fidelity identity-preserved image generation remains formidable, particularly with advanced Diffusion Transformers (DiTs) like FLUX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPPO: Accelerating the Training of Group Relative Policy Optimization-Based Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cppo-accelerating-the-training-of-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Completion Pruning Policy Optimization (CPPO) to accelerate the training of reasoning models based on Group Relative Policy Optimization (GRPO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cppo-accelerating-the-training-of-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IndexTTS: An Industrial-Level Controllable and Efficient Zero-Shot Text-To-Speech System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indextts-an-industrial-level-controllable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, large language model (LLM) based text-to-speech (TTS) systems have gradually become the mainstream in the industry due to their high naturalness and powerful zero-shot voice cloning capabilities. Here, we introduce the IndexTTS system, which is mainly based on the XTTS and Tortoise model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indextts-an-industrial-level-controllable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-R1: Reinforcing Video Reasoning in MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-r1-reinforcing-video-reasoning-in-mllms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, directly applying RL training with the GRPO algorithm to video reasoning presents two primary challenges: (i) a lack of temporal modeling for video reasoning, and (ii) the scarcity of high-quality video-reasoning data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-r1-reinforcing-video-reasoning-in-mllms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuPAN: Direct Point Robot Navigation with End-to-End Model-based Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neupan-direct-point-robot-navigation-with-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents NeuPAN: a real-time, highly accurate, map-free, easy-to-deploy, and environment-invariant robot motion planner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neupan-direct-point-robot-navigation-with-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Multi-Choice Dialogue Commonsense Inference with Graph-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverse-multi-choice-dialogue-commonsense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proliferation of dialogic data across the Internet, the Dialogue Commonsense Multi-choice Question Answering (DC-MCQ) task has emerged as a response to the challenge of comprehending user queries and intentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverse-multi-choice-dialogue-commonsense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing the Reasoning Economy: A Survey of Efficient Reasoning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-reasoning-economy-a-survey-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in Large Language Models (LLMs) have significantly enhanced their ability to perform complex reasoning tasks, transitioning from fast and intuitive thinking (System 1) to slow and deep reasoning (System 2).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/harnessing-the-reasoning-economy-a-survey-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zep: A Temporal Knowledge Graph Architecture for Agent Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zep-a-temporal-knowledge-graph-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Zep, a novel memory layer service for AI agents that outperforms the current state-of-the-art system, MemGPT, in the Deep Memory Retrieval (DMR) benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zep-a-temporal-knowledge-graph-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHM: Large Animatable Human Reconstruction Model from a Single Image in Seconds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Animatable 3D human reconstruction from a single image is a challenging problem due to the ambiguity in decoupling geometry, appearance, and deformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Effect of Reinforcement Learning on Video Understanding: Insights from SEED-Bench-R1</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effect-of-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) inherit this reasoning potential but remain underexplored in tasks requiring both perception and logical reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-the-effect-of-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Stepsize for Diffusion Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-stepsize-for-diffusion-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models achieve remarkable generation quality but suffer from computational intensive sampling due to suboptimal step discretization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-stepsize-for-diffusion-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFG-Zero*: Improved Classifier-Free Guidance for Flow Matching Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfg-zero-improved-classifier-free-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classifier-Free Guidance (CFG) is a widely adopted technique in diffusion/flow models to improve image fidelity and controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfg-zero-improved-classifier-free-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free4D: Tuning-free 4D Scene Generation with Spatial-Temporal Consistency</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free4d-tuning-free-4d-scene-generation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Free4D, a novel tuning-free framework for 4D scene generation from a single image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free4d-tuning-free-4d-scene-generation-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
