<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 09:12:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pearl: A Production-ready Reinforcement Learning Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pearl-a-production-ready-reinforcement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Learning (RL) offers a versatile framework for achieving long-term goals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pearl-a-production-ready-reinforcement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mamba: Linear-Time Sequence Modeling with Selective State Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-linear-time-sequence-modeling-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Foundation models, now powering most of the exciting applications in deep learning, are almost universally based on the Transformer architecture and its core attention module.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mamba-linear-time-sequence-modeling-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An LLM Compiler for Parallel Function Calling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-llm-compiler-for-parallel-function-calling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLMCompiler automatically computes an optimized orchestration for the function calls and can be used with open-source models such as LLaMA-2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-llm-compiler-for-parallel-function-calling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DemoFusion: Democratising High-Resolution Image Generation With No $$$</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demofusion-democratising-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-resolution image generation with Generative Artificial Intelligence (GenAI) has immense potential but, due to the enormous capital investment required for training, it is increasingly centralised to a few large corporations, and hidden behind paywalls.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demofusion-democratising-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magicoder: Source Code Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicoder-source-code-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Magicoder models are trained on 75K synthetic instruction data using OSS-Instruct, a novel approach to enlightening LLMs with open-source code snippets to generate high-quality instruction data for code.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicoder-source-code-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-conditioned Image Generation via Generating Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-conditioned-image-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During generation, RCG samples from such representation distribution using a representation diffusion model (RDM), and employs a pixel generator to craft image pixels conditioned on the sampled representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-conditioned-image-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repurposing Diffusion-Based Image Generators for Monocular Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repurposing-diffusion-based-image-generators</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Monocular depth estimation is a fundamental computer vision task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/repurposing-diffusion-based-image-generators</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TaskWeaver: A Code-First Agent Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskweaver-a-code-first-agent-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[TaskWeaver provides support for rich data structures, flexible plugin usage, and dynamic plugin selection, and leverages LLM coding capabilities for complex logic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/taskweaver-a-code-first-agent-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Style Aligned Image Generation via Shared Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-aligned-image-generation-via-shared</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale Text-to-Image (T2I) models have rapidly gained prominence across creative fields, generating visually compelling outputs from textual prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/style-aligned-image-generation-via-shared</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PatchFusion: An End-to-End Tile-Based Framework for High-Resolution Monocular Metric Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchfusion-an-end-to-end-tile-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Single image depth estimation is a foundational task in computer vision and generative modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/patchfusion-an-end-to-end-tile-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-large-language-models-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in important tasks such as natural language understanding, language generation, and complex reasoning and have the potential to make a substantial impact on our society.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-large-language-models-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning and Prompting Everything All at Once for Universal Visual Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-and-prompting-everything-all-at-once</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, predominant paradigms, driven by casting instance-level tasks as an object-word alignment, bring heavy cross-modality interaction, which is not effective in prompting object detection and visual grounding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-and-prompting-everything-all-at-once</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaussian Head Avatar: Ultra High-fidelity Head Avatar via Dynamic Gaussians</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-head-avatar-ultra-high-fidelity-head</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Creating high-fidelity 3D head avatars has always been a research hotspot, but there remains a great challenge under lightweight sparse view setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaussian-head-avatar-ultra-high-fidelity-head</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sequential Modeling Enables Scalable Learning for Large Vision Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-modeling-enables-scalable-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel sequential modeling approach which enables learning a Large Vision Model (LVM) without making use of any linguistic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sequential-modeling-enables-scalable-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpha-CLIP: A CLIP Model Focusing on Wherever You Want</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpha-clip-a-clip-model-focusing-on-wherever</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Alpha-CLIP not only preserves the visual recognition ability of CLIP but also enables precise control over the emphasis of image contents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpha-clip-a-clip-model-focusing-on-wherever</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OneLLM: One Framework to Align All Modalities with Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onellm-one-framework-to-align-all-modalities</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In detail, we first train an image projection module to connect a vision encoder with LLM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/onellm-one-framework-to-align-all-modalities</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs Follow Simple Rules?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-follow-simple-rules</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Large Language Models (LLMs) are deployed with increasing real-world responsibilities, it is important to be able to specify and constrain the behavior of these systems in a reliable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-follow-simple-rules</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnimateZero: Video Diffusion Models are Zero-Shot Image Animators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatezero-video-diffusion-models-are-zero</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For appearance control, we borrow intermediate latents and their features from the text-to-image (T2I) generation for ensuring the generated first frame is equal to the given generated image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatezero-video-diffusion-models-are-zero</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlled Text Generation via Language Model Arithmetic</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-generation-via-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the framework allows for more precise control of generated text than direct prompting and prior controlled text generation (CTG) techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlled-text-generation-via-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pose Anything: A Graph-Based Approach for Category-Agnostic Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-anything-a-graph-based-approach-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach not only enables object pose generation based on arbitrary keypoint definitions but also significantly reduces the associated costs, paving the way for versatile and adaptable pose estimation applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pose-anything-a-graph-based-approach-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
