<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 09:12:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DiffBIR: Towards Blind Image Restoration with Generative Diffusion Prior</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbir-towards-blind-image-restoration-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DiffBIR, which leverages pretrained text-to-image diffusion models for blind image restoration problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffbir-towards-blind-image-restoration-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Communicative Agents for Software Development</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communicative-agents-for-software-development</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At the core of this paradigm lies ChatDev, a virtual chat-powered software development company that mirrors the established waterfall model, meticulously dividing the development process into four distinct chronological stages: designing, coding, testing, and documenting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/communicative-agents-for-software-development</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrate-Search-Predict: Composing retrieval and language models for knowledge-intensive NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstrate-search-predict-composing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented in-context learning has emerged as a powerful approach for addressing knowledge-intensive tasks using frozen language models (LM) and retrieval models (RM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstrate-search-predict-composing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Gaussian Splatting for Real-Time Radiance Field Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-gaussian-splatting-for-real-time-radiance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Radiance Field methods have recently revolutionized novel-view synthesis of scenes captured with multiple photos or videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-gaussian-splatting-for-real-time-radiance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentVerse: Facilitating Multi-Agent Collaboration and Exploring Emergent Behaviors in Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentverse-facilitating-multi-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Autonomous agents empowered by Large Language Models (LLMs) have undergone significant improvements, enabling them to generalize across a broad spectrum of tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agentverse-facilitating-multi-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Anything with Decoupled Video Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-anything-with-decoupled-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To 'track anything' without training on video data for every individual task, we develop a decoupled video segmentation approach (DEVA), composed of task-specific image-level segmentation and class/task-agnostic bi-directional temporal propagation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracking-anything-with-decoupled-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyGraft: Configurable Generation of Schemas and Knowledge Graphs at Your Fingertips</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-03685</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In some data-sensitive fields such as education or medicine, access to public datasets is even more limited.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2309-03685</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nougat: Neural Optical Understanding for Academic Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nougat-neural-optical-understanding-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific knowledge is predominantly stored in books and scientific journals, often in the form of PDFs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/nougat-neural-optical-understanding-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cognitive Architectures for Language Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-architectures-for-language-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent efforts have incorporated large language models (LLMs) with external resources (e. g., the Internet) or internal control flows (e. g., prompt chaining) for tasks requiring grounding or reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cognitive-architectures-for-language-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeGeeX: A Pre-Trained Model for Code Generation with Multilingual Evaluations on HumanEval-X</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegeex-a-pre-trained-model-for-code</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large pre-trained code generation models, such as OpenAI Codex, can generate syntax- and function-correct code, making the coding of programmers more productive and our pursuit of artificial general intelligence closer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegeex-a-pre-trained-model-for-code</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relay Diffusion: Unifying diffusion process across resolutions for image synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relay-diffusion-unifying-diffusion-process-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models achieved great success in image synthesis, but still face challenges in high-resolution generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/relay-diffusion-unifying-diffusion-process-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnimateDiff: Animate Your Personalized Text-to-Image Diffusion Models without Specific Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatediff-animate-your-personalized-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advance of text-to-image models (e. g., Stable Diffusion) and corresponding personalization techniques such as DreamBooth and LoRA, everyone can manifest their imagination into high-quality images at an affordable cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatediff-animate-your-personalized-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SAM-Med2D</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-med2d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To bridge this gap, we introduce SAM-Med2D, the most comprehensive studies on applying SAM to medical 2D images.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sam-med2d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extending Context Window of Large Language Models via Positional Interpolation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-context-window-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Position Interpolation (PI) that extends the context window sizes of RoPE-based pretrained LLMs such as LLaMA models to up to 32768 with minimal fine-tuning (within 1000 steps), while demonstrating strong empirical results on various tasks that require long context, including passkey retrieval, language modeling, and long document summarization from LLaMA 7B to 65B.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/extending-context-window-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-InvestAR: Enhancing Stock Investment Strategies through Annual Report Analysis with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-investar-enhancing-stock-investment</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper aims to simplify the process of assessing Annual Reports of all the firms by leveraging the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-investar-enhancing-stock-investment</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Direct Preference Optimization: Your Language Model is Secretly a Reward Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-preference-optimization-your-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, RLHF is a complex and often unstable procedure, first fitting a reward model that reflects the human preferences, and then fine-tuning the large unsupervised LM using reinforcement learning to maximize this estimated reward without drifting too far from the original model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/direct-preference-optimization-your-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharpness-Aware Minimization Revisited: Weighted Sharpness as a Regularization Term</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpness-aware-minimization-revisited</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep Neural Networks (DNNs) generalization is known to be closely related to the flatness of minima, leading to the development of Sharpness-Aware Minimization (SAM) for seeking flatter minima and better generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sharpness-aware-minimization-revisited</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ResFields: Residual Neural Fields for Spatiotemporal Signals</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural fields, a category of neural networks trained to represent high-frequency signals, have gained significant attention in recent years due to their impressive performance in modeling complex 3D data, especially large neural signed distance (SDFs) or radiance fields (NeRFs) via a single multi-layer perceptron (MLP).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/resfields-residual-neural-fields-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProPainter: Improving Propagation and Transformer for Video Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propainter-improving-propagation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also propose a mask-guided sparse video Transformer, which achieves high efficiency by discarding unnecessary and redundant tokens.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/propainter-improving-propagation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Explanation Methods for Multivariate Time Series Classification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-explanation-methods-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In many applications classification alone is not enough, we often need to classify but also understand what the model learns (e. g., why was a prediction given, based on what information in the data).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/evaluating-explanation-methods-for</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
