<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 21:09:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>TripoSG: High-Fidelity 3D Shape Synthesis using Large-Scale Rectified Flow Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triposg-high-fidelity-3d-shape-synthesis</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we propose: 1) A large-scale rectified flow transformer for 3D shape generation, achieving state-of-the-art fidelity through training on extensive, high-quality data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triposg-high-fidelity-3d-shape-synthesis</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiniteYou: Flexible Photo Recrafting While Preserving Your Identity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving flexible and high-fidelity identity-preserved image generation remains formidable, particularly with advanced Diffusion Transformers (DiTs) like FLUX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Deep Search: Democratizing Search with Open-source Reasoning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open Search Tool is a novel web search tool that outperforms proprietary counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse Multi-Choice Dialogue Commonsense Inference with Graph-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverse-multi-choice-dialogue-commonsense</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the proliferation of dialogic data across the Internet, the Dialogue Commonsense Multi-choice Question Answering (DC-MCQ) task has emerged as a response to the challenge of comprehending user queries and intentions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reverse-multi-choice-dialogue-commonsense</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGGT: Visual Geometry Grounded Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present VGGT, a feed-forward neural network that directly infers all key 3D attributes of a scene, including camera parameters, point maps, depth maps, and 3D point tracks, from one, a few, or hundreds of its views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFG-Zero*: Improved Classifier-Free Guidance for Flow Matching Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfg-zero-improved-classifier-free-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classifier-Free Guidance (CFG) is a widely adopted technique in diffusion/flow models to improve image fidelity and controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfg-zero-improved-classifier-free-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHM: Large Animatable Human Reconstruction Model from a Single Image in Seconds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Animatable 3D human reconstruction from a single image is a challenging problem due to the ambiguity in decoupling geometry, appearance, and deformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zep: A Temporal Knowledge Graph Architecture for Agent Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zep-a-temporal-knowledge-graph-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Zep, a novel memory layer service for AI agents that outperforms the current state-of-the-art system, MemGPT, in the Deep Memory Retrieval (DMR) benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zep-a-temporal-knowledge-graph-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning Enhanced LLMs: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-enhanced-llms-a-survey</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper surveys research in the rapidly growing field of enhancing large language models (LLMs) with reinforcement learning (RL), a technique that enables LLMs to improve their performance by receiving feedback in the form of rewards based on the quality of their outputs, allowing them to generate more accurate, coherent, and contextually appropriate responses.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-enhanced-llms-a-survey</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KBLaM: Knowledge Base augmented Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kblam-knowledge-base-augmented-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Knowledge Base augmented Language Model (KBLaM), a new method for augmenting Large Language Models (LLMs) with external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kblam-knowledge-base-augmented-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model Agent: A Survey on Methodology, Applications and Challenges</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-agent-a-survey-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The era of intelligent agents is upon us, driven by revolutionary advancements in large language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-agent-a-survey-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImageNet Classification with Deep Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagenet-classification-with-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We trained a large, deep convolutional neural network to classify the 1. 3 million high-resolution images in the LSVRC-2010 ImageNet training set into the 1000 different classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagenet-classification-with-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Stepsize for Diffusion Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-stepsize-for-diffusion-sampling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models achieve remarkable generation quality but suffer from computational intensive sampling due to suboptimal step discretization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optimal-stepsize-for-diffusion-sampling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IndexTTS: An Industrial-Level Controllable and Efficient Zero-Shot Text-To-Speech System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indextts-an-industrial-level-controllable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, large language model (LLM) based text-to-speech (TTS) systems have gradually become the mainstream in the industry due to their high naturalness and powerful zero-shot voice cloning capabilities. Here, we introduce the IndexTTS system, which is mainly based on the XTTS and Tortoise model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indextts-an-industrial-level-controllable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video-R1: Reinforcing Video Reasoning in MLLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-r1-reinforcing-video-reasoning-in-mllms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, directly applying RL training with the GRPO algorithm to video reasoning presents two primary challenges: (i) a lack of temporal modeling for video reasoning, and (ii) the scarcity of high-quality video-reasoning data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-r1-reinforcing-video-reasoning-in-mllms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CPPO: Accelerating the Training of Group Relative Policy Optimization-Based Reasoning Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cppo-accelerating-the-training-of-group</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces Completion Pruning Policy Optimization (CPPO) to accelerate the training of reasoning models based on Group Relative Policy Optimization (GRPO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cppo-accelerating-the-training-of-group</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fin-R1: A Large Language Model for Financial Reasoning through Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fin-r1-a-large-language-model-for-financial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reasoning large language models are rapidly evolving across various domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fin-r1-a-large-language-model-for-financial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEC: Fast Euclidean Clustering for Point Cloud Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fec-fast-euclidean-clustering-for-point-cloud</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segmentation from point cloud data is essential in many applications such as remote sensing, mobile robots, or autonomous cars.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fec-fast-euclidean-clustering-for-point-cloud</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rankify: A Comprehensive Python Toolkit for Retrieval, Re-Ranking, and Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankify-a-comprehensive-python-toolkit-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval, re-ranking, and retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) are critical components of modern applications in information retrieval, question answering, or knowledge-based text generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rankify-a-comprehensive-python-toolkit-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniCheck: Efficient Fact-Checking of LLMs on Grounding Documents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicheck-efficient-fact-checking-of-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release LLM-AggreFact, code for data synthesis, and models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicheck-efficient-fact-checking-of-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
