<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 09:10:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Llama 2: Open Foundation and Fine-Tuned Chat Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop and release Llama 2, a collection of pretrained and fine-tuned large language models (LLMs) ranging in scale from 7 billion to 70 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-2-open-foundation-and-fine-tuned-chat</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FABRIC: Personalizing Diffusion Models with Iterative Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fabric-personalizing-diffusion-models-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In an era where visual content generation is increasingly driven by machine learning, the integration of human feedback into generative models presents significant opportunities for enhancing user experience and output quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fabric-personalizing-diffusion-models-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How is ChatGPT's behavior changing over time?</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-is-chatgpt-s-behavior-changing-over-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that the performance and behavior of both GPT-3. 5 and GPT-4 can vary greatly over time.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/how-is-chatgpt-s-behavior-changing-over-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta-Transformer: A Unified Framework for Multimodal Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-transformer-a-unified-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal learning aims to build models that can process and relate information from multiple modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/meta-transformer-a-unified-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AnimateDiff: Animate Your Personalized Text-to-Image Diffusion Models without Specific Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatediff-animate-your-personalized-text-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the advance of text-to-image models (e. g., Stable Diffusion) and corresponding personalization techniques such as DreamBooth and LoRA, everyone can manifest their imagination into high-quality images at an affordable cost.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/animatediff-animate-your-personalized-text-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic-SAM: Segment and Recognize Anything at Any Granularity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-sam-segment-and-recognize-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Semantic-SAM, a universal image segmentation model to enable segment and recognize anything at any desired granularity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/semantic-sam-segment-and-recognize-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petals: Collaborative Inference and Fine-tuning of Large Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/petals-collaborative-inference-and-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, these techniques have innate limitations: offloading is too slow for interactive inference, while APIs are not flexible enough for research that requires access to weights, attention or logits.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/petals-collaborative-inference-and-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CoTracker: It is Better to Track Together</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cotracker-it-is-better-to-track-together</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we thus propose CoTracker, an architecture that jointly tracks multiple points throughout an entire video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cotracker-it-is-better-to-track-together</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashAttention-2: Faster Attention with Better Parallelism and Work Partitioning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashattention-2-faster-attention-with-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the inefficiency is due to suboptimal work partitioning between different thread blocks and warps on the GPU, causing either low-occupancy or unnecessary shared memory reads/writes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flashattention-2-faster-attention-with-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLASK: Fine-grained Language Model Evaluation based on Alignment Skill Sets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flask-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce FLASK (Fine-grained Language Model Evaluation based on Alignment SKill Sets), a fine-grained evaluation protocol that can be used for both model-based and human-based evaluation which decomposes coarse-level scoring to an instance-wise skill set-level.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flask-fine-grained-language-model-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Diffusion Prior for Real-World Image Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-diffusion-prior-for-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel approach to leverage prior knowledge encapsulated in pre-trained text-to-image diffusion models for blind super-resolution (SR).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploiting-diffusion-prior-for-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metric3D: Towards Zero-shot Metric 3D Prediction from A Single Image</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric3d-towards-zero-shot-metric-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[State-of-the-art (SOTA) monocular metric depth estimation methods can only handle a single camera model and are unable to perform mixed-data training due to the metric ambiguity.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/metric3d-towards-zero-shot-metric-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNOS: A Strong Baseline for CAD-based Novel Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnos-a-strong-baseline-for-cad-based-novel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a simple three-stage approach to segment unseen objects in RGB images using their CAD models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cnos-a-strong-baseline-for-cad-based-novel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planting a SEED of Vision in Large Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planting-a-seed-of-vision-in-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Research on image tokenizers has previously reached an impasse, as frameworks employing quantized visual tokens have lost prominence due to subpar performance and convergence in multimodal comprehension (compared to BLIP-2, etc.)]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/planting-a-seed-of-vision-in-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Video Depth Stabilizer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-video-depth-stabilizer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video depth estimation aims to infer temporally consistent depth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-video-depth-stabilizer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>h2oGPT: Democratizing Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2ogpt-democratizing-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applications built on top of Large Language Models (LLMs) such as GPT-4 represent a revolution in AI due to their human-level capabilities in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2ogpt-democratizing-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L-Eval: Instituting Standardized Evaluation for Long Context Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-eval-instituting-standardized-evaluation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, there has been growing interest in extending the context length of instruction-following models in order to effectively process single-turn long input (e. g. summarizing a paper) and conversations with more extensive histories.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/l-eval-instituting-standardized-evaluation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dominant text generation models compose the output by sequentially selecting words from a fixed vocabulary.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/copy-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Approximations of Complete Interatomic Potentials for Crystal Property Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-approximations-of-complete</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is enabled by our approximations of infinite potential summations with provable error bounds.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-approximations-of-complete</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence for Science in Quantum, Atomistic, and Continuum Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-for-science-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Advances in artificial intelligence (AI) are fueling a new paradigm of discoveries in natural sciences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/artificial-intelligence-for-science-in</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
