<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 09:13:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>VToonify: Controllable High-Resolution Portrait Video Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although a series of successful portrait image toonification models built upon the powerful StyleGAN have been proposed, these image-oriented methods have obvious limitations when applied to videos, such as the fixed frame size, the requirement of face alignment, missing non-facial details and temporal inconsistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Blind Face Restoration with Codebook Lookup Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-blind-face-restoration-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate that a learned discrete codebook prior in a small proxy space largely reduces the uncertainty and ambiguity of restoration mapping by casting blind face restoration as a code prediction task, while providing rich visual atoms for generating high-quality faces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-blind-face-restoration-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo Numerical Methods for Diffusion Models on Manifolds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-numerical-methods-for-diffusion-models-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under such a perspective, we propose pseudo numerical methods for diffusion models (PNDMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-numerical-methods-for-diffusion-models-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing BERT for Convolutional Networks: Sparse and Hierarchical Masked Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-bert-for-convolutional-networks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is the first use of sparse convolution for 2D masked modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/designing-bert-for-convolutional-networks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAMO-YOLO : A Report on Real-Time Object Detection Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-yolo-a-report-on-real-time-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present a fast and accurate object detection method dubbed DAMO-YOLO, which achieves higher performance than the state-of-the-art YOLO series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-yolo-a-report-on-real-time-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mindcv</title>
      <link>https://github.com/mindspore-ecosystem/mindcv</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A toolbox of vision models and algorithms based on MindSpore]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/mindspore-ecosystem/mindcv</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utilizing supervised models to infer consensus labels and their quality from data with multiple annotators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-supervised-models-to-infer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Many algorithms also rely solely on annotator statistics, ignoring the features of the examples from which the annotations derive.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/utilizing-supervised-models-to-infer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracr: Compiled Transformers as a Laboratory for Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracr-compiled-transformers-as-a-laboratory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interpretability research aims to build tools for understanding machine learning (ML) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tracr-compiled-transformers-as-a-laboratory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BEAT: A Large-Scale Semantic and Emotional Multi-Modal Dataset for Conversational Gestures Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beat-a-large-scale-semantic-and-emotional</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving realistic, vivid, and human-like synthesized conversational gestures conditioned on multi-modal data is still an unsolved problem due to the lack of available datasets, models and standard evaluation metrics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/beat-a-large-scale-semantic-and-emotional</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ImMesh: An Immediate LiDAR Localization and Meshing Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immesh-an-immediate-lidar-localization-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This voxel-wise meshing operation is delicately designed for the purpose of efficiency; it first performs a dimension reduction by projecting 3D points to a 2D local plane contained in the voxel, and then executes the meshing operation with pull, commit and push steps for incremental reconstruction of triangle facets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/immesh-an-immediate-lidar-localization-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepMatcher: A Deep Transformer-based Network for Robust and Accurate Local Feature Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmatcher-a-deep-transformer-based-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose DeepMatcher, a deep Transformer-based network built upon our investigation of local feature matching in detector-free methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepmatcher-a-deep-transformer-based-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EDICT: Exact Diffusion Inversion via Coupled Transformations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edict-exact-diffusion-inversion-via-coupled</link>
      <description><![CDATA[EDICT enables mathematically exact inversion of real and model-generated images by maintaining two coupled noise vectors which are used to invert each other in an alternating fashion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/edict-exact-diffusion-inversion-via-coupled</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instant Neural Graphics Primitives with a Multiresolution Hash Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instant-neural-graphics-primitives-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural graphics primitives, parameterized by fully connected neural networks, can be costly to train and evaluate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instant-neural-graphics-primitives-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muse: Text-To-Image Generation via Masked Generative Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muse-text-to-image-generation-via-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to pixel-space diffusion models, such as Imagen and DALL-E 2, Muse is significantly more efficient due to the use of discrete tokens and requiring fewer sampling iterations; compared to autoregressive models, such as Parti, Muse is more efficient due to the use of parallel decoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muse-text-to-image-generation-via-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ankh: Optimized Protein Language Model Unlocks General-Purpose Modelling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ankh-optimized-protein-language-model-unlocks</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As opposed to scaling-up protein language models (PLMs), we seek improving performance via protein-specific optimization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ankh-optimized-protein-language-model-unlocks</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RTMDet: An Empirical Study of Designing Real-Time Object Detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmdet-an-empirical-study-of-designing-real</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to design an efficient real-time object detector that exceeds the YOLO series and is easily extensible for many object recognition tasks such as instance segmentation and rotated object detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rtmdet-an-empirical-study-of-designing-real</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmoothNet: A Plug-and-Play Network for Refining Human Poses in Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothnet-a-plug-and-play-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With a simple yet effective motion-aware fully-connected network, SmoothNet improves the temporal smoothness of existing pose estimators significantly and enhances the estimation accuracy of those challenging frames as a side-effect.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothnet-a-plug-and-play-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triton: An Intermediate Language and Compiler for Tiled Neural Network Computations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triton-an-intermediate-language-and-compiler</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The validation and deployment of novel research ideas in the field of Deep Learning is often limited by the availability of efficient compute kernels for certain basic primitives.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triton-an-intermediate-language-and-compiler</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free-Form Image Inpainting with Gated Convolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-form-image-inpainting-with-gated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a generative image inpainting system to complete images with free-form mask and guidance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/free-form-image-inpainting-with-gated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Fidelity Neural Audio Compression</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-neural-audio-compression</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a state-of-the-art real-time, high-fidelity, audio codec leveraging neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-fidelity-neural-audio-compression</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
