<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 21:06:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Eureka: Human-Level Reward Design via Coding Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eureka-human-level-reward-design-via-coding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The generality of Eureka also enables a new gradient-free in-context learning approach to reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF), readily incorporating human inputs to improve the quality and the safety of the generated rewards without model updating.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/eureka-human-level-reward-design-via-coding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAgents: An Open Platform for Language Agents in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagents-an-open-platform-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language agents show potential in being capable of utilizing natural language for varied and intricate tasks in diverse environments, particularly when built upon large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openagents-an-open-platform-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgentTuning: Enabling Generalized Agent Abilities for LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agenttuning-enabling-generalized-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though many prompting methods have been proposed to complete particular agent tasks, there is lack of research focusing on improving the agent capabilities of LLMs themselves without compromising their general abilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agenttuning-enabling-generalized-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero123++: a Single Image to Consistent Multi-view Diffusion Base Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero123-a-single-image-to-consistent-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We report Zero123++, an image-conditioned diffusion model for generating 3D-consistent multi-view images from a single input view.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero123-a-single-image-to-consistent-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Llemma: An Open Language Model For Mathematics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llemma-an-open-language-model-for-mathematics</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Llemma, a large language model for mathematics.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llemma-an-open-language-model-for-mathematics</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SALMONN: Towards Generic Hearing Abilities for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salmonn-towards-generic-hearing-abilities-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Hearing is arguably an essential ability of artificial intelligence (AI) agents in the physical world, which refers to the perception and understanding of general auditory information consisting of at least three types of sounds: speech, audio events, and music.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/salmonn-towards-generic-hearing-abilities-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PixArt-$α$: Fast Training of Diffusion Transformer for Photorealistic Text-to-Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixart-a-fast-training-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope PIXART-$\alpha$ will provide new insights to the AIGC community and startups to accelerate building their own high-quality yet low-cost generative models from scratch.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pixart-a-fast-training-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparse Fine-tuning for Inference Acceleration of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-finetuning-for-inference-acceleration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While the standard approach is to leverage sparsity for computational reduction, we observe that in the case of memory-bound LLMs sparsity can also be leveraged for reducing memory bandwidth.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparse-finetuning-for-inference-acceleration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoReTalking: Audio-based Lip Synchronization for Talking Head Video Editing In the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoretalking-audio-based-lip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our system disentangles this objective into three sequential tasks: (1) face video generation with a canonical expression; (2) audio-driven lip-sync; and (3) face enhancement for improving photo-realism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videoretalking-audio-based-lip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latent Consistency Models: Synthesizing High-Resolution Images with Few-Step Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-consistency-models-synthesizing-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by Consistency Models (song et al.), we propose Latent Consistency Models (LCMs), enabling swift inference with minimal steps on any pre-trained LDMs, including Stable Diffusion (rombach et al).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/latent-consistency-models-synthesizing-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contrastive Prefence Learning: Learning from Human Feedback without RL</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-prefence-learning-learning-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Thus, learning a reward function from feedback is not only based on a flawed assumption of human preference, but also leads to unwieldy optimization challenges that stem from policy gradients or bootstrapping in the RL phase.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contrastive-prefence-learning-learning-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iTransformer: Inverted Transformers Are Effective for Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itransformer-inverted-transformers-are</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These forecasters leverage Transformers to model the global dependencies over temporal tokens of time series, with each token formed by multiple variates of the same timestamp.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itransformer-inverted-transformers-are</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting the Object Back into Video Object Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-the-object-back-into-video-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The object queries act as a high-level summary of the target object, while high-resolution feature maps are retained for accurate segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/putting-the-object-back-into-video-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPM-Solver-v3: Improved Diffusion ODE Solver with Empirical Model Statistics</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpm-solver-v3-improved-diffusion-ode-solver</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a novel formulation towards the optimal parameterization during sampling that minimizes the first-order discretization error of the ODE solution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dpm-solver-v3-improved-diffusion-ode-solver</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separate Anything You Describe</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separate-anything-you-describe</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we introduce AudioSep, a foundation model for open-domain audio source separation with natural language queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/separate-anything-you-describe</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLVS: A SLAM System with Points, Lines, Volumetric Mapping, and 3D Incremental Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plvs-a-slam-system-with-points-lines</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An incremental and geometric-based segmentation method is implemented and integrated for RGB-D cameras in the PLVS framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plvs-a-slam-system-with-points-lines</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Video Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-video-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, existing surveys mainly focus on diffusion models in the context of image generation, with few up-to-date reviews on their application in the video domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-video-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitNet: Scaling 1-bit Transformers for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitnet-scaling-1-bit-transformers-for-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The increasing size of large language models has posed challenges for deployment and raised concerns about environmental impact due to high energy consumption.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitnet-scaling-1-bit-transformers-for-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoGen: Enabling Next-Gen LLM Applications via Multi-Agent Conversation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autogen-enabling-next-gen-llm-applications</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AutoGen is an open-source framework that allows developers to build LLM applications via multiple agents that can converse with each other to accomplish tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autogen-enabling-next-gen-llm-applications</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Habitat-Matterport 3D Semantics Dataset</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/habitat-matterport-3d-semantics-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The scale, quality, and diversity of object annotations far exceed those of prior datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/habitat-matterport-3d-semantics-dataset</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
