<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 21:08:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Byte Latent Transformer: Patches Scale Better Than Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byte-latent-transformer-patches-scale-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Byte Latent Transformer (BLT), a new byte-level LLM architecture that, for the first time, matches tokenization-based LLM performance at scale with significant improvements in inference efficiency and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byte-latent-transformer-patches-scale-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Flow Fields in Attention for Controllable Person Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we show that our loss is model-agnostic and can be used to improve the performance of other diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Concept Models: Language Modeling in a Sentence Representation Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-concept-models-language-modeling-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an attempt at an architecture which operates on an explicit higher-level semantic representation, which we name a concept.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-concept-models-language-modeling-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CosyVoice 2: Scalable Streaming Speech Synthesis with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosyvoice-2-scalable-streaming-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By training on a large-scale multilingual dataset, CosyVoice 2 achieves human-parity naturalness, minimal response latency, and virtually lossless synthesis quality in the streaming mode.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosyvoice-2-scalable-streaming-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary-steps Image Super-resolution via Diffusion Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-steps-image-super-resolution-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a new image super-resolution (SR) technique based on diffusion inversion, aiming at harnessing the rich image priors encapsulated in large pre-trained diffusion models to improve SR performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-steps-image-super-resolution-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-VL2: Mixture-of-Experts Vision-Language Models for Advanced Multimodal Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl2-mixture-of-experts-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DeepSeek-VL2, an advanced series of large Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) Vision-Language Models that significantly improves upon its predecessor, DeepSeek-VL, through two key major upgrades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl2-mixture-of-experts-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Diffusion Transformers for Generative Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-diffusion-transformers-for-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Causal Diffusion as the autoregressive (AR) counterpart of Diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-diffusion-transformers-for-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAM3R: Real-Time Dense Scene Reconstruction from Monocular RGB Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slam3r-real-time-dense-scene-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce SLAM3R, a novel and effective monocular RGB SLAM system for real-time and high-quality dense 3D reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slam3r-real-time-dense-scene-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaze-LLE: Gaze Target Estimation via Large-Scale Learned Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-lle-gaze-target-estimation-via-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of gaze target estimation, which aims to predict where a person is looking in a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-lle-gaze-target-estimation-via-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evolved Universal Transformer Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior methods propose to offset the escalating costs of modern foundation models by dropping specific parts of their contexts with hand-designed rules, while attempting to preserve their original performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyVolcap: Accelerating Neural Volumetric Video Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyvolcap-accelerating-neural-volumetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Volumetric video is a technology that digitally records dynamic events such as artistic performances, sporting events, and remote conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyvolcap-accelerating-neural-volumetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Seal: Open and Efficient Video Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-seal-open-and-efficient-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce these gaps, this paper introduces Video Seal, a comprehensive framework for neural video watermarking and a competitive open-sourced model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-seal-open-and-efficient-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Video Generation without Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-video-generation-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach that enables autoregressive video generation with high efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-video-generation-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableAnimator: High-Quality Identity-Preserving Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, we propose a novel Hamilton-Jacobi-Bellman (HJB) equation-based optimization to further enhance the face quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyra: An Efficient and Speech-Centric Framework for Omni-Cognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-an-efficient-and-speech-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) evolve, expanding beyond single-domain capabilities is essential to meet the demands for more versatile and efficient AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-an-efficient-and-speech-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Semantic Operators: A Declarative Model for Rich, AI-based Analytics Over Text Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lotus-enabling-semantic-queries-with-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we develop several novel optimizations that take advantage of the declarative nature of semantic operators to accelerate semantic filtering, clustering and join operators by up to $400\times$ while offering statistical accuracy guarantees.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lotus-enabling-semantic-queries-with-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenRLHF: An Easy-to-use, Scalable and High-performance RLHF Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openrlhf-an-easy-to-use-scalable-and-high</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, unlike pretraining or fine-tuning a single model, scaling reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF) for training large language models poses coordination challenges across four models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openrlhf-an-easy-to-use-scalable-and-high</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Language Models with Offline Learning from Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-offline</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Learning from human preferences is crucial for language models (LMs) to effectively cater to human needs and societal values.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-language-models-with-offline</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docling Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docling-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report introduces Docling, an easy to use, self-contained, MIT-licensed open-source package for PDF document conversion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docling-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RetroLLM: Empowering Large Language Models to Retrieve Fine-grained Evidence within Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrollm-empowering-large-language-models-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, to mitigate false pruning in the process of constrained evidence generation, we introduce (1) hierarchical FM-Index constraints, which generate corpus-constrained clues to identify a subset of relevant documents before evidence generation, reducing irrelevant decoding space; and (2) a forward-looking constrained decoding strategy, which considers the relevance of future sequences to improve evidence accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/retrollm-empowering-large-language-models-to</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
