<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 09:12:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>BioGPT: Generative Pre-trained Transformer for Biomedical Text Generation and Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biogpt-generative-pre-trained-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained language models have attracted increasing attention in the biomedical domain, inspired by their great success in the general natural language domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biogpt-generative-pre-trained-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attend-and-Excite: Attention-Based Semantic Guidance for Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attend-and-excite-attention-based-semantic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent text-to-image generative models have demonstrated an unparalleled ability to generate diverse and creative imagery guided by a target text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attend-and-excite-attention-based-semantic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Chain-of-Thought Reasoning in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the vision features in both stages, the model is able to generate effective rationales that contribute to answer inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIP-2: Bootstrapping Language-Image Pre-training with Frozen Image Encoders and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cost of vision-and-language pre-training has become increasingly prohibitive due to end-to-end training of large-scale models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tune-A-Video: One-Shot Tuning of Image Diffusion Models for Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tune-a-video-one-shot-tuning-of-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reproduce the success of text-to-image (T2I) generation, recent works in text-to-video (T2V) generation employ large-scale text-video dataset for fine-tuning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tune-a-video-one-shot-tuning-of-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstructPix2Pix: Learning to Follow Image Editing Instructions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructpix2pix-learning-to-follow-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a method for editing images from human instructions: given an input image and a written instruction that tells the model what to do, our model follows these instructions to edit the image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instructpix2pix-learning-to-follow-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>STEPS: Joint Self-supervised Nighttime Image Enhancement and Depth Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steps-joint-self-supervised-nighttime-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By fitting a bridge-shaped curve to the illumination map distribution, both regions are suppressed and two tasks are bridged naturally.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/steps-joint-self-supervised-nighttime-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NaturalSpeech: End-to-End Text to Speech Synthesis with Human-Level Quality</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naturalspeech-end-to-end-text-to-speech</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we answer these questions by first defining the human-level quality based on the statistical significance of subjective measure and introducing appropriate guidelines to judge it, and then developing a TTS system called NaturalSpeech that achieves human-level quality on a benchmark dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/naturalspeech-end-to-end-text-to-speech</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArchiSound: Audio Generation with Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/archisound-audio-generation-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent surge in popularity of diffusion models for image generation has brought new attention to the potential of these models in other areas of media generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/archisound-audio-generation-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parsel: A (De-)compositional Framework for Algorithmic Reasoning with Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parsel-a-unified-natural-language-framework</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite recent success in large language model (LLM) reasoning, LLMs struggle with hierarchical multi-step reasoning tasks like generating complex programs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/parsel-a-unified-natural-language-framework</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioLDM: Text-to-Audio Generation with Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioldm-text-to-audio-generation-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By learning the latent representations of audio signals and their compositions without modeling the cross-modal relationship, AudioLDM is advantageous in both generation quality and computational efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audioldm-text-to-audio-generation-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Blind Face Restoration with Codebook Lookup Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-blind-face-restoration-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate that a learned discrete codebook prior in a small proxy space largely reduces the uncertainty and ambiguity of restoration mapping by casting blind face restoration as a code prediction task, while providing rich visual atoms for generating high-quality faces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-blind-face-restoration-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut and Learn for Unsupervised Object Detection and Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Cut-and-LEaRn (CutLER), a simple approach for training unsupervised object detection and segmentation models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cut-and-learn-for-unsupervised-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Beauty in Songs: Neural Singing Voice Beautifier</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-beauty-in-songs-neural-singing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a latent-mapping algorithm in the latent space to convert the amateur vocal tone to the professional one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-the-beauty-in-songs-neural-singing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LogAI: A Library for Log Analytics and Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logai-a-library-for-log-analytics-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In order to enable users to perform multiple types of AI-based log analysis tasks in a uniform manner, we introduce LogAI (https://github. com/salesforce/logai), a one-stop open source library for log analytics and intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/logai-a-library-for-log-analytics-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAMO-YOLO : A Report on Real-Time Object Detection Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-yolo-a-report-on-real-time-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present a fast and accurate object detection method dubbed DAMO-YOLO, which achieves higher performance than the state-of-the-art YOLO series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-yolo-a-report-on-real-time-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Length-Extrapolatable Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-length-extrapolatable-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Position modeling plays a critical role in Transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-length-extrapolatable-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disentangling Random and Cyclic Effects in Time-Lapse Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-random-and-cyclic-effects-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the problem of disentangling time-lapse sequences in a way that allows separate, after-the-fact control of overall trends, cyclic effects, and random effects in the images, and describe a technique based on data-driven generative models that achieves this goal.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disentangling-random-and-cyclic-effects-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PADL: Language-Directed Physics-Based Character Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padl-language-directed-physics-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present PADL, which leverages recent innovations in NLP in order to take steps towards developing language-directed controllers for physics-based character animation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/padl-language-directed-physics-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-domain Neural Pitch and Periodicity Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-neural-pitch-and-periodicity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pitch is a foundational aspect of our perception of audio signals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-domain-neural-pitch-and-periodicity</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
