<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:08:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spark-TTS: An Efficient LLM-Based Text-to-Speech Model with Single-Stream Decoupled Speech Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2503-01710</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have driven significant progress in zero-shot text-to-speech (TTS) synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2503-01710</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOE: Real-Time Seeing Anything</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yoloe-real-time-seeing-anything</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Object detection and segmentation are widely employed in computer vision applications, yet conventional models like YOLO series, while efficient and accurate, are limited by predefined categories, hindering adaptability in open scenarios.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yoloe-real-time-seeing-anything</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Synthetic Data Creation with 1,000,000,000 Personas</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-synthetic-data-creation-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose a novel persona-driven data synthesis methodology that leverages various perspectives within a large language model (LLM) to create diverse synthetic data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-synthetic-data-creation-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoPainter: Any-length Video Inpainting and Editing with Plug-and-Play Context Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopainter-any-length-video-inpainting-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Video inpainting, which aims to restore corrupted video content, has experienced substantial progress.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videopainter-any-length-video-inpainting-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comet: Fine-grained Computation-communication Overlapping for Mixture-of-Experts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comet-fine-grained-computation-communication</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The inter-device communication of a MoE layer can occupy 47% time of the entire model execution with popular models and frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/comet-fine-grained-computation-communication</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GEN3C: 3D-Informed World-Consistent Video Generation with Precise Camera Control</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gen3c-3d-informed-world-consistent-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results demonstrate more precise camera control than prior work, as well as state-of-the-art results in sparse-view novel view synthesis, even in challenging settings such as driving scenes and monocular dynamic video.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gen3c-3d-informed-world-consistent-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual-RFT: Visual Reinforcement Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-rft-visual-reinforcement-fine-tuning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement Fine-Tuning (RFT) in Large Reasoning Models like OpenAI o1 learns from feedback on its answers, which is especially useful in applications when fine-tuning data is scarce.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-rft-visual-reinforcement-fine-tuning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AgiBot World Colosseo: A Large-scale Manipulation Platform for Scalable and Intelligent Embodied Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agibot-world-colosseo-a-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Introducing AgiBot World, a large-scale platform comprising over 1 million trajectories across 217 tasks in five deployment scenarios, we achieve an order-of-magnitude increase in data scale compared to existing datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agibot-world-colosseo-a-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FoundationStereo: Zero-Shot Stereo Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundationstereo-zero-shot-stereo-matching</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, achieving strong zero-shot generalization - a hallmark of foundation models in other computer vision tasks - remains challenging for stereo matching.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundationstereo-zero-shot-stereo-matching</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seg-Zero: Reasoning-Chain Guided Segmentation via Cognitive Reinforcement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-zero-reasoning-chain-guided-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional methods for reasoning segmentation rely on supervised fine-tuning with categorical labels and simple descriptions, limiting its out-of-domain generalization and lacking explicit reasoning processes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/seg-zero-reasoning-chain-guided-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>olmOCR: Unlocking Trillions of Tokens in PDFs with Vision Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olmocr-unlocking-trillions-of-tokens-in-pdfs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PDF documents have the potential to provide trillions of novel, high-quality tokens for training language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olmocr-unlocking-trillions-of-tokens-in-pdfs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lanpaint: Training-Free Diffusion Inpainting with Exact and Fast Conditional Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanpaint-training-free-diffusion-inpainting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion models generate high-quality images but often lack efficient and universally applicable inpainting capabilities, particularly in community-trained models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lanpaint-training-free-diffusion-inpainting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Executable Code Actions Elicit Better LLM Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/executable-code-actions-elicit-better-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LLM agents are typically prompted to produce actions by generating JSON or text in a pre-defined format, which is usually limited by constrained action space (e. g., the scope of pre-defined tools) and restricted flexibility (e. g., inability to compose multiple tools).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/executable-code-actions-elicit-better-llm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Graph Retrieval-Augmented Generation for Customized Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-graph-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in a wide range of tasks, yet their application to specialized domains remains challenging due to the need for deep expertise.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-graph-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chain of Draft: Thinking Faster by Writing Less</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-draft-thinking-faster-by-writing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable performance in solving complex reasoning tasks through mechanisms like Chain-of-Thought (CoT) prompting, which emphasizes verbose, step-by-step reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chain-of-draft-thinking-faster-by-writing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interpreting and Improving Diffusion Models from an Optimization Perspective</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-and-improving-diffusion-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising is intuitively related to projection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/interpreting-and-improving-diffusion-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HybridFlow: A Flexible and Efficient RLHF Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridflow-a-flexible-and-efficient-rlhf</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Traditional RL can be modeled as a dataflow, where each node represents computation of a neural network (NN) and each edge denotes data dependencies between the NNs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hybridflow-a-flexible-and-efficient-rlhf</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Residual Kolmogorov-Arnold Network for Enhanced Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-kolmogorov-arnold-network-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Despite the strong performance in many computer vision tasks, Convolutional Neural Networks (CNNs) can sometimes struggle to efficiently capture long-range, complex non-linear dependencies in deeper layers of the network.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/residual-kolmogorov-arnold-network-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Efficient Online 3D Bin Packing on Packing Configuration Trees</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-efficient-online-3d-bin-packing-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[PCT is a full-fledged description of the state and action space of bin packing which can support packing policy learning based on deep reinforcement learning (DRL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-efficient-online-3d-bin-packing-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-rewarding correction for mathematical reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-rewarding-correction-for-mathematical</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study self-rewarding reasoning large language models (LLMs), which can simultaneously generate step-by-step reasoning and evaluate the correctness of their outputs during the inference time-without external feedback.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-rewarding-correction-for-mathematical</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
