<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 09:13:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>AutoCodeRover: Autonomous Program Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in Large Language Models (LLMs) has significantly impacted the development process, where developers can use LLM-based programming assistants to achieve automated coding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Autoregressive Modeling: Scalable Image Generation via Next-Scale Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-autoregressive-modeling-scalable-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Visual AutoRegressive modeling (VAR), a new generation paradigm that redefines the autoregressive learning on images as coarse-to-fine "next-scale prediction" or "next-resolution prediction", diverging from the standard raster-scan "next-token prediction".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-autoregressive-modeling-scalable-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstantStyle: Free Lunch towards Style-Preserving in Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantstyle-free-lunch-towards-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tuning-free diffusion-based models have demonstrated significant potential in the realm of image personalization and customization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantstyle-free-lunch-towards-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIOS: LLM Agent Operating System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-agent-operating-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inspired by these challenges, this paper presents AIOS, an LLM agent operating system, which embeds large language model into operating systems (OS) as the brain of the OS, enabling an operating system "with soul" -- an important step towards AGI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-agent-operating-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReFT: Representation Finetuning for Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reft-representation-finetuning-for-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[LoReFT is a drop-in replacement for existing PEFTs and learns interventions that are 10x-50x more parameter-efficient than prior state-of-the-art PEFTs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reft-representation-finetuning-for-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HairFastGAN: Realistic and Robust Hair Transfer with a Fast Encoder-Based Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hairfastgan-realistic-and-robust-hair</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our paper addresses the complex task of transferring a hairstyle from a reference image to an input photo for virtual hair try-on.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hairfastgan-realistic-and-robust-hair</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SchurVINS: Schur Complement-Based Lightweight Visual Inertial Navigation System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schurvins-schur-complement-based-lightweight</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose a novel filter-based VINS framework named SchurVINS, which could guarantee both high accuracy by building a complete residual model and low computational complexity with Schur complement.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/schurvins-schur-complement-based-lightweight</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AniPortrait: Audio-Driven Synthesis of Photorealistic Portrait Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aniportrait-audio-driven-synthesis-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose AniPortrait, a novel framework for generating high-quality animation driven by audio and a reference portrait image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aniportrait-audio-driven-synthesis-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Attention Makes Inference Cumbersome in Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-makes-inference-cumbersome-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study explores the role of cross-attention during inference in text-conditional diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-attention-makes-inference-cumbersome-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PiSSA: Principal Singular Values and Singular Vectors Adaptation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pissa-principal-singular-values-and-singular</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, LoRA approximates Delta W through the product of two matrices, A, initialized with Gaussian noise, and B, initialized with zeros, while PiSSA initializes A and B with principal singular values and vectors of the original matrix W. PiSSA can better approximate the outcomes of full-parameter fine-tuning at the beginning by changing the essential parts while freezing the "noisy" parts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pissa-principal-singular-values-and-singular</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DN-Splatter: Depth and Normal Priors for Gaussian Splatting and Meshing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dn-splatter-depth-and-normal-priors-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[3D Gaussian splatting, a novel differentiable rendering technique, has achieved state-of-the-art novel view synthesis results with high rendering speeds and relatively low training times.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dn-splatter-depth-and-normal-priors-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StreamingT2V: Consistent, Dynamic, and Extendable Long Video Generation from Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamingt2v-consistent-dynamic-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome these limitations, we introduce StreamingT2V, an autoregressive approach for long video generation of 80, 240, 600, 1200 or more frames with smooth transitions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/streamingt2v-consistent-dynamic-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoWebGLM: Bootstrap And Reinforce A Large Language Model-based Web Navigating Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autowebglm-bootstrap-and-reinforce-a-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have fueled many intelligent agent tasks, such as web navigation -- but most existing agents perform far from satisfying in real-world webpages due to three factors: (1) the versatility of actions on webpages, (2) HTML text exceeding model processing capacity, and (3) the complexity of decision-making due to the open-domain nature of web.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autowebglm-bootstrap-and-reinforce-a-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoiceCraft: Zero-Shot Speech Editing and Text-to-Speech in the Wild</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voicecraft-zero-shot-speech-editing-and-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce VoiceCraft, a token infilling neural codec language model, that achieves state-of-the-art performance on both speech editing and zero-shot text-to-speech (TTS) on audiobooks, internet videos, and podcasts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/voicecraft-zero-shot-speech-editing-and-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document-Level Machine Translation with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-machine-translation-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) such as ChatGPT can produce coherent, cohesive, relevant, and fluent answers for various natural language processing (NLP) tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/document-level-machine-translation-with-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FoundationPose: Unified 6D Pose Estimation and Tracking of Novel Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundationpose-unified-6d-pose-estimation-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present FoundationPose, a unified foundation model for 6D object pose estimation and tracking, supporting both model-based and model-free setups.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/foundationpose-unified-6d-pose-estimation-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniTable: Towards a Unified Framework for Table Structure Recognition via Self-Supervised Pretraining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitable-towards-a-unified-framework-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Tables convey factual and quantitative data with implicit conventions created by humans that are often challenging for machines to parse.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unitable-towards-a-unified-framework-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branch-Train-MiX: Mixing Expert LLMs into a Mixture-of-Experts LLM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/branch-train-mix-mixing-expert-llms-into-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We investigate efficient methods for training Large Language Models (LLMs) to possess capabilities in multiple specialized domains, such as coding, math reasoning and world knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/branch-train-mix-mixing-expert-llms-into-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Position Paper: What Can Large Language Models Tell Us about Time Series Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-paper-what-can-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Time series analysis is essential for comprehending the complexities inherent in various real-world systems and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/position-paper-what-can-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OLMo: Accelerating the Science of Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olmo-accelerating-the-science-of-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the importance of these details in scientifically studying these models, including their biases and potential risks, we believe it is essential for the research community to have access to powerful, truly open LMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olmo-accelerating-the-science-of-language</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
