<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 09:16:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-instrument Music Synthesis with Spectrogram Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-instrument-music-synthesis-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[An ideal music synthesizer should be both interactive and expressive, generating high-fidelity audio in realtime for arbitrary combinations of instruments and notes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-instrument-music-synthesis-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image is Worth One Word: Personalizing Text-to-Image Generation using Textual Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-is-worth-one-word-personalizing-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, it is unclear how such freedom can be exercised to generate images of specific unique concepts, modify their appearance, or compose them in new roles and novel scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-is-worth-one-word-personalizing-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOPv2: Better, Faster, Stronger for Panoptic Driving Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolopv2-better-faster-stronger-for-panoptic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the last decade, multi-tasking learning approaches have achieved promising results in solving panoptic driving perception problems, providing both high-precision and high-efficiency performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolopv2-better-faster-stronger-for-panoptic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PeRFception: Perception using Radiance Fields</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfception-perception-using-radiance-fields</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent progress in implicit 3D representation, i. e., Neural Radiance Fields (NeRFs), has made accurate and photorealistic 3D reconstruction possible in a differentiable manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/perfception-perception-using-radiance-fields</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topology-aware Convolutional Neural Network for Efficient Skeleton-based Action Recognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-convolutional-neural-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we develop a novel cross-channel feature augmentation module, which is a combo of map-attend-group-map operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/topology-aware-convolutional-neural-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense of Online Models for Video Instance Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-defense-of-online-models-for-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In recent years, video instance segmentation (VIS) has been largely advanced by offline models, while online models gradually attracted less attention possibly due to their inferior performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/in-defense-of-online-models-for-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Synthesis of Artistic Images with Retrieval-Augmented Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In RDMs, a set of nearest neighbors is retrieved from an external database during training for each training instance, and the diffusion model is conditioned on these informative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Online Decision Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-decision-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work has shown that offline reinforcement learning (RL) can be formulated as a sequence modeling problem (Chen et al., 2021; Janner et al., 2021) and solved via approaches similar to large-scale language modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/online-decision-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Multi-band DenseNets for Audio Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-multi-band-densenets-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper deals with the problem of audio source separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-multi-band-densenets-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDM: Iterative Distribution Matching for Communication-Efficient Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddm-iterative-distribution-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning~(FL) has recently attracted increasing attention from academia and industry, with the ultimate goal of achieving collaborative training under privacy and communication constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddm-iterative-distribution-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning via Decentralized Dataset Distillation in Resource-Constrained Edge Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-decentralized-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel federated learning framework, FedD3, which reduces the overall communication volume and with that opens up the concept of federated learning to more application scenarios in network-constrained environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-decentralized-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-Visual Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To deal with the AVS problem, we propose a novel method that uses a temporal pixel-wise audio-visual interaction module to inject audio semantics as guidance for the visual segmentation process.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Training and Tuning Generative Neural Radiance Fields for Attribute-Conditional 3D-Aware Face Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-tuning-generative-neural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce a conditional GNeRF model that uses specific attribute labels as input in order to improve the controllabilities and disentangling abilities of 3D-aware generative models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/training-and-tuning-generative-neural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revisiting and Advancing Fast Adversarial Training Through The Lens of Bi-Level Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-and-advancing-fast-adversarial-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We first show that the commonly-used Fast-AT is equivalent to using a stochastic gradient algorithm to solve a linearized BLO problem involving a sign operation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/revisiting-and-advancing-fast-adversarial-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv7: Trainable bag-of-freebies sets new state-of-the-art for real-time object detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[YOLOv7 surpasses all known object detectors in both speed and accuracy in the range from 5 FPS to 160 FPS and has the highest accuracy 56. 8% AP among all known real-time object detectors with 30 FPS or higher on GPU V100.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold Diffusion: Inverting Arbitrary Image Transforms Without Noise</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-diffusion-inverting-arbitrary-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We observe that the generative behavior of diffusion models is not strongly dependent on the choice of image degradation, and in fact an entire family of generative models can be constructed by varying this choice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cold-diffusion-inverting-arbitrary-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USB: A Unified Semi-supervised Learning Benchmark</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usb-a-unified-semi-supervised-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Semi-supervised learning (SSL) improves model generalization by leveraging massive unlabeled data to augment limited labeled samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/usb-a-unified-semi-supervised-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NeuMan: Neural Human Radiance Field from a Single Video</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuman-neural-human-radiance-field-from-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Photorealistic rendering and reposing of humans is important for enabling augmented reality experiences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neuman-neural-human-radiance-field-from-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>towhee</title>
      <link>https://github.com/towhee-io/towhee</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towhee is a framework that is dedicated to making neural data processing pipelines simple and fast.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/towhee-io/towhee</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAMDA-SSL: Semi-Supervised Learning in Python</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamda-ssl-semi-supervised-learning-in-python</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The second part shows the usage of LAMDA-SSL by abundant examples in detail.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lamda-ssl-semi-supervised-learning-in-python</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
