<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 09:13:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Conditional Control to Text-to-Image Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adding-conditional-control-to-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, training a ControlNet is as fast as fine-tuning a diffusion model, and the model can be trained on a personal devices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adding-conditional-control-to-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAP: Memory-aware Automated Intra-op Parallel Training For Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-memory-aware-automated-intra-op-parallel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, finding an efficient distributed execution plan not only requires fine-grained model statistics, such as memory and computing overhead of each operator but also is a labor-intensive task even for an expert in the field of distributed training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/map-memory-aware-automated-intra-op-parallel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Motion Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-motion-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthesizing realistic animations of humans, animals, and even imaginary creatures, has long been a goal for artists and computer graphics professionals.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/single-motion-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy improvement by planning with Gumbel</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-improvement-by-planning-with-gumbel</link>
      <description><![CDATA[AlphaZero is a powerful reinforcement learning algorithm based on approximate policy iteration and tree search.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/policy-improvement-by-planning-with-gumbel</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multimodal Chain-of-Thought Reasoning in Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By incorporating the vision features in both stages, the model is able to generate effective rationales that contribute to answer inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multimodal-chain-of-thought-reasoning-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BioGPT: Generative Pre-trained Transformer for Biomedical Text Generation and Mining</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biogpt-generative-pre-trained-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained language models have attracted increasing attention in the biomedical domain, inspired by their great success in the general natural language domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/biogpt-generative-pre-trained-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offsite-Tuning: Transfer Learning without Full Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offsite-tuning-transfer-learning-without-full</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Offsite-Tuning, a privacy-preserving and efficient transfer learning framework that can adapt billion-parameter foundation models to downstream data without access to the full model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offsite-tuning-transfer-learning-without-full</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Robust Blind Face Restoration with Codebook Lookup Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-blind-face-restoration-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we demonstrate that a learned discrete codebook prior in a small proxy space largely reduces the uncertainty and ambiguity of restoration mapping by casting blind face restoration as a code prediction task, while providing rich visual atoms for generating high-quality faces.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-robust-blind-face-restoration-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-and-Play Diffusion Features for Text-Driven Image-to-Image Translation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-diffusion-features-for-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale text-to-image generative models have been a revolutionary breakthrough in the evolution of generative AI, allowing us to synthesize diverse images that convey highly complex visual concepts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/plug-and-play-diffusion-features-for-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contour Context: Abstract Structural Distribution for 3D LiDAR Loop Detection and Metric Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contour-context-abstract-structural</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes \textit{Contour Context}, a simple, effective, and efficient topological loop closure detection pipeline with accurate 3-DoF metric pose estimation, targeting the urban utonomous driving scenario.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/contour-context-abstract-structural</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wisdom of Hindsight Makes Language Models Better Instruction Followers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-wisdom-of-hindsight-makes-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we consider an alternative approach: converting feedback to instruction by relabeling the original one and training the model for better alignment in a supervised manner.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-wisdom-of-hindsight-makes-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DAMO-YOLO : A Report on Real-Time Object Detection Design</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-yolo-a-report-on-real-time-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this report, we present a fast and accurate object detection method dubbed DAMO-YOLO, which achieves higher performance than the state-of-the-art YOLO series.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/damo-yolo-a-report-on-real-time-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Outlier Removal Strategy Based on Reliability of Correspondence Graph for Fast Point Cloud Registration</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-outlier-removal-strategy-based-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use a simple and intuitive method to describe the 6-DOF (degree of freedom) curtailment process in point cloud registration and propose an outlier removal strategy based on the reliability of the correspondence graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-new-outlier-removal-strategy-based-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demonstrate-Search-Predict: Composing retrieval and language models for knowledge-intensive NLP</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstrate-search-predict-composing</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-augmented in-context learning has emerged as a powerful approach for addressing knowledge-intensive tasks using frozen language models (LM) and retrieval models (RM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/demonstrate-search-predict-composing</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AltCLIP: Altering the Language Encoder in CLIP for Extended Language Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/altclip-altering-the-language-encoder-in-clip</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we present a conceptually simple and effective method to train a strong bilingual/multilingual multimodal representation model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/altclip-altering-the-language-encoder-in-clip</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAMatcher: An Overlapping Areas-based Network for Accurate Local Feature Matching</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oamatcher-an-overlapping-areas-based-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Local feature matching is an essential component in many visual applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/oamatcher-an-overlapping-areas-based-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instant Neural Graphics Primitives with a Multiresolution Hash Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instant-neural-graphics-primitives-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural graphics primitives, parameterized by fully connected neural networks, can be costly to train and evaluate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instant-neural-graphics-primitives-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SmoothQuant: Accurate and Efficient Post-Training Quantization for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothquant-accurate-and-efficient-post</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose SmoothQuant, a training-free, accuracy-preserving, and general-purpose post-training quantization (PTQ) solution to enable 8-bit weight, 8-bit activation (W8A8) quantization for LLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smoothquant-accurate-and-efficient-post</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UniAdapter: Unified Parameter-Efficient Transfer Learning for Cross-modal Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniadapter-unified-parameter-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Particularly, on the MSRVTT retrieval task, UniAdapter achieves 49. 7% recall@1 with 2. 2% model parameters, outperforming the latest competitors by 2. 0%.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/uniadapter-unified-parameter-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIP-2: Bootstrapping Language-Image Pre-training with Frozen Image Encoders and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cost of vision-and-language pre-training has become increasingly prohibitive due to end-to-end training of large-scale models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
