<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Sep 2024 09:14:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA-Omni: Seamless Speech Interaction with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-omni-seamless-speech-interaction-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We build our model based on the latest Llama-3. 1-8B-Instruct model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-omni-seamless-speech-interaction-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PaperQA: Retrieval-Augmented Generative Agent for Scientific Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paperqa-retrieval-augmented-generative-agent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present PaperQA, a RAG agent for answering questions over the scientific literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paperqa-retrieval-augmented-generative-agent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Omni: Language Models Can Hear, Talk While Thinking in Streaming</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-omni-language-models-can-hear-talk-while</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce the VoiceAssistant-400K dataset to fine-tune models optimized for speech output.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-omni-language-models-can-hear-talk-while</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MemoRAG: Moving towards Next-Gen RAG Via Memory-Inspired Knowledge Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorag-moving-towards-next-gen-rag-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) leverages retrieval tools to access external databases, thereby enhancing the generation quality of large language models (LLMs) through optimized context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/memorag-moving-towards-next-gen-rag-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GeoCalib: Learning Single-image Calibration with Geometric Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geocalib-learning-single-image-calibration</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This single-image calibration can benefit various downstream applications like image editing and 3D mapping.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/geocalib-learning-single-image-calibration</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniCPM: Unveiling the Potential of Small Language Models with Scalable Training Strategies</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicpm-unveiling-the-potential-of-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For data scaling, we introduce a Warmup-Stable-Decay (WSD) learning rate scheduler (LRS), conducive to continuous training and domain adaptation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/minicpm-unveiling-the-potential-of-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SciAgents: Automating scientific discovery through multi-agent intelligent graph reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciagents-automating-scientific-discovery</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A key challenge in artificial intelligence is the creation of systems capable of autonomously advancing scientific understanding by exploring novel domains, identifying complex patterns, and uncovering previously unseen connections in vast scientific data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sciagents-automating-scientific-discovery</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can LLMs Generate Novel Research Ideas? A Large-Scale Human Study with 100+ NLP Researchers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-generate-novel-research-ideas-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have sparked optimism about their potential to accelerate scientific discovery, with a growing number of works proposing research agents that autonomously generate and validate new ideas.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-llms-generate-novel-research-ideas-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongCite: Enabling LLMs to Generate Fine-grained Citations in Long-context QA</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcite-enabling-llms-to-generate-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though current long-context large language models (LLMs) have demonstrated impressive capacities in answering user questions based on extensive text, the lack of citations in their responses makes user verification difficult, leading to concerns about their trustworthiness due to their potential hallucinations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/longcite-enabling-llms-to-generate-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iText2KG: Incremental Knowledge Graphs Construction Using Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itext2kg-incremental-knowledge-graphs</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our method demonstrates superior performance compared to baseline methods across three scenarios: converting scientific papers to graphs, websites to graphs, and CVs to graphs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/itext2kg-incremental-knowledge-graphs</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mutual Reasoning Makes Smaller LLMs Stronger Problem-Solvers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-reasoning-makes-smaller-llms-stronger</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces rStar, a self-play mutual reasoning approach that significantly improves reasoning capabilities of small language models (SLMs) without fine-tuning or superior models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mutual-reasoning-makes-smaller-llms-stronger</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Model-Based Agents for Software Engineering: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-based-agents-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent advance in Large Language Models (LLMs) has shaped a new paradigm of AI agents, i. e., LLM-based agents.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-model-based-agents-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards a Unified View of Preference Learning for Large Language Models: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-view-of-preference-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, based on our unified perspective, we explore the challenges and future research directions for aligning large language models with human preferences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-a-unified-view-of-preference-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>optillm</title>
      <link>https://github.com/codelion/optillm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Optimizing inference proxy for LLMs]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/codelion/optillm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docling Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docling-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report introduces Docling, an easy to use, self-contained, MIT-licensed open-source package for PDF document conversion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docling-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RealisDance: Equip controllable character animation with realistic hands</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realisdance-equip-controllable-character</link>
      <description><![CDATA[2) The hands generated using the DWPose sequence are blurry and unrealistic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/realisdance-equip-controllable-character</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RobustSAM: Segment Anything Robustly on Degraded Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustsam-segment-anything-robustly-on-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Segment Anything Model (SAM) has emerged as a transformative approach in image segmentation, acclaimed for its robust zero-shot segmentation capabilities and flexible prompting system.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robustsam-segment-anything-robustly-on-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KGRefiner: Knowledge Graph Refinement for Improving Accuracy of Translational Link Prediction Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgrefiner-knowledge-graph-refinement-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Link Prediction is the task of predicting missing relations between entities of the knowledge graph.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kgrefiner-knowledge-graph-refinement-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLUX that Plays Music</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flux-that-plays-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper explores a simple extension of diffusion-based rectified flow Transformers for text-to-music generation, termed as FluxMusic.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flux-that-plays-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-Shot Diffusion Mimicker for Handwritten Text Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-diffusion-mimicker-for-handwritten</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experiments demonstrate that our method can successfully generate handwriting scripts with just one sample reference in multiple languages, even outperforming previous methods using over ten samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-shot-diffusion-mimicker-for-handwritten</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
