<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 09:13:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pen and Paper Exercises in Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pen-and-paper-exercises-in-machine-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is a collection of (mostly) pen-and-paper exercises in machine learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pen-and-paper-exercises-in-machine-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Graph Fusion Networks for Urban Region Embedding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-graph-fusion-networks-for-urban-region</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Human mobility data contains rich but abundant information, which yields to the comprehensive region embeddings for cross domain tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-graph-fusion-networks-for-urban-region</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProGen2: Exploring the Boundaries of Protein Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progen2-exploring-the-boundaries-of-protein</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Attention-based models trained on protein sequences have demonstrated incredible success at classification and generation tasks relevant for artificial intelligence-driven protein design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/progen2-exploring-the-boundaries-of-protein</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denoised MDPs: Learning World Models Better Than the World Itself</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to separate signal from noise, and reason with clean abstractions, is critical to intelligence.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/denoised-mdps-learning-world-models-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivy: Templated Deep Learning for Inter-Framework Portability</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ivy-templated-deep-learning-for-inter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Ivy, a templated Deep Learning (DL) framework which abstracts existing DL frameworks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ivy-templated-deep-learning-for-inter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Autoregressive Models for Content-Rich Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-autoregressive-models-for-content</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the Pathways Autoregressive Text-to-Image (Parti) model, which generates high-fidelity photorealistic images and supports content-rich synthesis involving complex compositions and world knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-autoregressive-models-for-content</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPro-PnP: Generalized End-to-End Probabilistic Perspective-n-Points for Monocular Object Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epro-pnp-generalized-end-to-end-probabilistic</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The 2D-3D coordinates and corresponding weights are treated as intermediate variables learned by minimizing the KL divergence between the predicted and target pose distribution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/epro-pnp-generalized-end-to-end-probabilistic</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BokehMe: When Neural Rendering Meets Classical Rendering</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bokehme-when-neural-rendering-meets-classical-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Based on this formulation, we implement the classical renderer by a scattering-based method and propose a two-stage neural renderer to fix the erroneous areas from the classical renderer.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bokehme-when-neural-rendering-meets-classical-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Shot Text-to-Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-to-image-generation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-to-image generation has traditionally focused on finding better modeling assumptions for training on a fixed dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zero-shot-text-to-image-generation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LViT: Language meets Vision Transformer in Medical Image Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvit-language-meets-vision-transformer-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In our model, medical text annotation is introduced to compensate for the quality deficiency in image data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lvit-language-meets-vision-transformer-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weakly-supervised Video Anomaly Detection with Robust Temporal Feature Magnitude Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-video-anomaly-detection</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we introduce a novel and theoretically sound method, named Robust Temporal Feature Magnitude learning (RTFM), which trains a feature magnitude learning function to effectively recognise the positive instances, substantially improving the robustness of the MIL approach to the negative instances from abnormal videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/weakly-supervised-video-anomaly-detection</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HiVT: Hierarchical Vector Transformer for Multi-Agent Motion Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hivt-hierarchical-vector-transformer-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To tackle this challenge, we propose Hierarchical Vector Transformer (HiVT) for fast and accurate multi-agent motion prediction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hivt-hierarchical-vector-transformer-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision GNN: An Image is Worth Graph of Nodes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-gnn-an-image-is-worth-graph-of-nodes</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose to represent the image as a graph structure and introduce a new Vision GNN (ViG) architecture to extract graph-level feature for visual tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vision-gnn-an-image-is-worth-graph-of-nodes</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploiting Temporal Contexts with Strided Transformer for 3D Human Pose Estimation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifting-transformer-for-3d-human-pose</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The modified VTE is termed as Strided Transformer Encoder (STE), which is built upon the outputs of VTE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lifting-transformer-for-3d-human-pose</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elucidating the Design Space of Diffusion-Based Generative Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elucidating-the-design-space-of-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We argue that the theory and practice of diffusion-based generative models are currently unnecessarily convoluted and seek to remedy the situation by presenting a design space that clearly separates the concrete design choices.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/elucidating-the-design-space-of-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Rubik’s Cube: Twisting Resolution, Depth and Width for TinyNets</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-rubiks-cube-twisting-resolution-depth</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we summarize a tiny formula for downsizing neural architectures through a series of smaller models derived from the EfficientNet-B0 with the FLOPs constraint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/model-rubiks-cube-twisting-resolution-depth</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhostNet: More Features from Cheap Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghostnet-more-features-from-cheap-operations</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deploying convolutional neural networks (CNNs) on embedded devices is difficult due to the limited memory and computation resources.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghostnet-more-features-from-cheap-operations</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GhostNets on Heterogeneous Devices via Cheap Operations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghostnets-on-heterogeneous-devices-via-cheap</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The proposed C-Ghost module can be taken as a plug-and-play component to upgrade existing convolutional neural networks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ghostnets-on-heterogeneous-devices-via-cheap</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPT: Open Pre-trained Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opt-open-pre-trained-transformer-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models, which are often trained for hundreds of thousands of compute days, have shown remarkable capabilities for zero- and few-shot learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/opt-open-pre-trained-transformer-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SRCN3D: Sparse R-CNN 3D Surround-View Camera Object Detection and Tracking for Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srcn3d-sparse-r-cnn-3d-surround-view-camera</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes Sparse R-CNN 3D (SRCN3D), a novel two-stage fully-convolutional mapping pipeline for surround-view camera detection and tracking.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/srcn3d-sparse-r-cnn-3d-surround-view-camera</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
