<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 May 2023 09:11:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>QLoRA: Efficient Finetuning of Quantized LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our best model family, which we name Guanaco, outperforms all previous openly released models on the Vicuna benchmark, reaching 99. 3% of the performance level of ChatGPT while only requiring 24 hours of finetuning on a single GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree of Thoughts: Deliberate Problem Solving with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-thoughts-deliberate-problem-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models are increasingly being deployed for general problem solving across a wide range of tasks, but are still confined to token-level, left-to-right decision-making processes during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-thoughts-deliberate-problem-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Detail Preservation for Customized Text-to-Image Generation: A Regularization-Free Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, generating images of novel concept provided by the user input image is still a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any-to-Any Generation via Composable Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-to-any-generation-via-composable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Composable Diffusion (CoDi), a novel generative model capable of generating any combination of output modalities, such as language, image, video, or audio, from any combination of input modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-to-any-generation-via-composable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasySpider: A No-Code Visual System for Crawling the Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyspider-a-no-code-visual-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, web-crawling is an essential tool for both computational and non-computational scientists to conduct research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyspider-a-no-code-visual-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VanillaNet: the Power of Minimalism in Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vanillanet-the-power-of-minimalism-in-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce VanillaNet, a neural network architecture that embraces elegance in design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vanillanet-the-power-of-minimalism-in-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag Your GAN: Interactive Point-based Manipulation on the Generative Image Manifold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drag-your-gan-interactive-point-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthesizing visual content that meets users' needs often requires flexible and precise controllability of the pose, shape, expression, and layout of the generated objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drag-your-gan-interactive-point-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlVideo: Training-free Controllable Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlvideo-training-free-controllable-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-driven diffusion models have unlocked unprecedented abilities in image generation, whereas their video counterpart still lags behind due to the excessive training cost of temporal modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlvideo-training-free-controllable-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Vision, Text, and Layout for Universal Document Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-vision-text-and-layout-for-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UDOP leverages the spatial correlation between textual content and document image to model image, text, and layout modalities with one uniform representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-vision-text-and-layout-for-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecurrentGPT: Interactive Generation of (Arbitrarily) Long Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrentgpt-interactive-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to producing AI-generated content (AIGC), we also demonstrate the possibility of using RecurrentGPT as an interactive fiction that directly interacts with consumers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrentgpt-interactive-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechGPT: Empowering Large Language Models with Intrinsic Cross-Modal Conversational Abilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-empowering-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models are regarded as a crucial step towards Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) and have garnered significant interest with the emergence of ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-empowering-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fairseq</title>
      <link>https://github.com/pytorch/fairseq</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facebook AI Research Sequence-to-Sequence Toolkit written in Python.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/pytorch/fairseq</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook AI’s WMT21 News Translation Task Submission</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facebook-ais-wmt21-news-translation-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe Facebook’s multilingual model submission to the WMT2021 shared task on news translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facebook-ais-wmt21-news-translation-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-to-speech translation for a real-world unwritten language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-to-speech-translation-for-a-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use English-Taiwanese Hokkien as a case study, and present an end-to-end solution from training data collection, modeling choices to benchmark dataset release.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-to-speech-translation-for-a-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Speech Technology to 1,000+ Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expanding the language coverage of speech technology has the potential to improve access to information for many more people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BLIP-2: Bootstrapping Language-Image Pre-training with Frozen Image Encoders and Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The cost of vision-and-language pre-training has become increasingly prohibitive due to end-to-end training of large-scale models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/blip-2-bootstrapping-language-image-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sparks of Artificial General Intelligence: Early experiments with GPT-4</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparks-of-artificial-general-intelligence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We contend that (this early version of) GPT-4 is part of a new cohort of LLMs (along with ChatGPT and Google's PaLM for example) that exhibit more general intelligence than previous AI models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sparks-of-artificial-general-intelligence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE-PEACE: Exploring One General Representation Model Toward Unlimited Modalities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-peace-exploring-one-general</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we explore a scalable way for building a general representation model toward unlimited modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-peace-exploring-one-general</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>string2string: A Modern Python Library for String-to-String Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It includes traditional algorithmic solutions as well as recent advanced neural approaches to tackle various problems in string alignment, distance measurement, lexical and semantic search, and similarity analysis -- along with several helpful visualization tools and metrics to facilitate the interpretation and analysis of these methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/string2string-a-modern-python-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VideoLLM: Modeling Video Sequence with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-modeling-video-sequence-with-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Building upon this insight, we propose a novel framework called VideoLLM that leverages the sequence reasoning capabilities of pre-trained LLMs from natural language processing (NLP) for video sequence understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/videollm-modeling-video-sequence-with-large</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
