<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 21:08:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>SAMURAI: Adapting Segment Anything Model for Zero-Shot Visual Tracking with Motion-Aware Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The Segment Anything Model 2 (SAM 2) has demonstrated strong performance in object segmentation tasks but faces challenges in visual object tracking, particularly when managing crowded scenes with fast-moving or self-occluding objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/samurai-adapting-segment-anything-model-for-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EchoMimicV2: Towards Striking, Simplified, and Semi-Body Human Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echomimicv2-towards-striking-simplified-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent work on human animation usually involves audio, pose, or movement maps conditions, thereby achieves vivid animation quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/echomimicv2-towards-striking-simplified-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ShowUI: One Vision-Language-Action Model for GUI Visual Agent</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showui-one-vision-language-action-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we develop a vision-language-action model in digital world, namely ShowUI, which features the following innovations: (i) UI-Guided Visual Token Selection to reduce computational costs by formulating screenshots as an UI connected graph, adaptively identifying their redundant relationship and serve as the criteria for token selection during self-attention blocks; (ii) Interleaved Vision-Language-Action Streaming that flexibly unifies diverse needs within GUI tasks, enabling effective management of visual-action history in navigation or pairing multi-turn query-action sequences per screenshot to enhance training efficiency; (iii) Small-scale High-quality GUI Instruction-following Datasets by careful data curation and employing a resampling strategy to address significant data type imbalances.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/showui-one-vision-language-action-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OminiControl: Minimal and Universal Control for Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ominicontrol-minimal-and-universal-control</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce OminiControl, a highly versatile and parameter-efficient framework that integrates image conditions into pre-trained Diffusion Transformer (DiT) models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ominicontrol-minimal-and-universal-control</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Attention: Efficient LLM Inference over Long Sequences</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-attention-efficient-llm-inference-over</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference with Transformer-based Large Language Models (LLMs) on long sequences is both costly and slow due to the quadratic complexity of the self-attention mechanism.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/star-attention-efficient-llm-inference-over</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mooncake: A KVCache-centric Disaggregated Architecture for LLM Serving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mooncake-a-kvcache-centric-disaggregated</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to the baseline method, Mooncake can achieve up to a 525% increase in throughput in certain simulated scenarios while adhering to SLOs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mooncake-a-kvcache-centric-disaggregated</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpacking DPO and PPO: Disentangling Best Practices for Learning from Preference Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpacking-dpo-and-ppo-disentangling-best</link>
      <description><![CDATA[High-quality preference data leads to improvements of up to 8% in instruction following and truthfulness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unpacking-dpo-and-ppo-disentangling-best</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Diffusion to Generate Them All</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-diffusion-to-generate-them-all</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Experimental results demonstrate competitive performance across tasks in both generation and prediction such as text-to-image, multiview generation, ID preservation, depth estimation and camera pose estimation despite relatively small training dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/one-diffusion-to-generate-them-all</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco-o1: Towards Open Reasoning Models for Open-Ended Solutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marco-o1-towards-open-reasoning-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Currently OpenAI o1 sparks a surge of interest in the study of large reasoning models (LRM).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/marco-o1-towards-open-reasoning-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableAnimator: High-Quality Identity-Preserving Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, we propose a novel Hamilton-Jacobi-Bellman (HJB) equation-based optimization to further enhance the face quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DINO-X: A Unified Vision Model for Open-World Object Detection and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dino-x-a-unified-vision-model-for-open-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[DINO-X employs the same Transformer-based encoder-decoder architecture as Grounding DINO 1. 5 to pursue an object-level representation for open-world object understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dino-x-a-unified-vision-model-for-open-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cautious Optimizers: Improving Training with One Line of Code</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cautious-optimizers-improving-training-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose a \textbf{single-line modification in Pytorch} to any momentum-based optimizer, which we rename Cautious Optimizer, e. g. C-AdamW and C-Lion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cautious-optimizers-improving-training-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatRex: Taming Multimodal LLM for Joint Perception and Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[From the data perspective, we build a fully automated data engine and construct the Rexverse-2M dataset which possesses multiple granularities to support the joint training of perception and understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatrex-taming-multimodal-llm-for-joint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DROID-Splat: Combining end-to-end SLAM with 3D Gaussian Splatting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droid-splat-combining-end-to-end-slam-with-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in scene synthesis makes standalone SLAM systems purely based on optimizing hyperprimitives with a Rendering objective possible \cite{monogs}.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/droid-splat-combining-end-to-end-slam-with-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlipSketch: Flipping Static Drawings to Text-Guided Sketch Animations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flipsketch-flipping-static-drawings-to-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Sketch animations offer a powerful medium for visual storytelling, from simple flip-book doodles to professional studio productions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flipsketch-flipping-static-drawings-to-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WF-VAE: Enhancing Video VAE by Wavelet-Driven Energy Flow for Latent Video Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wf-vae-enhancing-video-vae-by-wavelet-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, as the resolution and duration of generated videos increase, the encoding cost of Video VAEs becomes a limiting bottleneck in training LVDMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wf-vae-enhancing-video-vae-by-wavelet-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DiffusionDrive: Truncated Diffusion Model for End-to-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondrive-truncated-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the numerous denoising steps in the robotic diffusion policy and the more dynamic, open-world nature of traffic scenes pose substantial challenges for generating diverse driving actions at a real-time speed.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/diffusiondrive-truncated-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Convex Splatting: Radiance Field Rendering with 3D Smooth Convexes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-convex-splatting-radiance-field-rendering</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our results highlight the potential of 3D Convex Splatting to become the new standard for high-quality scene reconstruction and novel view synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/3d-convex-splatting-radiance-field-rendering</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenScholar: Synthesizing Scientific Literature with Retrieval-augmented LMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openscholar-synthesizing-scientific</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Scientific progress depends on researchers' ability to synthesize the growing body of literature.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openscholar-synthesizing-scientific</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborative Decoding Makes Visual Auto-Regressive Modeling Efficient</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decoding-makes-visual-auto</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The large model serves as the 'drafter', specializing in generating low-frequency content at smaller scales, while the smaller model serves as the 'refiner', solely focusing on predicting high-frequency details at larger scales.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/collaborative-decoding-makes-visual-auto</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
