<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 09:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>QLoRA: Efficient Finetuning of Quantized LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Our best model family, which we name Guanaco, outperforms all previous openly released models on the Vicuna benchmark, reaching 99. 3% of the performance level of ChatGPT while only requiring 24 hours of finetuning on a single GPU.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/qlora-efficient-finetuning-of-quantized-llms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree of Thoughts: Deliberate Problem Solving with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-thoughts-deliberate-problem-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models are increasingly being deployed for general problem solving across a wide range of tasks, but are still confined to token-level, left-to-right decision-making processes during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-thoughts-deliberate-problem-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Detail Preservation for Customized Text-to-Image Generation: A Regularization-Free Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, generating images of novel concept provided by the user input image is still a challenging task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/enhancing-detail-preservation-for-customized</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasySpider: A No-Code Visual System for Crawling the Web</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyspider-a-no-code-visual-system-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As such, web-crawling is an essential tool for both computational and non-computational scientists to conduct research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyspider-a-no-code-visual-system-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any-to-Any Generation via Composable Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-to-any-generation-via-composable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Composable Diffusion (CoDi), a novel generative model capable of generating any combination of output modalities, such as language, image, video, or audio, from any combination of input modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/any-to-any-generation-via-composable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unifying Vision, Text, and Layout for Universal Document Processing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-vision-text-and-layout-for-universal</link>
      <description><![CDATA[UDOP leverages the spatial correlation between textual content and document image to model image, text, and layout modalities with one uniform representation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unifying-vision-text-and-layout-for-universal</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sophia: A Scalable Stochastic Second-order Optimizer for Language Model Pre-training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sophia-a-scalable-stochastic-second-order</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Given the massive cost of language model pre-training, a non-trivial improvement of the optimization algorithm would lead to a material reduction on the time and cost of training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sophia-a-scalable-stochastic-second-order</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VanillaNet: the Power of Minimalism in Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vanillanet-the-power-of-minimalism-in-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce VanillaNet, a neural network architecture that embraces elegance in design.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vanillanet-the-power-of-minimalism-in-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drag Your GAN: Interactive Point-based Manipulation on the Generative Image Manifold</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drag-your-gan-interactive-point-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Synthesizing visual content that meets users' needs often requires flexible and precise controllability of the pose, shape, expression, and layout of the generated objects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drag-your-gan-interactive-point-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecurrentGPT: Interactive Generation of (Arbitrarily) Long Text</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrentgpt-interactive-generation-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition to producing AI-generated content (AIGC), we also demonstrate the possibility of using RecurrentGPT as an interactive fiction that directly interacts with consumers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recurrentgpt-interactive-generation-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>fairseq</title>
      <link>https://github.com/pytorch/fairseq</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Facebook AI Research Sequence-to-Sequence Toolkit written in Python.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/pytorch/fairseq</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook AI’s WMT21 News Translation Task Submission</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facebook-ais-wmt21-news-translation-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We describe Facebook’s multilingual model submission to the WMT2021 shared task on news translation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/facebook-ais-wmt21-news-translation-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speech-to-speech translation for a real-world unwritten language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-to-speech-translation-for-a-real-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We use English-Taiwanese Hokkien as a case study, and present an end-to-end solution from training data collection, modeling choices to benchmark dataset release.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speech-to-speech-translation-for-a-real-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpeechGPT: Empowering Large Language Models with Intrinsic Cross-Modal Conversational Abilities</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-empowering-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal large language models are regarded as a crucial step towards Artificial General Intelligence (AGI) and have garnered significant interest with the emergence of ChatGPT.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/speechgpt-empowering-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Speech Technology to 1,000+ Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Expanding the language coverage of speech technology has the potential to improve access to information for many more people.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scaling-speech-technology-to-1000-languages</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AlpacaFarm: A Simulation Framework for Methods that Learn from Human Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2305-14387</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As a demonstration of the research possible in AlpacaFarm, we find that methods that use a reward model can substantially improve over supervised fine-tuning and that our reference PPO implementation leads to a +10% improvement in win-rate against Davinci003.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2305-14387</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InternGPT: Solving Vision-Centric Tasks by Interacting with ChatGPT Beyond Language</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internchat-solving-vision-centric-tasks-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Different from existing interactive systems that rely on pure language, by incorporating pointing instructions, the proposed iGPT significantly improves the efficiency of communication between users and chatbots, as well as the accuracy of chatbots in vision-centric tasks, especially in complicated visual scenarios where the number of objects is greater than 2.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/internchat-solving-vision-centric-tasks-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VisionLLM: Large Language Model is also an Open-Ended Decoder for Vision-Centric Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionllm-large-language-model-is-also-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We hope this model can set a new baseline for generalist vision and language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visionllm-large-language-model-is-also-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlVideo: Training-free Controllable Text-to-Video Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlvideo-training-free-controllable-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text-driven diffusion models have unlocked unprecedented abilities in image generation, whereas their video counterpart still lags behind due to the excessive training cost of temporal modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlvideo-training-free-controllable-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C-Eval: A Multi-Level Multi-Discipline Chinese Evaluation Suite for Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-eval-a-multi-level-multi-discipline-chinese</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present C-Eval, the first comprehensive Chinese evaluation suite designed to assess advanced knowledge and reasoning abilities of foundation models in a Chinese context.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/c-eval-a-multi-level-multi-discipline-chinese</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
