<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 09:17:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Less-to-More Generalization: Unlocking More Controllability by In-Context Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-to-more-generalization-unlocking-more</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we propose a highly-consistent data synthesis pipeline to tackle this challenge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/less-to-more-generalization-unlocking-more</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDT: Decoupled Diffusion Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddt-decoupled-diffusion-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[For ImageNet $256\times256$, Our DDT-XL/2 achieves a new state-of-the-art performance of {1. 31 FID}~(nearly $4\times$ faster training convergence compared to previous diffusion transformers).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ddt-decoupled-diffusion-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advances and Challenges in Foundation Agents: From Brain-Inspired Intelligence to Evolutionary, Collaborative, and Safe Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-and-challenges-in-foundation-agents</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The advent of large language models (LLMs) has catalyzed a transformative shift in artificial intelligence, paving the way for advanced intelligent agents capable of sophisticated reasoning, robust perception, and versatile action across diverse domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/advances-and-challenges-in-foundation-agents</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IndexTTS: An Industrial-Level Controllable and Efficient Zero-Shot Text-To-Speech System</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indextts-an-industrial-level-controllable-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recently, large language model (LLM) based text-to-speech (TTS) systems have gradually become the mainstream in the industry due to their high naturalness and powerful zero-shot voice cloning capabilities. Here, we introduce the IndexTTS system, which is mainly based on the XTTS and Tortoise model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/indextts-an-industrial-level-controllable-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zep: A Temporal Knowledge Graph Architecture for Agent Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zep-a-temporal-knowledge-graph-architecture</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Zep, a novel memory layer service for AI agents that outperforms the current state-of-the-art system, MemGPT, in the Deep Memory Retrieval (DMR) benchmark.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/zep-a-temporal-knowledge-graph-architecture</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGGT: Visual Geometry Grounded Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present VGGT, a feed-forward neural network that directly infers all key 3D attributes of a scene, including camera parameters, point maps, depth maps, and 3D point tracks, from one, a few, or hundreds of its views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark-TTS: An Efficient LLM-Based Text-to-Speech Model with Single-Stream Decoupled Speech Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2503-01710</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have driven significant progress in zero-shot text-to-speech (TTS) synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2503-01710</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio-visual Controlled Video Diffusion with Masked Selective State Spaces Modeling for Natural Talking Head Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-controlled-video-diffusion-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we introduce \textbf{ACTalker}, an end-to-end video diffusion framework that supports both multi-signals control and single-signal control for talking head video generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/audio-visual-controlled-video-diffusion-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent S2: A Compositional Generalist-Specialist Framework for Computer Use Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-s2-a-compositional-generalist</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Computer use agents automate digital tasks by directly interacting with graphical user interfaces (GUIs) on computers and mobile devices, offering significant potential to enhance human productivity by completing an open-ended space of user queries.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/agent-s2-a-compositional-generalist</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-ImgEval: A Comprehensive Benchmark for Diagnosing GPT4o in Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-imgeval-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recent breakthroughs in OpenAI's GPT4o model have demonstrated surprisingly good capabilities in image generation and editing, resulting in significant excitement in the community.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-imgeval-a-comprehensive-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympus: A Universal Task Router for Computer Vision Tasks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olympus-a-universal-task-router-for-computer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Olympus, a new approach that transforms Multimodal Large Language Models (MLLMs) into a unified framework capable of handling a wide array of computer vision tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/olympus-a-universal-task-router-for-computer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LightRAG: Simple and Fast Retrieval-Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightrag-simple-and-fast-retrieval-augmented</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) systems enhance large language models (LLMs) by integrating external knowledge sources, enabling more accurate and contextually relevant responses tailored to user needs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lightrag-simple-and-fast-retrieval-augmented</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVDQuant: Absorbing Outliers by Low-Rank Components for 4-Bit Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdqunat-absorbing-outliers-by-low-rank</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this, we co-design an inference engine Nunchaku that fuses the kernels of the low-rank branch into those of the low-bit branch to cut off redundant memory access.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/svdqunat-absorbing-outliers-by-low-rank</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking RL Scaling for Vision Language Models: A Transparent, From-Scratch Framework and Comprehensive Evaluation Scheme</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-rl-scaling-for-vision-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Reinforcement learning (RL) has recently shown strong potential in improving the reasoning capabilities of large language models and is now being actively extended to vision-language models (VLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/rethinking-rl-scaling-for-vision-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFG-Zero*: Improved Classifier-Free Guidance for Flow Matching Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfg-zero-improved-classifier-free-guidance</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Classifier-Free Guidance (CFG) is a widely adopted technique in diffusion/flow models to improve image fidelity and controllability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cfg-zero-improved-classifier-free-guidance</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SkyReels-A2: Compose Anything in Video Diffusion Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyreels-a2-compose-anything-in-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents SkyReels-A2, a controllable video generation framework capable of assembling arbitrary visual elements (e. g., characters, objects, backgrounds) into synthesized videos based on textual prompts while maintaining strict consistency with reference images for each element.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/skyreels-a2-compose-anything-in-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHM: Large Animatable Human Reconstruction Model from a Single Image in Seconds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Animatable 3D human reconstruction from a single image is a challenging problem due to the ambiguity in decoupling geometry, appearance, and deformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiniteYou: Flexible Photo Recrafting While Preserving Your Identity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving flexible and high-fidelity identity-preserved image generation remains formidable, particularly with advanced Diffusion Transformers (DiTs) like FLUX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-SWE-bench: A Multilingual Benchmark for Issue Resolving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-swe-bench-a-multilingual-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The task of issue resolving is to modify a codebase to generate a patch that addresses a given issue.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-swe-bench-a-multilingual-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Deep Search: Democratizing Search with Open-source Reasoning Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Open Search Tool is a novel web search tool that outperforms proprietary counterparts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/open-deep-search-democratizing-search-with</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
