<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 09:20:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Human Motion Diffusion Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce Motion Diffusion Model (MDM), a carefully adapted classifier-free diffusion-based generative model for the human motion domain.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/human-motion-diffusion-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TabDDPM: Modelling Tabular Data with Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabddpm-modelling-tabular-data-with-diffusion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Denoising diffusion probabilistic models are currently becoming the leading paradigm of generative modeling for many important data modalities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tabddpm-modelling-tabular-data-with-diffusion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DreamBooth: Fine Tuning Text-to-Image Diffusion Models for Subject-Driven Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreambooth-fine-tuning-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once the subject is embedded in the output domain of the model, the unique identifier can then be used to synthesize fully-novel photorealistic images of the subject contextualized in different scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreambooth-fine-tuning-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GET3D: A Generative Model of High Quality 3D Textured Shapes Learned from Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get3d-a-generative-model-of-high-quality-3d</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As several industries are moving towards modeling massive 3D virtual worlds, the need for content creation tools that can scale in terms of the quantity, quality, and diversity of 3D content is becoming evident.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/get3d-a-generative-model-of-high-quality-3d</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Neural Networks to Detect Weeds from Crops in Agricultural Environments in Real-Time: A Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-networks-to-detect-weeds-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Machine vision has wide applications in agriculture, including the detection of weeds and pests in crops.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-neural-networks-to-detect-weeds-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Reinforcement Learning with Implicit Q-Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-reinforcement-learning-with-implicit</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The main insight in our work is that, instead of evaluating unseen actions from the latest policy, we can approximate the policy improvement step implicitly by treating the state value function as a random variable, with randomness determined by the action (while still integrating over the dynamics to avoid excessive optimism), and then taking a state conditional upper expectile of this random variable to estimate the value of the best actions in that state.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-reinforcement-learning-with-implicit</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Few-Shot Learning Without Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-few-shot-learning-without-prompts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This simple framework requires no prompts or verbalizers, and achieves high accuracy with orders of magnitude less parameters than existing techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-few-shot-learning-without-prompts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Min-Max Similarity: A Contrastive Semi-Supervised Deep Learning Network for Surgical Tools Segmentation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/min-max-similarity-a-contrastive-learning</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address this issue, we proposed a semi-supervised segmentation network based on contrastive learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/min-max-similarity-a-contrastive-learning</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dilated Neighborhood Attention Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-neighborhood-attention-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[These models typically employ localized attention mechanisms, such as the sliding-window Neighborhood Attention (NA) or Swin Transformer's Shifted Window Self Attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dilated-neighborhood-attention-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SoundStream: An End-to-End Neural Audio Codec</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soundstream-an-end-to-end-neural-audio-codec</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SoundStream, a novel neural audio codec that can efficiently compress speech, music and general audio at bitrates normally targeted by speech-tailored codecs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/soundstream-an-end-to-end-neural-audio-codec</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LAVIS: A Library for Language-Vision Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lavis-a-library-for-language-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce LAVIS, an open-source deep learning library for LAnguage-VISion research and applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lavis-a-library-for-language-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protein structure generation via folding diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protein-structure-generation-via-folding</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The ability to computationally generate novel yet physically foldable protein structures could lead to new biological discoveries and new treatments targeting yet incurable diseases.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/protein-structure-generation-via-folding</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Speech Recognition via Large-Scale Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-speech-recognition-via-large-scale</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study the capabilities of speech processing systems trained simply to predict large amounts of transcripts of audio on the internet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/robust-speech-recognition-via-large-scale</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>rl</title>
      <link>https://github.com/facebookresearch/rl</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A modular, primitive-first, python-first PyTorch library for Reinforcement Learning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/facebookresearch/rl</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-Resolution Image Synthesis with Latent Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-synthesis-with-latent</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By decomposing the image formation process into a sequential application of denoising autoencoders, diffusion models (DMs) achieve state-of-the-art synthesis results on image data and beyond.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/high-resolution-image-synthesis-with-latent</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>towhee</title>
      <link>https://github.com/towhee-io/towhee</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Towhee is a framework that is dedicated to making neural data processing pipelines simple and fast.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/towhee-io/towhee</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega: Moving Average Equipped Gated Attention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mega-moving-average-equipped-gated-attention</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The design choices in the Transformer attention mechanism, including weak inductive bias and quadratic computational complexity, have limited its application for modeling long sequences.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mega-moving-average-equipped-gated-attention</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VToonify: Controllable High-Resolution Portrait Video Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Although a series of successful portrait image toonification models built upon the powerful StyleGAN have been proposed, these image-oriented methods have obvious limitations when applied to videos, such as the fixed frame size, the requirement of face alignment, missing non-facial details and temporal inconsistency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vtoonify-controllable-high-resolution</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EditEval: An Instruction-Based Benchmark for Text Improvements</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editeval-an-instruction-based-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Evaluation of text generation to date has primarily focused on content created sequentially, rather than improvements on a piece of text.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/editeval-an-instruction-based-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pseudo Numerical Methods for Diffusion Models on Manifolds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-numerical-methods-for-diffusion-models-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Under such a perspective, we propose pseudo numerical methods for diffusion models (PNDMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pseudo-numerical-methods-for-diffusion-models-1</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
