<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:15:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>GLM-130B: An Open Bilingual Pre-trained Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-130b-an-open-bilingual-pre-trained-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GLM-130B, a bilingual (English and Chinese) pre-trained language model with 130 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-130b-an-open-bilingual-pre-trained-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HyperReel: High-Fidelity 6-DoF Video with Ray-Conditioned Sampling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperreel-high-fidelity-6-dof-video-with-ray</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Volumetric scene representations enable photorealistic view synthesis for static scenes and form the basis of several existing 6-DoF video techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperreel-high-fidelity-6-dof-video-with-ray</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muse: Text-To-Image Generation via Masked Generative Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muse-text-to-image-generation-via-masked</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Compared to pixel-space diffusion models, such as Imagen and DALL-E 2, Muse is significantly more efficient due to the use of discrete tokens and requiring fewer sampling iterations; compared to autoregressive models, such as Parti, Muse is more efficient due to the use of parallel decoding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/muse-text-to-image-generation-via-masked</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dominant sequence transduction models are based on complex recurrent or convolutional neural networks in an encoder-decoder configuration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Box2Mask: Box-supervised Instance Segmentation via Level-set Evolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box2mask-box-supervised-instance-segmentation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to fully supervised methods using pixel-wise mask labels, box-supervised instance segmentation takes advantage of simple box annotations, which has recently attracted increasing research attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/box2mask-box-supervised-instance-segmentation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConvNeXt V2: Co-designing and Scaling ConvNets with Masked Autoencoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This co-design of self-supervised learning techniques and architectural improvement results in a new model family called ConvNeXt V2, which significantly improves the performance of pure ConvNets on various recognition benchmarks, including ImageNet classification, COCO detection, and ADE20K segmentation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/convnext-v2-co-designing-and-scaling-convnets</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PACO: Parts and Attributes of Common Objects</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paco-parts-and-attributes-of-common-objects</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This motivates the need for large datasets which go beyond traditional object masks and provide richer annotations such as part masks and attributes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paco-parts-and-attributes-of-common-objects</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reasoning over Different Types of Knowledge Graphs: Static, Temporal and Multi-Modal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-over-different-types-of-knowledge</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The early works in this domain mainly focus on static KGR and tend to directly apply general knowledge graph embedding models to the reasoning task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reasoning-over-different-types-of-knowledge</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DynaGAN: Dynamic Few-shot Adaptation of GANs to Multiple Domains</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynagan-dynamic-few-shot-adaptation-of-gans</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose DynaGAN, a novel few-shot domain-adaptation method for multiple target domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dynagan-dynamic-few-shot-adaptation-of-gans</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colossal-AI: A Unified Deep Learning System For Large-Scale Parallel Training</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colossal-ai-a-unified-deep-learning-system</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The success of Transformer models has pushed the deep learning model scale to billions of parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/colossal-ai-a-unified-deep-learning-system</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red Teaming Language Models to Reduce Harms: Methods, Scaling Behaviors, and Lessons Learned</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-teaming-language-models-to-reduce-harms</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We provide our own analysis of the data and find a variety of harmful outputs, which range from offensive language to more subtly harmful non-violent unethical outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/red-teaming-language-models-to-reduce-harms</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT Takes the Bar Exam</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-takes-the-bar-exam</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nearly all jurisdictions in the United States require a professional license exam, commonly referred to as "the Bar Exam," as a precondition for law practice.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gpt-takes-the-bar-exam</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cramming: Training a Language Model on a Single GPU in One Day</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cramming-training-a-language-model-on-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent trends in language modeling have focused on increasing performance through scaling, and have resulted in an environment where training language models is out of reach for most researchers and practitioners.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cramming-training-a-language-model-on-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unilm</title>
      <link>https://github.com/microsoft/unilm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale Self-supervised Pre-training Across Tasks, Languages, and Modalities]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://github.com/microsoft/unilm</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ALIKE: Accurate and Lightweight Keypoint Detection and Descriptor Extraction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alike-accurate-and-lightweight-keypoint</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The reprojection loss is then proposed to directly optimize these sub-pixel keypoints, and the dispersity peak loss is presented for accurate keypoints regularization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alike-accurate-and-lightweight-keypoint</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point-E: A System for Generating 3D Point Clouds from Complex Prompts</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-e-a-system-for-generating-3d-point</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is in stark contrast to state-of-the-art generative image models, which produce samples in a number of seconds or minutes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/point-e-a-system-for-generating-3d-point</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CiT: Curation in Training for Effective Vision-Language Data</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cit-curation-in-training-for-effective-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large vision-language models are generally applicable to many downstream tasks, but come at an exorbitant training cost that only large institutions can afford.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cit-curation-in-training-for-effective-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text2Poster: Laying out Stylized Texts on Retrieved Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2poster-laying-out-stylized-texts-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Poster generation is a significant task for a wide range of applications, which is often time-consuming and requires lots of manual editing and artistic experience.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text2poster-laying-out-stylized-texts-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Killer: Optimizing Backdoor Trigger Yields a Stealthy and Powerful Data Poisoning Attack</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silent-killer-optimizing-backdoor-trigger</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In contrast to previous attacks, both the poison and the trigger in our method are stealthy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/silent-killer-optimizing-backdoor-trigger</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross Modal Transformer via Coordinates Encoding for 3D Object Dectection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-transformer-via-coordinates</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a robust 3D detector, named Cross Modal Transformer (CMT), for end-to-end 3D multi-modal detection.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-modal-transformer-via-coordinates</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
