<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:17:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Byte Latent Transformer: Patches Scale Better Than Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byte-latent-transformer-patches-scale-better</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce the Byte Latent Transformer (BLT), a new byte-level LLM architecture that, for the first time, matches tokenization-based LLM performance at scale with significant improvements in inference efficiency and robustness.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/byte-latent-transformer-patches-scale-better</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Concept Models: Language Modeling in a Sentence Representation Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-concept-models-language-modeling-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an attempt at an architecture which operates on an explicit higher-level semantic representation, which we name a concept.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-concept-models-language-modeling-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Flow Fields in Attention for Controllable Person Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we show that our loss is model-agnostic and can be used to improve the performance of other diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-VL2: Mixture-of-Experts Vision-Language Models for Advanced Multimodal Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl2-mixture-of-experts-vision</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present DeepSeek-VL2, an advanced series of large Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) Vision-Language Models that significantly improves upon its predecessor, DeepSeek-VL, through two key major upgrades.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepseek-vl2-mixture-of-experts-vision</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaze-LLE: Gaze Target Estimation via Large-Scale Learned Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-lle-gaze-target-estimation-via-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We address the problem of gaze target estimation, which aims to predict where a person is looking in a scene.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/gaze-lle-gaze-target-estimation-via-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Causal Diffusion Transformers for Generative Modeling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-diffusion-transformers-for-generative</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce Causal Diffusion as the autoregressive (AR) counterpart of Diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/causal-diffusion-transformers-for-generative</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary-steps Image Super-resolution via Diffusion Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-steps-image-super-resolution-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a new image super-resolution (SR) technique based on diffusion inversion, aiming at harnessing the rich image priors encapsulated in large pre-trained diffusion models to improve SR performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-steps-image-super-resolution-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FunAudioLLM: Voice Understanding and Generation Foundation Models for Natural Interaction Between Humans and LLMs</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funaudiollm-voice-understanding-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This report introduces FunAudioLLM, a model family designed to enhance natural voice interactions between humans and large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/funaudiollm-voice-understanding-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Evolved Universal Transformer Memory</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Prior methods propose to offset the escalating costs of modern foundation models by dropping specific parts of their contexts with hand-designed rules, while attempting to preserve their original performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-evolved-universal-transformer-memory</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EasyVolcap: Accelerating Neural Volumetric Video Research</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyvolcap-accelerating-neural-volumetric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Volumetric video is a technology that digitally records dynamic events such as artistic performances, sporting events, and remote conversations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/easyvolcap-accelerating-neural-volumetric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Seal: Open and Efficient Video Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-seal-open-and-efficient-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To reduce these gaps, this paper introduces Video Seal, a comprehensive framework for neural video watermarking and a competitive open-sourced model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/video-seal-open-and-efficient-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SLAM3R: Real-Time Dense Scene Reconstruction from Monocular RGB Videos</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slam3r-real-time-dense-scene-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we introduce \textbf{SLAM3R}, a novel and effective monocular RGB SLAM system for real-time and high-quality dense 3D reconstruction.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/slam3r-real-time-dense-scene-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyra: An Efficient and Speech-Centric Framework for Omni-Cognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-an-efficient-and-speech-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) evolve, expanding beyond single-domain capabilities is essential to meet the demands for more versatile and efficient AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-an-efficient-and-speech-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docling Technical Report</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docling-technical-report</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This technical report introduces Docling, an easy to use, self-contained, MIT-licensed open-source package for PDF document conversion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/docling-technical-report</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HelloMeme: Integrating Spatial Knitting Attentions to Embed High-Level and Fidelity-Rich Conditions in Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellomeme-integrating-spatial-knitting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose an effective method for inserting adapters into text-to-image foundation models, which enables the execution of complex downstream tasks while preserving the generalization ability of the base model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hellomeme-integrating-spatial-knitting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StableAnimator: High-Quality Identity-Preserving Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</link>
      <description><![CDATA[During inference, we propose a novel Hamilton-Jacobi-Bellman (HJB) equation-based optimization to further enhance the face quality.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stableanimator-high-quality-identity</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FireFlow: Fast Inversion of Rectified Flow for Image Semantic Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fireflow-fast-inversion-of-rectified-flow-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Though Rectified Flows (ReFlows) with distillation offers a promising way for fast sampling, its fast inversion transforms images back to structured noise for recovery and following editing remains unsolved.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fireflow-fast-inversion-of-rectified-flow-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best-of-N Jailbreaking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-of-n-jailbreaking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We find that BoN Jailbreaking achieves high attack success rates (ASRs) on closed-source language models, such as 89% on GPT-4o and 78% on Claude 3. 5 Sonnet when sampling 10, 000 augmented prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/best-of-n-jailbreaking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Representing Long Volumetric Video with Temporal Gaussian Hierarchy</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-long-volumetric-video-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In addition, the tree-like structure of the Gaussian hierarchy allows us to efficiently represent the scene at a particular moment with a subset of Gaussian primitives, leading to nearly constant GPU memory usage during the training or rendering regardless of the video length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/representing-long-volumetric-video-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs-as-Judges: A Comprehensive Survey on LLM-based Evaluation Methods</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-as-judges-a-comprehensive-survey-on-llm</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we provide a detailed analysis of the limitations of LLM judges and discuss potential future directions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llms-as-judges-a-comprehensive-survey-on-llm</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
