<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 09:13:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To discriminate the difference in parameter scale, the research community has coined the term large language models (LLM) for the PLMs of significant size.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-of-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragDiffusion: Harnessing Diffusion Models for Interactive Point-based Image Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragdiffusion-harnessing-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we extend such an editing framework to diffusion models and propose DragDiffusion.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragdiffusion-harnessing-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Survey on Evaluation of Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-evaluation-of-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) are gaining increasing popularity in both academia and industry, owing to their unprecedented performance in various applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-survey-on-evaluation-of-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>h2oGPT: Democratizing Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2ogpt-democratizing-large-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Applications built on top of Large Language Models (LLMs) such as GPT-4 represent a revolution in AI due to their human-level capabilities in natural language processing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/h2ogpt-democratizing-large-language-models</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focused Transformer: Contrastive Training for Context Scaling</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-transformer-contrastive-training-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This novel approach enhances the structure of the (key, value) space, enabling an extension of the context length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/focused-transformer-contrastive-training-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatLaw: Open-Source Legal Large Language Model with Integrated External Knowledge Bases</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlaw-open-source-legal-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, we propose a self-attention method to enhance the ability of large models to overcome errors present in reference data, further optimizing the issue of model hallucinations at the model level and improving the problem-solving capabilities of large models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/chatlaw-open-source-legal-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segment Anything Meets Point Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-meets-point-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SAM-PT leverages robust and sparse point selection and propagation techniques for mask generation, demonstrating that a SAM-based segmentation tracker can yield strong zero-shot performance across popular video object segmentation benchmarks, including DAVIS, YouTube-VOS, and MOSE.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/segment-anything-meets-point-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DragonDiffusion: Enabling Drag-style Manipulation on Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragondiffusion-enabling-drag-style</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we construct classifier guidance based on the strong correspondence of intermediate features in the diffusion model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dragondiffusion-enabling-drag-style</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SDXL: Improving Latent Diffusion Models for High-Resolution Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdxl-improving-latent-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present SDXL, a latent diffusion model for text-to-image synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sdxl-improving-latent-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MME: A Comprehensive Evaluation Benchmark for Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mme-a-comprehensive-evaluation-benchmark-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multimodal Large Language Model (MLLM) relies on the powerful LLM to perform multimodal tasks, showing amazing emergent abilities in recent studies, such as writing poems based on an image.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mme-a-comprehensive-evaluation-benchmark-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flacuna: Unleashing the Problem Solving Power of Vicuna using FLAN Fine-Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flacuna-unleashing-the-problem-solving-power</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Interestingly, despite being introduced four years ago, T5-based LLMs, such as FLAN-T5, continue to outperform the latest decoder-based LLMs, such as LLAMA and VICUNA, on tasks that require general problem-solving skills.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flacuna-unleashing-the-problem-solving-power</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GLM-130B: An Open Bilingual Pre-trained Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-130b-an-open-bilingual-pre-trained-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce GLM-130B, a bilingual (English and Chinese) pre-trained language model with 130 billion parameters.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/glm-130b-an-open-bilingual-pre-trained-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleDrop: Text-to-Image Generation in Any Style</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in-any</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Pre-trained large text-to-image models synthesize impressive images with an appropriate use of text prompts.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/styledrop-text-to-image-generation-in-any</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WizardCoder: Empowering Code Large Language Models with Evol-Instruct</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardcoder-empowering-code-large-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Moreover, our model even outperforms the largest closed LLMs, Anthropic's Claude and Google's Bard, on HumanEval and HumanEval+.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/wizardcoder-empowering-code-large-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mPLUG-DocOwl: Modularized Multimodal Large Language Model for Document Understanding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-docowl-modularized-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Nevertheless, without in-domain training, these models tend to ignore fine-grained OCR features, such as sophisticated tables or large blocks of text, which are essential for OCR-free document understanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mplug-docowl-modularized-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree of Thoughts: Deliberate Problem Solving with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-thoughts-deliberate-problem-solving</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Language models are increasingly being deployed for general problem solving across a wide range of tasks, but are still confined to token-level, left-to-right decision-making processes during inference.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tree-of-thoughts-deliberate-problem-solving</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CodeGen2: Lessons for Training LLMs on Programming and Natural Languages</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we attempt to render the training of LLMs for program synthesis more efficient by unifying four key components: (1) model architectures, (2) learning methods, (3) infill sampling, and, (4) data distributions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/codegen2-lessons-for-training-llms-on</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisCo: Disentangled Control for Referring Human Dance Generation in Real World</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-disentangled-control-for-referring</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generative AI has made significant strides in computer vision, particularly in image/video synthesis conditioned on text descriptions.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/disco-disentangled-control-for-referring</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaMA-Adapter V2: Parameter-Efficient Visual Instruction Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-v2-parameter-efficient-visual</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This strategy effectively alleviates the interference between the two tasks of image-text alignment and instruction following and achieves strong multi-modal reasoning with only a small-scale image-text and instruction dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llama-adapter-v2-parameter-efficient-visual</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepfakeBench: A Comprehensive Benchmark of Deepfake Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfakebench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To fill this gap, we present the first comprehensive benchmark for deepfake detection, called DeepfakeBench, which offers three key contributions: 1) a unified data management system to ensure consistent input across all detectors, 2) an integrated framework for state-of-the-art methods implementation, and 3) standardized evaluation metrics and protocols to promote transparency and reproducibility.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepfakebench-a-comprehensive-benchmark-of</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
