<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 21:08:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Monolith: Real Time Recommendation System With Collisionless Embedding Table</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monolith-real-time-recommendation-system-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present Monolith, a system tailored for online training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/monolith-real-time-recommendation-system-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating the Search for Artificial Life with Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-search-for-artificial-life</link>
      <description><![CDATA[With the recent Nobel Prize awarded for radical advances in protein discovery, foundation models (FMs) for exploring large combinatorial spaces promise to revolutionize many scientific fields.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/automating-the-search-for-artificial-life</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arbitrary-steps Image Super-resolution via Diffusion Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-steps-image-super-resolution-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This study presents a new image super-resolution (SR) technique based on diffusion inversion, aiming at harnessing the rich image priors encapsulated in large pre-trained diffusion models to improve SR performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arbitrary-steps-image-super-resolution-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLEAR: Conv-Like Linearization Revs Pre-Trained Diffusion Transformers Up</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clear-conv-like-linearization-revs-pre</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Diffusion Transformers (DiT) have become a leading architecture in image generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clear-conv-like-linearization-revs-pre</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter, Better, Faster, Longer: A Modern Bidirectional Encoder for Fast, Memory Efficient, and Long Context Finetuning and Inference</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smarter-better-faster-longer-a-modern</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Encoder-only transformer models such as BERT offer a great performance-size tradeoff for retrieval and classification tasks with respect to larger decoder-only models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/smarter-better-faster-longer-a-modern</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dora: Sampling and Benchmarking for 3D Shape Variational Auto-Encoders</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-sampling-and-benchmarking-for-3d-shape-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the widely adopted uniform point sampling strategy in Shape VAE training often leads to a significant loss of geometric details, limiting the quality of shape reconstruction and downstream generation tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-sampling-and-benchmarking-for-3d-shape-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DisPose: Disentangling Pose Guidance for Controllable Human Image Animation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispose-disentangling-pose-guidance-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Specifically, we generate a dense motion field from a sparse motion field and the reference image, which provides region-level dense guidance while maintaining the generalization of the sparse pose control.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dispose-disentangling-pose-guidance-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking in Space: How Multimodal Large Language Models See, Remember, and Recall Spaces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-in-space-how-multimodal-large</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Humans possess the visual-spatial intelligence to remember spaces from sequential visual observations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/thinking-in-space-how-multimodal-large</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Concept Models: Language Modeling in a Sentence Representation Space</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-concept-models-language-modeling-in-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an attempt at an architecture which operates on an explicit higher-level semantic representation, which we name a concept.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-concept-models-language-modeling-in-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Measure of Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-measure-of-intelligence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To make deliberate progress towards more intelligent and more human-like artificial systems, we need to be following an appropriate feedback signal: we need to be able to define and evaluate intelligence in a way that enables comparisons between two systems, as well as comparisons with humans.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-measure-of-intelligence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenEMMA: Open-Source Multimodal Model for End-to-End Autonomous Driving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openemma-open-source-multimodal-model-for-end</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Furthermore, OpenEMMA demonstrates effectiveness, generalizability, and robustness across a variety of challenging driving scenarios, offering a more efficient and effective approach to autonomous driving.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/openemma-open-source-multimodal-model-for-end</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRT-o1: Optimized Deep Reasoning Translation via Long Chain-of-Thought</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drt-o1-optimized-deep-reasoning-translation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To simulate LLMs' long thought ability in MT, we first mine sentences containing similes or metaphors from existing literature books, and then develop a multi-agent framework to translate these sentences via long thought.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/drt-o1-optimized-deep-reasoning-translation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KAG: Boosting LLMs in Professional Domains via Knowledge Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2409-13731</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The recently developed retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) technology has enabled the efficient construction of domain-specific applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2409-13731</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning Flow Fields in Attention for Controllable Person Image Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Additionally, we show that our loss is model-agnostic and can be used to improve the performance of other diffusion models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-flow-fields-in-attention-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyra: An Efficient and Speech-Centric Framework for Omni-Cognition</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-an-efficient-and-speech-centric</link>
      <description><![CDATA[As Multi-modal Large Language Models (MLLMs) evolve, expanding beyond single-domain capabilities is essential to meet the demands for more versatile and efficient AI.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lyra-an-efficient-and-speech-centric</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autoregressive Video Generation without Vector Quantization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-video-generation-without</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents a novel approach that enables autoregressive video generation with high efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autoregressive-video-generation-without</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-View Referring Multi-Object Tracking</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-referring-multi-object-tracking</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It introduces the cross-view to obtain the appearances of objects from multiple views, avoiding the problem of the invisible appearances of objects in RMOT task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cross-view-referring-multi-object-tracking</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offline Reinforcement Learning for LLM Multi-Step Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-reinforcement-learning-for-llm-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Direct Preference Optimization (DPO) has shown promise in aligning LLMs with human preferences, it is less suitable for multi-step reasoning tasks because (1) DPO relies on paired preference data, which is not readily available for multi-step reasoning tasks, and (2) it treats all tokens uniformly, making it ineffective for credit assignment in multi-step reasoning tasks, which often come with sparse reward.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/offline-reinforcement-learning-for-llm-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Allegro: Open the Black Box of Commercial-Level Video Generation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allegro-open-the-black-box-of-commercial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Significant advancements have been made in the field of video generation, with the open-source community contributing a wealth of research papers and tools for training high-quality models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/allegro-open-the-black-box-of-commercial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imitate, Explore, and Self-Improve: A Reproduction Report on Slow-thinking Reasoning Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitate-explore-and-self-improve-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce an ``imitate, explore, and self-improve'' framework, denoted as \textbf{STILL-2}, as our primary technical approach to train the reasoning model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imitate-explore-and-self-improve-a</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
