<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 09:17:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ImageNet Classification with Deep Convolutional Neural Networks</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagenet-classification-with-deep</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We trained a large, deep convolutional neural network to classify the 1. 3 million high-resolution images in the LSVRC-2010 ImageNet training set into the 1000 different classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/imagenet-classification-with-deep</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VGGT: Visual Geometry Grounded Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present VGGT, a feed-forward neural network that directly infers all key 3D attributes of a scene, including camera parameters, point maps, depth maps, and 3D point tracks, from one, a few, or hundreds of its views.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/vggt-visual-geometry-grounded-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InfiniteYou: Flexible Photo Recrafting While Preserving Your Identity</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Achieving flexible and high-fidelity identity-preserved image generation remains formidable, particularly with advanced Diffusion Transformers (DiTs) like FLUX.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/infiniteyou-flexible-photo-recrafting-while</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LHM: Large Animatable Human Reconstruction Model from a Single Image in Seconds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Animatable 3D human reconstruction from a single image is a challenging problem due to the ambiguity in decoupling geometry, appearance, and deformation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lhm-large-animatable-human-reconstruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KBLaM: Knowledge Base augmented Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kblam-knowledge-base-augmented-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose Knowledge Base augmented Language Model (KBLaM), a new method for augmenting Large Language Models (LLMs) with external knowledge.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/kblam-knowledge-base-augmented-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Step-Video-TI2V Technical Report: A State-of-the-Art Text-Driven Image-to-Video Generation Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-video-ti2v-technical-report-a-state-of</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Step-Video-TI2V, a state-of-the-art text-driven image-to-video generation model with 30B parameters, capable of generating videos up to 102 frames based on both text and image inputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/step-video-ti2v-technical-report-a-state-of</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UI-TARS: Pioneering Automated GUI Interaction with Native Agents</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ui-tars-pioneering-automated-gui-interaction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces UI-TARS, a native GUI agent model that solely perceives the screenshots as input and performs human-like interactions (e. g., keyboard and mouse operations).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ui-tars-pioneering-automated-gui-interaction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock Pose Diversity: Accurate and Efficient Implicit Keypoint-based Spatiotemporal Diffusion for Audio-driven Talking Portrait</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlock-pose-diversity-accurate-and-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Keypoint-based methods effectively preserve character identity but struggle to capture fine facial details due to the fixed points limitation of the 3D Morphable Model.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unlock-pose-diversity-accurate-and-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spark-TTS: An Efficient LLM-Based Text-to-Speech Model with Single-Stream Decoupled Speech Tokens</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2503-01710</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent advancements in large language models (LLMs) have driven significant progress in zero-shot text-to-speech (TTS) synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/2503-01710</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Overthinking: A Survey on Efficient Reasoning for Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-overthinking-a-survey-on-efficient</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) have demonstrated remarkable capabilities in complex tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stop-overthinking-a-survey-on-efficient</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cube: A Roblox View of 3D Intelligence</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cube-a-roblox-view-of-3d-intelligence</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We show how our tokenization scheme can be used in applications for text-to-shape generation, shape-to-text generation and text-to-scene generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cube-a-roblox-view-of-3d-intelligence</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search-R1: Training LLMs to Reason and Leverage Search Engines with Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-r1-training-llms-to-reason-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Efficiently acquiring external knowledge and up-to-date information is essential for effective reasoning and text generation in large language models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/search-r1-training-llms-to-reason-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcement Learning for Reasoning in Small LLMs: What Works and What Doesn't</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-for-reasoning-in-small</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Enhancing the reasoning capabilities of large language models (LLMs) typically relies on massive computational resources and extensive datasets, limiting accessibility for resource-constrained settings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/reinforcement-learning-for-reasoning-in-small</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neural Fields with Thermal Activations for Arbitrary-Scale Super-Resolution</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fields-with-thermal-activations-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a novel way to design neural fields such that points can be queried with an adaptive Gaussian PSF, so as to guarantee correct anti-aliasing at any desired output resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/neural-fields-with-thermal-activations-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunyuan3D 2.0: Scaling Diffusion Models for High Resolution Textured 3D Assets Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-0-scaling-diffusion-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This system includes two foundation components: a large-scale shape generation model -- Hunyuan3D-DiT, and a large-scale texture synthesis model -- Hunyuan3D-Paint.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hunyuan3d-2-0-scaling-diffusion-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmos-Reason1: From Physical Common Sense To Embodied Reasoning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmos-reason1-from-physical-common-sense-to</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We begin by defining key capabilities for Physical AI reasoning, with a focus on physical common sense and embodied reasoning.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/cosmos-reason1-from-physical-common-sense-to</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Formulator 2: Iterative Creation of Data Visualizations, with AI Transforming Data Along the Way</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-formulator-2-iteratively-creating-rich</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Data analysts often need to iterate between data transformations and chart designs to create rich visualizations for exploratory data analysis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-formulator-2-iteratively-creating-rich</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sonata: Self-Supervised Learning of Reliable Point Representations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonata-self-supervised-learning-of-reliable</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we question whether we have a reliable self-supervised point cloud model that can be used for diverse 3D tasks via simple linear probing, even with limited data and minimal computation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/sonata-self-supervised-learning-of-reliable</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Scientist: Towards Fully Automated Open-Ended Scientific Discovery</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ai-scientist-towards-fully-automated-open</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This approach signifies the beginning of a new era in scientific discovery in machine learning: bringing the transformative benefits of AI agents to the entire research process of AI itself, and taking us closer to a world where endless affordable creativity and innovation can be unleashed on the world's most challenging problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-ai-scientist-towards-fully-automated-open</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tokenize Image as a Set</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenize-image-as-a-set</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper proposes a fundamentally new paradigm for image generation through set-based tokenization and distribution modeling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tokenize-image-as-a-set</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
