<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2022 09:15:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>DreamBooth: Fine Tuning Text-to-Image Diffusion Models for Subject-Driven Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreambooth-fine-tuning-text-to-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Once the subject is embedded in the output domain of the model, the unique identifier can then be used to synthesize fully-novel photorealistic images of the subject contextualized in different scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dreambooth-fine-tuning-text-to-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLIP-Mesh: Generating textured meshes from text using pretrained image-text models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-mesh-without-3d-supervision-using</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present a technique for zero-shot generation of a 3D model using only a target text prompt.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-to-mesh-without-3d-supervision-using</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOX-PAI: An Improved YOLOX, Stronger and Faster than YOLOv6</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolox-pai-an-improved-yolox-version-by-pai</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop an all-in-one computer vision toolbox named EasyCV to facilitate the use of various SOTA computer vision methods.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolox-pai-an-improved-yolox-version-by-pai</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Gentle Introduction to Conformal Prediction and Distribution-Free Uncertainty Quantification</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-gentle-introduction-to-conformal-prediction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Conformal prediction is a user-friendly paradigm for creating statistically rigorous uncertainty sets/intervals for the predictions of such models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-gentle-introduction-to-conformal-prediction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedBN: Federated Learning on Non-IID Features via Local Batch Normalization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedbn-federated-learning-on-non-iid-features-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The emerging paradigm of federated learning (FL) strives to enable collaborative training of deep models on the network edge without centrally aggregating raw data and hence improving data privacy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fedbn-federated-learning-on-non-iid-features-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProDiff: Progressive Fast Diffusion Model For High-Quality Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodiff-progressive-fast-diffusion-model-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Through the preliminary study on diffusion model parameterization, we find that previous gradient-based TTS models require hundreds or thousands of iterations to guarantee high sample quality, which poses a challenge for accelerating sampling.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prodiff-progressive-fast-diffusion-model-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behavior Trees in Robotics and AI: An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-trees-in-robotics-and-ai-an</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A Behavior Tree (BT) is a way to structure the switching between different tasks in an autonomous agent, such as a robot or a virtual entity in a computer game.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/behavior-trees-in-robotics-and-ai-an</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers are Sample Efficient World Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-sample-efficient-world</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep reinforcement learning agents are notoriously sample inefficient, which considerably limits their application to real-world problems.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/transformers-are-sample-efficient-world</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Free Learning of a Natural Language Interface for Pretrained Face Generators</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-free-learning-of-a-natural-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Fast text2StyleGAN, a natural language interface that adapts pre-trained GANs for text-guided human face synthesis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-free-learning-of-a-natural-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LibMTL: A Python Library for Multi-Task Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libmtl-a-python-library-for-multi-task</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents LibMTL, an open-source Python library built on PyTorch, which provides a unified, comprehensive, reproducible, and extensible implementation framework for Multi-Task Learning (MTL).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/libmtl-a-python-library-for-multi-task</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Image is Worth One Word: Personalizing Text-to-Image Generation using Textual Inversion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-is-worth-one-word-personalizing-text</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Yet, it is unclear how such freedom can be exercised to generate images of specific unique concepts, modify their appearance, or compose them in new roles and novel scenes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-image-is-worth-one-word-personalizing-text</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large-Scale Intelligent Microservices</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-intelligent-microservices</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deploying Machine Learning (ML) algorithms within databases is a challenge due to the varied computational footprints of modern ML algorithms and the myriad of database technologies each with its own restrictive syntax.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-scale-intelligent-microservices</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Synthesis of Artistic Images with Retrieval-Augmented Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In RDMs, a set of nearest neighbors is retrieved from an external database during training for each training instance, and the diffusion model is conditioned on these informative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adan: Adaptive Nesterov Momentum Algorithm for Faster Optimizing Deep Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adan-adaptive-nesterov-momentum-algorithm-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Then Adan adopts NME to estimate the first- and second-order moments of the gradient in adaptive gradient algorithms for convergence acceleration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/adan-adaptive-nesterov-momentum-algorithm-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feature Selection Methods for Uplift Modeling and Heterogeneous Treatment Effect</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-methods-for-uplift-modeling</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Uplift modeling is a causal learning technique that estimates subgroup-level treatment effects.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feature-selection-methods-for-uplift-modeling</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YourTTS: Towards Zero-Shot Multi-Speaker TTS and Zero-Shot Voice Conversion for everyone</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yourtts-towards-zero-shot-multi-speaker-tts</link>
      <description><![CDATA[YourTTS brings the power of a multilingual approach to the task of zero-shot multi-speaker TTS.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yourtts-towards-zero-shot-multi-speaker-tts</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDM: Iterative Distribution Matching for Communication-Efficient Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddm-iterative-distribution-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning~(FL) has recently attracted increasing attention from academia and industry, with the ultimate goal of achieving collaborative training under privacy and communication constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddm-iterative-distribution-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning via Decentralized Dataset Distillation in Resource-Constrained Edge Environments</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-decentralized-dataset</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce a novel federated learning framework, FedD3, which reduces the overall communication volume and with that opens up the concept of federated learning to more application scenarios in network-constrained environments.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/federated-learning-via-decentralized-dataset</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention Is All You Need</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-is-all-you-need</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The dominant sequence transduction models are based on complex recurrent or convolutional neural networks in an encoder-decoder configuration.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/attention-is-all-you-need</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FocusNet: Classifying Better by Focusing on Confusing Classes</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clonalnet-classifying-better-by-focusing-on</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also introduce a novel focus-picking loss function to improve classification accuracy by encouraging FocusNet to focus on the most confusing classes.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/clonalnet-classifying-better-by-focusing-on</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
