<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:17:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>MNN: A Universal and Efficient Inference Engine</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnn-a-universal-and-efficient-inference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deploying deep learning models on mobile devices draws more and more attention recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mnn-a-universal-and-efficient-inference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Industrial Image Anomaly Detection: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-visual-anomaly-detection-in-industrial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we provide a comprehensive review of deep learning-based image anomaly detection techniques, from the perspectives of neural network architectures, levels of supervision, loss functions, metrics and datasets.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deep-visual-anomaly-detection-in-industrial</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAGAS: Automated Evaluation of Retrieval Augmented Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragas-automated-evaluation-of-retrieval</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce RAGAs (Retrieval Augmented Generation Assessment), a framework for reference-free evaluation of Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) pipelines.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ragas-automated-evaluation-of-retrieval</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pySLAM: An Open-Source, Modular, and Extensible Framework for SLAM</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyslam-an-open-source-modular-and-extensible</link>
      <description><![CDATA[pySLAM is an open-source Python framework for Visual SLAM, supporting monocular, stereo, and RGB-D cameras.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyslam-an-open-source-modular-and-extensible</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Large Language Models for Cyber Security: A Systematic Literature Review</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-cyber-security-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Overall, our survey provides a comprehensive overview of the current state-of-the-art in LLM4Security and identifies several promising directions for future research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/large-language-models-for-cyber-security-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Empirical Study of Mamba-based Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-mamba-based-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[On an additional 23 long-context tasks, the hybrid model continues to closely match or exceed the Transformer on average.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/an-empirical-study-of-mamba-based-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning Multimodal LLM with Human Preference: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-multimodal-llm-with-human-preference</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we aim to provide a comprehensive and systematic review of alignment algorithms for MLLMs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/aligning-multimodal-llm-with-human-preference</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TinyLlama: An Open-Source Small Language Model</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllama-an-open-source-small-language-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present TinyLlama, a compact 1. 1B language model pretrained on around 1 trillion tokens for approximately 3 epochs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/tinyllama-an-open-source-small-language-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards Deeper, Lighter and Interpretable Cross Network for CTR Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-deeper-lighter-and-interpretable-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[It is crucial to effectively model feature interactions to improve the prediction performance of CTR models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/towards-deeper-lighter-and-interpretable-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optuna: A Next-generation Hyperparameter Optimization Framework</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optuna-a-next-generation-hyperparameter</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We will present the design-techniques that became necessary in the development of the software that meets the above criteria, and demonstrate the power of our new design through experimental results and real world applications.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/optuna-a-next-generation-hyperparameter</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Multi-modal Recommender Systems by Denoising and Aligning Multi-modal Content and User Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-multi-modal-recommender-systems-by</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multi-modal recommender systems (MRSs) are pivotal in diverse online web platforms and have garnered considerable attention in recent years.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/improving-multi-modal-recommender-systems-by</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the Use and Misuse of Absorbing States in Multi-agent Reinforcement Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-and-misuse-of-absorbing-states-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we first demonstrate that sample complexity increases with the quantity of absorbing states in a toy supervised learning task for a fully connected network, while attention is more robust to variable size input.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/on-the-use-and-misuse-of-absorbing-states-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pyribs: A Bare-Bones Python Library for Quality Diversity Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyribs-a-bare-bones-python-library-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent years have seen a rise in the popularity of quality diversity (QD) optimization, a branch of optimization that seeks to find a collection of diverse, high-performing solutions to a given problem.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pyribs-a-bare-bones-python-library-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyperbolic Dataset Distillation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-dataset-distillation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the computational and storage challenges posed by large-scale datasets in deep learning, dataset distillation has been proposed to synthesize a compact dataset that replaces the original while maintaining comparable model performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hyperbolic-dataset-distillation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyTorch: An Imperative Style, High-Performance Deep Learning Library</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-an-imperative-style-high-performance-1</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Deep learning frameworks have often focused on either usability or speed, but not both.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pytorch-an-imperative-style-high-performance-1</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Efficient Prediction of SO(3)-Equivariant Hamiltonian Matrices via SO(2) Local Frames</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-prediction-of-so-3-equivariant</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This is achieved by introducing a set of new efficient and powerful SO(2)-equivariant operations and performing all off-diagonal feature updates and message passing within SO(2) local frames, thereby eliminating the need of SO(3) tensor products.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/efficient-prediction-of-so-3-equivariant</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Progress in Multivariate Time Series Forecasting: Comprehensive Benchmarking and Heterogeneity Analysis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-progress-in-multivariate-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Multivariate Time Series (MTS) analysis is crucial to understanding and managing complex systems, such as traffic and energy systems, and a variety of approaches to MTS forecasting have been proposed recently.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/exploring-progress-in-multivariate-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Framework For Contrastive Self-Supervised Learning And Designing A New Approach</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-contrastive-self-supervised</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Contrastive self-supervised learning (CSL) is an approach to learn useful representations by solving a pretext task that selects and compares anchor, negative and positive (APN) features from an unlabeled dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-framework-for-contrastive-self-supervised</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desiderata for next generation of ML model serving</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desiderata-for-next-generation-of-ml-model</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Inference is a significant part of ML software infrastructure.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/desiderata-for-next-generation-of-ml-model</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyPop7: A Pure-Python Library for Population-Based Black-Box Optimization</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypop7-a-pure-python-library-for-population</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we present an open-source pure-Python library called PyPop7 for black-box optimization (BBO).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/pypop7-a-pure-python-library-for-population</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
