<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2024 21:05:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>World Model on Million-Length Video And Language With RingAttention</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/world-model-on-million-length-video-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This work paves the way for training on massive datasets of long video and language to develop understanding of both human knowledge and the multimodal world, and broader capabilities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/world-model-on-million-length-video-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UFO: A UI-Focused Agent for Windows OS Interaction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufo-a-ui-focused-agent-for-windows-os</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We introduce UFO, an innovative UI-Focused agent to fulfill user requests tailored to applications on Windows OS, harnessing the capabilities of GPT-Vision.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/ufo-a-ui-focused-agent-for-windows-os</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoRA: Weight-Decomposed Low-Rank Adaptation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-weight-decomposed-low-rank-adaptation</link>
      <description><![CDATA[By employing DoRA, we enhance both the learning capacity and training stability of LoRA while avoiding any additional inference overhead.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/dora-weight-decomposed-low-rank-adaptation</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative Representational Instruction Tuning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-representational-instruction</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, we find that GRIT matches training on only generative or embedding data, thus we can unify both at no performance loss.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/generative-representational-instruction</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLO-World: Real-Time Open-Vocabulary Object Detection</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-world-real-time-open-vocabulary-object</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The You Only Look Once (YOLO) series of detectors have established themselves as efficient and practical tools.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolo-world-real-time-open-vocabulary-object</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BitDelta: Your Fine-Tune May Only Be Worth One Bit</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitdelta-your-fine-tune-may-only-be-worth-one</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) are typically trained in two phases: pre-training on large internet-scale datasets, and fine-tuning for downstream tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/bitdelta-your-fine-tune-may-only-be-worth-one</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lag-Llama: Towards Foundation Models for Probabilistic Time Series Forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lag-llama-towards-foundation-models-for-time</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Over the past years, foundation models have caused a paradigm shift in machine learning due to their unprecedented capabilities for zero-shot and few-shot generalization.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lag-llama-towards-foundation-models-for-time</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guiding Instruction-based Image Editing via Multimodal Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-instruction-based-image-editing-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Extensive experimental results demonstrate that expressive instructions are crucial to instruction-based image editing, and our MGIE can lead to a notable improvement in automatic metrics and human evaluation while maintaining competitive inference efficiency.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/guiding-instruction-based-image-editing-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scalable Diffusion Models with Transformers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-diffusion-models-with-transformers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We explore a new class of diffusion models based on the transformer architecture.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/scalable-diffusion-models-with-transformers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The boundary of neural network trainability is fractal</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-boundary-of-neural-network-trainability</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some fractals -- for instance those associated with the Mandelbrot and quadratic Julia sets -- are computed by iterating a function, and identifying the boundary between hyperparameters for which the resulting series diverges or remains bounded.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/the-boundary-of-neural-network-trainability</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GraphCast: Learning skillful medium-range global weather forecasting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphcast-learning-skillful-medium-range</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Global medium-range weather forecasting is critical to decision-making across many social and economic domains.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/graphcast-learning-skillful-medium-range</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fiddler: CPU-GPU Orchestration for Fast Inference of Mixture-of-Experts Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fiddler-cpu-gpu-orchestration-for-fast</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large Language Models (LLMs) based on Mixture-of-Experts (MoE) architecture are showing promising performance on various tasks.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fiddler-cpu-gpu-orchestration-for-fast</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Play Fine-Tuning Converts Weak Language Models to Strong Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-play-fine-tuning-converts-weak-language</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we delve into the prospect of growing a strong LLM out of a weak one without the need for acquiring additional human-annotated data.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/self-play-fine-tuning-converts-weak-language</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mobile-Agent: Autonomous Multi-Modal Mobile Device Agent with Visual Perception</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobile-agent-autonomous-multi-modal-mobile</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To assess the performance of Mobile-Agent, we introduced Mobile-Eval, a benchmark for evaluating mobile device operations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mobile-agent-autonomous-multi-modal-mobile</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MagicPose: Realistic Human Poses and Facial Expressions Retargeting with Identity-aware Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicdance-realistic-human-dance-video</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we propose MagicPose, a diffusion-based model for 2D human pose and facial expression retargeting.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magicdance-realistic-human-dance-video</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Timing-Conditioned Latent Audio Diffusion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-timing-conditioned-latent-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Generating long-form 44. 1kHz stereo audio from text prompts can be computationally demanding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/fast-timing-conditioned-latent-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgedit: Text Guided Image Editing via Learning and Forgetting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgedit-text-guided-image-editing-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Text guided image editing on real images given only the image and the target text prompt as inputs, is a very general and challenging problem, which requires the editing model to reason by itself which part of the image should be edited, to preserve the characteristics of original image, and also to perform complicated non-rigid editing.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/forgedit-text-guided-image-editing-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prismatic VLMs: Investigating the Design Space of Visually-Conditioned Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prismatic-vlms-investigating-the-design-space</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Visually-conditioned language models (VLMs) have seen growing adoption in applications such as visual dialogue, scene understanding, and robotic task planning; adoption that has fueled a wealth of new models such as LLaVa, InstructBLIP, and PaLI-3.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/prismatic-vlms-investigating-the-design-space</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MaskNet: Introducing Feature-Wise Multiplication to CTR Ranking Models by Instance-Guided Mask</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masknet-introducing-feature-wise</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We also turn the feed-forward layer in DNN model into a mixture of addictive and multiplicative feature interactions by proposing MaskBlock in this paper.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/masknet-introducing-feature-wise</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering for Scaling Language Models to 128K Context</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-engineering-for-scaling-language-models</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We demonstrate that continual pretraining of the full model on 1B-5B tokens of such data is an effective and affordable strategy for scaling the context length of language models to 128K.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/data-engineering-for-scaling-language-models</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
