<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 09:14:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>PAConv: Position Adaptive Convolution with Dynamic Kernel Assembling on Point Clouds</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paconv-position-adaptive-convolution-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The key of PAConv is to construct the convolution kernel by dynamically assembling basic weight matrices stored in Weight Bank, where the coefficients of these weight matrices are self-adaptively learned from point positions through ScoreNet.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paconv-position-adaptive-convolution-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM.int8(): 8-bit Matrix Multiplication for Transformers at Scale</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-int8-8-bit-matrix-multiplication-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We develop a procedure for Int8 matrix multiplication for feed-forward and attention projection layers in transformers, which cut the memory needed for inference by half while retaining full precision performance.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llm-int8-8-bit-matrix-multiplication-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Library for Representing Python Programs as Graphs for Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-library-for-representing-python-programs-as</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Graph representations of programs are commonly a central element of machine learning for code research.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/a-library-for-representing-python-programs-as</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musika! Fast Infinite Waveform Music Generation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musika-fast-infinite-waveform-music</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We release the source code and pretrained autoencoder weights at github. com/marcoppasini/musika, such that a GAN can be trained on a new music domain with a single GPU in a matter of hours.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/musika-fast-infinite-waveform-music</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCR-free Document Understanding Transformer</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/donut-document-understanding-transformer</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Current Visual Document Understanding (VDU) methods outsource the task of reading text to off-the-shelf Optical Character Recognition (OCR) engines and focus on the understanding task with the OCR outputs.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/donut-document-understanding-transformer</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flow-Guided Transformer for Video Inpainting</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-guided-transformer-for-video-inpainting</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Especially in spatial transformer, we design a dual perspective spatial MHSA, which integrates the global tokens to the window-based attention.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/flow-guided-transformer-for-video-inpainting</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Language Models Make Fun? A Case Study in Chinese Comical Crosstalk</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-make-fun-a-case-study-in</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, the humor aspect of natural language is relatively under-investigated, especially in the age of pre-trained language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/can-language-models-make-fun-a-case-study-in</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StyleFaceV: Face Video Generation via Decomposing and Recomposing Pretrained StyleGAN3</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylefacev-face-video-generation-via</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Notably, StyleFaceV is capable of generating realistic $1024\times1024$ face videos even without high-resolution training videos.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/stylefacev-face-video-generation-via</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paint2Pix: Interactive Painting based Progressive Image Synthesis and Editing</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint2pix-interactive-painting-based</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In particular, we propose a novel approach paint2pix, which learns to predict (and adapt) "what a user wants to draw" from rudimentary brushstroke inputs, by learning a mapping from the manifold of incomplete human paintings to their realistic renderings.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/paint2pix-interactive-painting-based</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TotalSegmentator: robust segmentation of 104 anatomical structures in CT images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totalsegmentator-robust-segmentation-of-104</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Finally, we train a segmentation algorithm on this new dataset.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/totalsegmentator-robust-segmentation-of-104</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YOLOv7: Trainable bag-of-freebies sets new state-of-the-art for real-time object detectors</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</link>
      <description><![CDATA[YOLOv7 surpasses all known object detectors in both speed and accuracy in the range from 5 FPS to 160 FPS and has the highest accuracy 56. 8% AP among all known real-time object detectors with 30 FPS or higher on GPU V100.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/yolov7-trainable-bag-of-freebies-sets-new</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alpa: Automating Inter- and Intra-Operator Parallelism for Distributed Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpa-automating-inter-and-intra-operator</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Existing model-parallel training systems either require users to manually create a parallelization plan or automatically generate one from a limited space of model parallelism configurations.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/alpa-automating-inter-and-intra-operator</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepNet: Scaling Transformers to 1,000 Layers</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepnet-scaling-transformers-to-1000-layers</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we propose a simple yet effective method to stabilize extremely deep Transformers.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/deepnet-scaling-transformers-to-1000-layers</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text-Guided Synthesis of Artistic Images with Retrieval-Augmented Diffusion Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In RDMs, a set of nearest neighbors is retrieved from an external database during training for each training instance, and the diffusion model is conditioned on these informative samples.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/text-guided-synthesis-of-artistic-images-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Instant Neural Graphics Primitives with a Multiresolution Hash Encoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instant-neural-graphics-primitives-with-a</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Neural graphics primitives, parameterized by fully connected neural networks, can be costly to train and evaluate.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instant-neural-graphics-primitives-with-a</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Count Anything: Reference-less Class-agnostic Counting with Weak Supervision</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-count-anything-reference-less</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While there are class-agnostic counting methods that can generalise to unseen classes, these methods require reference images to define the type of object to be counted, as well as instance annotations during training.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/learning-to-count-anything-reference-less</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FedDM: Iterative Distribution Matching for Communication-Efficient Federated Learning</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddm-iterative-distribution-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Federated learning~(FL) has recently attracted increasing attention from academia and industry, with the ultimate goal of achieving collaborative training under privacy and communication constraints.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/feddm-iterative-distribution-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delving into Effective Gradient Matching for Dataset Condensation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-effective-gradient-matching-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this work, we delve into the gradient matching method from a comprehensive perspective and answer the critical questions of what, how, and where to match.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/delving-into-effective-gradient-matching-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-scale Multi-band DenseNets for Audio Source Separation</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-multi-band-densenets-for-audio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper deals with the problem of audio source separation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/multi-scale-multi-band-densenets-for-audio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HorNet: Efficient High-Order Spatial Interactions with Recursive Gated Convolutions</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we show that the key ingredients behind the vision Transformers, namely input-adaptive, long-range and high-order spatial interactions, can also be efficiently implemented with a convolution-based framework.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/hornet-efficient-high-order-spatial</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
