<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Papers with Code: Trending (unofficial)</title>
    <link>https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds</link>
    <description>As a disclaimer, this is an unofficial feed and has no affiliation with Papers with Code.</description>
    <atom:link href="https://github.com/yitao-yu/pwc-feeds" rel="self"/>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 09:12:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Assisting in Writing Wikipedia-like Articles From Scratch with Large Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assisting-in-writing-wikipedia-like-articles</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We study how to apply large language models to write grounded and organized long-form articles from scratch, with comparable breadth and depth to Wikipedia pages.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/assisting-in-writing-wikipedia-like-articles</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mini-Gemini: Mining the Potential of Multi-modality Vision Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-gemini-mining-the-potential-of-multi</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We try to narrow the gap by mining the potential of VLMs for better performance and any-to-any workflow from three aspects, i. e., high-resolution visual tokens, high-quality data, and VLM-guided generation.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mini-gemini-mining-the-potential-of-multi</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InstantMesh: Efficient 3D Mesh Generation from a Single Image with Sparse-view Large Reconstruction Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantmesh-efficient-3d-mesh-generation-from</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present InstantMesh, a feed-forward framework for instant 3D mesh generation from a single image, featuring state-of-the-art generation quality and significant training scalability.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/instantmesh-efficient-3d-mesh-generation-from</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LM Transparency Tool: Interactive Tool for Analyzing Transformer Language Models</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lm-transparency-tool-interactive-tool-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present the LM Transparency Tool (LM-TT), an open-source interactive toolkit for analyzing the internal workings of Transformer-based language models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/lm-transparency-tool-interactive-tool-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magic Clothing: Controllable Garment-Driven Image Synthesis</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-clothing-controllable-garment-driven</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We propose Magic Clothing, a latent diffusion model (LDM)-based network architecture for an unexplored garment-driven image synthesis task.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/magic-clothing-controllable-garment-driven</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Data Quality Problems with Desbordante: a Demo</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-data-quality-problems-with</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, most existing data profiling systems that focus on complex statistics do not provide proper integration with the tools used by contemporary data scientists.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/solving-data-quality-problems-with</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megalodon: Efficient LLM Pretraining and Inference with Unlimited Context Length</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megalodon-efficient-llm-pretraining-and</link>
      <description><![CDATA[The quadratic complexity and weak length extrapolation of Transformers limits their ability to scale to long sequences, and while sub-quadratic solutions like linear attention and state space models exist, they empirically underperform Transformers in pretraining efficiency and downstream task accuracy.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/megalodon-efficient-llm-pretraining-and</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actions Speak Louder than Words: Trillion-Parameter Sequential Transducers for Generative Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actions-speak-louder-than-words-trillion</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Large-scale recommendation systems are characterized by their reliance on high cardinality, heterogeneous features and the need to handle tens of billions of user actions on a daily basis.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/actions-speak-louder-than-words-trillion</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MyGO: Discrete Modality Information as Fine-Grained Tokens for Multi-modal Knowledge Graph Completion</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mygo-discrete-modality-information-as-fine</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To overcome their inherent incompleteness, multi-modal knowledge graph completion (MMKGC) aims to discover unobserved knowledge from given MMKGs, leveraging both structural information from the triples and multi-modal information of the entities.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/mygo-discrete-modality-information-as-fine</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visual Autoregressive Modeling: Scalable Image Generation via Next-Scale Prediction</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-autoregressive-modeling-scalable-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We present Visual AutoRegressive modeling (VAR), a new generation paradigm that redefines the autoregressive learning on images as coarse-to-fine "next-scale prediction" or "next-resolution prediction", diverging from the standard raster-scan "next-token prediction".]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/visual-autoregressive-modeling-scalable-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arc2Face: A Foundation Model of Human Faces</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arc2face-a-foundation-model-of-human-faces</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper presents Arc2Face, an identity-conditioned face foundation model, which, given the ArcFace embedding of a person, can generate diverse photo-realistic images with an unparalleled degree of face similarity than existing models.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/arc2face-a-foundation-model-of-human-faces</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Space Model for New-Generation Network Alternative to Transformers: A Survey</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-space-model-for-new-generation-network</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this paper, we give the first comprehensive review of these works and also provide experimental comparisons and analysis to better demonstrate the features and advantages of SSM.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/state-space-model-for-new-generation-network</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLaVA-UHD: an LMM Perceiving Any Aspect Ratio and High-Resolution Images</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-uhd-an-lmm-perceiving-any-aspect-ratio</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To address the challenges, we present LLaVA-UHD, a large multimodal model that can efficiently perceive images in any aspect ratio and high resolution.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/llava-uhd-an-lmm-perceiving-any-aspect-ratio</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unrecognizable Yet Identifiable: Image Distortion with Preserved Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrecognizable-yet-identifiable-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In the realm of security applications, biometric authentication systems play a crucial role, yet one often encounters challenges concerning privacy and security while developing one.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/unrecognizable-yet-identifiable-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RecAI: Leveraging Large Language Models for Next-Generation Recommender Systems</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recai-leveraging-large-language-models-for</link>
      <description><![CDATA[This paper introduces RecAI, a practical toolkit designed to augment or even revolutionize recommender systems with the advanced capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs).]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/recai-leveraging-large-language-models-for</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ControlNet++: Improving Conditional Controls with Efficient Consistency Feedback</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnet-improving-conditional-controls</link>
      <description><![CDATA[To this end, we propose ControlNet++, a novel approach that improves controllable generation by explicitly optimizing pixel-level cycle consistency between generated images and conditional controls.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/controlnet-improving-conditional-controls</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joint Physical-Digital Facial Attack Detection Via Simulating Spoofing Clues</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-physical-digital-facial-attack</link>
      <description><![CDATA[SPSC and SDSC augment live samples into simulated attack samples by simulating spoofing clues of physical and digital attacks, respectively, which significantly improve the capability of the model to detect "unseen" attack types.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/joint-physical-digital-facial-attack</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TriForce: Lossless Acceleration of Long Sequence Generation with Hierarchical Speculative Decoding</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triforce-lossless-acceleration-of-long</link>
      <description><![CDATA[However, key-value (KV) cache, which is stored to avoid re-computation, has emerged as a critical bottleneck by growing linearly in size with the sequence length.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/triforce-lossless-acceleration-of-long</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Champ: Controllable and Consistent Human Image Animation with 3D Parametric Guidance</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/champ-controllable-and-consistent-human-image</link>
      <description><![CDATA[In this study, we introduce a methodology for human image animation by leveraging a 3D human parametric model within a latent diffusion framework to enhance shape alignment and motion guidance in curernt human generative techniques.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/champ-controllable-and-consistent-human-image</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AutoCodeRover: Autonomous Program Improvement</title>
      <link>https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Recent progress in Large Language Models (LLMs) has significantly impacted the development process, where developers can use LLM-based programming assistants to achieve automated coding.]]></description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://paperswithcode.com/paper/autocoderover-autonomous-program-improvement</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
